I'VE JUST GOT TO HAND THIS IN TO ARMSTRONG.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
SO I'M TELLING MY MOM THAT JOKE.
YOU KNOW. THE ONE ABOUT THE DUCK?
THAT ONE'S PRETTY GOOD.
AND WHEN I TELL HER THE PUNCHLINE?
SHE SPEWS MILK - OUT OF HER NOSE!
EMMA. MILK. OUT OF MY MOM'S NOSE.
FUNNY.
HUH? OH, YEAH. FUNNY, J.T.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
NOTHING. JUST WRITING SOME E-MAILS.
UM, I WANTED TO ASK YOU....
I SAW YOU AND ARMSTRONG THIS MORNING.
AND? WHAT'S YOUR POINT?
IT LOOKED LIKE -
LOOKED LIKE WHAT? I HAD A FEW QUESTIONS.
ABOUT EQUATIONS. SO?
ARE YOU TRYING TO READ MY E-MAILS?
NO. NOT AT ALL.
E-MAILS ARE PRIVATE. MIND YOUR OWN BUSINESS.
♪ WHAT EVER IT TAKES
♪ I KNOW I CAN MAKE IT THROUGH
♪ IF I HOLD OUT
♪ BE THE BEST
♪ THE BEST I CAN BE
♪ HEAR WHAT I SAY TO YOU
♪ WHAT EVER IT TAKES
♪ I KNOW I CAN MAKE IT
♪ I KNOW I CAN MAKE IT THROUGH
DON'T YOU THINK YOU'RE BEING A BIT OBVIOUS?
ABOUT WHAT?
SEAN. IF YOU STARE ANY HARDER YOUR EYEBALLS WILL POP OUT.
J.T.? WHAT DO YOU THINK OF ARMSTRONG?
I MEAN AS A PERSON.
TEACHERS AREN'T PEOPLE. THEY'RE-- TEACHERS.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN. DO YOU THINK HE'S-- OKAY?
OH YEAH. ARMSTRONG'S GIVEN ME LOTS OF EXTRA HELP.
HE'S BEEN REALLY NICE. TO ME, ANYWAY.
YEAH, COME TO THINK OF IT, HE'S NICE TO EVERYONE--
YOU GONNA EAT THAT?
HUH? NO. YOU TAKE IT.
SOMETHING I SAID?
HEY, SHEILA. TWO SPECIALS PLEASE.
WHAT IS THAT? NUCLEAR WASTE?
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR ABOUT IT, GAVIN.
HEY GUYS. DID YA SEE THE SIGN IN THE BATHROOM?
'FLUSH TWICE - IT'S A LONG WAY TO THE CAFETERIA.'
GAVIN? IT MIGHT TAKE YOU A FEW EXTRA YEARS,
BUT I CAN'T WAIT FOR THE DAY YOU GRADUATE.
AW MAN!
EW, WHAT IS IT? EW! EW!
SHEILA, THERE'S A BUG IN MY SQUASH.
I THINK THE JOKE GOES, 'WAITER, THERE'S A FLY IN MY SOUP.'
I'M SERIOUS. IT'S RIGHT OVER--
NICE TRY, GAVIN. BY THE WAY, DON'T FORGET TO PAY FOR THAT.
IT'S FOUR NINETY-NINE PLUS TAX. NEXT!
SO, EM, FOR MEDIA IMMERSION. SHOULD WE USE HTML?
YEAH. SURE. WHATEVER.
MANNY? HAS ARMSTRONG EVER TOUCHED YOU?
WHAT? NO! DID HE TOUCH YOU?
NO, NO. NOT ME. LIBERTY. I SAW HIM TOUCHING LIBERTY.
ARE YOU SURE?
YEAH. I KNOW WHAT I SAW.
I DON'T KNOW, EM. ARMSTRONG'S A PRETTY PHYSICAL GUY.
MAYBE YOU GOT THE WRONG IDEA?
I HOPE SO.
BUT THIS MORNING? HE HAD HIS ARM AROUND LIBERTY.
THEN I SAW HIM PASS HER A NOTE OUTSIDE.
IT REALLY LOOKED LIKE HE WAS COMING ON TO HER.
MR. ARMSTRONG? YOU'VE GOT TO BE MAKING THIS UP.
NO. I SWEAR.
IT JUST SO HAPPENS THAT YOU'RE ALWAYS COMPLAINING
ABOUT THE FOOD AND NOW YOU FIND A BUG. HMM.
PAIGE, C'MON. DOES THIS LOOK LIKE THE FACE OF A LIAR?
YOU WANT AN HONEST ANSWER?
WHY WON'T ANYONE BELIEVE ME? TELL HER, JIMMY.
THERE WAS SOME KIND OF WEIRDNESS ON HIS PLATE.
YOU SURE IT WASN'T JUST A HAIR?
A MOTH, I THINK.
AN EARWIG, DUDE. AN EARWIG.
SEE? YOU TWO CAN'T EVEN GET YOUR STORIES STRAIGHT.
BOYCOTT THE CAF!
HEY GUYS, THE CAF HAS BUGS! BOYCOTT THE CAF!
THAT'S A SERIOUS ACCUSATION.
MS. KWAN. I FOUND A BUG IN MY FOOD. AN EARWIG.
AND WHERE IS THIS OFFENSIVE CREATURE NOW?
STUCK TO A KID'S SHOE.
GAVIN. DEFAMATION AND RUMOUR MONGERING ARE SERIOUS OFFENCES.
THE NEXT TIME YOU HAVE AN ACCUSATION LIKE THAT
YOU BETTER HAVE PROOF.
WHAT'S WITH YOU? YOU LOOK AWFUL.
THANKS, PAIGE.
NO, I MEAN, WHAT'S GOING ON?
IT'S GOOD TO GET THINGS OFF YOUR CHEST.
YOU'LL FEEL WAY BETTER.
I GUESS SO. BUT --
TERRI. WE'RE FRIENDS, RIGHT? FRIENDS TALK TO EACH OTHER.
OKAY, BUT YOU HAVE TO PROMISE TO KEEP IT SECRET.
I REALLY MEAN IT.
OF COURSE. WHAT IS IT?
YOU KNOW LIBERTY? THAT KID IN SEVENTH GRADE?
WELL, I HEARD ARMSTRONG... WAS COMING ON TO HER.
EW. YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
NO, I OVERHEARD EMMA. SHE SAW HIM WITH HIS ARM AROUND HER.
THEN, ON THE STEPS, HE GAVE HER A LOVE NOTE.
SO WHAT DO WE DO? REPORT IT?
HON, YOU CAN'T REPORT A RUMOUR.
AFTERNOON, EVERYONE.
SOMETHING WRONG, GIRLS?
OH, NO. NOTHING, MR. ARMSTRONG.
OKAY.
TODAY WE'RE GONNA TAKE A LOOK AT DISTRIBUTIVE PROPERTIES.
ALRIGHT, IN REVIEW YOU'LL REMEMBER THE THREE MAIN RULES,
THE OPERATIONS IN BRACKETS...
GET THIS. LIBERTY AND ARMSTRONG WERE SEEN KISSING OUTSIDE.
YEAH. THEY WERE IN HIS CAR, KISSING IN FRONT OF EVERYBODY.
SHE GOT A RIDE IN WITH HIM THIS MORNING.
DO YOU THINK THEY SPENT THE NIGHT TOGETHER?
HOW COULD COACH ARMSTRONG DO THAT?
DUDE. LIBERTY AND ARMSTRONG ARE DOING IT!
NEXT ON THE AGENDA?
THE MOTION THAT LIBERTY PUT FORWARD LAST MEETING.
RIGHT. ABOUT THE TALENT SHOW.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK, ASHLEY? SHOULD WE HAVE ONE?
SURE. SOUNDS GREAT.
WOW. THAT WAS EASY. WE ARGUED ABOUT IT FOR HOURS LAST WEEK.
GUYS? YOU CAN STOP WHISPERING.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
YOU DO?
OF COURSE. EVERYBODY KNOWS WHAT HAPPENED.
SO WE MIGHT AS WELL DISCUSS IT.
UM, OKAY. BUT DON'T YOU WANT TO DISCUSS IT IN PRIVATE?
IT'S NO SECRET, ASHLEY. WE ALL KNOW SOME MICROPHONES
WERE STOLEN AT LAST YEAR'S SHOW.
BUT IT WON'T HAPPEN THIS YEAR, I PROMISE.
LIBERTY?
IF IT'S ABOUT THE MICROPHONES--
IT'S NOT. DO YOU EVEN KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON?
PEOPLE ARE TALKING. ABOUT YOU AND ARMSTRONG.
THAT YOU'RE PRETTY CLOSE.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
IT MEANS PEOPLE THINK YOU TWO ARE, UH... EXTRA-FRIENDLY.
THEY- THEY THINK HE'S DOING THINGS TO ME?
YES. IS IT TRUE?
OF COURSE NOT!
IF IT IS, WE HAVE TO REPORT IT. LIBERTY, PLEASE!
JUST WAIT WE CAN TALK!
I KNEW SOMETHING WAS GOING ON.
YOU DID?
WE TALKED ABOUT IT YESTERDAY. I JUST COULDN'T BELIEVE IT.
I STILL CAN'T. MAYBE WE SHOULD REPORT IT?
ARMSTRONG WOULD BE TOAST.
THAT'S TRUE. WE SHOULD WAIT AND FIND OUT FOR SURE.
THIS WHOLE THING? IT'S DISGUSTING.
JUST THE THOUGHT OF IT -- YECH. MAKES ME WANT TO TAKE A SHOWER.
THAT WOULDN'T BE SUCH A BAD IDEA.
SO, WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
LEAVE ME ALONE, EMMA.
LIBERTY, WHAT YOU NEED RIGHT NOW IS A FRIEND.
SOMEONE TO TALK TO.
BUT THERE'S NOTHING TO TALK ABOUT!
IT'S OKAY. YOU CAN TELL ME.
I AM TELLING YOU.
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE NOT LYING?
BECAUSE WE REALLY HAVE TO REPORT IT --
EMMA! I SWEAR ON MY LIFE THAT NOTHING'S GOING ON.
THE WHOLE SCHOOL IS TALKING.
I KNOW! BUT IT'S JUST A VICIOUS RUMOUR. HONEST.
WHAT IF IT GETS TO RADITCH? TO MY PARENTS?
WHAT'LL MR. ARMSTRONG SAY WHEN HE HEARS THIS?
THEN THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY TO HANDLE THIS.
STOP THE RUMOUR AND TRACK DOWN IT'S SOURCE.
THEN GIVE WHOEVER STARTED IT A --
-- GOOD SWIFT KICK?
I WAS GOING TO SAY 'A GOOD TALKING TO'. BUT THAT'LL DO.
HEY SPINNER, FIND ANY BUGS IN YOUR BREAKFAST THIS MORNING?
VERY FUNNY. SO I MADE A MISTAKE.
WHY'D YOU SAY YOU MADE A MISTAKE?
BECAUSE I DID.
WHAT?
I'M ALWAYS COMPLAINING ABOUT THE FOOD, RIGHT?
SO I MUST'VE MADE IT UP.
OKAY, NOW I'M COMPLETELY CONFUSED.
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN TOTALLY DIFFERENT IF SOMEONE ELSE
FOUND THAT BUG. THEN EVERYONE WOULD BELIEVE IT.
EVEN THE WRATH OF KWAN.
I GUESS SO.
BETTER NOT BE TUNA SALAD IN HERE.
AW!
TODAY'S SPECIAL? EARWIG SURPRISE.
TOOK ME HOURS TO COLLECT THEM.
WHEN I GET DONE? CAF WILL BE CLOSED. PERMANENTLY.
ARE YOU SURE IT ISN'T TRUE, THOUGH?
WHEN I TALKED TO LIBERTY YESTERDAY,
SHE WAS REALLY DEFENSIVE. LIKE SHE WAS HIDING SOMETHING.
SHE WAS PROBABLY JUST UPSET. WOULDN'T YOU BE?
YEAH, I WOULD. POOR GIRL.
WHO WOULD SPREAD A RUMOUR LIKE THAT?
THAT'S WHAT I'M TRYING TO FIGURE OUT.
WHO DID YOU HEAR IT FROM, ASHLEY?
IT WAS JIMMY. BUT HE HEARD IT FROM SPINNER!
HEY, IT WASN'T ME WHO STARTED IT. TALK TO THIS GUY --
SEAN!?
WHAT!?
HE'S THE ONE WHO TOLD ME.
ABOUT COACH ARMSTRONG AND LIBERTY?
MAN, IT'S JUST SICK.
IT'S NOT TRUE, SEAN.
IT ISN'T?
NO.
MAN, I KNEW IT SOUNDED FAKE.
I SHOULD HAVE NEVER BELIEVED HER.
BELIEVED WHO?
I'M INNOCENT. TALK TO PAIGE.
I WAS MERELY IMPARTING INFORMATION.
AND BESIDES, I HEARD IT FROM TERRI.
SHE'S THE ONE YOU NEED TO SPEAK TO.
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
O-KAY.
THE WHOLE SCHOOL'S GOSSIPING ABOUT LIBERTY AND ARMSTRONG.
NO KIDDING. I HAVE EARS TOO.
WELL, IT'S NOT TRUE. IT'S JUST A RUMOUR.
PAIGE SPREAD IT AROUND. BUT SHE HEARD IT FROM YOU.
I SWORE HER TO SECRECY!
AS IF SHE'D KEEP QUIET. PAIGE LIVES FOR RUMOURS.
I WAS UPSET, OKAY? I WAS SHOCKED. I HAD TO TELL SOMEONE.
I'M SORRY.
WELL, TOO LATE. I HOPE YOU'RE HAPPY.
ME!?
HELLO? YOU'RE THE ONE WHO STARTED THE RUMOUR.
HATE TO TELL YOU, BUT -- NO.
IT WAS RIGHT HERE. YESTERDAY. YOU WERE TALKING TO MANNY.
ABOUT LIBERTY AND ARMSTRONG. REMEMBER?
YOU STARTED THE RUMOUR, EMMA.
SPIN, YOU SURE YOU WANT TO DO THIS?
DON'T YOU THINK IT'S A BIT DRASTIC?
NOPE. ALL IS FAIR IN LOVE AND WAR. AND DUDE? THIS IS WAR.
YOU'RE EATING THE CAFETERIA FOOD AGAIN?
I DECIDED TO BE, YOU KNOW, MATURE.
I PROBABLY NEVER EVEN SAW THAT BUG.
GOOD FOR YOU, SPINNER.
JIMMY, CAN YOU PASS ME THE PEPPER, PLEASE?
WHAT'RE YOU SMILING AT?
AHHHHHHHHH!!!
YOU PUT BUGS ON HER TRAY!?
NOBODY BELIEVES ME. BUT THEY'LL BELIEVE HER.
SPINNER! YOU IDIOT!
ASH, CALM DOWN. I TOLD YOU. THERE'S BUGS IN THE FOOD.
BECAUSE YOU PUT THEM THERE!
WHAT'S IN THAT CONTAINER?
NOTHING.
UGH!
GAVIN. WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?
MATH CLASS. I'VE BEEN DREADING THIS ALL DAY.
SO, DID YOU TRACK DOWN THE RUMOUR?
YEAH, BUT I NEED TO SAY SOMETHING TO YOU FIRST.
OKAY, TODAY WE'RE GOING TO BE WORKING ON EQUATIONS.
NOW WHEN DEALING WITH EQUATIONS WE ALWAYS USE THE BEDMAS RULE.
NOW WHO CAN TELL ME WHAT THAT STANDS FOR?
WHAT'S WITH EVERYONE TODAY?
OKAY, UH, WHY DON'T YOU TELL US, LIBERTY?
YOU AND I HAVE BEEN WORKING ON IT.
WHAT IS SO FUNNY?
THAT'S ENOUGH!
MR. ARMSTRONG, CAN I HAVE FIVE MINUTES OF YOUR TIME?
I WAS JUST ABOUT TO GET STARTED HERE.
MRS. SMITH WILL TAKE OVER THE CLASS.
RIGHT... UH, OKAY.
CLASS, I WANT YOU TO BEGIN WORKING ON THE UH,
ORDER OF OPERATIONS EXERCISES ON PAGE 129.
LIBERTY? WILL YOU JOIN US PLEASE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
EMMA. GO BACK TO CLASS.
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU, MR. RADITCH.
WELL IT'LL HAVE TO WAIT.
I'M IN THE MIDDLE OF SOMETHING RIGHT NOW.
IT CAN'T WAIT. YOU SEE...
I'M IN THE MIDDLE OF IT, TOO.
YOU'LL HELP ME SERVE AT EVERY LUNCH.
AND THEN AFTER SCHOOL YOU CAN HELP ME CLEAN UP.
OH, AND UH, DON'T FORGET ABOUT THIS.
I'M NOT WEARING THAT.
HEALTH REGULATIONS, PRINCESS.
YOU DO KNOW ABOUT HEALTH REGULATIONS.
HEY, SPIN. HOW LONG ARE YOU --
NICE NET, SPINNER.
CHEER UP. IT WON'T BE FOR LONG. ONLY FOR ABOUT TWO MONTHS.
TWO MONTHS!
YOU OWE THE SCHOOL THREE HUNDRED DOLLARS.
THAT'S WHAT IT'LL COST TO EXTERMINATE THE CAFETERIA.
BUT THE CAF NEEDED TO BE EXTERMINATED ANYWAY!
SURE IT DID, GAVIN. SURE IT DID.
LIBERTY?
I KNOW YOU'RE IN HERE.
I WAS RESPONSIBLE FOR THE RUMOUR STARTING.
BUT I DIDN'T SPREAD IT.
AND THERE'S A DIFFERENCE?
YOU'RE LUCKY MR. ARMSTRONG DIDN'T LOSE HIS JOB.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT MAKES ME REALLY MAD?
THAT YOU THOUGHT I COULD DO THAT.
DO WHAT? BE VIOLATED?
AND WHAT WERE YOU DOING WITH MR. ARMSTRONG ANYWAY?
HE HAD HIS ARM AROUND YOU. PASSED YOU A NOTE -
YOU WANT TO SEE MY 'NOTE'?
DYSCALCULIA?
IT'S A LEARNING DISORDER. LIKE DYSLEXIA BUT WITH NUMBERS.
I'VE BEEN REALLY UPSET ABOUT IT.
MR. ARMSTRONG'S BEEN HELPING ME.
SO THAT'S THE EXPLANATION? WHY DIDN'T YOU SAY SOMETHING?
BECAUSE IT MEANS YOU'RE NOT PERFECT?
BECAUSE IT MEANS I'M STUPID!
STUPID? YOU'RE ONE OF THE SMARTEST KIDS IN SCHOOL.
NOT IN MATH, I'M NOT.
WHO CARES?
I DO! IT'S IMPORTANT TO ME TO BE THE BEST.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND!
LIBERTY, I FEEL REALLY BAD.
IS THERE'S SOMETHING I CAN DO? TO HELP?
NO, EMMA. GO BACK TO SAVING RAINFORESTS. AND WHALES.
'CAUSE WHEN IT COMES TO HELPING PEOPLE - YOU SUCK.