OH, HEY.
UM...
YOUR MOM SAID
I COULD HELP MYSELF.
OH, YEAH, OF COURSE.
THIS IS REALLY WEIRD,
ISN'T IT?
UH, YEAH, KINDA.
(LAUGHS)
UH, CAN I GET YOU SOME?
NO, IT'S OKAY.
I'M AN INDEPENDENT WOMAN.
(CEREAL RATTLES)
(BOTH LAUGH)
YEAH.
(LAUGHS)
(KNOCK AT THE DOOR)
OH, HEY!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
SURPRISING YOU
WITH A RIDE TO SCHOOL.
MAYA:
UM, LISTEN, I NEED TO TALK
TO YOU ABOUT SOMETHING.
MILES:
OKAY, ME FIRST.
MAYA MATLIN,
WILL YOU COME TO THE SWEETHEART
SEMI-FORMAL WITH ME?
(LAUGHS)
ZIG:
HEY, MAYA?
WHAT'S HE DOING HERE?
THAT'S WHAT I WANTED
TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ (The best that I can be) ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
COME ON, HOW MANY TIMES
DO I HAVE TO SAY I'M SORRY?
MAYA, THERE'S ANOTHER GUY
SLEEPING IN YOUR HOUSE!
YOU TRUST ME,
DON'T YOU?
YES, BUT NOT ZIG!
I MEAN HE DEALS DRUGS!
THAT'S JUST A RUMOUR.
YEAH?
HAVE YOU ASKED HIM?!
I PROMISE YOU THERE'S NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT, OKAY?
I CAN PROVE IT!
WE CAN ALL HANG OUT
AT THE DANCE TOGETHER.
YOU'RE JOKING.
PLEASE, MILES?
YOU'RE LUCKY
YOU'RE CUTE.
I'M LUCKY
YOU'RE THE BEST.
SO WHAT YOU WANNA DO
IS YOU WANNA TAKE THAT-
JENNA:
LOOK AT THOSE NINER GIRLS
WITH THEIR PERFECT
LITTLE FACES
AND THEIR PERFECT
LITTLE BODIES.
WHOA!
GREEN MONSTER MUCH?
I AM IN CRISIS MODE,
ALLI!
CONNOR'S BEEN TUTORING
THOSE GIRLS.
A LOT!
YEAH, BUT DON'T YOU
TRUST HIM?
I MEAN, IT IS CONNOR,
AFTER ALL.
EXCEPT NOW
HE'S CONNOR 2.0.
ALLI:
EASE UP, CLINGER,
YOU NEED TO RELAX!
OR I CAN NIP THIS
IN THE BUD.
(BELL RINGS)
OKAY, EXPERIMENT'S OVER,
RESULTS ARE INCONCLUSIVE!
NO, RESULTS ARE
VERY CONCLUSIVE!
I'VE GOTTEN
THREE DOUBLE TAKES
AND SEVEN VERBAL COMPLIMENTS
TODAY ALONE!
THEN WE'VE COLLECTED
ENOUGH DATA.
WHERE'S YOUR NERDY T-SHIRT?
YOU STILL WANNA WIN
KING AND QUEEN, DON'T YOU?
YES.
THEN YOU'RE BEING
IRRATIONAL.
YEAH, I GUESS I AM.
DURING HYPER INFLATION,
BARS WERE FULL OF PEOPLE
TRYING TO SPEND MONEY
BEFORE IT LOST ITS VALUE.
(GIGGLES)
BECKY:
AND THEN JACK WILL FINISH OFF
THE REPUBLIC'S DECLINE.
IMOGEN:
EASY PEASY.
OKAY, I GOTTA RUN,
DEGRASSI TV WAITS FOR NO WOMAN.
UH, HEY,
HOLD UP FOR A SEC.
I WAS GOING TO ASK IMOGEN
TO THE SEMI.
ACTUALLY, SHE'S ALREADY
GOING WITH SOMEONE.
ME.
BUT YOU'RE NOT GAY.
I LIKE IMOGEN A LOT.
BUT DO YOU WANT
TO KISS HER?
THAT'S NONE
OF YOUR BUSINESS.
(FRUSTRATED SIGH)
I KNOW YOU'RE BEST FRIENDS
OR WHATEVER,
BUT IF IMOGEN FINDS OUT
THAT YOU'RE LEADING HER ON...
ZOE:
NOT TELLING YOUR BOYFRIEND
YOU'RE MOVING ANOTHER GUY
INTO YOUR HOUSE?
REAL SMART.
MILES THINKS ZIG IS A BAD GUY,
BUT HE JUST DOESN'T KNOW HIM!
DO YOU?
YES!
WHICH IS WHY I KNOW
THAT IF THEY SPENT
SOME TIME TOGETHER,
THEY'D START LIKING
EACH OTHER!
WHAT, ARE THEY GOING TO BOND
OVER THEIR MUTUAL ADMIRATION
OF A CERTAIN BLONDE
CELLO PLAYER?
NO, ZOE!
ME, ZIG, AND MILES
WOULD ALL HANG OUT
AT THE SEMI-FORMAL TOGETHER!
LET ME TELL YOU HOW THIS PLAN
OF YOURS IS GONNA GO.
MILES IS GONNA BE ALL,
"MAYA, I LOVE YOU,
LET'S DANCE."
AND ZIG WILL BE ALL
BROODY LIKE,
"MAYA, I LOVE YOU,
LET'S DANCE."
TRISTAN:
YEAH, AND THEN MILES
WILL SLUG ZIG,
AND ZIG WILL PROBABLY
HAVE A KNIFE
AND WILL LIKE
STAB MILES!
AND GRACE WILL GO
ALL CRAZY
AND SHE'LL SPIKE THE PUNCH
WITH LSD!
ZOE:
AND THAT WEIRDO TINY
WILL LIKE BURN THE GYM DOWN!
AND THEN THE SEMI-FORMAL
WILL END
WITH EVERYONE DYING
IN A FIERY INFERNO!
I THINK YOU GUYS ARE BEING
A BIT DRAMATIC.
ARE WE, MAYA?
ARE WE?
ZOE:
OR... ARE WE JUST BEING
TOO REAL FOR YOU?
WELL, I HAVE TO TRY SOMETHING.
MM-MM.
CLARE:
DIDN'T WE BUY MORE CANDY
THAN THIS?
(BALLOON DEFLATES)
UH, BEATS ME.
GUYS, I NEED YOUR HELP!
I TAKE IT YOU DIDN'T
SORT THINGS OUT WITH IMOGEN?
I ACCIDENTALLY ASKED HER
TO BE MY DATE TO THE DANCE.
HOW DO YOU ACCIDENTALLY
ASK SOMEONE OUT?!
IT'S EASIER THAN YOU THINK,
ACTUALLY.
BECKY:
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT WENT WRONG!
ALL I SAID WAS THAT
I WANTED A NIGHT
TO GET TO KNOW EACH OTHER
MORE INTIMATELY.
CLARE:
INTIMATELY?
THAT MIGHT BE
WHERE THINGS WENT WRONG.
OH.
WELL, YOU COULD BECOME
A LESBIAN.
CLARE:
I'M PRETTY SURE
THAT'S NOT HOW IT WORKS.
OR YOU COULD PRETEND
TO BE A LESBIAN, YOU KNOW?
KISSING GIRLS ISN'T
ALL THAT BAD.
MAYBE IF WE TAKE IT
SUPER SLOW,
I WON'T HAVE TO KISS HER
AT ALL.
(SIGHS)
(MAYA LAUGHS)
SO, UH, WHAT'S-HIS-FACE
WASN'T TOO HAPPY
TO SEE ME THIS MORNING.
"MILES" WASN'T.
HE JUST DOESN'T KNOW YOU.
WHICH IS WHY YOU'RE COMING
TO THE SEMI-FORMAL.
YOU ALL ARE!
TINY:
THAT'S NOT A VERY GOOD IDEA.
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE THIS IS WHAT'LL HAPPEN
IF WE COME.
EVERYONE WILL SIT AROUND
EATING TINY SANDWICHES
AND CAVIAR.
TINY:
AND DRINKING TEA,
PINKIES UP!
BUT THIS ONE WILL GET UNDER
MONEYBAG'S SKIN.
BY BEING
A LITTLE TOO LIPPY.
AND THEN I'LL HAVE TO PUT MILES
IN A CHOKE HOLD
TO KEEP HIM FROM KILLING
OUR DARLING ZIG.
TINY:
AND I'LL ACCIDENTALLY
SET THE GYM ON FIRE.
AND THEN IT'S OFF TO JUVIE
FOR ALL OF US.
I THINK YOU GUYS ARE BEING
A LITTLE PESSIMISTIC ABOUT THIS.
IT COULD BE FUN!
COME ON, ZIG,
I'VE SEEN YOU BUST A MOVE.
IT'S NOT MY JOB TO FIX
YOUR RELATIONSHIP, MAYA.
BUT-
LEARN TO TAKE "NO"
FOR AN ANSWER!
ADORABLE! PERFECT!
LET'S GO!
IT'S NOT TOO POUFY?
ALLI:
NO, IT'S GREAT!
BESIDES, YOU'VE TRIED ON
LIKE A MILLION OTHER DRESSES!
I NEED TO LOOK
HOT TONIGHT.
CONNOR WOULD LOVE YOU
EVEN IF YOU LOOKED LIKE
A GIANT CUPCAKE.
YOU THINK I LOOK LIKE
A GIANT CUPCAKE!
SO NOT WHAT I MEANT!
NOPE, I'M NOT WEARING
THIS TONIGHT!
OKAY,
BUT WE'RE ALREADY LATE
AND WE'RE THE ONES
BRINGING THE TICKETS!
JUST- YOU GO AHEAD,
I'LL CATCH UP.
ALLI:
OKAY, BUT FOR THE RECORD,
MY FAVOURITE IS STILL
THE FIRST DRESS YOU TRIED ON -
TWO HOURS AGO!
(SIGHS)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(DISHES CLANK)
UH...
YOU'RE ALL DRESSED UP.
YEAH, BECAUSE I'M GOING
TO A SEMI-FORMAL.
SO WHEN DOES YOUR
HORSE-DRAWN CARRIAGE SHOW UP?
I THINK I'LL WAIT FOR MILES
OUTSIDE.
MAYA, I WAS JUST TRYING
TO COMPLIMENT YOU.
AND HOW WOULD I KNOW?!
YOU WERE SUCH A JERK
TODAY, ZIG!
WHAT, BECAUSE I DIDN'T
WANT TO GO THE DANCE
WITH YOU
AND YOUR STUPID BOYFRIEND?!
UNTIL YOU AND MILES
CAN GET ALONG,
MY LIFE IS GONNA BE HELL,
BUT AT LEAST
HE'S WILLING TO TRY!
SO WHAT, HE'S A BETTER GUY
THAN ME?
YEAH!
(KNOCK AT THE DOOR)
MAYA:
HEY.
WHOA!
ONE SEC.
EVERYTHING OKAY?
MAYA:
YEAH, IT IS NOW
THAT YOU'RE HERE.
♪ Please let go ♪
♪ And I'll let go of you ♪
(DOOR SLAMS)
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYS,
STUDENTS CHATTER)
HAVE I TOLD YOU
HOW AMAZING YOU LOOK?
ONLY ABOUT THIRTY TIMES,
WHICH IS TWENTY-NINE
TOO MANY
FOR A TOTALLY PLATONIC
SCIENCE PARTNER.
WHOA!
THAT'S A DRESS.
ALLI:
THAT I BOUGHT IN GRADE TEN
AND NEVER WORE
BECAUSE IT WAS TOO SMALL FOR ME!
HOW DO I LOOK?
OPEN FOR BUSINESS.
CONNOR:
WOW, JENNA,
YOU LOOK... AMAZING.
THANK YOU, CONNOR.
I WORE THIS FOR YOU.
♪ I feel all right ♪
♪ Tonight, tonight
I'm gonna dance all night ♪
you make me high ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Ohhhhh tonight ♪
(DANCERS CHATTER)
(JENNA GIGGLES)
MILES:
I'M SORRY YOUR PLANS
TO GET EVERYONE TOGETHER
DIDN'T WORK OUT.
NO, I'M OVER IT.
TONIGHT, I JUST WANNA
HAVE A FUN TIME
WITH MY BOYFRIEND.
GIRL:
I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU COULD DANCE!
CAN YOU STOP STEPPING
ON MY FEET?
WHAT?!
YOU'RE THE CLUMSY ONE!
ONLY BECAUSE I'M DISTRACTED
BY HOW MUCH I WANT TO KISS YOU.
THERE'S AN EASY FIX
TO THAT.
ZIG:
WELL, THAT'S PRETTY RUDE.
GRACE:
(LAUGHING)
SHE INVITES US HERE,
AND ALL SHE DOES IS MAKE OUT
WITH HER BOYFRIEND!
MAYA:
YOU CAME.
GRACE:
ONLY BECAUSE ZIGMUND
BEGGED US.
WE SNUCK IN
THROUGH THE SIDE DOOR.
MAYA:
LOOK WHO'S HERE!
TRISTAN:
NICE BOOTS!
GO TO HELL.
I WAS BEING SERIOUS!
THEY'RE VERY
ALEXANDER MCQUEEN.
IS THAT A GOOD THING?
COME ON,
LET'S DANCE.
BUY YOU A DRINK?
MAKE IT A DOUBLE.
♪ Tonight, tonight ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
♪♪♪
(IMOGEN LAUGHS)
(SLOW SONG PLAYS)
♪♪♪
HEY, DO-
OH! WHOOPS! UH...
BECKY:
I'M SORRY,
I'VE NEVER SLOW DANCED
WITH A GIRL BEFORE.
HOW DO YOU DO IT?
LIKE THIS.
(PANICKED)
NO, I CAN'T!
I THOUGHT I COULD
DANCE WITH YOU
AND MAYBE PRETEND
TO BE A LESBIAN,
BUT I CAN'T
BECAUSE I'M NOT!
OH, THANK HEAVENS!
BECAUSE YOU ALREADY
HATE ME?
NO!
YOU'RE MY FIRST GIRLFRIEND
AT DEGRASSI
WHO ISN'T MY GIRLFRIEND,
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
I DO.
ME AND FIONA
WERE INSEPARABLE,
BUT NOW
WE BARELY EVEN TALK.
THAT'S SO SAD.
YEAH.
BUT I HEARD A RUMOUR THAT,
THOUGH GIRLFRIENDS
COME AND GO,
BEST FRIENDS
STAY FOR LIFE.
BEST FRIENDS?
DEFINITELY.
(GIGGLING)
ALLI:
DEGRASSIANS,
IT'S TIME FOR THE MOMENT
YOU'VE ALL BEEN WAITING FOR!
DALLAS:
THE KING AND QUEEN
OF THE SWEETHEART SEMI-FORMAL.
HERE WE GO!
FINGERS CROSSED!
WHAT DID YOU USE ON THIS,
WOMAN, CRAZY GLUE?
OH, FOR THE LOVE OF-
GIMME!
(DRUM ROLL)
OKAY,
THE KING AND QUEEN:
CONNOR DELAURIER
AND JENNA MIDDLETON!
(STUDENTS CHEER)
♪ Hold me tight,
hold me tight ♪
♪ And every dream I have
will come alive, come alive ♪
♪ Throw my hands up ♪
DALLAS:
ANY WORDS
FOR YOUR ADORING MASSES?
YES, UM...
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
ESPECIALLY
TO MY WONDERFUL BOYFRIEND,
CONNOR.
BOO-YAH!
(STUDENTS GASP,
LAUGH)
(MUSIC STOPS ABRUPTLY)
(SHOCKED GASPS AND LAUGHTER)
I DIDN'T KNOW
THERE'D BE A SHOW.
(CAMERA SHUTTER SNAPS)
(GUYS LAUGH)
DALLAS:
UH... DJ!
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYS)
♪ Been there d-d-done it
it's the same every day ♪
♪ D-D-Don'tcha
don'tcha want it ♪
DID YOU, UM, CATCH
THE BASKETBALL GAME LAST NIGHT?
ZIG:
NO, I'M NOT REALLY INTO
WATCHING A BUNCH OF MEATHEADS
CHASE A BALL AROUND.
LOOK, I'M JUST TRYING
TO MAKE NICE.
YEAH, WELL,
DON'T DO ME ANY FAVOURS.
I'M DOING IT FOR MAYA,
BECAUSE I CARE.
AND IF YOU CARED,
YOU'D TRY, TOO.
I DO CARE ABOUT HER.
A LOT.
AS A FRIEND?
WELL, IT'S GONNA BE HARD
TO STAY FRIENDLY WITH SOMEONE
WHEN YOU SLEEP DOWN
THE HALL FROM THEM.
JUST KEEP HER OUT
OF YOUR CRAP, OKAY?
YOU KNOW, THE DRUGS
AND STUFF?
I'LL DEAL WHATEVER I WANT,
WHENEVER I WANT.
OH, AND REMEMBER,
HOLLINGSWORTH,
PLAY NICE.
♪ It's a serious vibe ♪
♪ Better take a chance
you know I won't ask you twice ♪
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYS,
MUFFLED)
HOW'S THE PUNCH?
"VERY CHERRY."
BECKY:
GOOD TO KNOW.
SO THAT'S WHY
YOU CAME HERE?
TO GET MY OPINION
ON TONIGHT'S
BEVERAGE SELECTION?
NO, I UH...
DO THEY TEACH YOU
HOW TO SHARE IN GERMANY?
I'M SORRY?
WELL, WE LEARNED
IN KINDERGARTEN.
SNACKS, TOYS...
IMOGENS.
I PLAY WELL WITH OTHERS.
WHY DO YOU ASK?
IMOGEN'S MY FIRST
BEST FRIEND.
LIKE, EVER.
YEAH, I DIDN'T REALLY WANT
TO GET BETWEEN YOU GUYS.
THEN YOU SHOULD GO
ASK HER TO DANCE.
I THOUGHT SHE WAS YOUR DATE.
YOUU WERE RIGHT.
I'M NOT... I'M NOT GAY,
I JUST... I DIDN'T WANT
TO LOSE A FRIEND.
SO YOU THINK
SHE'D SAY YES?
(LAUGHS)
I HAVE A HUNCH.
(BOTH LAUGH)
I WISH I HAD A FRIEND
LIKE YOU.
WELL, PLAY YOUR CARDS RIGHT
AND MAYBE YOU WILL.
(LAUGHS) THANKS.
YEAH.
♪ The only party hero ♪
SO THOSE ARE ACTUAL HOLES
IN YOUR FACE.
YES.
AH.
CAN I TOUCH THEM?
NO! OKAY.
NO...
HAVE YOU GUYS SEEN MILES?
ZIG, I NEED YOU
TO COME WITH ME.
MAYA:
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I'VE GOTTEN REPORTS
THERE'S DRUGS IN YOUR LOCKER.
I NEED YOU TO OPEN IT
SO I CAN DO AN INSPECTION.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS!
ZIG:
YEAH, WHAT GIVES YOU THE RIGHT
TO SEARCH MY LOCKER?!
THE SCHOOL CHARTER!
COME ON.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOU RAT!
I KNOW IT WAS YOU!
MAYA:
NO, MILES WOULD NEVER DO
ANYTHING LIKE THAT!
RIGHT?
RIGHT.
HE CAN'T EVEN
LOOK AT YOU!
HE'S LYING TO YOU,
MATLIN!
MILES, JUST TELL ME
THE TRUTH.
THE GUY'S A HUGE JERK.
(SCOFFS)
SERIOUSLY?
CAN WE NOT DO THIS HERE?
NO, JUST ANSWER
THE QUESTION.
DID YOU TELL ON ZIG?
I WAS WORRIED ABOUT YOU,
MAYA.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT HIS LIFE IS LIKE!
YOU HAVE NO CLUE
HOW HARD IT IS FOR HIM!
ARE YOU SERIOUSLY
DEFENDING HIM RIGHT NOW?!
YOU KNOW WHAT
HE SAID TO ME?!
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'D DO
SOMETHING SO SPITEFUL
JUST BECAUSE WHAT,
YOU WERE JEALOUS?
BECAUSE HE'S FOOLING YOU,
MAYA,
AND YOU'RE FALLING
FOR IT!
THE ONLY THING
I FELL FOR
WAS BELIEVING
THAT YOU WERE SOMEONE
THAT I COULD ACTUALLY
BE WITH!
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
I'M SAYING THAT I NEED
SOME TIME TO THINK.
SO YOU'RE CHOOSING HIM.
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT!
WHATEVER YOU SAY.
(SIGHS)
YOUR SUBJECTS AWAIT.
ON WHAT,
ANOTHER STRIP SHOW?!
WELL, AT LEAST
IT WASN'T BOTH BOOBS.
IS THAT SUPPOSED
TO MAKE ME FEEL BETTER?
YES?
(HUFFS)
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I LET THOSE NINER GIRLS
GET TO ME.
CONNOR MUST THINK
I'M AN IDIOT!
SOMEHOW,
I DON'T THINK HE DOES.
(ALLI LAUGHS)
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT WANT
TO CHANGE.
THANKS.
WHY DID YOU WEAR
A GARMENT
THAT COULDN'T CONTAIN
YOUR AMPLE BOSOM?
WELL, YOU SAID
YOU LIKED IT!
BUT OKAY, REALLY...
BECAUSE THOSE STUPID
LITTLE GIRLS
WERE TRYING
TO GET WITH YOU!
THEY ONLY LIKE ME NOW THAT
I'M CONVENTIONALLY DRESSED.
YOU LIKED ME
BEFORE THEN.
BESIDES, I DON'T LOVE
ANY OF THOSE OTHER GIRLS.
YOU LOVE ME?
YES, AND I HOPE
YOU RECIPROCATE.
YES, OF COURSE
I RECIPROCATE!
CONNOR, I LOVE YOU,
JUST THE WAY YOU ARE.
(LAUGHS)
♪ You in this light ♪
(DOOR CREAKS OPEN)
♪ I give up my fight ♪
♪ In the deepest
of the night ♪
WERE YOU EXPELLED?
SUSPENDED?
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
IF I HADN'T BUGGED YOU
TO COME-
MAYA, IT'S FINE.
WHAT HAPPENED
WITH PERINO?
NOTHING!
THERE'S NO DRUGS
IN MY LOCKER.
MILES,
HE'S NOT A BAD GUY,
THOUGH I DON'T KNOW WHY
HE'D DO SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
I DO.
DO YOU REMEMBER
WHEN I TOLD YOU
I'D WAIT FOR YOU?
OF COURSE.
WELL, I SHOULDN'T
HAVE SAID THAT.
I SHOULD'VE JUST
KISSED YOU.
BUT...
RULES ARE RULES.
GOOD NIGHT,
MAYA MATLIN.
(DOOR CLICKS SHUT)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)