♪♪♪
ALLI:
OH, LOOKING CUTE, GIRL!
OH, THANKS.
I WANTED A LOOK THAT SAYS,
"I'M READY TO TAKE ON
THE SCHOOL!"
(ALLI GIGGLES)
ALLI:
OH YEAH, DALLAS WENT TO GO
FIND THE KEY.
HEY!
CLARE:
AHEM! AHEM! AHEM!
HAS THE CANCER SPREAD
TO YOUR LUNGS?
CLARE:
NO! I'M STILL IN REMISSION.
I WAS JUST HOPING THAT YOU GUYS
WOULD STOP KISSING
LONG ENOUGH FOR ME
TO GET SOME HUGS?
BRING IT IN.
(CLARE AND JENNA GIGGLE)
NO KEY?
ONLY THE KEY
TO MY HEART.
ALLI:
OH, YOU CAN PUT THAT ONE BACK
ON YOUR KEYCHAIN, BUD.
CLARE:
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
PEOPLE ARE GONNA BE HERE
IN TWO HOURS,
AND WE NEED TO GET READY
FOR THE "WELCOME BACK" ASSEMBLY.
(DOORS OPEN,
MUSIC BLARES)
DREW:
HEY, GUYS!
WHY DO YOU ALL LOOK
SO SURPRISED?
ALLI:
(GASPS)
CLARE:
IT'S 6 A.M.!
THIS IS SCHOOL,
YOU'RE DREW TORRES!
STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT
DREW TORRES,
AND, UH, I COULDN'T SLEEP,
SO INSTEAD OF JUST STARING
AT THE CEILING,
I DECIDED TO COME HERE.
ANYWAY, I'VE GOT
THE "WELCOME BACK" ASSEMBLY
ALL SET UP.
COME ON!
CLARE:
WHAT?!
SOUND SYSTEM... CRANKED!
MAKE ROOM!
VIDEO FEED... READY!
UH-HUH, UH...
SMOKE MACHINE,
AND, EXCUSE ME,
EXCUSE ME, EXCUSE ME!
AND... LIGHT SHOW ON!
WOW!
YOU REALLY WENT ALL OUT!
I WANTED TO MAKE
OUR SENIOR YEAR
THE BEST ONE
DEGRASSI'S EVER HAD!
YOU GUYS IN?
ALL:
YEAH! WOO!
(CHANTING)
WOO!
♪ Black light,
black lightning ♪
♪ Whoa! ♪
♪ Black light,
black lightning ♪
IMOGEN:
HEY! HEY, BECKY!
HI.
UM, FUN SUMMER?
OH... SORRY.
THAT'S OKAY.
TRISTAN:
IT MUST BE NICE
HAVING YOUR CRUSH LINED UP
FOR THE YEAR.
I TOLD YOU,
I'M FOCUSING ON MUSIC,
NOT BOYS.
IS THAT WHY YOU
GOT CONTACTS?
SO YOU COULD EXCHANGE
FLIRTY GLANCES AT YOUR CELLO?
SHUT UP!
HEY, I...
MILES:
(LAUGHS) JEEZ!
CHEWY, YOU WERE HERE
FOR AN ENTIRE YEAR,
IT'S LIKE NONE OF THESE GIRLS
EVEN KNOW YOU.
TRUST ME,
NONE OF THESE GIRLS
ARE WORTH KNOWING.
I DON'T KNOW,
THERE MIGHT BE ONE OR TWO
WORTH CHECKING OUT.
(ENERGETIC MUSIC PLAYS)
(STUDENTS APPLAUD)
DREW:
GOOOOD MORNING, DEGRASSI!
WELCOME TO THE BEST YEAR
OF YOUR LIFE!
I AM HERE
TO INTRODUCE TO YOU
THE TEAM THAT'S GOING
TO BRING YOU THE RUCKUS!
YOUR STUDENT COUNCIL!
FIRST UP,
YOUR ATHLETIC REP:
THE MAN WITH THE MUSCLES,
MIKE DALLAS!
(STUDENTS CHEER AND APPLAUD)
DREW:
SHE'S SMART AND SASSY!
YOUR SOCIAL COORDINATOR,
ALLI BHANDARI!
(STUDENTS CHEER
AND APPLAUD)
DREW:
HE PUTS THE FUN
INTO FINANCIAL STATEMENTS:
TREASURER,
CONNOR DELAURIER!
(STUDENTS CHEER AND APPLAUD)
SHE'LL TAKE MINUTES
AND YOUR HEART:
SECRETARY,
JENNA MIDDLETON!
(STUDENTS CHEER
AND APPLAUD)
NEXT UP,
SHE IS MY PARTNER IN CRIME,
THE VOICE IN THE BACK
OF MY MIND,
HER NEW HAIRDO
SURE IS FINE...
YOUR VICE PRESIDENT,
CLARE EDWARDS!
(STUDENTS CHEER
AND APPLAUD)
NOW, FINALLY, FINALLY,
HE'S HANDSOME,
HE'S FUNNY...
HE'S ME.
YOUR STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT,
DREW TORRES!
(STUDENTS CHEER
AND APPLAUD)
WELCOME TO DEGRASSI,
EVERYBODY!
TODAY IS A FRESH START
FOR EVERYONE,
INCLUDING ME.
THIS YEAR IS ABOUT FUN,
OLD FRIENDS,
NEW DEVELOPMENTS,
ABOUT-
(STUDENTS GASP)
ALLI:
UM...
DALLAS: DREW!
ALLI: IS HE OKAY?
DALLAS:
DREW!
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ (The best that I can be) ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
ALLI:
WELL, THAT WAS AN ASSEMBLY
NO ONE'LL EVER FORGET.
CLARE:
I HOPE DREW'S OKAY.
WELL, AFTER HE CAME TO,
I SAW SEVEN GRADE NINE GIRLS
OFFER TO CARRY HIS BOOKS,
SO I THINK HE'LL BE FINE.
WELL, UNTIL HIS FIANCEE
COMES HOME FROM UNIVERSITY
FOR A VISIT.
JENNA:
SO YOU HAVE PHYSICS
FOURTH PERIOD.
UM, I COULD SWITCH
INTO THAT.
BUT YOU KNOW NOTHING
ABOUT PHYSICS.
YEAH,
BUT WOULDN'T IT BE FUN
TO HAVE
ALL OUR CLASSES TOGETHER?
BUT IT'S PHYSICS,
IT'S ALREADY FUN.
OH, YOU GUYS ONLY HAVE
THREE CLASSES TOGETHER?
IT MUST FEEL LIKE
AN OCEAN APART.
JENNA:
YOU'RE STILL THINKING
ABOUT LEO?
HE'S IN FRANCE,
LET HIM ROT THERE!
COME ON,
LEO'S A GOOD GUY.
WELL, SHE CAN'T BE THINKING
ABOUT HIM THAT HARD
IF SHE'S ALREADY GOT
A DATE TONIGHT.
WELL, JEEZ, YOU MOVE FAST.
IT'S NOT EVEN FIRST PERIOD!
WITH WHO?
SHE WON'T TELL ME!
I JUST DON'T WANT
TO SAY ANYTHING
UNTIL I KNOW FOR SURE
THAT IT'S GONNA WORK OUT.
SO IT'S DALLAS.
IT'S NOT DALLAS!
IT'S GOTTA BE DALLAS.
ABOUT TIME!
YEAH, YOU TWO WILL MAKE
THE CUTEST BABIES!
OKAY, JUST LET ME GO
ON MY DATE,
AND IF THERE'S FIREWORKS,
THEN YOU GUYS CAN MEET HIM.
OKAY, BUT IF DALLAS
IS IN MY NEXT CLASS,
CAN I MEET HIM THEN?
UGH!
(SIGHS)
I TOLD YOU,
I'M FINE!
DUDE, YOU COLLAPSED
ON STAGE!
THE NURSE TOOK
MY BLOOD PRESSURE,
DID HER LITTLE TESTS
OR WHATEVER,
I PASSED, I'M-
WHAT MORE DO YOU WANT
FROM ME?
YOU ALSO SAID
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN SLEEPING.
SO? DUDE, CAN WE JUST GET
THE SCHOOL YEAR STARTED?
WE'RE GONNA BE LATE
FOR MATH.
DALLAS:
HOLD UP.
YOU CAN PRETEND
FOR EVERYONE ELSE,
BUT YOU CAN'T PRETEND
FOR ME.
WHAT?
I COULD LIKE MATH.
YOU THINKING ABOUT ADAM?
I'M TRYING NOT TO.
BUT YOU'VE GOTTA SLEEP.
HAVE YOU BEEN TAKING THOSE PILLS
THE DOCTOR GAVE YOU?
THE ZOLPIDEM
OR WHATEVER IT'S CALLED?
NO, I DON'T NEED THEM.
YOU NEED SOMETHING.
YEAH, I-I NEED THIS:
SCHOOL, STUDENT COUNCIL,
STUFF TO KEEP ME BUSY,
MAYBE TIRE ME OUT.
FOR THE FIRST TIME
SINCE ADAM DIED,
I'M EXCITED
ABOUT STUFF AGAIN.
EXCEPT MATH CLASS,
RIGHT?
YOU CRAZY?
MR. SIMPSON:
ZOE RIVAS!
A REAL LIVE CELEBRITY
AT OUR SCHOOL!
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT LIKE
GATSBY GARCIA IN REAL LIFE.
YOU WATCH "WEST DRIVE"?
OH, NO, NO.
MY SON...
HE LOVES THE SHOW.
I'M GONNA GO
SET YOU UP.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
CAN WE LEAVE NOW?
WE TALKED ABOUT THIS.
AND I BELIEVE I SAID,
"I DON'T WANNA GO
TO THAT STEAMING HELLHOLE!"
YOU'RE FIFTEEN.
IF YOU'RE NOT WORKING,
YOU HAVE TO BE IN SCHOOL.
BUT THIS ONE?
I SENT YOU TO PARIS
THIS SUMMER,
SO YOU COULD GET TO KNOW
SOME FRIENDS WHO GO HERE.
WHAT IF EVERYONE
FINDS OUT
WHY I GOT KICKED OFF
THE SHOW?
OH HONEY, THEY WON'T.
LET'S CALL THIS PARTY
TO ORDER!
ALLI: ALL RIGHT!
CLARE: ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE OKAY?
DREW:
YEAH, I'M FINE.
'CAUSE IT'S OKAY
IF YOU'RE NOT,
YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH A LOT
WITH ADAM AND-
NO, I'M FINE!
YOU KNOW,
I TALKED TO SIMPSON.
HE SAID THAT WE COULD
SPLIT THE WORKLOAD,
IF IT'S TOO MUCH-
CLARE, I'M THE PRESIDENT,
I CAN DO THIS, ALL RIGHT?
S-S-START.
CLARE:
OKAY, UM...
BUT WE'RE STILL SHORT
A FEW REPS -
DRAMA, KNITTING SOCIETY,
OUTDOORS CLUB.
DREW:
JUST, UH, BANG THE GAVEL.
OKAY, I'D LIKE CALL TO ORDER
THE FIRST OFFICIAL MEETING
OF THIS YEAR'S
STUDENT COUNCIL!
(STUDENTS APPLAUD)
AND I WOULD LIKE TO GET
RIGHT TO THE GOOD STUFF,
PLANNING THE FIRST EVENT
OF THE YEAR.
WE NEED SOMETHING BIG,
SOMETHING SPECIAL.
I WAS THINKING MAYBE A DANCE?
I SECOND THAT!
WHAT IF WE DID SOMETHING
TO REMEMBER ADAM?
BECKY:
YEAH, LIKE A "NO TEXTING
AND DRIVING" CAMPAIGN!
FOR THE FIRST EVENT
OF THE YEAR?
ALLI:
ALL PEOPLE CAN LEARN
FROM THE TRAGEDY.
ADAM WOULD'VE WANTED THIS.
NO, HE WOULDN'T HAVE!
HE WOULD'VE WANTED...
A DEGRASSI
"BEACH BASH" DANCE!
BECKY:
(SIGHS)
LET'S PUT IT
TO THE PEOPLE.
SHALL WE PREPARE PRESENTATIONS
AND TAKE A VOTE
AT TOMORROW'S MEETING?
YEAH, I GUESS.
CLARE:
GREAT. UM, NEXT ORDER
OF BUSINESS:
SHOULD WE USE THE GRANT MONEY
TO REVIVE DEGRASSI TV?
YEAH, BUT I LIKED HER
AFTER SHE GOT MAD AT US
AND SENT US TO DETENTION!
OH MY GOSH!
MILES:
MAYA, SINCE I'M NEW HERE,
GOT ANY GOOD
GIRLFRIEND RECOMMENDATIONS?
YOU REALLY THINK
I'D SIC YOU ON SOME POOR,
UNSUSPECTING GIRL?
MM, YOU MEAN
SOME EXTREMELY LUCKY GIRL.
TRISTAN:
OH, LIKE ZOE,
WHO YOU MADE OUT WITH
ALL OVER FRANCE
AND THEN DROPPED
LIKE A HOT...
WHAT'S FRENCH FOR POTATO?
YEAH,
ZOE WAS A MISTAKE.
BUT, UM, THAT'S ALL
BEHIND ME NOW.
LITERALLY.
WHAT?
SURPRISE.
YOU'RE AT DEGRASSI NOW?
UM, THIS IS AWKWARD,
RIGHT?
YUP.
TOTALLY AWKWARD.
(BELL RINGS)
YOU'RE NEW, YES?
THIS IS THE PART OF CLASS
WHERE WE ALL SIT DOWN.
ZOE:
UM, ACTUALLY, I THINK I FORGOT
SOMETHING IN MY LOCKER,
SO I SHOULD GO.
MR. PERINO:
THE BELL RANG.
YOU'RE MINE NOW.
I SEE YOU'VE GOT
FIRST DAY JITTERS,
BUT I NEED TO START
THIS CLASS,
SO JUST GET OVER
WHATEVER BOY DRAMA THIS IS,
TAKE A DEEP BREATH,
CHILL OUT.
WHY DON'T YOU
CHILL OUT?!
(STUDENTS GASP)
TRISTAN:
THAT REALLY IS HER
GO-TO MOVE, HUH?
(STUDENTS CHUCKLE
AND WHISPER)
(CARS RUMBLE)
(BLOWS OUT BREATH)
♪♪♪
♪ I will never let you go ♪
♪ I know you won't leave,
know you won't leave ♪
♪ Being in love
means I have to know ♪
♪ And learn to take it,
learn to take your love ♪
♪ I won't ever let you go ♪
♪ I float away
into your afterglow ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm never gonna
let you go ♪
DREW:
I SWERVE...
FIRE MISSILES...
BOO-YAH!
WOO! IN YOUR FACE!
DALLAS:
ALL RIGHT,
I'M GOING TO BED.
WHAT, WAS IT
THE VICTORY DANCE?
IT'S THE 1:00 A.M.
THAT OKAY?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
WHAT?
I JUST- I CAN'T BELIEVE
CLARE PROPOSED
A TEXTING AND DRIVING EVENT
INSTEAD OF A DANCE.
IT'S NICE TO KNOW ADAM'S
STILL ON PEOPLE'S MINDS.
BUT IT'S NOT GOING
TO BRING HIM BACK, SO...
WHY DO WE HAVE TO DWELL?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
JUST TRY
AND GET SOME SLEEP.
DALLAS:
YOU GONNA CRASH HERE AGAIN?
WITH THE TV ON,
YEAH.
NIGHT.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(PILLS RATTLE)
(SIGHS)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
CLARE:
YOU ARE GLOWING.
AND WEARING
A LITTLE EXTRA MAKEUP!
WHAT ARE YOU HIDING?
NOTHING.
JENNA:
WHEN DO WE GET TO KNOW WHAT KIND
OF A KISSER MIKE DALLAS IS?
UM, IT WASN'T DALLAS.
IT WAS LEO!
N-NO.
YEAH, HE FLEW IN YESTERDAY.
HE MISSED ME.
ISN'T THAT SO ROMANTIC?
TRY INSANE!
THIS GUY CAN'T BE TRUSTED.
THAT'S A LITTLE HARSH.
NO. LEO HURT HER, CLARE,
PHYSICALLY!
I SAW THE BRUISES!
IT WAS NOTHING.
WE GOT INTO A FIGHT,
IT GOT HEATED.
BUT I GRABBED HIM, TOO.
STILL, ALLI,
THAT'S A WARNING SIGN.
ALLI:
OH, LIKE DRIVING A CAR
INTO A WALL?
OR BRINGING A GUN
TO SCHOOL?
OR, YOU KNOW,
STEALING UNDERWEAR?
YOUR BOYFRIENDS
AREN'T SAINTS!
SO HE CAME HERE
JUST FOR YOU,
WITHOUT A PLAN?
HE CAME BECAUSE HE LOVES ME.
WHY ARE YOU GUYS
TRYING TO RUIN THAT?
MR. PERINO:
TODAY, WE START UNIT ONE,
THE NATURE OF POLITICS!
BUT DREW TORRES,
YOU'LL BE MISSING OUT.
YOU'RE WANTED IN THE OFFICE.
WHERE'S DREW?
(CELL PHONE BUZZES)
(DREW GROANS)
MORNING, B.
BIANCA:
HEY. I DIDN'T EXPECT YOU
TO ANSWER.
SO THEN WHY'D YOU CALL?
BIANCA:
TO LEAVE YOU
A SEXY MESSAGE.
(LAUGHS)
BIANCA:
SHOULDN'T YOU BE IN CLASS?
IT'S NINE!
DO YOU KNOW
WHAT THIS MEANS?
BIANCA:
DETENTION?
NO! NO, I FINALLY SLEPT
FOR LIKE HOURS!
BIANCA:
YEAH, YOU FELL ASLEEP
TALKING TO ME
ON THE PHONE
LAST NIGHT.
WE TALKED LAST NIGHT?
BIANCA:
AT LIKE 4:00 A.M.
YOU WERE GROGGY.
IT WAS PRETTY CUTE.
WHATEVER. I'M JUST GLAD
I FINALLY GOT SOME REST.
I FEEL LIKE A NEW MAN!
I SHOULD PROBABLY
GET TO CLASS.
FEEL FREE TO CALL BACK
AND LEAVE THAT SEXY MESSAGE!
BIANCA:
(SQUEALS SEXILY)
SIMPSON:
I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU BEHAVE
ON A TV SHOW, ZOE,
BUT WHAT YOU DID
YESTERDAY
HAS NO PLACE
IN THE REAL WORLD!
CAN'T YOU JUST TRANSFER ME
OUT OF THAT CLASS?
YOU ASSAULTED A TEACHER!
WE MAY BE TALKING
ABOUT EXPULSION.
ZOE HAS A LEARNING
DISABILITY.
ZOE:
MOM!
DYSLEXIA.
IS THIS TRUE?
ABSOLUTELY.
ZOE, WILL YOU REQUIRE
EXTRA HELP WITH TESTS?
NO, I WILL NOT.
CAN I HAVE A MINUTE WITH
MY DAUGHTER, ALONE?
I GUESS SO.
HOW COULD YOU
TELL HIM THAT?!
I JUST SAVED YOUR ASS!
HE WAS GONNA KICK YOU OUT!
I WANTED HIM TO!
CAN'T YOU JUST HOME SCHOOL ME?
NO!
UNTIL YOU GET
ANOTHER JOB,
I HAVE TO GET ONE
OF MY OWN.
I'M NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE HERE.
I KNOW.
YOU SHOULD STILL BE
ON "WEST DRIVE,"
BUT YOU GOT YOURSELF FIRED.
NOBODY WANTS TO WORK
WITH YOU NOW,
SO DO WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO MAKE THIS WORK.
(PANTING)
DREW:
WHAT IS GOING ON?
JUST CATCHING SOME RAYS
DURING MY SPARE!
AM I STILL DREAMING?
CLARE:
NOT COOL, DREW!
IF YOU DIDN'T WANNA DO
THE TEXTING AND DRIVING CAMPAIGN
BECAUSE OF ADAM,
YOU COULD'VE SAID SO.
I'M FINE, CLARE.
THEN I'M OFFICIALLY MAD
THAT YOU ORDERED THIS STUFF
WITHOUT ME!
WHAT?! I-I DIDN'T ORDER
ANY OF THIS STUFF!
THIS INVOICE SAYS
OTHERWISE.
IMOGEN:
HEY!
IF YOU GUYS FIND OUT
WHO DID ORDER ALL THIS STUFF,
CAN YOU ASK THEM TO GET US
A MINI WAVE POOL, TOO?
DREW:
YEAH...
(BELL RINGS)
DUDE, CLARE IS NOT HAPPY.
I KNOW,
IT'S HILARIOUS.
SO DID YOU ORDER
ALL THE SAND?
WHAT? NO.
YOU DID!
LAST NIGHT.
YOU DON'T REMEMBER?
NO!
YOU WERE BANGING AROUND
THE KITCHEN AT LIKE 3:00 A.M.,
SO I GOT UP.
YOU WERE EATING ICE CREAM
AND PLACING AN ORDER ONLINE.
WHAT?! ALL RIGHT,
BIANCA SAID THAT
I TALKED TO HER, TOO.
I TOOK THOSE SLEEPING PILLS;
I THOUGHT I SLEPT SO WELL!
DUDE, THOSE PILLS WORK
FOR SOME PEOPLE,
BUT OTHER PEOPLE
GET CRAZY SIDE EFFECTS.
SO I ORDERED THE SAND.
BIG TIME.
GUESS YOU REALLY WANTED
THAT BEACH DANCE.
SO WHAT DO I DO?
PRAY FOR A MIRACLE,
AND HOPE YOU WIN THE VOTE
AT COUNCIL.
OH GOSH...
(GIRLS GIGGLE)
I THINK THERE MIGHT BE A WAY.
IS ANYONE GOING TO THE FASHION
CLUB MEETING TONIGHT?
NO, I'M GONNA WORK
ON A SONG.
I'M THINKING OF STARTING
A NEW BAND.
NO, DON'T LOOK AT ME.
THE ONLY THING I DO
IS BASKETBALL
AND THAT'S 'CAUSE MY DAD
MAKES ME.
TRISTAN:
COOL. I COULD PLAY BASKETBALL.
SERIOUSLY?!
TRISTAN:
MY BROTHER PLAYED.
I COULD DO IT.
I HAVE A KILLER JUNK SHOT.
MILES:
YOU MEAN JUMP SHOT?
TRISTAN:
SERIOUSLY?
ZOE:
UM, HEY, DO THEY HAVE
CHEERLEADERS HERE?
MAYBE I COULD CHEER YOU GUYS ON.
LET ME PUT THIS
IN TV TERMS,
SO YOU'LL UNDERSTAND.
I DON'T DO RERUNS,
ESPECIALLY WITH MEAN GIRLS
LIKE YOU.
SCREW YOU!
(STARTLED GRUNT)
DREW: HEY.
ZOE: HEY!
DREW: I NEED YOU.
ZOE: I'M SORRY?
DREW:
FOR A STUDENT COUNCIL MEETING
LIKE NOW. CAN YOU?
UM... WHAT DO I HAVE TO DO?
I'LL EXPLAIN ON THE WAY.
(BOTH SIGH)
LEO:
WHOA! THIS IS THE COFFEE
YOU PINED FOR IN FRANCE?
ALLI:
WHAT ARE WE DOING HERE?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
I SHOULD'VE ORDERED
THE ESPRESSO.
I MEAN WITH US,
YOU COMING HERE.
I MEAN,
WHAT'S OUR GAME PLAN?
TO TAKE A CHANCE
ON LOVE.
OKAY, BUT WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU LEAVE?
I WON'T.
I CAN STAY WITH MY GODFATHER
AS LONG AS I WANT.
BUT WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO?
I HAVE SCHOOL,
AND A FAMILY, AND-
I'VE LOOKED INTO TRANSFERRING
TO T.U. -
THEY HAVE A GREAT
BIOLOGY DEPARTMENT -
AND I'LL GET A JOB.
WHERE?
HERE.
THEY NEED SOMEONE TO TEACH THEM
HOW TO MAKE COFFEE.
WE CAN DO THIS,
ALLI.
OKAY, AND UM...
WHAT HAPPENS
IF YOU GET JEALOUS AGAIN?
I MEAN, LAST TIME
YOU HURT ME.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO.
YOU LEFT BRUISES!
I OVERREACTED,
I LOST CONTROL.
IT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
I DON'T WANT TO BE
THAT PERSON,
AND I REALLY HOPED
YOU COULD HELP ME BE BETTER.
(SIGHS)
(CELL PHONE BUZZES)
OH.
I HAVE TO GET BACK
TO SCHOOL.
STUDENT COUNCIL MEETING.
NO, STAY HERE WITH ME,
AND I'LL STAY HERE
WITH YOU.
(CHUCKLES AND SIGHS)
DID YOU SORT OUT
THE SAND?
I THOUGHT WE MIGHT HAVE
THE VOTE FIRST.
BUT WE KINDA ALREADY KNOW
HOW THE VOTE'S GONNA GO, RIGHT?
DO WE?
CLARE:
WHY ARE THERE LIKE
20 LITTLE GIRLS HERE?
THESE ARE THE NEW
COUNCIL MEMBERS.
I FILLED SOME OPEN POSITIONS.
THIS IS THE DRAMA REP
AND THE OUTDOORS CLUB REP.
NO, YOU CAN'T DO THAT!
DREW:
YOU WANT ME TO TURN AWAY
ENTHUSIASTIC
NEW COUNCIL MEMBERS?!
I'D LIKE TO CALL
THIS MEETING TO ORDER.
FIRST UP, THE VOTE ON COUNCIL'S
FIRST EVENT.
CLARE?
(LOUD THUD)
(MUFFLED LAUGHTER)
I'D LIKE TO PROPOSE
AN ANTI-TEXTING
AND DRIVING CAMPAIGN.
WE'LL HANG FOUR THOUSAND
CELL PHONES IN THE FOYER,
ONE FOR EVERY TEEN TEXTING
AND DRIVING DEATH A YEAR.
ALL THOSE IN FAVOUR?
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR, FIVE,
SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT.
AND I PROPOSE A DEGRASSI
"BEACH BASH" DANCE.
SUN, SAND,
AND A FRESH NEW START
FOR EVERYONE THIS YEAR.
ALL IN FAVOUR?
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR,
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT...
NINE.
(GAVEL BANGS)
WHO'S READY TO PARTY?
WHAT IS THIS?
IT'S A DEMOCRACY.
WELL, IF THIS IS HOW
YOU WANT TO RUN COUNCIL,
YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN.
AND DREW,
YOU'D BETTER GET SOME SLEEP
BECAUSE IT'S GONNA TAKE
A LOT OF ENERGY
TO WRANGLE
ALL THESE CHILDREN!
I THINK I'LL SLEEP
JUST FINE.
I HOPE SO.
LOOKS LIKE WE HAVE
A DANCE TO PLAN.
FIRST THINGS FIRST,
IF WE'RE GONNA PULL THIS OFF,
I'M GONNA NEED EVERYONE'S
CONTACT INFORMATION.
FEEL FREE TO CALL ME ANYTIME.
WELL, IF YOU KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT PLANNING A DANCE,
I DEFINITELY WILL.
I DON'T YET,
BUT I'M A FAST LEARNER.
(LAUGHS)
(CRICKETS CHIRP)
♪♪♪
(PILLS RATTLE)
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
ZOE:
WHO IS THIS?
IT'S 4:00 A.M.!
DREW: (GROGGILY)
HEY, CUTIE, HOW'RE YOU DOING?
DREW?
DREW:
I JUST WANTED TO CALL YOU
AND TELL YOU HOW GREAT YOU ARE.
TODAY WAS PERFECT.
REALLY?
DREW:
I'M SO HAPPY
YOU FELL INTO MY ARMS.
DID I WAKE YOU?
NOT THAT YOU...
NOT THAT YOU NEED
YOUR BEAUTY SLEEP,
YOU'RE...
YOU'RE ALREADY SO PRETTY.
YOU'RE THE PRETTIEST GIRL.
YOU HAVE REALLY PRETTY EYES...
PRETTY EVERYTHING.