(SIGHS TEARFULLY)
ALLI:
LEO, CALM DOWN,
PLEASE JUST CALM DOWN!
LEO: DON'T TELL ME WHAT TO DO!
ALLI: AGGHHH!
JENNA:
OKAY, WHOA.
OKAY,
THAT'S A SERIOUS CAKE JOB.
GIVE IT TO ME,
I CAN FIX.
NO, THERE'S NO USE.
I STAYED UP ALL NIGHT
STUDYING FOR MY SATS.
"STUDYING," YEAH.
SURE.
HOW'D YOUR TALK
WITH LEO GO?
DID YOU FIGURE OUT
A PLAN FOR M.I.T.?
NO, WE ACTUALLY ENDED UP
IN A HUGE FIGHT,
BUT I DON'T REALLY WANT
TO TALK ABOUT IT RIGHT NOW.
CLARE: ARE YOU OKAY?
ALLI: I'M FINE!
I JUST HAVE TO FOCUS ON
ROCKING THE SATS TODAY.
I'M FINE, I SWEAR!
JENNA:
PUMPKIN!
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE!
I DIDN'T.
THEY'RE FOR ALLI.
JENNA:
WHAT?
LEO IS SUCH A SWEETHEART!
(BELL RINGS)
WHATEVER HAPPENED,
IT SEEMS LIKE HE'S SORRY.
(ALLI SIGHS)
I HAVE SIX HOURS
UNTIL THE SATS.
I HAVE TO STAY...
FOCUSED!
(SIGHS)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ (The best that I can be) ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
DEGRASSI TAKES BULLYING
VERY SERIOUSLY.
THE BOYS IN MAYA'S ENGLISH CLASS
HAVE BEEN SPOKEN TO.
AND THE FACERANGE PAGE?
WELL, UH,
DURING THE SCHOOL YEAR,
SOCIAL MEDIA SITES ARE BANNED
FROM THE RESOURCE CENTRE
COMPUTERS.
UNFORTUNATELY, WE'RE NOT
EQUIPPED TO POLICE THAT.
OKAY, SO CAN YOU HELP US
FIND THE PERSON
WHO STARTED THAT PAGE?
MR. SIMPSON:
WE'LL LOOK INTO IT.
I CAN'T MAKE ANY PROMISES.
HOW WOULD YOU FEEL
IF PEOPLE STARTED SPREADING LIES
ABOUT YOUR DAUGHTER?
WITH ALL DUE RESPECT
MRS. MATLIN,
I DON'T CONTROL THE INTERNET.
WE'RE DOING THE BEST WE CAN,
I'M SORRY.
SORRY ISN'T GONNA
MAKE THINGS BETTER!
MRS. MATLIN:
MAYA!
I'M SORRY,
MR. SIMPSON,
BUT IT WON'T.
♪♪♪
I TAKE IT
THEY DIDN'T FIND THE PERSON
WHO MADE THE FACERANGE PAGE?
NO. NO ONE CAN DO
ANYTHING.
WHO WOULD DO THIS TO ME?
I WISH I KNEW.
IT COULD BE ANYONE.
JUST LAY LOW
FOR A FEW DAYS
AND THIS'LL BLOW OVER.
I JUST WANNA DISAPPEAR.
DREW:
HEY, DALLAS, BUDDY,
YOU AWAKE?
I MADE YOU A PROTEIN SHAKE:
CREATIN, AVOCADO,
CHOCOLATE POWDER.
HEY, BUDDY,
I KNOW YOU'RE PISSED AT ME
AND UH...
I DON'T BLAME YOU.
I'M SORRY, MAN.
(DRAWERS RATTLE)
DALLAS?
(CELLO PLAYS)
♪♪♪
MY MOM USED TO PLAY THAT
ALL THE TIME,
AND YOU'RE REALLY GOOD.
THANKS.
PEOPLE STILL GIVING YOU
A REALLY HARD TIME
ABOUT THAT VIDEO, EH?
WHATEVER.
WELL, IF YOU NEED ME
TO KICK ANYBODY'S ASS,
I GOT YOUR BACK.
AND WHAT A SWEET
BACK IT IS!
MAYA: GET OFF OF ME!
NEIL: COME ON!
I KNOW YOU WANT IT,
I SAW THOSE PHOTOS.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO PRETEND
WITH ME.
MAYA: GET OFF OF ME!
MILES: GET OFF OF HER!
NEIL:
WHOA!
OOF!
NEIL: WHOA, DUDE! WHA-
MILES: GET LOST!
(NEIL GRUNTS)
MAYA:
(GASPS)
YOU JUST HIT HIM...
WITH YOUR FIST!
IS YOUR HAND OKAY?
UM, NO, NOT REALLY,
BUT IT WAS WORTH IT.
I THOUGHT IF I COULD
JUST LAY LOW,
EVERYTHING WOULD BE OKAY.
EVERYONE THINKS
I'M A SLUT.
THEY'RE WRONG.
I WAS WRONG.
LOOK, HOW MANY GUYS
HAVE YOU KISSED?
THREE.
I'VE KISSED FIFTY.
GUYS?
NO, GIRLS,
AND... ONE TRISTAN.
SOMEONE SHOULD MAKE
A PAGE ABOUT ME!
WELL, THEY WOULD NEVER.
YOU'RE A BOY.
THEY'D PROBABLY BUILD
YOU A STATUE.
(LAUGHS WRYLY)
I JUST WISH THERE WAS A WAY
I COULD MAKE THIS
ALL GO AWAY.
I MIGHT HAVE AN IDEA.
CLARE: SALACIOUS.
ALLI: INDECENT.
CLARE: CAPRICIOUS.
ALLI: UNPREDICTABLE.
INSOLENT.
WHAT WAS THE WORD?
THAT'S THE THIRD TIME
HE'S CALLED,
MAYBE YOU SHOULD ANSWER.
CAN YOU USE IT
IN A SENTENCE?
ALLI IS BEING INSOLENT
TO HER BOYFRIEND.
IT MEANS RUDE.
CAN WE TALK?
NOT A GOOD TIME.
PLEASE, ALLI,
I WANT TO APOLOGIZE.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
YOU CAN'T JUST SHOW UP
AT MY SCHOOL!
YOU HAVE TO KNOW
HOW SORRY I AM.
YOU SAID THAT WOULD
NEVER HAPPEN AGAIN
AND I BELIEVED YOU!
THE THOUGHT OF LOSING YOU...
I THOUGHT WE WOULD BE
TOGETHER FOREVER.
SO DID I.
BUT WE STILL CAN!
I'LL GO WITH YOU TO M.I.T.,
TO THE MOON, ANYWHERE!
NO! I AM NOT GONNA BE
THAT STUPID GIRL
THAT GOES BACK
AND LETS IT HAPPEN AGAIN,
AND AGAIN, AND AGAIN!
ALLI, PLEASE...
I LOVE YOU.
THEN YOU WOULDN'T
HAVE HURT ME!
YOU HAVE RAGE ISSUES, LEO,
SERIOUS RAGE ISSUES,
AND YOU NEED HELP!
I KNOW,
YOU'RE RIGHT.
BUT I CAN'T DO IT
WITHOUT YOU.
I'M BROKEN, ALLI.
FIX ME.
(BELL RINGS)
I HAVE MY SATS.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(LOUD ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
EW! WHAT'RE WE DOING
IN THE RUBBER ROOM HALLWAY?
HEY, YOU'RE THE VIDEO GIRL.
NICE PICS.
AND WE'RE LEAVING NOW.
STOP. THIS IS GRACE.
SHE CAN HELP.
THE FACERANGE PAGE WAS SET UP
FROM A FAKE ACCOUNT.
YEAH,
I ALREADY KNOW THAT.
YOU WANNA LET ME FINISH,
BLONDIE?
AS PER RICHIE-RICH'S REQUEST,
I SCRUBBED AND DELETED
THE PAGE,
BUT IF THESE PEOPLE
ARE OUT TO GET YOU,
THEY'RE GONNA MAKE
A NEW ONE.
YEAH, WELL, THEY'LL HAVE
TO START FROM SCRATCH.
THEY'VE STILL GOT
ALL THE PICTURES.
MILES:
YEAH, WHICH IS WHY...
WHICH IS WHY I SENT A MESSAGE
TO THE FAKE ACCOUNT
ASKING THEM TO CONFIRM
THEIR ACCOUNT INFO
BY ENTERING THEIR EMAIL.
PEOPLE ARE SUCH IDIOTS,
IT WORKS EVERY TIME.
SO WHO WAS IT?
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
ICE HOUNDS!
OFF TO PRACTICE?
WHERE'S YOUR CAPTAIN?
RIGHT HERE.
HOW CAN I HELP YOU?
UM, NO,
I MEANT DALLAS.
DID HE PASS OUT ON ONE
OF YOUR COUCHES LAST NIGHT?
NO, DALLAS HASN'T TALKED
TO ANY OF US
IN A COUPLE WEEKS.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I THOUGHT YOU GUYS
TRAVELLED IN A PACK.
NO, NOT SINCE
COACH CUT HIM.
HAD TO MAKE ROOM
FOR NEW TALENT.
WHAT?!
HE DIDN'T TELL YOU?
NO, NO, I...
I JUST ASSUMED.
H-HOCKEY'S HIS LIFE!
YEAH, YEAH, WELL...
MAN, IF YOU SEE HIM,
TELL HIM WE SAY, "WHAT'S UP?"
WE MISS THAT DUDE.
YEAH, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT,
SEE YA, BUD.
SEE YA.
HOCKEY PLAYERS:
YEAH! LUKE! LUKE! LUKE!
LUKE! LUKE!
(LAUGHING)
TEAMMATE:
BUDDY, SIT DOWN, MAN!
HEY, MAN, I KNOW-
I KNOW ABOUT THE TEAM.
THAT SUCKS!
BUT IT DOESN'T MEAN YOU HAVE
TO THROW EVERYTHING AWAY.
JUST COME BACK TO THE SCHOOL,
OR...
OR AT LEAST SHOW ME
PROOF OF LIFE.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
MAYA:
(SIGHS) SO...
I KNOW WHO STARTED
THE FACERANGE PAGE.
YOU DO?
WHO, MILES?
OMG! TRISTAN?
I KNOW IT WAS YOU!
OH MAYA, WHERE DID YOU GET
A CRAZY IDEA LIKE THAT?
I THOUGHT
WE WERE FRIENDS, ZOE!
FRIENDS DON'T STEAL
FRIENDS' BOYFRIENDS.
MILES AND I ARE NOT
EVEN DATING!
WHATEVER, SLUT.
(ZOE GASPS)
DO YOU KNOW HOW TO HARD IT IS
TO GET OUT NAIL POLISH?!
NOT AS HARD AS IT IS
TO GET OUT BITCH!
(STRUGGLING GRUNTS)
(FABRIC TEARS)
MAYA:
OW! OW!
GET OFF OF ME!
MR. PERINO:
HEY!
SIMPSON'S OFFICE! NOW!
SHE RUINED
MY REPUTATION!
$200 DOLLAR JEANS
AND SHE ATTACKED ME!
SHE STARTED
THE FACERANGE PAGE!
ENOUGH!
FIGHTING IS NOT ACCEPTABLE
AT SCHOOL.
TWO WEEKS DETENTION,
BOTH OF YOU.
UH, SHOULDN'T ZOE'S PUNISHMENT
BE WORSE?
SHE STARTED THE FACERANGE PAGE!
ZOE, IS THIS TRUE?
I MADE A BIG MISTAKE.
I NEVER MEANT
TO HURT ANYONE.
AND THIS IS WHERE
SHE THANKS THE ACADEMY!
MR. SIMPSON:
OKAY, LOOK, SCHOOL COMPUTERS
WEREN'T USED,
SO I'VE DONE WHAT I CAN
FROM AN ADMINISTRATIVE
STANDPOINT.
THE NEXT STEP IS UP
TO YOU GUYS.
LEGAL ACTION.
ZOE:
MAYA, MRS. MATLIN,
I'M SO SORRY.
I DON'T THINK IT'S NECESSARY
TO GET THE POLICE INVOLVED.
I AGREE.
MOM!
SHE RUINED MY LIFE!
ZOE:
I SAID I'M SORRY!
SHOW SOME MERCY!
YOU DON'T DESERVE IT!
MRS. MATLIN:
LOOK, I KNOW YOU'RE UPSET -
I AM, TOO -
BUT I DON'T THINK GOING
TO THE POLICE IS THE ANSWER.
SO SHE GETS OFF,
SCOTT-FREE?
MAYA, I ASSURE YOU,
I WILL DEAL WITH THIS.
(ANNOYED SIGH)
MR. SIMPSON:
THANK YOU, EVERYONE.
HOPEFULLY, WE CAN PUT THIS
ALL BEHIND US.
♪♪♪
(SIGHS)
VENI, VIDI, VICI!
I CAME, I SAW,
I CONQUERED!
MM-HMM.
WHERE'S DALLAS?
UH, HE IS...
AH!
STOMACH FLU ALL CLEARED UP?
YES, SIR,
I FEEL GREAT!
GEOGRAPHY IS
MY FAVOURITE SUBJECT.
(LAUGHS)
I TOLD YOU, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO WORRY ABOUT ME!
MIKE DALLAS IS ALIVE
AND WELL!
I CAN'T WAIT
TO SEE THIS.
HAVE YOU BEEN DRINKING?!
NO! (LAUGHS)
OKAY, MAYBE ONE...
CASE.
DREW:
OKAY, NO PROBLEM.
WE CAN DO THIS,
JUST...
PUT THIS ON!
OH MAN,
ARE WE GONNA BE GHOSTS?
OH, THIS'LL BE SPOOKY!
OKAY, NEW PLAN.
YOU BE CAESAR
AND I'LL BE BRUTUS.
HEY, DREW,
YOU WERE RIGHT, MAN,
I'M A FAILURE.
SHHH!
I ADMIT IT,
I. AM. A FAILURE.
SHH! DALLAS, OKAY,
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
JUST PRETEND TO BE
DEAD FOR ME.
ALAS!
CAESAR AND BRUTUS!
HERE GOES NOTHING.
THE RISE OF THE ROMAN EMPIRE
CAME AFTER THE DEATH
OF JULIUS CAESAR,
WHO WAS BETRAYED
BY HIS FRIEND, BRUTUS.
UNGH!
WHY, BRUTUS, WHY?
(STUDENTS CHUCKLE)
BRUTUS THOUGHT IT WAS HIS DUTY
TO KILL HIS FRIEND
TO SAVE THE PEOPLE OF ROME.
DALLAS:
WHOA!
DESPITE HOW MUCH BRUTUS
HAD COME TO LOVE CAESAR...
CAESAR'S GHOST CAME BACK
TO SAY THAT HE-
THAT HE FORGAVE BRUTUS!
(RETCHING)
(VOMITING NOISILY)
LOOK AT THAT.
CAESAR HAD THE STOMACH FLU
AFTER ALL.
(LAUGHS)
I'M GUESSING THE MEETING
DIDN'T GO WELL?
MY MOM DOESN'T WANT
TO PRESS CRIMINAL CHARGES
BECAUSE ZOE SAID
SHE WAS SORRY.
(MILES PLAYS BLUES RIFF)
I WANT ZOE DEAD!
♪♪♪
♪ SO DEAD ♪
(PLAYS BLUES REFRAIN)
♪ REALLY DEAD ♪
I CAN'T STAND
ALL THESE RUMOURS
AND FAKE PICS OF ME
IN MY BLOOMERS.
(LAUGHS)
THERE YOU GO!
(MILES PLAYS BLUES REFRAIN)
I'VE GOT A FAN PAGE
THAT'S PHOTOSHOPPED
AND SIMPSON SAYS
IT CAN'T BE STOPPED.
♪♪♪
♪ YOU WANT HER DEAD ♪
♪ REALLY, REALLY DEAD ♪
♪ I'VE GOT THE LYING, ♪
♪ SNEAKY BITCH-IS-GONNA-
ROT-IN-HELL ♪
♪ BACKSTABBING FRIEND BLUES ♪
♪♪♪
YEAH!
(BOTH LAUGH)
MILES:
SEE? DON'T YOU FEEL BETTER?
I'D FEEL BETTER
IF EVERYONE KNEW
HOW EVIL ZOE WAS.
MAYBE YOU NEED TO FIND
A WAY TO...
ENLIGHTEN THEM.
♪♪♪
DREW:
HEY, DALLAS,
WAIT UP, MAN!
CONSIDERING THE CIRCUMSTANCES,
I THINK THAT WENT PRETTY WELL,
DON'T YOU?
DOESN'T MATTER.
THAT GHOST THING
WAS GENIUS.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
I'M MOVING BACK
TO GUELPH.
WHAT? WHY?
NO, YOU CAN'T, MAN!
YOU THINK I WANT TO,
GO BACK HOME
A BIG LOSER?
LOOK, LOSING HOCKEY SUCKS,
I GET IT-
I'VE DREAMT ABOUT
GETTING INTO THE NHL
MY ENTIRE LIFE.
WHO AM I WITHOUT HOCKEY?
AFTER MY CONCUSSION,
I THOUGHT THERE WAS
NOTHING FOR ME.
NOW I'M THE PRESIDENT...
AND YOU'RE BETTER
AT WAY MORE STUFF THAN ME.
LIKE WHAT, DRINKING?
MAKING A FOOL
OUT OF MYSELF?
KEEPING ME
OUT OF TROUBLE.
(GROANS)
I HAVE NO REASON
TO STAY.
YEAH, YOU DO.
I ALREADY LOST ONE BROTHER
THIS YEAR,
I CAN'T LOSE ANOTHER.
♪♪♪
♪ I will always have open eyes ♪
♪ You've come alive ♪
♪ I will hold you away ♪
OR DO PEOPLE CHANGE?
♪ My dear ♪
(SIGHS)
MS. OH:
WE HAVE TIME FOR ONE MORE
SONGWRITING ASSIGNMENT TODAY.
UM, ACTUALLY,
I WROTE ANOTHER NEW SONG.
OKAY, GIVE IT UP
FOR THE PROLIFIC MAYA MATLIN!
MILES:
WAIT, ARE YOU SURE YOU WANNA
GO THROUGH WITH THIS?
I WASN'T BEING
ENTIRELY SERIOUS.
I WAS.
OKAY, THIS SONG
IS ABOUT KARMA...
AND, SPOILER ALERT,
IT SUCKS.
(STRUMMING CHORDS)
♪ YOU WERE A SUPERSTAR ♪
♪ NOW YOU'RE A HAS-BEEN ♪
♪ THOUGHT WE WERE FRIENDS
BUT YOU WERE JUST ACTING ♪
♪ ONE DAY I'LL WATCH YOU DIE ♪
♪ MAYBE IN YOUR SLEEP ♪
♪ PUT YOU SIX FEET UNDER
SO YOU DON'T MAKE A PEEP! ♪
MS. OH:
MAYA!
♪ WATCH YOUR BACK ♪
♪ YOU'RE DEAD WITH A CAPITAL
D-EEE EEE-EEE-EEE ♪
MS. MATLIN!
♪ THE WORLD WILL BE A MUCH
BETTER PLACE WITHOUT YOU ♪
♪ ZOE-EEE-EEE-EEE-EEE ♪
MS. OH:
THAT'S ENOUGH!
MAYA:
LET ME GUESS,
GO TO THE OFFICE?
MS. OH:
YES.
♪♪♪
NEED ANY HELP?
IF YOU STILL GOT SPACE
FOR AN EX-HOCKEY PLAYER
WITH NO PROSPECTS.
DEPENDS.
ARE YOU DONE
WITH ALL THE DRINKING?
AFTER THIS AFTERNOON?
YEAH.
WHAT ABOUT THE GIRLS?
I CAN'T HELP IT
IF THE LADIES LOVE ME!
(BOTH LAUGH)
NEXT TIME,
UH...
TRY TO LEARN A GIRL'S NAME
BEFORE YOU BRING HER HOME,
OKAY?
SURE THING, AUDRA.
(DALLAS SIGHS)
SUSPENDED, MAYA,
FOR THREATENING
A GIRL'S LIFE?!
IT WAS A SONG!
YOU REALLY THINK
I'M CAPABLE OF MURDER?
YOU-YOU ARE GROUNDED,
OBVIOUSLY,
WHICH MEANS NO TV
AND NO INTERNET!
YOU DON'T GET IT,
DO YOU?!
I WAS GROPED
BY A RANDOM JERK TODAY
AND PEOPLE LOOK AT ME
LIKE I HAVE A DISEASE,
AND ZOE GETS TO GO
AROUND LAUGHING
AND FLIPPING HER HAIR,
LIKE OMG!
YOU CAN'T LET THEM
HURT YOU,
YOU HAVE TO TURN
THE OTHER CHEEK!
MOM, DO YOU REALIZE
HOW HARD THAT IS
WHEN THEY'RE AT SCHOOL
AND ONLINE?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SINK
TO THEIR LEVEL.
YOU ARE BETTER THAN THAT.
ARE WE DONE?
NO!
LOOK, IF YOU WANNA PRESS
CRIMINAL CHARGES AGAINST ZOE,
WE CAN.
SERIOUSLY?
IT'S GONNA BE LONG
AND IT'S GONNA BE DIFFICULT,
BUT I WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT I AM ON YOUR SIDE.
I'LL THINK ABOUT IT.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
ALLI:
AHEM!
HEY, LEO,
CAN WE TALK?
ALLI.
I CAN'T TELL YOU
HOW HAPPY I AM TO SEE YOU.
YOU AND I HAVE
SOMETHING SPECIAL.
ABSOLUMENT.
(SHAKY SIGH)
BUT IF WE'RE GOING
TO BE TOGETHER,
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO GET THERAPY.
I CAN DO THAT.
AND I STILL WANT
TO GO TO M.I.T.
M.I.T. IS YOUR DREAM.
I DON'T WANT TO STAND
IN YOUR WAY.
AND PROMISE ME, LEO,
IF YOU EVER GET UPSET,
THAT YOU'LL TALK TO ME.
BECAUSE IF YOU EVER
HIT ME AGAIN,
I'M GONE.
NO MORE CHANCES.
NEVER AGAIN.
YOU HAVE MY WORD.
YOU CAN'T LET ME DOWN,
LEO.
NOT AGAIN.
NO.
(CELLO MUSIC PLAYS)
♪♪♪
(KNOCKING)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I JUST WANTED
TO APOLOGIZE.
I FEEL LIKE I PUSHED YOU
TO DO THAT SONG.
ZOE RUINED MY LIFE,
SHE DESERVES IT.
SHE'S JUST JEALOUS
BECAUSE YOU ARE TALENTED,
AND FUNNY,
AND AWESOME IN WAYS
SHE'LL NEVER BE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SAY THINGS
TO MAKE ME FEEL BETTER.
I'M NOT,
TRUST ME.
(BOTH LAUGH)
SCHOOL'S GONNA SUCK
WITHOUT YOU.
MRS. MATLIN:
MAYA, I TOLD YOU NO TV!
SHE'S COMING, GO!
WAIT, NO!
(LAUGHS)
I-I SWEAR I HEARD THE TV.
OH, WELL, MAYBE YOU SHOULD
GET YOUR HEARING CHECKED.
YOU KNOW,
YOU ARE GETTING OLD.
VERY FUNNY.
SO HAVE YOU THOUGHT ANY MORE
ABOUT PRESSING CHARGES?
(SIGHS) WELL...
JUST BECAUSE ZOE'S EVIL
DOESN'T MEAN I HAVE TO BE.
I WANNA MOVE ON,
AND I HAVE THINGS
TO LOOK FORWARD TO.
I'M GLAD TO HEAR IT.
(LAUGHS)