IMOGEN:
ALL RIGHT, TRISTAN,
TELL US WHY YOU'RE AUDITIONING
TO M.C. THE FIRST ANNUAL
STUDENT COUNCIL
FUNDRAISER FASHION SHOW?
TRISTAN:
HAVE YOU MET ME?
I WAS INSPIRED BY THE THEME -
OLD HOLLYWOOD GLAMOUR.
NOW JUST PICTURE THIS
AS YOUR OPENING NUMBER!
(TRISTAN TURNS ON
A SLOW TEMPO SHOW TUNE)
♪ They say Hollywood
is where you find ♪
♪ The drama
and the glamour ♪
♪ But they've clearly
never been here ♪
♪ To our precious alma mater! ♪
(TEMPO PICKS UP)
♪ From torrid love affairs ♪
♪ Disgusting overshares ♪
♪ Degrassi, you make drama
look so good! ♪
♪ From trying to mack
on a crush ♪
♪ Eat cafeteria mush ♪
♪ Degrassi, you make drama
look so good! ♪
♪ But tonight's the night
to ooh and ahhh ♪
♪ At sexy bods
and chiseled jaws ♪
♪ Degrassi you make drama
look so good! ♪
♪ So sit right down ♪
♪ Enjoy the show ♪
♪ Designs by
the genius Moreno ♪
♪ Degrassi you make drama ♪
♪ Look so good! ♪
♪ So good! ♪
(STUDENTS APPLAUD
AND CHEER)
YATES:
BRAVO!
BECKY:
THAT WAS AMAZING, TRISTAN.
IMOGEN:
TECHNICALLY, I'M JUST DESIGNING
THE FORMAL WEAR.
THE REST IS COMING
FROM THE MALL.
YATES:
YOU TWO HAVE AN IMMENSE TALENT
BEFORE YOU.
TRISTAN:
UH, MR. YATES.
UH, THANKS.
NO NEED TO THANK ME,
THAT WAS SERIOUSLY IMPRESSIVE.
WELL, HOPEFULLY A GOOD WORD
FROM A COOL TEACHER
HELPS MY CHANCES.
NO PROBLEM, TRISTAN.
ANYTIME.
OOH!
SOMEONE'S TEACHER'S PET!
NO! HE'S JUST...
SUPER SUPPORTIVE.
DON'T FIGHT IT.
WE ALL JUST SAW
THAT TUSH.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ (The best that I can be) ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
ZOE:
HOW'S MY HAIR WIND?
KEISHA:
ALMOST AS GOOD
AS MY SMIZING!
FRANKIE:
WE'VE GOT THESE MODEL AUDITIONS
LOCKED DOWN!
WINSTON:
FRANKIE?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I'M AUDITIONING
TO BE A MODEL.
SERIOUSLY? I DIDN'T THINK
THAT WAS YOUR THING.
IMOGEN:
CHEWY! ARE YOU GETTING
ANY OF THIS FOR DTV?
YOU'RE MISSING
ALL THE GOOD STUFF!
OH. GOTTA GO.
UH... GOOD LUCK!
WHAT DO YOU THINK HE MEANT
WHEN HE SAID
HE "DIDN'T THINK
IT WAS MY THING"?
WHO CARES?
DOES HE NOT THINK
I'M PRETTY ENOUGH?
NO! YOU ARE NOT LETTING
SOME STUPID BOY
RUIN THIS FOR YOU!
BECKY:
OKAY! WHO'S UP NEXT?
ZOE:
RIGHT HERE!
FRANKIE HOLLINGSWORTH!
♪ Say yeah! ♪
BECKY:
OH, OKAY.
AH, SHOW US WHAT YOU GOT!
♪ If you're down with me ♪
♪ (Yeah, yeah, yeah) ♪
♪ Say yeah! ♪
(Yeah!)
♪ 'Cause my jam is gonna
set you free ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Mr. DJ ♪
♪ Get loose! ♪
BECKY:
THAT WAS AWESOME!
YOU LOOKED FIERCE
UP THERE!
FRANKIE:
REALLY?!
ABSOLUTELY.
WINSTON CHU,
EAT YOUR HEART OUT!
(TRISTAN'S PHONE CHIMES)
TRISTAN:
BECKY JUST TEXTED ME!
YOU ARE NOW LOOKING AT THE M.C.
FOR THE FASHION SHOW!
AND THE CROWD GOES WILD!
(FEIGNED CHEERS)
WHOA! YEAH! TRISTAN!
DOES THAT MEAN
YOU CAN MAKE SURE
SHE CHOOSES ME
TO BE A MODEL?
WELL, BUY ME LUNCH FIRST
AND I'LL SEE WHAT I CAN DO.
YATES:
CONGRATULATIONS, TRISTAN.
YOU DESERVE IT.
TRISTAN:
THANKS, MR. YATES.
AW, MY LITTLE TRIS-TRIS.
ALWAYS GOING
FOR THE UNAVAILABLE GUYS.
YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN
HOW SUPPORTIVE HE WAS
AT MY AUDITION.
YES!
BECAUSE HE'S YOUR TEACHER!
OH, WHATEVS.
GATSBY GARCIA HAD A TORRID
AFFAIR WITH MR. LORENZO!
NO. DON'T YOU DARE
QUOTE WEST DRIVE.
WE HAD THIS CONVERSATION.
AND BESIDES,
THAT STORYLINE ENDED
WITH GATSBY
GETTING GONORRHEA.
BECKY:
UGH! WE STILL HAVE SO MUCH
TO DO!
SELECT THE MODELS,
FIND A CHOREOGRAPHER,
FINISH DESIGNS...
IMOGEN:
MM-HMM.
BECKY:
BUT I'M SURE MY SUPER-TALENTED
CO-COORDINATOR
HAS SOME AWESOME FORMAL WEAR
SKETCHES TO SHOW ME?
THESE ARE ALL SKETCHES
OF JACK.
YEAH...
BECKY:
(SIGHS) OH DEAR.
YOU'VE GOT IT BAD.
IMOGEN:
I CAN'T STOP THINKING
ABOUT HER.
I ACCIDENTALLY WROTE HER NAME
INSTEAD OF MINE
ON MY HISTORY TEST
LAST WEEK.
SHE GOT A B-PLUS.
WHY ALL THE PINING?
I THOUGHT THINGS WERE MOVING
ALONG WITH YOU TWO.
WE HAD A TOTALLY ROMANTIC DANCE
AT THE SEMIFORMAL,
AND EVER SINCE THEN,
NOTHING, NADA, ZILCH.
YOU HAVE TO ASK HER OUT.
IMOGEN: MM-MM.
BECKY: MM-HMM.
IMOGEN:
WHAT IF SHE SAYS NO?
IF I NEVER ASK HER OUT,
I COULD ALWAYS PRETEND
SHE SAID YES.
BECKY:
LIVING IN FEAR
IS NOT LIVING AT ALL!
NOW, COME ON, MORENO,
GROW SOME OVARIES!
HEY, GUYS!
HI, JACK.
AH, IMOGEN JUST HAS SOMETHING
SHE'D LIKE TO ASK YOU.
WILL YOU GO OUT WITH ME
TONIGHT?
OH, BUMMER.
I CAN'T, I'VE GOT A THING.
IMOGEN:
W-WELL MAYBE I CAN COME
WITH YOU?
I JUST INVITED MYSELF.
HOW RUDE.
I'M GONNA GO.
(LAUGHS) NO, NO.
WAIT UP, WEIRDO!
I WAS JUST ABOUT TO ASK YOU
IF YOU WANTED TO COME.
YEAH?
TEXT YOU THE DETAILS.
SEE?!
LIFE REWARDS THE BRAVE!
(BELL RINGS)
COME ON, TRIS!
I OWE YOU LUNCH!
YEAH,
I'LL BE THERE IN A SEC.
I JUST NEED TO ASK
MR. YATES A QUESTION...
ABOUT THE SYMBOLISM
OF THE MOCKINGBIRD.
MAYA:
YOU'RE NOT NEARLY AS GOOD
AN ACTOR AS YOU THINK YOU ARE.
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU?
I JUST WANTED TO ASK YOU
SOMETHING...
IF THAT'S OKAY?
OF COURSE,
THAT'S WHAT I'M HERE.
WELL, UM,
SINCE I GOT THE M.C. GIG,
I HAVE TO WRITE ALL THIS STUFF
TO SAY IN BETWEEN THE NUMBERS.
(HALF LAUGHS)
IT'S CALLED BANTER.
UH, WELL,
I WAS JUST WONDERING
IF MAYBE YOU COULD HELP ME
WRITE IT?
I WANT TO MAKE SURE
IT'S LIKE...
NEXT-LEVEL SOPHISTICATED
AND WITTY,
UM... LIKE YOU.
OF COURSE.
I'D BE HAPPY TO.
OH, BUT IF YOU WANT
TO DO IT TODAY
IT'LL HAVE TO BE
AT MY PLACE.
YOUR PLACE?!
I NEED TO BE THERE
FOR A DELIVERY
RIGHT AFTER SCHOOL.
NO SENSE COMING BACK.
IS THAT ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, YEAH, THAT'S PERFECT.
THAT'S REALLY GOOD.
YATES:
HERE'S THE ADDRESS.
THANKS.
UH, TRISTAN?
UM, DON'T MENTION IT
TO ANYONE, OKAY?
I JUST DON'T WANT THE OTHER
STUDENTS GETTING JEALOUS.
OH. IT'LL BE
OUR LITTLE SECRET!
OKAY.
FRANKIE:
I CAN'T LOOK!
KEISHA:
ME NEITHER!
ZOE:
GET IT TOGETHER,
YOU TWO!
YES!
I MADE IT!
NO!
YOU MADE IT.
YOU DIDN'T.
ZOE:
WELL, THIS IS AWKWARD.
MAYBE WINSTON
WAS RIGHT.
MAYBE THIS
ISN'T MY THING.
DON'T BE TOO HARD
ON YOURSELF.
FRANKIE:
BUT WHY?
AM I TOO UGLY?
TOO SKINNY?
IS IT MY WEIRD NOSE?
DON'T LET IT GET
TO YOU.
IF I FALL APART EVERY TIME
I DIDN'T GET A ROLE,
WELL...
I'D BE IN PIECES.
♪ ...the moon
hitting the blacktop ♪
♪ Just like a fuse ♪
♪ Making the night so hot ♪
♪ Forget the truth
until tomorrow ♪
♪ You'll be my Hughes ♪
♪ I'll be your Harlow ♪
♪ You're the yellow stars
up in my silver sky ♪
♪ You are a ray, ray... ♪
IMOGEN:
YOU GOT THIS, MORENO.
♪ All of the lights went down
when you came with me ♪
♪ Now there's
a million diamonds ♪
♪ That I just can't see ♪
♪ You... ♪
♪ Make my blue eyes blind ♪
HEY, UM,
DO YOU KNOW WHERE JACK IS?
THAT'S HER RIGHT THERE.
IMOGEN:
IT IS?!
LUCY:
CUTE? ALWAYS ROCKIN'
RED LIPSTICK AND KILLER HAIR?
YEAH, THAT'S JACK.
YOU WANT?
UH, NO THANKS.
I'M GOOD.
♪ Caught in the afterglow ♪
♪ The world is brave ♪
LUCY:
YOU GO TO DEGRASSI WITH HER?
IMOGEN:
YEAH.
ARE ALL THE GIRLS
IN LOVE WITH HER THERE, TOO?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHY?
JUST WONDERING WHAT HER DATING
SITUATION IS LIKE AT SCHOOL.
I MEAN, LOOK AT HER.
WHO WOULDN'T WANNA GO OUT
ON A DATE WITH HER?
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(KNOCKING)
TRISTAN,
GREAT TO SEE YOU.
AH, I BROUGHT SOME
HORS D'OEUVRES OR WHATEVER.
COME IN. THAT'S GREAT,
THANK YOU.
I GOT ADDICTED TO HUMMUS
WHEN I WAS IN JORDAN.
TRISTAN:
(NERVOUSLY) OH.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU SEEM A BIT NERVOUS.
NO, I'M AWESOME.
I'VE JUST...
I'VE NEVER BEEN IN
A TEACHER'S APARTMENT BEFORE.
OH.
WELL, IF IT HELPS,
THEN DON'T THINK OF ME
AS A TEACHER.
THEN HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO THINK OF YOU?
A CREATIVE COLLABORATOR.
SIT DOWN.
RELAX.
I'LL GRAB US SOMETHING
TO DRINK.
(DISHES CLANK)
I THINK YOU'LL LIKE THIS.
IF NOT THE TASTE,
THEN AT LEAST THE ROMANCE
OF THE RITUAL.
IS THAT ABSINTHE?
LIKE IN BAZ LUHRMANN'S
MASTERPIECE,
MOULIN ROUGE?
EXACTLY.
ALTHOUGH, I'M MORE OF
A ROMEO AND JULIET MAN MYSELF.
(ABSINTHE SLOSHES,
LID CLATTERS)
HERE'S TO YOU,
TRISTAN.
(GLASSES CLINK)
(COUGHS THREE TIMES)
(MODERN JAZZ MUSIC PLAYS
IN STUDIO)
JACK:
IMOGEN!
I'M SO GLAD YOU CAME!
IMOGEN:
ME TOO!
GLAD I CAME,
NOT GLAD YOU CAME.
THAT WOULDN'T MAKE SENSE.
THIS IS YOUR THING.
OF COURSE YOU CAME.
JACK:
AND I SEE YOU'VE MET LUCY.
SHE DANCES HERE TOO,
BUT SHE'S WAY BETTER THAN ME.
YOU'RE ALWAYS LYING.
WHAT'S WITH THAT?
ARE YOU PATHOLOGICAL?
(LAUGHS)
IMOGEN:
LUCY ACTUALLY HAD
TO POINT YOU OUT TO ME.
I DIDN'T EVEN
RECOGNIZE YOU.
AND WHAT'D YOU THINK?
YOU WERE INCREDIBLE.
THANKS, GIRL.
I'LL GET YOU BACK
NEXT TIME, OKAY?
NO.
SHE DOESN'T SMOKE.
I NEVER SAID THAT!
HEY, NO PRESSURE.
NO, NO, NO,
I WANT TO.
OKAY.
WELL, THEN,
OPEN YOUR MOUTH.
(HOARSE COUGH)
OW!
(LAUGHS)
TRISTAN:
I WHIP AROUND AND SAY
"FRANKLY, MY DEAR,
I DON'T GIVE A DAMN."
I DIDN'T THINK ANYONE YOUR AGE
HAD SEEN "GONE WITH THE WIND."
WELL, I'M NOT LIKE
MOST PEOPLE MY AGE.
NO, YOU'RE CERTAINLY NOT.
YOU'RE GONNA BE
A GREAT M.C.
I DON'T EVEN THINK
YOU NEEDED MY HELP.
I'M SO SORRY.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I WAS THINKING.
DON'T APOLOGIZE.
NOT FOR THAT.
(LIPS SMACK)
(TRISTAN'S BREATH QUICKENS,
BELT BUCKLES CLANK)
(STAMMERS, NERVOUS)
I'M... I'M SORRY.
YATES:
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
TRISTAN:
UH, I... I HAVE TO GO.
(DOOR CLICKS SHUT)
(DOOR SQUEAKS OPEN)
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH:
SNACK BREAK
FOR MY LITTLE SCHOLAR!
FRANKIE:
CAN I HAVE A BOOB JOB
FOR MY BIRTHDAY?
(CLICKS TONGUE)
HMM...
OR A NOSE JOB?
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH:
MM-HM.
OR MAYBE, I DON'T KNOW,
A BUTT IMPLANT?
MMM...
FIRST OFF,
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
SECOND, WHERE'S ALL THIS
COMING FROM?!
I DIDN'T GET A MODELING SPOT
IN THE FASHION SHOW.
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH:
(SYMPATHETIC MOAN)
WHICH MEANS I'M UGLY
I GUESS.
(LAUGHS)
YOU ARE NOT UGLY!
YOU'RE MY BEAUTIFUL GIRL!
THEN WHY
DIDN'T THEY PICK ME?
THOSE THINGS AREN'T ABOUT
THE WAY YOU LOOK,
THEY'RE ABOUT POLITICS.
I WAS TOTALLY GOOD!
JUST AS GOOD AS KEISHA
AND ZOE, ANYWAY!
WHY DON'T YOU TRY TALKING
TO THE GIRLS
WHO ARE ORGANIZING IT?
YOU HAVE BEEN TO THE FASHION
CAPITALS OF EUROPE!
YOU HAVE SAT FRONT ROW
AT NEW YORK FASHION WEEK!
SHOW THEM
WHAT THEY'RE MISSING OUT ON!
ARE YOU SURE
I CAN'T JUST GET A BOOB JOB?
UNH-UNH.
♪ Hey Sugar! ♪
♪ Are you coming with me?
Zip bop ba doo ♪
♪ Hey Sugar! ♪
(KNOCKING)
HELLO?
HELLO?!
ZIG: HEY! WHAT'S UP?
TRISTAN: UH, WHERE'S MAYA?
UH, SHE'S OUT WITH HER MOM.
TRISTAN:
(SIGHS) OF COURSE SHE IS!
THEY SHOULD BE BACK SOON.
WANNA WAIT?
UH... YEAH, I GUESS.
YOU SEEM UPSET.
YOU WANNA TALK OR SOMETHING?
UH, NOT WITH YOU.
OKAY.
JUST THOUGHT I'D ASK.
(BLENDER WHIRS)
(YELLING) WHAT DO YOU DO
IF A GIRL WANTS TO, YOU KNOW,
"GO DOWNSTAIRS"
ON A FIRST DATE?
WHAT-WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
LIKE TO THE BASEMENT?
YEAH...
IN A MANNER OF SPEAKING.
OH! OH, UH...
UM, WELL, UH...
I GUESS
I'D MAKE HER DINNER.
BUT LIKE,
IT'S NOT TOO FORWARD?
NO. IF ANYTHING,
IT'S TOO AWESOME.
(CHUCKLES)
SOMEHOW, I THINK
I NEED A SECOND OPINION.
MUST BE A REASON GIRLS
READ THESE THINGS, RIGHT?
SERIOUSLY?
YEAH.
OH, LOOK AT THIS!
"QUIZ OF THE MONTH."
"ARE YOU READY TO TAKE
YOUR RELATIONSHIP
TO THE NEXT LEVEL?"
(SUCKS TEETH)
FINE.
ALL RIGHT.
FIRST QUESTION.
"DOES YOUR BOYFRIEND MAKE
YOU FEEL...
A) SELF-CONSCIOUS, B) BORED,
OR C) CONFIDENT?
C.
QUESTION NUMBER TWO.
"WOULD YOU DESCRIBE
THE COMMUNICATION BETWEEN YOU
AND YOUR BOYFRIEND
AS A) NON-EXISTENT,
B) LIMITED TO CONVERSATIONS
ABOUT PIZZA TOPPINGS,
OR C) OPEN AND HONEST?"
(HALF LAUGHS)
C.
AND FINALLY,
DO YOU WANNA BE THE IDIOT
WHO TURNS DOWN
A BASEMENT RENDEZVOUS?
A) NO,
B) DEFINITELY NOT,
AND C) ARE YOU FREAKING
KIDDING ME?!
HAR-HAR.
"IF YOU ANSWERED MOSTLY C'S...
CONGRATS!
SOUNDS LIKE YOU'RE READY
TO GET STEAMY WITH YOUR SWEETIE!
JUST REMEMBER TO STAY SAFE
WHEN YOU'RE GETTING SEXY."
IN CONCLUSION,
I THINK YOU'RE READY.
TRISTAN:
(LAUGHS)
THIS ISN'T YOUR FIRST TIME
BEING HIGH, IS IT?
NO WAY, I TOKE THE REEFER
ON THE DAILY!
(JACK LAUGHS)
LUCY:
WE'RE GONNA GRAB SOME FOOD.
YOU GUYS COMING?
I WAS WONDERING
IF WE COULD HANG OUT HERE
A BIT MORE
AND YOU CAN SHOW ME
SOME MOVES?
YEAH.
I'D LOVE THAT.
I'LL CATCH UP WITH YOU GUYS
LATER, OKAY?
(SLOW JAZZ TUNE PLAYS)
♪ I got the message, baby ♪
I HAD NO IDEA
YOU WERE SUCH AN AMAZING DANCER.
I'VE ALWAYS LOVED DANCING.
I MEAN...
BUT A COUPLE YEARS AGO
I WATCHED THIS DOCUMENTARY
ON MARTHA GRAHAM.
WHO?
SHE WAS A CHOREOGRAPHER.
SHE MADE ME FALL IN LOVE
WITH DANCE
AS A FORM OF COMMUNICATION.
OH.
WELL, WHAT DOES THIS MEAN?
(LAUGHS)
I'M NOT REALLY SURE.
I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW YOU DO THOSE AMAZING THINGS
WITH YOUR BODY.
JACK:
JUST TAKES A GOOD TEACHER.
♪ When I was a kid
I wanted fortune ♪
♪ And fame ♪
♪ But all of that's changed ♪
♪ Since I've been a man ♪
♪ Love walked in my door ♪
IMOGEN:
UGH! SORRY!
IMOGEN AND JACK:
(LAUGH)
♪ Messed up my mind ♪
♪ And nothing
would ever change ♪
♪ This love of mine ♪
JACK, I JUST...
REALLY WANT SOME NACHOS.
JACK AND IMOGEN:
(LAUGH)
IMOGEN:
I DON'T KNOW WHY!
♪ Now that you know... ♪
FRANKIE:
HELLO, BECKY.
I'D LIKE TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT YOUR DECISION
NOT TO CHOOSE ME AS A MODEL.
BECKY:
UH, YEAH, OF COURSE.
FRANKIE:
WELL, I THINK YOU SHOULD
GIVE ME A CHANCE.
ONE, CLOTHES LOOK
REALLY GOOD ON ME,
AS I HAVE BEEN TOLD
BY MY MOM;
TWO, I'VE BEEN TO NEW YORK
FASHION WEEK
AND TOTALLY PAID ATTENTION,
AND THREE,
I'M VERY PUNCTUAL.
BECKY:
OKAY, GREAT.
YOU'RE IN!
FRANKIE:
I AM?! THAT WAS EASY.
I'D ALREADY DECIDED
TO GIVE YOU A SECOND CHANCE.
WE MADE A MISTAKE
NOT CHOOSING YOU
THE FIRST TIME AROUND.
OKAY,
SO JUST MAKE ME PROUD!
(EXCITED GIGGLE)
♪ Get loose! ♪
♪ Everybody on the floor ♪
YATES:
LAST CHANCE TO TURN IN
YOUR ESSAYS.
DID YOU NEED SOMETHING?
I'M SO, SO SORRY
ABOUT LAST NIGHT.
IT'S FINE.
THANK YOU.
NO. NO, IT'S NOT.
I'M SO EMBARASSED.
PLEASE KEEP
YOUR VOICE DOWN.
I HAD A GREAT TIME
LAST NIGHT,
I JUST WASN'T EXPECTING THINGS
TO HAPPEN-
I THOUGHT YOU WERE MATURE,
TRISTAN.
OBVIOUSLY I WAS WRONG.
WHAT HAPPENED NEEDS
TO STAY BETWEEN US.
YOU UNDERSTAND THAT,
RIGHT?
YES, OF COURSE.
YOU LEFT YOUR M.C. NOTES
AT MY PLACE.
I TOOK THE LIBERTY OF WRITING
A FEW THINGS DOWN FOR YOU.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE
TO DO THAT.
I KNOW.
(RECEDING FOOTSTEPS)
IMOGEN:
SORRY, SORRY, SORRY!
I SLEPT IN!
BECKY:
IT'S 4:30 IN THE AFTERNOON.
YEAH, I MAY HAVE SLEPT THROUGH
ALL MY CLASSES.
WHAT'S WRONG?
ARE YOU SICK?
IT'S NOT A FEVER.
IMOGEN:
NO, I'M JUST A LITTLE TIRED
FROM...
MY DATE WITH JACK
LAST NIGHT.
SO DID YOU HAVE A GOOD TIME?
IMOGEN:
WE SMOKED A JOINT
AND WE DANCED AND WE KISSED!
IMOGEN!
HUGS NOT DRUGS!
THAT'S WHY
YOU'RE SUCH A MESS!
DID YOU AT LEAST FINISH
YOUR FORMAL WEAR SKETCHES?
NO.
I WAS GONNA GET UP AND DO IT
THIS MORNING AND THEN I-
YOU GOT TOO HIGH
ON ILLEGAL DRUGS
WITH YOUR GIRLFRIEND
AND SLEPT IN.
I'M SORRY, BECKY.
(KNOCKING)
TRISTAN:
(APPREHENSIVE GASP)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I WANTED TO THANK YOU
FOR THE M.C. STUFF YOU WROTE.
IT WAS PERFECT.
MY PLEASURE.
HAVE A GOOD NIGHT.
I KNOW I FREAKED OUT
BEFORE,
BUT IT WAS ONLY
BECAUSE I WAS SURPRISED.
I KNOW YOU THINK
I'M IMMATURE,
BUT I'M NOT.
I'M MATURE.
I'M READY.
SO...
♪ It's easier to hide ♪
GET IN HERE.