(MAYA LAUGHS)
MAYA:
MILES, PUT ME DOWN!
MILES
WHAT IF I DON'T WANT
TO PUT YOU DOWN?
WHAT IF I WANT TO CARRY
YOU AROUND ALL DAY?
(MAYA GIGGLES)
WELL, THEN I CAN'T PRINT OFF
MY RUBBER ROOM ESSAY.
I'LL BE STUCK
WITH THOSE FREAKS FOREVER.
IT'S BAD ENOUGH
YOU HAVE TO SPEND
FIRST AND LAST PERIOD
THERE.
WELL, THE BETTER I DO
ON THIS ESSAY,
THE BETTER MY CHANCES
OF GETTING OUT.
THEN WE CAN SPEND
ALL OUR TIME TOGETHER.
I LIKE THE SOUND
OF THAT.
AHEM!
DO I REALLY HAVE TO WATCH
YOU TWO LOVEBIRDS SUCK FACE?
I SHOULD GO PRINT OFF
MY ESSAY.
WHAT'S IT ABOUT,
ANYWAY?
"TRUST BUILDING TECHNIQUES."
NO!
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
WHAT'S WRONG?
MY LAPTOP IS MISSING!
WELL, MAYBE YOU
FORGOT IT AT HOME?
NO, I WOULD NEVER!
I LEFT MY BAG
IN THE RUBBER ROOM
FOR LIKE TWO SECONDS
TO USE THE WASHROOM.
TRISTAN:
WELL, THOSE KIDS ARE BAD NEWS.
ESPECIALLY THAT SKETCHBAG
EX OF YOURS!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
TO BEG MS. GRELL
FOR AN EXTENSION,
AND TO GET TO THE BOTTOM
OF THIS!
NOBODY STEALS
FROM MAYA MATLIN!
WELL, EXCEPT ZIG NOVAK,
APPARENTLY.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ (The best that I can be) ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
WHAT'S THAT?
WAIT, WE DON'T HAVE A LAB
DUE TODAY, DO WE?
(JENNA SIGHS)
AHEM!
"WHY SHOULD YOU BE
KING AND QUEEN
OF THE SWEETHEART
SEMIFORMAL?"
YOU'RE NOMINATING
YOU AND CONNOR?
IT'S NOT THAT FAR-FETCHED!
CLARE AND ELI WON AT PROM
LAST YEAR!
YEAH,
BECAUSE ELI FIXED IT.
CLARE:
THE IDIOTS WHO VOTE FOR THIS,
THEY JUST CARE ABOUT IMAGE.
ALLI:
YEAH, I MEAN LOOK
AT THIS QUESTION.
IF YOU AND YOUR PARTNER STARRED
IN YOUR OWN ROMANTIC COMEDY,
WHAT WOULD IT BE CALLED?
"TALK NERDY TO ME!"
CONNOR IS HIS OWN PERSON.
IT'S... SEXY.
ALLI:
BUT WILL THE STUDENT BODY AGREE?
MS. GRELL:
"REHAB,"
UH, "WITNESS PROTECTION,"
"MY DAD'S A DEPOSED DICTATOR."
THIS ISN'T AN EXCUSE,
MS. GRELL,
MY LAPTOP REALLY WAS STOLEN!
I'M SORRY, MAYA,
THERE ARE NO EXTENSIONS
AND NO EXCEPTIONS.
MAYA:
(SIGHS)
ZIG:
PRINCESS MATLIN DIDN'T DO
HER HOMEWORK?
MY LAPTOP WAS TAKEN!
13-INCH MACBOOK?
STICKY "Y" KEY?
THAT'S THE ONE,
HAVE YOU SEEN IT?
NO.
MS. GRELL:
ZIG, DO YOU HAVE
YOUR ASSIGNMENT?
BAD PLAN, BLONDIE,
ZIG WON'T LIKE THAT.
HE BASICALLY ADMITTED
TO TAKING MY LAPTOP.
ZIG:
BUT I WOULDN'T BE STUPID ENOUGH
TO LEAVE IT IN MY BAG.
(BELL RINGS)
BECKY:
WHAT DO YOU WEAR
TO A SEMIFORMAL?
HALF A BALL GOWN?
WE'LL FIND YOU SOMETHING
PERFECTLY PASTEL
AT THE MALL TOMORROW.
THANKS FOR BEING
SO GREAT.
IT'S BEEN HARD AT HOME.
WELL, YOU'RE
MY FAVOURITE TURNCOAT.
BECKY:
I'M SO GLAD
WE HAVE EACH OTHER.
WHOA!
LISTEN UP,
WE'VE GOT A NEW STUDENT!
JACQUELINE.
JACK:
UH, THE NAME'S JACK.
MR. PERINO:
ANYBODY HAVE ROOM FOR JACK
IN THEIR GROUP?
IMOGEN:
UM, WE DO.
WELL, THANK YOU,
MISS MORENO.
OKAY, JACK, YOU'LL WORK
WITH IMOGEN AND BECKY
ON THE WEIMAR REPUBLIC.
JACK:
PROTO-FASCISM
AND HYPER INFLATION!
WHAT'S NOT TO LOVE?
IMOGEN:
I LIKE YOU ALREADY!
MAYBE WE CAN ALL GET TOGETHER
AFTER SCHOOL!
ANYWHERE AROUND HERE
MAKE A SOLID MACCHIATO?
NO.
(JACK AND IMOGEN LAUGH)
YOU'RE FUNNY.
UM, WHAT'S A...
WHAT'S A MACCHIATO?
(BELL RINGS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
♪♪♪
♪ Found this baby bird ♪
♪ Easily I said goodbye ♪
OKAY, TOMORROW.
♪ Taking off the past ♪
♪ Wondering where you are
tonight ♪
♪ I can't breathe
tucked under these sheets ♪
(GASPS)
(LAUGHING)
JUMPY MUCH?
I WAS LOOKING EVERYWHERE
FOR YOU.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I THINK ZIG STOLE
MY LAPTOP.
WANT ME TO PUNCH HIM
IN THE FACE?
I HAVE TO MAKE SURE
I'M RIGHT FIRST.
WHOA! NO, WAIT!
WHAT?
YOU CAN'T FOLLOW HIM
ALONE,
HE'S PROBABLY GOING
SOMEWHERE SKETCHY.
FINE. GUESS YOU'RE COMING
WITH ME THEN!
IMOGEN:
INCORRECT, "KID A" IS TOTALLY
THE SUPERIOR ALBUM!
JACK:
MM, NO.
GO BACK AND LISTEN
TO "HAIL TO THE THIEF."
IT IS SUCH AN EVOLUTION!
BECKY:
WOW! THAT'S HOW I FEEL ABOUT
THE NEW TAYLOR SWIFT.
(LAUGHS)
OH, UH, SORRY!
UM, NO, I HAVEN'T HEARD IT.
BUT I'M SURE IT'S...
UH, VERY POPPY.
IT IS, IT'S GREAT.
SO I HEAR THE GALLERY HERE
IS LIKE BEYOND-
IMOGEN:
YEAH, THEY'VE GOT
THE CRAZIEST AI WEIWEI EXHIBIT.
BECKY:
AI WHAT-WHAT?
JACK:
I SAW SOME OF HIS STUFF
IN BERLIN.
MY EX WORKED
AT A GALLERY THERE.
BECKY:
OOH! A EUROPEAN BF!
DID HE HAVE A SEXY ACCENT?
SHE WAS FROM MICHIGAN.
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
UH, GUYS, IT WAS GREAT
STUDYING WITH YOU,
BUT I GOTTA RUN.
IZAKAYA DATE
WITH MY MOM.
HEY, DO YOU WANT
TO HANG OUT TOMORROW,
UM, MAYBE GO
TO THE GALLERY?
DO CHICKENS HAVE BEAKS?
BECKY:
EXCEPT, UM,
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO GO SHOPPING
FOR THE SEMIFORMAL.
WHY DON'T YOU
JUST COME ALONG?
SURE!
YEAH, THAT SOUNDS GREAT!
SO I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT MAD
I INVITED HER.
NO! NO, NO.
UH, THE MORE THE MERRIER.
THANKS, BECKS.
♪ You never know
what you're gonna find ♪
♪ You'll never know
if you don't ask why ♪
♪ You live and learn
and then you die ♪
THESE JEANS ARE
VERY UNCOMFORTABLE.
TRY THIS PAIR.
WITH ALL THE HOLES?
DISTRESSED DENIM
IS VERY FASHIONABLE.
ALSO VERY ILLOGICAL.
HOW IS THIS HELPING YOU
WITH YOUR ART PROJECT AGAIN?
UM, I'M DOING A STUDY
ON CONTEMPORARY MEN'S FASHION
AND... OTHER STUFF?
YOU LOOKED UP
WHEN YOU SAID THAT.
SO?
YOU LOOK UP
WHEN YOU'RE LYING.
(SIGHS)
I NOMINATED US
FOR KING AND QUEEN
OF THE SWEETHEART SEMIFORMAL.
I WANNA PROVE
WE'RE A GREAT COUPLE!
AND I NEED NEW JEANS
FOR THAT?
WELL, TO GET VOTES,
YOU CAN'T JUST BE
A GREAT COUPLE,
YOU HAVE TO LOOK
LIKE ONE.
THINK OF IT
AS AN EXPERIMENT.
WHAT'S THE RESEARCH QUESTION?
UH... DOES, UM,
CHANGING ONE'S APPEARANCE
INCREASE ONE'S CHANCE
OF WINNING?
AND THE HYPOTHESIS?
YES?
GIMME THE JEANS.
BUT A HYPOTHESIS SHOULD BE
IN THE FORM
OF A COMPLETE SENTENCE.
(LAUGHS)
(CARS RUMBLE)
(MAYA AND MILES GASP)
(MAYA GASPS)
(WINDOW RATTLES)
OH MY GOD!
MILES:
MAYBE HE'S SQUATTING.
MAYA:
SQUATTING?
YEAH, YOU KNOW,
LIVING IN AN ABANDONED HOUSE.
NO, THAT MAKES NO SENSE.
HE LIVES
WITH HIS PARENTS.
(WINDOW SLAMS SHUT)
(SIGHS)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
I THINK I'M JUST GONNA GO HOME,
I HAVE A LOT OF HOMEWORK.
OKAY, I'LL WALK YOU.
NO, IT'S TOTALLY
OUT OF YOUR WAY!
THE SUN'S STILL UP,
MILES.
DON'T WORRY,
I'LL BE FINE.
WELL, OKAY.
UH, CALL ME LATER?
OF COURSE.
(UNSURE CHUCKLE)
(CHILDREN HOLLER
IN THE DISTANCE)
(KNOCKING)
HOW DID YOU FIND
THIS PLACE?!
I FOLLOWED YOU
FROM SCHOOL.
SO WHAT,
NOW YOU'RE STALKING ME?!
I JUST WANTED TO KNOW...
IF YOU TOOK MY LAPTOP
OR NOT.
OH MY-
YOU NEED TO GO!
NO, NOT UNTIL YOU TELL ME
WHY YOU'RE CAMPING OUT
IN SOME ABANDONED HOUSE!
ZIG!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
TRISTAN:
ROSES! GET YOUR ROSES HERE!
MAYA:
IT WAS AWFUL!
AND DON'T FORGET TO VOTE
FOR KING AND QUEEN!
OR KING AND KING,
OR QUEEN AND QUEEN
OF THE SEMIFORMAL!
ZIG'S LIVING THERE
ALL BY HIMSELF.
YOU KNOW,
I TRIED TO TALK TO HIM,
BUT HE SLAMMED THE DOOR
IN MY FACE.
YOU SAID
YOU WERE GOING HOME.
MILES, I HAD TO KNOW
WHAT WAS GOING ON.
WHY?
SOMETHING COULD'VE HAPPENED!
HE COULD'VE HURT YOU!
THIS IS ZIG
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT.
THAT GUY IS BAD NEWS.
YEAH,
AND IT'S MY FAULT!
I BLEW HIM OFF ALL SUMMER
AND NOW HE'S HOMELESS.
TRISTAN:
WAIT, YOU THINK
HE'S SQUATTING
BECAUSE YOU WOULDN'T
GO OUT WITH HIM?
YOU MAY BE OVERESTIMATING
YOUR EFFECT ON GUYS.
MAYA:
I'M JUST SAYING,
WE WERE FRIENDS,
I SHOULD'VE BEEN THERE
FOR HIM.
THIS ISN'T YOUR PROBLEM!
TRISTAN:
YEAH, WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
ADOPT HIM?
MILES:
OR DATE HIM?!
MILES!
WELL, YOU SEEM
TO CARE A WHOLE LOT
ABOUT HIS WELFARE.
YEAH,
BECAUSE I HAVE A HEART!
WHICH, OBVIOUSLY,
YOU THREE ARE LACKING!
YOU KNOW,
I'M GONNA TALK TO MS. GRELL.
I'M SURE SHE'D BE HAPPY
TO HELP.
(SIGHS)
TRISTAN AND ZOE:
ROSES!
(BECKY LAUGHS)
(DREW COUGHS)
PLEASE DON'T TELL CLARE.
I JUST LOVE
THESE CINNAMON HEARTS SO MUCH.
YOU LIVED WITH FIONA,
RIGHT?
YEAH.
WHEN IMOGEN DATED HER,
DID THEY HAVE OTHER FRIENDS
OR DID THEY JUST...
SIT AROUND KISSING ALL DAY?
UH NO, THEY DIDN'T HAVE
A LOT OF OTHER FRIENDS.
AND YES,
THEY KISSED A LOT, WHY?
UH, THERE'S SORT OF THIS
NEW LESBIAN GIRL, JACK.
I THINK IMOGEN
MIGHT LIKE HER.
AND YOU THINK IMOGEN'S
GONNA DITCH YOU
IF THEY START DATING.
WELL, SHE ALREADY INVITED HER
TO COME SHOPPING!
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE I'M CUT OUT COMPLETELY!
WELL, JUST BECAUSE
THEY BOTH LIKE GIRLS
DOESN'T MEAN
THEY'RE GONNA HOOK UP.
NO, BUT THEY HAVE
SO MUCH IN COMMON!
THEY'RE ALL LIKE,
"AI WOO-WAH IS SO GREAT!"
WHAT?
EXACTLY!
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
I MEAN YOU COULD TRY
TALKING TO IMOGEN.
WHAT, AND TELL HER
NOT TO DATE
THAT SUPER COOL CHICK
'CAUSE I'M AFRAID
OF LOSING HER?
NO. NO, 'CAUSE THAT SOUNDS
PRETTY PATHETIC.
MAYBE YOU JUST NEED
A BOY'S NIGHT.
OR A- OR A SIS NIGHT?
TIME TO BOND.
TO LOCKDOWN OUR BFF-SHIP.
MM-HMM.
HMM...
OH NO, WATCH-
WATCH THE CINNAMON HEARTS!
(CLEARS THROAT)
I WON'T TELL
IF YOU DON'T.
(DREW LAUGHS)
MAYA:
THERE WAS A BLANKET,
A LAMP.
THERE WERE SOME
FAST FOOD WRAPPERS,
THAT'S IT.
IT SOUNDS LIKE
HE'S IN A TOUGH PLACE.
HE HAS A MOM AND A DAD,
HOW CAN HE BE HOMELESS?
THERE MIGHT BE TROUBLE
AT HOME.
HE COULD'VE RUN AWAY
OR BEEN KICKED OUT.
HE SHOULD'VE ASKED
FOR HELP!
HE'S PROBABLY EMBARRASSED.
MY FRIENDS TOLD ME
TO MIND MY OWN BUSINESS.
THEY THINK HE'S TROUBLE.
DO YOU?
NO.
LAST YEAR, HE WASN'T.
SO IS THERE SOMETHING
YOU CAN DO?
DON'T WORRY,
I'LL TAKE IT FROM HERE.
(SIGHS) OKAY.
ALLI:
CAN YOU GUYS HURRY UP?!
THIS IS THE GIRLS' BATHROOM
AFTER ALL,
I CAN'T KEEP PEOPLE
OUT OF HERE FOREVER!
JENNA:
WELL, THE MAKEOVER'S
ALMOST COMPLETE.
I JUST NEED TO GET
THESE CONTACTS IN,
WHICH WOULD BE A LOT EASIER
IF CONNOR STOPPED
BLINKING THEM OUT!
I THINK WE SHOULD ABORT
THIS PHASE OF THE EXPERIMENT.
CONTACTS CAN LEAD
TO PERMANENT CORNEAL DAMAGE.
BUT WE'RE GETTING
OUR NOMINEE PHOTO TAKEN
AFTER SCHOOL!
WHY DO YOU WANT ME
TO CHANGE SO MUCH?
UH, I TOLD YOU,
IT'S FOR AN EXPERIMENT.
I'M NOT STUPID,
WHAT'S THE REAL REASON?
ALLI:
MAYBE I SHOULD GIVE YOU TWO
A MINUTE ALONE.
LOOK, I JUST WANT PEOPLE
TO RESPECT YOU.
US!
I'M SICK OF PEOPLE THINKING
WE'RE A WEIRD COUPLE!
WHY DO YOU CARE SO MUCH
WHAT OTHER PEOPLE THINK?
BECAUSE MAYBE
THEY'RE RIGHT!
I HAVE A HYPOTHESIS.
I DON'T THINK THE PROBLEM
IS OTHER PEOPLE,
I THINK IT'S YOU.
MAYA AND MILES:
I'M SORRY.
(BOTH LAUGH)
LOOK...
ZIG WAS MY FRIEND
AND THAT'S HIS LIFE NOW.
IT'S SCARY.
DID YOU TALK
TO MS. GRELL?
YEAH, SHE SAID
SHE'D FIGURE SOMETHING OUT.
WELL, MS. GOOD SAMARITAN,
YOU'VE DEFINITELY EARNED
THE FUN WE'RE GONNA HAVE
AT THE SEMIFORMAL.
YOU KNOW, YOU NEVER
OFFICIALLY ASKED ME.
HUH, I COULD'VE SWORN.
I GUESS I WAS THINKING ABOUT
MY OTHER GIRLFRIEND.
RIGHT, WELL, YOU TWO
HAVE A NICE TIME.
MAYBE CALL ME AFTER?
♪♪♪
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M SAYING THIS,
BUT I PROMISED TO BE HOME
FOR DINNER.
GO. DUTIFUL SON
LOOKS GOOD ON YOU!
(LAUGHS)
WHO THE HELL
DO YOU THINK YOU ARE?!
YOU TOLD MS. GRELL!
AS WHAT, LIKE REVENGE
OR SOMETHING?
I DIDN'T STEAL
YOUR STUPID LAPTOP, MAYA!
I DON'T CARE
ABOUT MY LAPTOP!
I CARE ABOUT YOU.
THEN YOU SHOULD
MIND YOUR OWN BUSINESS!
YOU KNOW GRELL'S GOING
TO CALL CHILDREN'S AID?!
AND SINCE I HAVE
NOWHERE TO GO,
THEY'RE GONNA PUT ME
IN A GROUP HOME.
ISN'T THAT BETTER
THAN SQUATTING?
IF YOU'VE EVER SEEN ONE
OF THOSE PLACES...
ZIG, WHY CAN'T YOU
JUST GO BACK HOME?
MY PARENTS KICKED ME OUT.
OH.
I DIDN'T KNOW.
YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
JENNA:
OH! THERE YOU ARE, CONNOR!
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR YOU
EVERYWHERE TO...
APOLOGIZE.
CONNOR:
YOU'RE MAKING A WEIRD FACE;
ARE YOU GONNA VOMIT
OR SOMETHING?
NO! I...
CONNOR,
YOU LOOK AMAZING.
I COULD ONLY GET
MY LEFT CONTACT IN.
MY DEPTH PERCEPTION
IS TERRIBLE,
I KEEP TRIPPING.
I'M SO SORRY.
WE DON'T HAVE TO DO
THE STUPID COMPETITION.
I REALLY DON'T CARE
WHAT OTHER PEOPLE THINK.
I ACCEPT YOUR APOLOGY,
AND WE HAVE TO WIN
THE COMPETITION.
BUT YOU THINK IT'S STUPID.
YOU DON'T,
AND I'VE READ THAT COMPROMISE
IS IMPORTANT
IN A RELATIONSHIP.
DREW:
JENNA MIDDLETON
AND CONNOR DELAURIER,
YOU'RE UP!
CONNOR:
IMAGE IS AN INTEGRAL PART
OF ANY POLITICAL CAMPAIGN.
SOME PEOPLE THINK
IT WAS A DECISIVE FACTOR
IN JFK'S 1960 VICTORY
OVER NIXON.
WHAT?
YOU CAN TALK NERDY
TO ME ANYTIME.
HUH!
AND EVEN THOUGH
I FORGOT MY BRA,
I GOT TO REWRITE
THE WHOLE DRESS CODE!
YOU'RE PRETTY WEIRD,
AREN'T YOU?
IMOGEN'S NOT WEIRD!
IT'S A GOOD THING.
ANYWAY...
BECKY:
UH, YOU SHOULD WASH THE CITY
OFF YOUR HANDS,
IT'S PRETTY GROSS OUT THERE.
UH, BATHROOM'S DOWN THE HALL.
RIGHT. OKAY.
BE RIGHT BACK.
NOW I FEEL KINDA ICKY.
I THINK I'M GONNA GO
WASH UP TOO-
UH...
DO YOU WANT TO GO
TO THE SEMIFORMAL WITH ME?
FUN!
WE SHOULD INVITE JACK TOO.
IS IT OKAY IF WE DON'T?
I MEAN I JUST WANT
A NIGHT ALONE,
YOU KNOW,
JUST THE TWO OF US.
WE CAN GET TO KNOW EACH OTHER
MORE INTIMATELY.
WOW.
ARE YOU SURE?
BECKY:
OH, AM I SCARING YOU?
I'M REALLY GOOFY
WITH THIS KIND OF STUFF!
IMOGEN:
NO, NO, NO! I SUPPOSE
WE COULD GIVE IT A TRY.
I JUST DIDN'T KNOW
YOU FELT THAT WAY.
YOU'RE THE MOST IMPORTANT PERSON
IN MY LIFE RIGHT NOW.
OKAY.
IT'S A DATE!
A DATE?
OH, RIGHT.
IT'S A DATE.
I'LL PICK YOU UP
AT SEVEN.
OKAY!
COOKIE TIME!
BECKY:
BON APPETIT!
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
I FOUND YOUR LAPTOP
IN KATIE'S ROOM.
IT MUST'VE SLIPPED
DOWN BESIDE THE BED.
I WAS DOING HOMEWORK
IN THERE!
OH MY GOD,
I'M SUCH A TERRIBLE PERSON!
I ACCUSED ZIG
OF TAKING IT,
AND NOW HE'S GONNA BE
PUT IN A GROUP HOME!
WHOA, THERE, GIRLIE.
ACCUSING ZIG OF TAKING
THE LAPTOP WITHOUT PROOF
WAS WRONG,
BUT TALKING TO MS. GRELL
WASN'T!
I DON'T KNOW, MOM.
I'VE BEEN READING
HORROR STORIES
ABOUT THOSE PLACES!
THEY'RE LIKE "OLIVER,"
BUT WITHOUT THE SINGING
AND DANCING.
THOSE HOMES ARE EXPECTED
TO DO A LOT
WITH VERY LIMITED RESOURCES.
IT'S NOT FAIR!
I WISH THERE WAS SOMETHING
WE COULD DO.
ZIG SPENT ALL THAT TIME
HERE LAST YEAR.
HE FELT LIKE FAMILY.
MS. GRELL SAID...
IF ZIG COULD FIND
A SAFE PLACE TO STAY,
THEN SHE WOULDN'T HAVE
TO CALL CHILDREN'S AID.
MAYA, ZIG CAN'T LIVE
WITH US.
EVEN IF IT'S ONLY
FOR A FEW WEEKS?
ALLI:
I HAVE TO ADMIT
YOU GUYS LOOK GOOD.
WE LOOK GREAT!
WE'RE GONNA WIN THIS THING.
WELL, CONNOR DEFINITELY
HAS THE YOUTH VOTE.
FRANKIE:
BYE!
HEY, WHO ARE
YOUR NEW FRIENDS?
THEY'RE NOT MY FRIENDS,
THEY'RE JUST SOME GRADE NINES
WHO WANT MATH HELP.
WELL, WHEN DID THEY ASK YOU,
LIKE LAST WEEK?
NO, JUST NOW.
AFTER YOUR MAKEOVER.
ALLI:
HUH. WHAT A COINCIDENCE.
(BELL RINGS)
MS. GRELL:
THE POINT OF THIS EXERCISE
IS TO TRUST YOUR PARTNER ENOUGH
TO LET THEM CATCH YOU.
SO GO AHEAD,
AND WHEN I SAY SO, SWITCH.
DROP ME AND DIE,
GRACE.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
HI.
ZIG, I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT WOULD HAPPEN
WHEN I TALKED
TO MS. GRELL.
YOU SHOULD'VE JUST
STAYED OUT OF IT!
I KNOW, AND I'M SORRY,
BUT I WANNA HELP!
MS. GRELL:
AND SWITCH!
WELL, YOU CAN'T.
YES, I CAN.
YOU SAID IF YOU HAD
A PLACE TO STAY,
THEN MS. GRELL WOULDN'T
CALL CHILDREN'S AID!
RIGHT. BUT I DON'T,
SO SHE WILL.
BUT YOU DO HAVE
A PLACE TO STAY.
WHAT, YOUR NEW RICH BOYFRIEND
IS GONNA SPRING FOR A SUITE?
MS. GRELL:
LESS CHATTING, MORE FALLING!
NO, BUT MY SISTER'S AWAY
AT COLLEGE,
SO THERE'S AN EXTRA ROOM
AT MY HOUSE.
(MAYA CRASHES ON FLOOR)
OOF!
YOUR MOM WOULD NEVER
SAY YES!
MAYA:
SHE ALREADY DID.
IT TOOK SOME CONVINCING.
ALSO, THERE ARE RULES:
10:00 P.M. CURFEW,
NO DRUGS OR ALCOHOL,
NO VISITORS,
AND UM...
NO HANKY PANKY.
SO... WHAT DO YOU SAY?
HOUSEMATES?
(LAUGHS)
YOU BETTER NOT HOG
THE BATHROOM.
♪ Too young for monogamy ♪
♪ It's getting harder
to fight this feeling ♪