(RAIN SPLASHES,
THUNDER RUMBLES)
ZOE:
MAYA! MAYA!
(WIND HOWLS)
MAYA,
WE HAVE TO GET INSIDE!
LET'S GO!
DUH! I'M GOING
TO THE SCHOOL!
NO, IT'S BLOCKS AWAY!
YOU'RE DRUNK!
YEAH, AND YOU'RE A BITCH!
LEAVE ME ALONE!
NO WAY!
IF I LET YOU DIE OUT HERE,
YOU'LL PROBABLY JUST BLAME ME
FOR THAT, TOO!
I'M FINE!
AND IF I DIE,
I WILL TOTALLY HAUNT YOU!
I'LL TOTALLY HAUNT
THE CRAP OUT OF YOU!
ARGHH!
(LOUD CRACK OF THUNDER)
QUICK!
WE NEED TO TAKE SHELTER!
LET'S GO!
MAYA:
NO, YOU'VE BEEN AFTER ME
ALL YEAR LONG.
YOU'LL PROBABLY USE THIS
AS YOUR CHANCE TO FINISH ME OFF!
HELP! A WASHED UP TEEN STAR
IS TRYING TO KILL ME!
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(GRUNTS WITH EFFORT)
IF YOU'RE GONNA INSULT ME,
YOU MIGHT AS WELL JUST DO IT
FROM INSIDE!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ (The best that I can be) ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(LOUD THUNDERCLAP)
RADIO DJ:
SECTIONS OF HIGHWAY 401
ARE SUBMERGED,
MANY NEIGHBOURHOODS
ARE UNDER WATER,
AND WE'VE SEEN FIVE INCHES
OF RAIN ALREADY,
A RECORD FOR THREE HOURS.
DREW:
HEY, HAVE YOU SEEN BECKY BAKER?
YOU SURE?
RADIO DJ:
GET INSIDE NOW!
IF YOU ARE INDOORS,
MAKE PLANS TO STAY THERE
FOR THE NIGHT
AS THIS STORM
IS NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
DREW:
HEY.
NOBODY'S SEEN BECKY
SINCE I LAST TALKED TO HER.
WHAT IF SHE TRIED TO GO HOME
IN THIS?!
DALLAS:
YOU'RE NOT EVEN
DATING THE GIRL,
AND YOU STILL MANAGED
TO PUT HER LIFE IN DANGER?
DALLAS,
I MAY SUCK AT DATING,
BUT I DON'T PUT ANYONE'S LIFE
IN DANGER!
DIDN'T BIANCA ALMOST GET KILLED
BY A GANG LIKE TWICE?
FINE, YOU'RE RIGHT.
BECKY'S FACE DOWN
IN A GUTTER RIGHT NOW
AND IT'S ALL MY FAULT!
THE GAME, MY FRIENDS,
IS... MURDER!
(LOUD THUNDERCLAP)
FRANKIE: OH MY GOSH!
TRISTAN:
CAN YOU BELIEVE MILES GOT THIS
GAME TOGETHER SO QUICKLY?
HANDSOME AND RESOURCEFUL -
HE'S THE COMPLETE PACKAGE.
WINSTON:
UM, GUYS, THE RULES?
THIS IS THE MURDER WEAPON.
IF THE MURDERER SHOWS YOU
THE WEAPON,
CONSIDER YOURSELF MURDERED.
TRISTAN:
HE DOESN'T EVEN HAVE
TO TOUCH YOU.
BUT HE CAN IF HE WANTS.
(MILES LAUGHS)
MILES:
NOW, EVERYBODY SCATTER.
(TRISTAN LAUGHS EXCITEDLY)
WINSTON:
WHAT'S GOING ON?
UH, TIME TO HIDE,
CHEWY.
DIDN'T YOU LISTEN
TO THE RULES?!
ARE YOU BLIND, MAN?
HE WANTS YOU!
TRIS AND I ARE
JUST FRIENDS.
DOES HE KNOW THAT?
JUST DON'T BE A JERK,
OKAY?
WHEN HAVE I EVER
BEEN A JERK?
I'LL MAKE A LIST
WHILE I'M HIDING.
(LOUD THUNDERCLAP)
(SIRENS WAIL,
HORNS HONK)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
THANKS FOR LENDING ME
THESE DRY CLOTHES.
I MAY HAVE TO STEAL
THIS HOODIE.
OKAY...
THIS IS AWKWARD,
ISN'T IT?
I SHOULD GO.
I-I WILL GO!
ELI:
WHAT?!
AND WHERE WOULD YOU SLEEP?
UM...
ELI:
WHAT, IN THE SUBWAY
WITH THE RATS?
COME ON, YOU NEED
TO GET SOME REST
BEFORE YOUR BIG
COLUMBIA INTERVIEW!
I KNOW, BUT...
I HAVE NO RIGHT BEING HERE,
NOT AFTER WHAT HAPPENED.
SO THERE WAS A LITTLE
BREAKING UP OVER VOICEMAIL,
AND A LITTLE MAKING OUT
WITH A MEATHEAD.
NO BIG DEAL.
OKAY, I KNOW THINGS
ARE A LITTLE TIGHT,
BUT THERE'S ENOUGH ROOM HERE
FOR BOTH OF US.
IS YOUR ROOMMATE GONNA MIND
SOME STRANGE GIRL
SLEEPING IN HIS BED?
NO, NO, NO,
I'M SURE HE'LL LOVE IT
IF HE FINDS YOU THERE
WHEN HE GETS HOME.
HE'S COMING BACK?!
YEAH.
CLARE: UM, I, UH, CAN...
ELI: TAKE THE BED.
I'LL BUNK ON THE FLOOR.
CLARE:
WELL, THAT'S NOT FAIR TO YOU.
I'LL TAKE THE FLOOR.
WHY DON'T WE JUST SHARE
THE BED, THEN?
CLARE: IS THAT A GOOD IDEA?
ELI: YEAH...
WE'LL GO HEAD TO TOE.
OKAY.
CLARE: (LAUGHS AT ABSURDITY)
ELI: GO AHEAD.
(SNICKERS)
AHH...
SEE?
TONS OF ROOM.
♪♪♪
ARE YOU HUNGRY?
I'M HUNGRY.
STARVING!
(CRACK OF THUNDER)
MAYA:
TALK TO HER AGAIN,
LET HER KNOW WE'RE OKAY!
OKAY? THANK YOU.
BYE.
OH...
STRIP.
WHY, SO YOU CAN TAKE
MORE PHOTOS
AND CONTINUE YOUR CAMPAIGN
TO RUIN MY LIFE?!
GET OVER
YOUR DRUNK SELF!
IT'S SO YOU DON'T CATCH
PNEUMONIA.
(SHIVERING)
OHHHH MY HEAD!
I DON'T NEED YOU BARFING
ALL OVER THE PLACE.
HERE.
OKAY, LIFT.
LET'S GO.
I CAN'T SEE.
IT'S FINE,
YOU DON'T NEED TO SEE!
OKAY.
FIND THE HOLE.
SEE MY HAND?
I CAN'T. I DON'T KNOW
HOW TO DO THIS!
YES, YES,
FIND IT! GO!
EXCUSE ME!
I'M TRYING TO HELP.
I DON'T...
OKAY!
I'M TRYING, MAYA!
LIKE I'VE BEEN TRYING
TO BE YOUR FRIEND ALL YEAR!
OH, LIKE YOU WERE TRYING
WHEN YOU STOLE MY BOYFRIEND
AND GOT ALL UP IN HIM
AT THAT PARTY,
AND NOW YOU'RE "TRYING"
WITH ZIG?
I GET IT.
ZOE JUST LOVES
MY SLOPPY SECONDS.
WELL, IF WE'RE
GETTING TECHNICAL,
MILES WAS
MY SLOPPY SECONDS.
I HAD HIM FIRST
AND YOU STOLE HIM FROM ME.
THAT HURT A LOT,
YOU KNOW.
I REALLY LIKED HIM.
(SIGHS)
BECKY?
(HISSING NOISE)
BECKY, ARE YOU OKAY?
OF COURSE I AM SILLY,
I'M IN THE SAFEST PLACE
IN THE BUILDING.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE IN THE GYM
WITH EVERYONE ELSE.
I'M FROM FLORIDA.
I'VE BEEN THROUGH
SEVEN HURRICANES,
AND THAT GYM HAS WAY
TOO MANY WINDOWS FOR ME!
STILL,
WE SHOULD GET BACK,
LET EVERYONE KNOW
YOU'RE OKAY.
YOU CAN SIT WITH IMOGEN,
AND I'LL...
I'LL HANG AT A SAFE DISTANCE
WITH DALLAS.
WHY ARE YOU BEING
SO WEIRD?
BECAUSE I KNOW YOU LIKE ME.
SO WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
WE'RE GONNA GET OUT OF HERE
AS QUICKLY AS POSSIBLE.
(DOOR CREAKS SHUT)
(RATTLES DOORKNOB)
OH NO!
IT'S STUCK!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'S OKAY,
WE'LL BE SAFE IN HERE
UNTIL THE STORM PASSES.
AND THEN WHAT?!
I DIDN'T TELL ANYONE
WHERE I WAS GOING!
SO?
SO AS SOON
AS THE STORM PASSES,
EVERYONE'S GONNA GO HOME -
FOR A WEEK!
OKAY, THEN WE'LL CALL SOMEONE
TO COME GET US!
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
MY PHONE GOT FRIED IN THE STORM.
IS YOURS WORKING?
YEAH.
MY PHONE DIED.
OH GOD!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
UH...
DREW, DID YOU GET NERVOUS
AND...
DREW:
WHAT?
I DON'T WANNA SAY,
IT'S GROSS.
BECKY, I HONESTLY HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
DID YOU FART?
WHAT?
IN FRONT OF YOU?
NO! NO WAY!
BECKY:
OKAY THEN, WHAT'S THAT SMELL?
(SNIFFS)
(HISSING)
(GAGS)
(PIPE HISSING)
(GASPS FOR BREATH)
OKAY, WE NEED TO TURN IT OFF!
WHERE'S THE SHUTOFF?
(CREAKS AND SNAPS)
OH GOD!
DREW AND BECKY:
(YELLING) HELP US! HELP!
(MUTED SHOUTS)
SOMEBODY HELP US!
PLEASE! HELP US!
PLEASE, SOMEBODY HELP US!
♪♪♪
ELI:
COME ON, HURRY UP!
THESE GUYS WILL NOT STOP!
CLARE:
I'M GONNA GET HIT!
(GIGGLES)
ELI:
WE'RE GOOD.
CLARE:
LOOKS LIKE THE STORM'S PASSED.
YEAH.
OH, OKAY, YOU HAVE TO TRY
MARION'S KEBABS,
THEY'RE THE BEST!
COME HERE.
HEY, MARION.
UH, CAN I GET TWO
CHICKEN KEBABS, PLEASE?
THANKS.
IS EVERYTHING BETTER
IN NEW YORK?
PRETTY MUCH.
OH. HERE YOU ARE.
THANK YOU!
OH, JUST BE CAREFUL,
THEY'RE LIKE PRETTY HOT.
GOIN' IN.
GO AHEAD.
WHAT?!
YEAH,
THEY'RE PRETTY AMAZING.
OH MY GOD,
THAT IS SO GOOD!
ABOVE AVERAGE.
YEAH! YES!
YEAH.
WHAT?!
SO UM...
HOW'S DREW?
UH, I DON'T KNOW.
GOOD?
YOU DON'T KNOW
HOW YOUR OWN BOYFRIEND IS?
WHOA, NO! WE NEVER...
DIDN'T...
NO?
OH, I-I JUST ASSUMED.
HOW ABOUT YOU
AND LENORE?
NO, WE NEVER...
YOU KNOW.
REALLY?
I GUESS I JUST THOUGHT
THAT...
WHAT, THAT SHE COULD HOLD
A CANDLE TO CLARE EDWARDS?
NOT EVEN CLOSE.
CLARE: ELI?
ELI: WHAT?
I AM SO SORRY.
FOR WHAT?
BREAKING UP WITH YOU
HOW I DID.
NO, NO. HEY.
I SHOULD THANK YOU.
YOU KNOW, IN A WEIRD WAY,
YOU UM...
YOU SET ME FREE.
YOU LET ME EXPERIENCE
NEW YORK LIFE,
FILM SCHOOL LIFE,
YOU KNOW, ALL OF THAT,
ON MY OWN TERMS.
YOU KNOW,
WE SHOULD GO.
YOU NEED SOME REST
BEFORE YOUR INTERVIEW TOMORROW,
AND I WOULDN'T WANT TONIGHT
TO JEOPARDIZE
YOUR OWN NEW YORK
EXPERIENCE.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S HURRY UP,
THESE GUYS COME OUT OF NOWHERE!
ELI: COME ON! LET'S GO!
CLARE: OH! OKAY, OKAY!
(GASPS)
HOW'D YOU FIND ME?
CIRCLING BACK
TO THE STARTING POINT?
OLDEST TRICK IN THE BOOK.
PLUS, I WANTED TO MAKE SURE
YOU WERE OKAY
AFTER EVERYTHING
WE TALKED ABOUT OUT THERE.
DO YOU HAVE THE LIGHTER?
I DON'T KNOW!
FEELIN' ME UP?
YOU KNOW, CHEWY DID HAVE
THIS CRAZY IDEA
THAT YOU WANT ME.
THAT IS A CRAZY IDEA.
THE LIGHTER.
COME ANY CLOSER
AND... I'LL KISS YOU!
GO AHEAD.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(LOUD THUNDERCLAP)
(FLASHLIGHT CLATTERS)
(HUFFS)
UH, I'LL LET YOU TWO
CATCH UP.
(LAUGHS)
WINSTON:
SO WHAT, YOU'RE GAY NOW?
BI?
MILES:
IT FELT RIGHT, MAN,
AND KINDA FUN.
WINSTON:
IS HE GONNA THINK IT'S FUN
WHEN IT NEVER HAPPENS AGAIN?
YOU'RE A MESS,
DUDE!
FIGURE OUT WHAT YOU WANT
BEFORE YOU HURT SOMEONE ELSE
YOU CARE ABOUT!
WINSTON...
WHAT?
(SIGHS)
YOU'RE DEAD.
(CRACK OF THUNDER)
DREW:
(YELLING)
HELP! HELP US!
(BECKY AND DREW COUGH)
(BECKY SOBS)
IT'S NO USE!
BECKY:
SO, THAT'S IT?
WE'RE JUST GIVING UP?
WE'RE JUST GONNA SUFFOCATE
IN HERE?
DREW:
OBVIOUSLY NO ONE CAN HEAR US.
THERE'S NOTHING LEFT TO DO
BUT PRAY.
(LAUGHS AND SOBS)
WE'RE PROBABLY LOCKED IN HERE
AS PUNISHMENT
FOR MY FEELINGS FOR YOU.
DREW:
THAT'S NOT HOW GOD WORKS,
IS IT?
HE'S NOT VENGEFUL
LIKE THAT?
AFTER THE YEAR
HE PUT ME THROUGH,
I'M NOT SO SURE ANYMORE.
IF HE REALLY WANTED
TO STRIKE US DOWN,
WOULDN'T HE JUST ZAP US
WITH LIGHTNING OR SOMETHING?
(LAUGHS)
WHAT I MEAN IS,
IF GOD REALLY DIDN'T WANT US
TO BE TOGETHER,
WHY WOULD HE TRAP ME
IN SUCH A TINY ROOM
WITH SUCH A BEAUTIFUL,
SMART, FUNNY GIRL
TO TEMPT ME?
ARE YOU TEMPTED?
(LOUD CRASH)
(CRASHING BLOWS)
(JACK AND IMOGEN COUGH)
OH, THANK GOODNESS!
DALLAS:
OKAY, PARTS OF THE CEILING
ARE STILL COLLAPSING UP THERE,
WE GOTTA GET BACK
TO THE GYM!
AH!
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
MAYA:
(SIGHS) YOU WERE RIGHT.
I CAME BETWEEN
YOU AND MILES,
SO...
I'M PREPARED TO ACCEPT
SOME OF THE BLAME.
I DON'T ACCEPT YOU
ACCEPTING IT.
HUH?
MILES IS THE REAL JERK HERE.
HE HAS BEEN THE SOURCE
OF ALL MY DRAMA THIS YEAR.
I'VE NEVER BEEN GOOD
AT GIRLFRIENDS.
I'M ALWAYS JEALOUS OF THEM.
AS IF YOU WERE
JEALOUS OF ME!
ZOE:
I WAS! I AM!
EVERYBODY LOVES YOU,
AND YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE TO TRY.
YEAH, WELL,
I GUESS I WAS PRETTY JEALOUS
OF YOU, TOO.
OH, WELL,
THAT I JUST ASSUMED.
(BOTH LAUGH)
IT'D BE NICE TO BE
ON THE SAME TEAM, FOR ONCE.
YEAH.
(SIGHS)
♪ THANK YOU FOR BEING A FRIEND ♪
♪ TRAVELED DOWN THE ROAD
AND BACK AGAIN ♪
♪ YOUR HEART IS TRUE,
YOU'RE A PAL AND A CONFIDANTE ♪
♪ DAH, DAH, DAH ♪
♪ AND IF YOU THREW A PARTY ♪
MAYA AND ZOE:
(SINGING IN HARMONY)
♪ INVITED EVERYONE YOU KNEW ♪
♪ YOU WOULD SEE THE BIGGEST GIFT
WOULD BE FROM ME ♪
♪ AND THE CARD ATTACHED
WOULD SAY ♪
♪ THANK YOU FOR BEING A FRIEND ♪
♪ BAH-BAH BAH BAH BAH BAH ♪
(BOTH LAUGH)
INTERVIEWER:
YOU SURVIVED THE STORM.
CLARE:
YES, YES, I DID.
INTERVIEWER:
THAT'S NOT SURPRISING.
YOU ARE A VERY IMPRESSIVE
YOUNG WOMAN.
OUTSTANDING MARKS,
TONS OF EXTRACURRICULARS,
AND YOU SURVIVED CANCER?
RHABDOMYOSARCOMA!
I LOVED YOUR ESSAY,
BY THE WAY,
ABOUT BREAKING OUT
OF THE HOSPITAL.
REALLY? THANKS.
IT WAS A BREATH
OF FRESH AIR.
MOST ESSAYS ARE ABOUT
MISSION TRIPS.
I TOOK A RISK WITH THAT,
I GUESS.
INTERVIEWER:
WELL...
COLUMBIA WOULD BE VERY LUCKY
TO HAVE YOU, MS. EDWARDS.
THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR YOUR TIME.
OKAY.
(LAUGHS INCREDULOUSLY)
(EXCITED GIGGLING)
I'M FRIENDS WITH HER.
WHAT...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
YOU KNOW I HAVE TO CATCH
MY FLIGHT.
YEAH, THIS'LL ONLY
TAKE A SECOND.
SO, UM, I LIED LAST NIGHT.
I DIDN'T WANT
TO COMPLICATE THINGS
BEFORE YOUR INTERVIEW,
BUT UH...
I'M NOT OVER YOU.
I REALLY HAVE TO CATCH
MY FLIGHT.
I KNOW.
JUST THINK ABOUT IT.
♪♪♪
(LAUGHS)
(BIRDS CHIRP)
WE DON'T EVER HAVE
TO TALK ABOUT IT,
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO.
(LAUGHS)
I'M A BAD DUDE,
TRIS.
WINSTON'S RIGHT;
I ALWAYS HURT THE PEOPLE
I CARE ABOUT.
I GET IT.
IT'S FINE.
I FIGURED IT WAS ALL A WAY
TO GET BACK AT MAYA, ANYWAY,
WHICH I DIDN'T MIND.
BUT I SHOULD GET HOME.
LOOK, DON'T GO, OKAY?
MILES...
I'M HONESTLY GAMED OUT
RIGHT NOW.
I'M CONFUSED, TRIS.
I-IT WAS WEIRD.
GOTCHA.
BUT GOOD WEIRD.
LOOK, I JUST KNOW
THAT I FEEL...
I FEEL GOOD
WHEN I'M AROUND YOU.
LIKEWISE.
SO WHAT NOW?
♪ Thank you for being a friend ♪
IMOGEN:
I LOVE YOU, TREE!
HEY! I LOVE YA!
(MAKES AIRPLANE SOUNDS)
I LOVE YOU, GROUND.
(KISSING SOUND)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
WEIRDO?
IMOGEN:
OH, I'M JUST SO HAPPY
THE WORLD DIDN'T END,
I WANT TO SHOW MOTHER EARTH
HOW MUCH I APPRECIATE HER!
WELL, SAVE SOME OF THOSE
KISSES FOR ME.
(LAUGHS)
HEY, YOU GUYS NEED
SOME HELP?
I THINK WE'RE GOOD.
THEY MIGHT NEED SOME HELP
LIFTING UP THAT SIGN.
ACTUALLY, MY UH...
MY BACK'S PRETTY SORE.
DUDE, CHILL.
IF YOU WANNA GO FOR HER,
GO FOR HER.
ALLI:
AND I THINK YOU GUYS ARE
ACTUALLY KINDA SWEET TOGETHER.
LIFE IS SHORT.
GO GET 'EM, TIGER.
(LAUGHS)
♪ Have no fear
even though it's hard to hear ♪
♪ I will stand real close
and say...
DREW:
HEY.
BEX, ABOUT THE-
KISS? I KNOW.
IT WASN'T RIGHT.
I CAN FORGET IT
IF YOU CAN.
WHAT IF I DON'T WANT TO?
WE SHOULD JUST TAKE THIS
VERY, VERY SLOWLY.
I'D LIKE THAT.
(BOTH LAUGH)
♪♪♪
OH!
(SQUEALS)
ALLI: HI!
CLARE: HEY!
OH!
WHAT IS GOING ON OVER THERE?
ALLI:
A LOT HAPPENED
DURING THE STORM.
YOU OKAY ABOUT THAT?
YEAH, ACTUALLY,
I'M, UH, I'M GREAT.
SO THE INTERVIEW
WENT WELL?
SHE REALLY LIKED ME.
AND UM...
SO DID ELI.
SAY WHAT?!
HE SHOWED UP
AFTER MY INTERVIEW,
PROFESSED HIS LOVE.
THINKS WE CAN DO IT,
IF IT'S NOT LONG DISTANCE.
DO YOU?
I DON'T KNOW,
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN A WHILE,
IT FEELS LIKE
ANYTHING'S POSSIBLE.
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
ELI?
IT IS A NEW YORK NUMBER.
HELLO?
NURSE:
HI, IS THIS CLARE EDWARDS?
IT IS.
NURSE:
THIS IS THE NEW YORK
CIVIC HOSPITAL.
I JUST WANTED TO LET YOU KNOW
YOUR BLOODWORK CAME BACK
AND NOTHING WAS OUT
OF THE ORDINARY.
EVERYTHING LOOKS A-OKAY
FOR YOU AND YOUR BABY.
♪♪♪