♪♪♪
(MAYA AND TRISTAN LAUGH)
MAYA:
I NEVER THOUGHT I'D BE
SO EXCITED TO VISIT SCHOOL
ON MY SUMMER VACATION.
TRISTAN:
OH, I AM FREAKING OUT!
CAN WE JUST BE THERE ALREADY?
BEST SUMMER EVER!
I WONDER
WHO ELSE IS GOING.
WELL, OBVIOUSLY
AWESOME PEOPLE.
ONLY AWESOME PEOPLE
WOULD SPEND TWO MONTHS IN...
MAYA:
(WHISPERS) PARIS!
DALLAS:
DUDE, IT'S FINE!
DREW:
NO, IT'S CROOKED!
GO LEFT.
DALLAS: YOURS OR MINE?
DREW: EITHER, MAN.
OH, SORRY! OH!
DREW:
I GOT IT, I GOT IT,
I GOT IT, I GOT IT.
DREW: OH, I GOT IT, IT'S OKAY.
MAYA: SORRY.
(LAUGHS)
TRISTAN:
NO!
NO BOYS FOR YOU.
TORI'S FAMILY MOVED AWAY,
SO NOW YOU'RE MY BEST FRIEND.
WE HAVE TO STICK
TOGETHER.
PROMISE ME?
PROMISE?
I PROMISE!
(LAUGHS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
TRISTAN! YOU'RE COMING?
YAY!
MADAME JEAN-AUX:
BONJOUR, LES AMIES!
ALORS, QUI VEUT PASSER LEUR ETE
DANS LA VILLE DES LUMIERES?
ALL:
WOO-HOO!
PARIS, HERE WE COME!
MADAME JEAN-AUX:
UM... WE ARE MISSING TWO.
UM, CLARE HAS AN APPOINTMENT.
OKAY.
ZOE:
KNOCK, KNOCK!
BONJOUR, BITCHES!
THAT'S... THAT'S...
MADAME JEAN-AUX:
AH YES, MADEMOISELLE ZOE.
SHE WILL JOINING YOU
IN PARIS.
ISN'T THAT THAT GIRL
FROM THAT SHOW?
TRISTAN:
YOU MEAN THE GATSBY GARCIA,
QUEEN MEAN GIRL
ON "WEST DRIVE,"
THE BEST SHOW EVER!
OH, SHE'S AMAZEBALLS.
IS ANYBODY SITTING THERE?
JUST YOU!
I'M TRISTAN.
ZOE:
AKA THE "WEST DRIVE"
EXPERIENCE?
YOU KNOW WHO I AM?!
THE CAST WATCHES
YOUR VLOG.
I'M MAKING HER
MY NEW BFF.
I THOUGHT I WAS
YOUR NEW BFF.
WELL, WE CAN BE A BFF TRIO!
I HAVE FREE TICKETS TO
THE SUMMERFEST CONCERT TONIGHT.
WANNA GO?
MAYA:
SOUNDS AWESOME!
GUESS YOU CAN
COME TOO.
DOORS OPEN AT NINE.
OH, WHAT ABOUT YOUR SUPER
EARLY CURFEW?
CURFEW?
WHAT CURFEW?
(LAUGHS UNEASILY)
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ (The best that I can be) ♪
♪ Ooh... ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
JENNA:
DO YOU KNOW HOW MUCH
WE'LL BE WALKING IN PARIS?
IT WOULDN'T KILL YOU
TO WEAR SNEAKERS!
ALLI:
UH, YOU'RE WRONG,
IT WOULD KILL ME!
JENNA:
EARTH TO EDWARDS!
YOU'VE BEEN GLUED
TO YOUR PHONE ALL MORNING!
THAT'S NOT...
YOU DIDN'T GET YOUR TEST
RESULTS BACK, DID YOU?
NO.
NO, THE DOCTOR SAID
IT MIGHT BE ANOTHER DAY.
THERE'S NO WAY
YOU HAVE CANCER.
RIGHT!
YOU'LL FIND OUT
YOUR TEST RESULTS ARE NEGATIVE,
AND WE'LL BE STROLLING ALONG
THE CHAMPS-ELYSEES,
WHERE YOU TWO CAN HELP ME
FIND UN GARCON.
OH, SO NO MORE PINING AFTER
A CERTAIN HOCKEY CAPTAIN, THEN?
(SIGHS)
THAT SHIP HAS SAILED.
(PHONE BEEPS)
JENNA:
AGAIN? OKAY, IT MUST BE
THE BOYFRIEND.
HOW ARE YOU TWO
KEEPING THINGS SPICY?
WHAT?
WELL,
LET'S FIND OUT!
NO, ALLI!
OH ALLI, COME ON!
"MORNING, CLARE-BEAR.
I DREAMT OF YOU LAST NIGHT."
OOH-WEEE!
CLARE:
CAN I HAVE IT?
JENNA:
"HAVE YOU WATCHED...
THIS WEEK'S 'MAD MEN'?"
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
WHERE ARE THE SEXY PARTS?
CLARE:
ARE YOU SAYING ELI
AND I SHOULD...
WE DO HAVE THE TECHNOLOGY,
CLARE.
ALLI:
BEATS WAITING AROUND
FOR A DOCTOR'S CALL, RIGHT?
(ALLI AND JENNA GIGGLE)
♪♪♪
♪ There is a fire ♪
♪ Why don't you climb aboard ♪
♪ Just imagine it ♪
♪ Everything it touches falls ♪
♪ Hollywood has burned ♪
♪ I got a life to live ♪
♪ On my knees I'm begging
but have nothing to forgive ♪
♪ Because everybody got
a little devil inside ♪
SO DO YOU THINK ICE CREAM
TASTES DIFFERENT IN FRANCE?
KATIE:
I DON'T KNOW,
BUT I DOUBT THEY EVEN HAVE
PEANUT BUTTER CHOCOLATE
AT SOCCER CAMP, SO.
THE LAST ICE CREAM.
SO GOOD.
MRS. MATLIN:
OKAY. SO, PASSPORT?
CHECK!
RAPE WHISTLE?
CHECK,
BUT SERIOUSLY UNNECESSARY.
CAN YOU HUMOUR ME?
I'M LETTING MY BABY GO
TO A FOREIGN COUNTRY ALONE.
I MUST BE CRAZY!
EUROS?
CHECK! OH, PERMISSION TO GO
TO AN ALL-AGES CONCERT TONIGHT,
CHECK?
UM...
THE OTHER PARIS PEEPS
ARE GOING,
INCLUDING ZOE RIVAS,
STAR OF "WEST DRIVE."
WHO'S ZOE RIVAS?!
MAYA:
TRISTAN'S OBSESSING.
NOW THAT TORI'S GONE THOUGH,
I'M AFRAID SHE'S GONNA SWOOP IN
AND STEAL MY BEST FRIEND.
OOH, SHE'S PRETTY.
GREAT STYLE...
YEAH, SHE'S TOTALLY GONNA
STEAL TRISTAN.
AND SOMEHOW GOING
TO THIS CONCERT
WILL PREVENT THAT
FROM HAPPENING?
DUH! YES!
OKAY, YOU CAN GO.
BUT YOUR CURFEW'S STILL
TEN O'CLOCK.
TEN O'CLOCK?
MOM, THAT'S SO EARLY!
YOU'RE LETTING ME GO
TO PARIS, REMEMBER?
MRS. MATLIN:
YES, WHERE YOUR CURFEW
WILL BE TEN O'CLOCK. DUH!
(SCOFFS)
OKAY, UM... TO BE FAIR,
THE CONCERT PROBABLY WON'T START
TILL 9:30.
OKAY, YOUR CURFEW
IS 11:30,
NOT A MINUTE LATER,
OR THERE WILL BE CONSEQUENCES.
THANK YOU!
KATIE:
THANK ME.
OKAY, SMILE!
EAT YOUR ICE CREAM.
MR. SIMPSON:
SOMEHOW, DREW, YOU'RE
MY STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT
STARTING IN THE FALL.
IT'S THE WILL
OF THE PEOPLE, SIR.
MR. SIMPSON:
UH-HUH.
THIS SUMMER,
YOU ARE THE CAMP DIRECTORS,
AND YOU ARE IN CHARGE
OF OVER A HUNDRED CAMPERS.
PLEASE, DO ME A FAVOUR.
DO NOT FAIL ME!
DREW:
UH-HUH.
MR. SIMPSON:
LET COUNSELOR
ORIENTATION BEGIN.
IMOGEN:
EXCUSE ME! PARDON ME! SORRY!
DREW:
WELCOME TO DEGRASSI PANTHERS
SUMMER DAY CAMP.
TODAY WE LEARN HOW THE CAMP
WILL BE RUN, AND TONIGHT...
WELL, TONIGHT WE BOND
AT SUMMERFEST!
COUNSELORS:
WOO-HOO! YEAH!
HEY, AT LEAST THERE'S ONE
COOL CAMP COUNSELOR HERE.
WELL, TWO,
IF YOU INCLUDE ME.
HI, IMOGEN.
WHY SO GLUM, CHUM?
BECKY LEAVES
FOR FLORIDA TOMORROW.
YIKES! IT WAS FUN
WHILE IT LASTED?
NO, WE'RE NOT BREAKING UP
JUST BECAUSE SHE'S GONE
FOR THE SUMMER.
WE'RE ROCK SOLID,
LIKE YOU AND FIONA.
OH NO.
YOU GUYS WERE TOGETHER
FOREVER!
SIX MONTHS, THREE WEEKS,
FOUR DAYS.
THAT'S LONGER THEN ME
AND BECKS.
I TOLD MYSELF
I WOULDN'T WORRY.
THEN DON'T!
YOU'RE A GREAT GUY,
BECKY IS LUCKY TO HAVE YOU.
I DON'T WANNA BE
THAT CRAZY JEALOUS GUY
WHO ASKS
A BAZILLION QUESTIONS.
THEN DON'T!
LEAVE THAT TO ME.
YOU'D DO THAT FOR ME?
WELL, AS LONG AS YOU PROMISE
TO BE MY CAMP BESTIE.
DONE.
AND THERE'S A SMILE!
WELL, LET'S KEEP
THAT PERMANENT!
(LAUGHS)
(PHONE RINGING
ON THE OTHER END OF THE LINE)
ELI:
YEP! SMOOTHIES
ARE ON THEIR WAY!
UH, WHAT?
OH, HEY! I'M SORRY,
I THOUGHT YOU WERE BRET.
THE GUY IS A SMOOTHIE-ADDICT.
DAMN, DID I FORGET THAT
EXTRA SHOT OF WHEATGRASS?
WELCOME TO THE GLAMOROUS LIFE
OF A PRODUCTION ASSISTANT!
IS THIS A BAD TIME?
NO, NO, IT'S NEVER
A BAD TIME FOR YOU.
CLARE:
AW, THAT'S SWEET.
DID YOU GET THAT PICTURE
THAT I TEXTED?
UH, YEAH.
YEAH, UM, SURE DID.
UH, WERE YOU...
WERE YOU IMPLYING SOMETHING
THERE?
CLARE:
I WAS.
I MISS YOU,
AND I WAS THINKING,
MAYBE I'D MISS YOU
A LITTLE BIT LESS IF WE...
DID A LITTLE LONG DISTANCE
SOMETHING SEXY?
SE... UM...
WHAT, UM...
WHAT'D YOU HAVE IN MIND?
VIDEO CHAT SEX.
SERIOUSLY?
ASSISTANT DIRECTOR:
COME ON, GOLDSWORTHY!
UM, BUT NOT RIGHT NOW.
UM, TEN O'CLOCK?
YEAH, GREAT!
GREAT.
GREAT!
(LAUGHS)
MAYA:
IN TWO DAYS, WE'LL BE ABLE
TO SEE THE REAL MONA LISA!
IT'S SHOCKINGLY SMALL.
WE GO TO PARIS
LIKE ONCE A YEAR
TO PROMOTE THE SHOW.
DID YOU AND MACK LAWFORD
EVER HOOK UP
ON ONE OF THOSE
EUROPEAN VACATIONS?
ZOE:
MACK'S NICE,
BUT, UH, I'M NOT HIS TYPE.
(CHUCKLES SUGGESTIVELY)
I KNEW IT!
ZOE:
AN INTRODUCTION
WILL BE MADE.
COME ON,
WE DON'T STAND IN LINE.
THE PERKS OF BEING
WITH A SUPERSTAR!
THESE GUYS ARE WITH ME.
BOUNCER:
IT'S THIRTEEN AND OVER ONLY,
MISS.
I'M FOURTEEN,
IDIOT!
YEAH, RIGHT.
KEEP THE LINE MOVING, GUYS.
HEY ZOE,
A LITTLE HELP HERE?
TRIS, YOU'RE LEAVING ME
OUT HERE?!
TRISTAN:
I CAN'T LET ZOE
GO IN ALONE!
I'M SORRY!
(SCOFFS)
(SIGHS)
(MUFFLED MUSIC,
PEOPLE SHOUT)
(CAN CLATTERS)
(SIGHS)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(KNOCKS)
PIZZA DELIVERY!
(MILES LAUGHS)
IT'S A NICE TRY,
BUT...
IT WON'T WORK.
WELL, IT MIGHT.
NO.
HEY, DIDN'T I SEE YOU
AT DEGRASSI THIS MORNING?
MILES:
YEAH, I WAS ENROLLING
FOR SEPTEMBER.
(MILES LAUGHS)
MAYA: OH.
MILES:
YEAH, I REMEMBER YOU.
MAYA:
RIGHT, YEAH, I'M WORKING ON
MY NOT WALKING INTO THINGS,
I SWEAR.
WHEN YOU'RE NOT WORKING ON
YOUR PIZZA DELIVERY CONS?
WELL, ALL MY FRIENDS GOT IN,
BUT I DIDN'T
BECAUSE THE DUMB BOUNCER THINKS
I'M UNDERAGE!
MILES:
WELL...
I CAN GET YOU INSIDE.
YOU'RE WITH THE BAND?
ISH.
YOU WANT A DRAG?
YOU SEEM ANXIOUS.
WELL, THAT'S VERY PEER
PRESSURE-Y OF YOU.
(LAUGHS)
I'M MILES... HOLLINGSWORTH.
MATLIN. MAYA MATLIN.
YOU WANNA WATCH
THE CONCERT BACKSTAGE,
MATLIN, MAYA MATLIN?
YEAH, SURE. SURE!
UM, CAN MY FRIENDS
COME TOO?
SURE.
OKAY!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
♪♪♪
♪ If this is all I ever see
on this crowded street ♪
♪ Like no one's watching you
to play the act of fooling me ♪
♪ You made me dance in public ♪
♪ Trippin' on my own two feet ♪
♪ Just like a drum my heart
is jumping like a trampoline ♪
♪ No, I don't want to lay
my worries at the angry sea ♪
♪ Having a good old time ♪
♪ Livin' on the edge
of my seat ♪
MAKE YOURSELVES
AT HOME.
WOW! FIRST THIS,
THEN FRANCE!
WHAT AN AMAZING START
TO THE SUMMER!
I KNOW,
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
I'M BACKSTAGE
AT A ROCK CONCERT
WITH ZOE RIVAS!
I AM THE ONE WHO GOT YOU
BACKSTAGE, YOU KNOW!
ZOE:
OOH! GREEN IS NOT
YOUR COLOUR.
AND BESIDES,
ISN'T YOUR NEW BOYFRIEND,
THE ONE WITH
THE BACKSTAGE PASS?
MAYA:
HE'S NOT MY BOYFRIEND,
HE'S JUST SOME GUY I MET.
MILES:
(CHUCKLES) YOU FLATTER ME.
TRISTAN:
MAYA'S ALWAYS GOT SOME POOR DUDE
ON THE HOOK.
ZOE:
HAH! SHE'S ONE OF THOSE GIRLS?
TRISTAN:
OH, SHE TOTALLY IS!
LAST YEAR SHE HAD TWO GUYS
FIGHT OVER HER!
WHAT HAPPENED?
NOTHING!
ZOE:
IT'S LUCKY YOU FOUND ME!
IF MAYA DITCHES YOU
FOR SOME PARIS BOY,
I'M RIGHT HERE.
"WEST DRIVE" IS HUGE IN FRANCE
AND THAT MEANS MEGA-PERKS!
EVEN THOUGH YOUR CHARACTER'S
OFF THE SHOW NOW?
WHAT?!
NO, THAT-
THAT CAN'T BE TRUE!
THEY'RE KILLING OFF
HER CHARACTER,
IT IS TRUE.
KATIE READ IT
ON THAT BLOG.
OW!
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
(BUZZING,
MUSIC STOPS)
SO CLUMSY.
WHOA! WHAT'S GOING ON
BACK HERE?
UM, HE'S WITH THE BAND!
SECURITY GUARD:
NO, HE'S NOT.
DON'T YOU DARE MOVE,
ANY OF YOU!
ZOE:
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT!
(LIGHTER CLICKS)
♪♪♪
♪ In the groove ♪
♪ Let your hair down ♪
♪ The way you move ♪
♪ Brings them around ♪
ELI:
HELLO, MILADY.
HIYA. NICE FACE.
ELI:
NICE FACE YOURSELF.
SO, UH, HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
GOOD.
I ACTUALLY JUST FINISHED
PACKING FOR PARIS.
(LAUGHS)
WOULD YOU LIKE TO SEE THIS
NEW PIECE OF CLOTHING I BOUGHT?
UH...
SURE, YEAH.
♪ Make my body burn
with desire ♪
♪ You're so hot it hurts ♪
♪ Feels so right ♪
♪ I toss and turn
and sweat it out ♪
♪ Keep me up all night ♪
WHOA!
♪ Got a fever,
Got a fever ♪
OH.
♪ Gonna keep me up
all night ♪
♪ Got a fever,
Got a fever ♪
ELI:
UM...
I'M NOT EXACTLY SURE
WHAT'S SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN NEXT.
I COULD TAKE OFF MY PANTS.
UH, Y-YEAH, OKAY.
UH, YOU SHOULD TAKE
SOMETHING OFF TOO!
ELI:
R-RIGHT, YEAH.
OF COURSE, YEAH!
(KNOCKING,
DOORKNOB RATTLES)
HELEN:
CLARE, HONEY,
ARE YOU STILL AWAKE?
UM, SORRY, IT'S JUST A-
IT'S JUST A BAD TIME!
HELEN:
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU
DOWNSTAIRS, PLEASE.
THE HOSPITAL CALLED.
UM, I-I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
THE HOSPITAL?
IT'S-IT'S NOTHING.
BE RIGHT THERE!
(SIGHS)
ALL:
♪ CHARGE! ♪
♪♪♪
CHARGE!
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
(FINAL STRAINS OF SONG PLAY)
FEFE DOBSON:
THANK YOU!
SO, BECKY, YOU'LL BE
LIFE-GUARDING ALL SUMMER?
WHAT ARE YOUR
CO-WORKERS LIKE?
ALL OLD GIRLFRIENDS?
NO, ACTUALLY.
IT'S MOSTLY GUYS.
THEY'RE SO FUNNY.
NOT AS FUNNY AS ME THOUGH,
RIGHT?
OW! OOH!
I THINK I SPRAINED
MY ANKLE.
ADAM, CAN YOU GET ME
SOME ICE?
I'LL BE BACK
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
IMOGEN:
SO YOU'LL BE SURROUNDED
BY GUYS ALL SUMMER?
THAT'S PRETTY TEMPTING.
YOU'LL ALSO BE SURROUNDED
BY A BUNCH OF BOYS.
YEAH, BUT THE ONLY ONE
WHO'S NOT TOTALLY REVOLTING
IS ADAM.
YOU STILL LIKE GIRLS,
RIGHT?
I'M OPEN-MINDED,
LIKE YOU.
WELL, THEN YOU BETTER OPEN
YOUR MIND TO THE FACT
THAT ADAM HAS A GIRLFRIEND.
ADAM:
IMMY, HERE'S YOUR ICE.
WHOA!
WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
LET'S GO SOMEWHERE
PRIVATE.
WHATEVER YOU SAID,
THANK YOU!
YOU'RE THE BEST!
♪♪♪
HELEN:
THE DOCTOR CALLED.
HE SAID THE LUMP ON YOUR BACK
IS...
(MURMURING QUIETLY)
♪♪♪
YOU HAVE TO GO
TO THE HOSPITAL TOMORROW.
YOU'RE GONNA START
CHEMOTHERAPY.
YOU HAVE TO PACK A BAG.
(SOBS)
TRISTAN:
WHAT IF I GO TO JAIL?
IF THEY CALL THE POLICE,
THERE'S NO WAY I'M GETTING
ON THAT PLANE TO PARIS!
(MR. HOLLINGSWORTH SIGHS)
HEY, DAD.
OKAY, MILES,
YOU COME WITH ME.
EVERYONE ELSE CAN
GO HOME.
COME ON
TRISTAN:
OH, THANK GOD.
WELL, IT'S 11:15.
DO THINK YOU HAVE TIME
TO MAKE IT HOME FOR CURFEW?
NOT LIKE YOU CARE!
YOU'VE ALREADY FOUND SOMEONE
TO REPLACE TORI
THAT'S BETTER THAN ME!
I CAN'T WAIT TO GET DITCHED
ALL OVER PARIS!
UH, I WOULD NEVER
DITCH YOU!
YOU DID TONIGHT.
I KNOW.
LOOK, I THOUGHT IT
WOULD BE EASIER
IF I HAD ANOTHER FRIEND
BECAUSE I WORRY ABOUT YOU
DITCHING ME.
FOR SOME STUPID GUY?
TRIS, I WOULD NEVER!
WELL, WE BETTER CALL YOU
A CAB, ASAP.
DO YOU HAVE ANY MONEY,
OR...?
NO!
(MILES SIGHS)
MILES: TAKE THIS.
TRISTAN: WHOA!
THIS PIN IS 1562.
THANK YOU!
OKAY, LET'S GO!
(DOOR CLICKS OPEN AND SHUT)
(ELI CLEARS HIS THROAT)
SORRY, I DIDN'T THINK
IT WOULD TAKE SO LONG.
OH, NO, NO PROBLEM!
UM, ANYWAY, UM...
WHERE WERE WE?
OH! UH, SORRY!
CAN WE TAKE A RAIN CHECK?
I HAVE TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING.
THE LUMP ON MY BACK
TESTED POSITIVE
FOR RHABDOMYOSARCOMA.
I HAVE CANCER.
I'M COMING HOME.
NO, DON'T!
NO, I'LL GET ON
THE NEXT RED EYE,
OR I'LL FIND A BUS.
LIKE IT WON'T TAKE ME-
CLARE:
DON'T, PLEASE!
I HAVE TO START
CHEMOTHERAPY TREATMENT.
I WILL BE SITTING IN
A HOSPITAL BED FOR SIX WEEKS,
DOING NOTHING.
YOU CAN'T QUIT YOUR DREAM JOB
TO COME SIT AROUND WITH ME!
CLARE...
I WILL BE SO MAD
IF YOU COME.
I LOVE YOU.
I KNOW.
I'M GONNA BE OKAY.
(CAR RUMBLES)
(DOOR CLICKS SHUT,
KEYS JINGLE)
(CLOCK CHIMES)
MRS. MATLIN: AHEM.
MAYA: (GASPS SHARPLY)
MOM? PLEASE DON'T BE MAD!
I'M ONLY TWENTY MINUTES LATE.
OH, IT'S NOT ABOUT
THE MINUTES.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT YOU,
YOU'RE-
IS THAT MARIJUANA
I'M SMELLING?!
IT-IT WASN'T MINE.
CLEARLY YOU ARE NOT
RESPONSIBLE ENOUGH
TO SPEND THE SUMMER
ON YOUR OWN!
NO! NO, NO, NO, MOM,
PLEASE!
BLOWING CURFEW
WASN'T MY FAULT!
I FULLY INTENDED
TO LEAVE ON TIME!
MRS. MATLIN: BUT?
MAYA: BUT THERE WAS THIS GUY,
HE SAID HE COULD
GET US BACKSTAGE -
IT WAS HIS MARIJUANA -
AND THEN WE ENDED UP
IN CONCERT JAIL!
MRS. MATLIN:
SO YOU WENT OFF WITH A GUY
WHO WAS ON DRUGS?
OKAY, I KNOW
THAT SOUNDS BAD-
MRS. MATLIN:
THAT'S THE FIRST REASONABLE
THING YOU'VE SAID!
MAYA:
MOM, TRISTAN, MY ONLY FRIEND
IN THE WORLD NOW,
IS GOING TO PARIS!
YOU CAN'T RUIN MY LIFE
OVER SOMETHING SO STUPID!
MRS. MATLIN:
I CAN'T LET YOU GO
TO PARIS!
YOU'RE BEHAVING LIKE SOME...
SOME TROUBLED YOUNG GIRL!
THIS IS NOT FAIR!
MRS. MATLIN: MAYA-
MAYA: I HATE YOU!
THAT WAS A LITTLE HARSH,
DON'T YOU THINK?
LIKE YOU'VE NEVER BLOWN
CURFEW BEFORE?
OH RIGHT,
YOU NEVER HAD ONE!
MAYA, WHEN I WAS 14,
I WAS PLAYING SOCCER
AND DOING SCHOOL STUFF,
NOT SMOKING WEED
WITH STRANGERS.
YOU WERE ADDICTED
TO PAINKILLERS.
YOU MESSED UP,
JUST FACE IT.
YOU DON'T THINK I SHOULD GO
TO PARIS, EITHER?
LET'S JUST TALK TOMORROW.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
♪♪♪