DETECTIVE:
CAN YOU TELL US ABOUT
THE INCIDENT THAT OCCURRED
AT MILES HOLLINGSWORTH'S PARTY
INVOLVING ZOE RIVAS?
I WASN'T THERE,
BUT I'VE DONE A LOT OF RESEARCH.
I BELIEVE ZOE WAS ASSAULTED
BY TWO BOYS IN THIS VIDEO.
NO ONE KNEW WHO THEY WERE,
BUT THEN SOMEONE SENT ME
SECURITY FOOTAGE
FROM THAT NIGHT.
THIS IS WINSTON CHU
AND THIS IS MILES HOLLINGSWORTH.
DETECTIVE:
ARE THOSE THE BOYS
WHO ASSAULTED YOU?
I DON'T KNOW.
DETECTIVE:
BUT YOU KNOW THESE BOYS?
YEAH.
I TRIED TO KISS MILES
AT THE PARTY...
I THINK.
DETECTIVE:
YOU THINK?
LOOK, I BLACKED OUT.
I REMEMBER BEING ALONE
WITH TWO GUYS,
BUT I HAVE NO IDEA
WHO THEY WERE
OR WHAT HAPPENED.
DETECTIVE:
IS THIS YOU IN THE VIDEO?
NO, I...
NO, I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING WRONG.
CAN I GO TO BASKETBALL PRACTICE?
THIS IS THE LAST ONE
BEFORE THE PLAYOFFS.
DETECTIVE:
ANSWER THE QUESTION.
WINSTON:
YES, IT'S US
IN THE SECURITY FOOTAGE.
WE CARRIED ZOE OFF
TO THE POOL HOUSE
SO SHE COULD SLEEP IT OFF.
BUT IT'S NOT US
IN THE ASSAULT VIDEO.
DETECTIVE:
I'VE SEEN SOME
PRETTY CONVINCING EVIDENCE.
IT'S WRONG!
I'M SORRY, DETECTIVE,
BUT... I CAN PROVE IT!
THERE'S A TIME CODE EMBEDDED
IN THE ASSAULT VIDEO -
10:15 P.M.
10:10 P.M., 10:16 P.M.,
ALL ACCOUNTED FOR.
FALSE ACCUSATIONS
ARE VERY SERIOUS.
I'M SO, SO SORRY.
I HONESTLY THOUGHT IT WAS THEM.
DETECTIVE:
WELL, WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO KEEP THESE.
OF COURSE.
(STEADYING BREATHS)
BUT IF IT WASN'T THEM,
WHO WAS IT?
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ (The best that I can be) ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
BECKY:
THIS IS CRAZY!
ARE THEY INTERVIEWING
EVERY GUY IN SCHOOL?
YEAH, EVERYONE
WHO WAS AT THE PARTY
AND EVERYONE
WHO TWEETED PICTURES.
THE WHOLE
BASKETBALL TEAM?
YEAH. ONE BY ONE.
(CRIES)
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
I NEVER SHOULD HAVE
GOTTEN INVOLVED.
I'M GONNA TAKE
MY EVIDENCE DOWN RIGHT NOW,
IF I'M EVEN WELCOME
IN THE STUDENT COUNCIL ROOM.
HEY, HEY.
IF ANYONE GIVES YOU
ANY PROBLEMS,
YOU JUST TELL 'EM
TO TALK TO YOUR BRO.
(HALF LAUGHS)
ALL RIGHT?
IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
NO, YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT IT'S LIKE FOR HER
RIGHT NOW.
STUDENT COUNCIL CAN'T POSSIBLY
STILL THROW A PEP RALLY!
DALLAS:
BUT THIS IS DEGRASSI'S
FIRST PLAYOFF BASKETBALL GAME
IN TWO SEASONS.
DREW:
YEAH. THE SCHOOL
SHOULD SUPPORT THE TEAM.
CLARE:
TWO OF WHOM
ARE SEXUAL PREDATORS.
DALLAS:
MILES WAS CLEARED.
THERE'S NO PROOF
THAT MY BOYS DID THIS.
CLARE:
THERE'S NO PROOF THEY DIDN'T.
DREW:
BUT THE POLICE HAVEN'T
PRESSED CHARGES.
THE WHOLE SCHOOL
SHOULDN'T BE PUNISHED
BECAUSE OF TWO IDIOTS.
IT WASN'T JUST TWO GUYS,
DREW!
EVERYONE AT THAT THIS PARTY
LET THIS HAPPEN.
YOU LET THIS HAPPEN.
IT'S JUST NOT THE RIGHT TIME
FOR A PEP RALLY.
WE SHOULDN'T EVEN
HAVE THE GAME.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
SORRY.
(SCOFFED LAUGHTER)
YOU DIDN'T MAKE THE VIDEO.
I GOT THE POLICE
INVOLVED.
I BROKE HER HEART.
ZOE WAS DRUNK AT THAT PARTY
'CAUSE OF ME.
(EXHALES, STRESSED)
BECKY:
OKAY, SO HOW DO WE FIX THIS?
TILL EVERYONE FINDS OUT
WHO WAS ACTUALLY
IN THAT VIDEO,
WE CAN'T.
MILES PLUS WINSTON
EQUALS...
NOT PERVS!
NOT PERVS.            HA-HA!
NOW I'M FREE TO FOCUS
ON THE BIG GAME.
YOU WANT FRONT ROW SEATS
SO YOU CAN CHEER ME ON?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
WHAT? WE'RE CLEARED,
SERIOUSLY.
CHEWY.
IN OFFICIAL
POLICE PARLANCE,
WE'RE "NO LONGER
PERSONS OF INTEREST."
I THOUGHT
YOU'D BE HAPPY.
MILES,
THEY CANCELLED
THE PEP RALLY.
WHAT? WHY?
BECAUSE OBVIOUSLY
THEY THINK
THE GUYS WERE ON
THE BASKETBALL TEAM.
WELL,
THEY COULDN'T HAVE BEEN.
BUT IT IS YOU
IN THOSE PARTY PHOTOS,
ISN'T IT,
CARRYING ZOE, HALF-NAKED,
THROUGH THE PARTY?
LOOK,
I ALREADY TOLD YOU-
YOU DIDN'T GROPE HER.
BUT WHAT ELSE HAPPENED?
WHY WERE YOU WITH HER?
(SIGHS)
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING WRONG!
TWO GUYS MADE THE VIDEO.
IT COULD'VE BEEN ANY TWO!
DREW:
SO WHAT, WE NEED TO FIND
EVERY PICTURE
WITH, WHAT, TWO GUYS IN IT?!
BECKY: BINGO!
IMOGEN: GUYS!
IMOGEN:
DON'T YOU THINK THE POLICE HAVE
ALREADY THOUGHT ABOUT OF THIS?
BECKY:
WELL, ISN'T IT OUR DUTY TO HELP
AS CONCERNED CITIZENS?
WHY DO YOU EVEN CARE?
YOU BARELY KNOW ZOE.
BECKY:
WELL, WHAT IF IT HAD BEEN ME?
IMOGEN:
YOU DON'T DRINK.
BECKY:
WHAT IF I TRIED?
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO DRINK.
WHAT IF I HAD PASSED OUT
AT THAT PARTY?
WHAT IF YOU DID?
LOOK, GUYS,
EVERYONE IS BEING BLAMED.
ALL RIGHT,
THAT ANONYMOUS JERK,
THE WATCHER,
HAS BEEN POSTING PHOTOS
OF EVERY GUY IN THE SCHOOL
WITH THE LABEL "RAPIST"
ON IT, ALL RIGHT?
INCLUDING ME!
AND THOSE GUYS,
THE REAL GUYS
WHO DID THIS TO ZOE,
THEY'RE STILL OUT THERE.
OKAY.
SO WE'RE LOOKING
AT ALL THE PICTURES
WITH TWO GUYS TOGETHER.
OKAY.
DOCTOR:
ZOE...
THIS IS A DELICATE SITUATION,
BUT I HAVE YOUR RESULTS.
WOULD YOU LIKE ME TO CALL
YOUR MOTHER IN?
UNLESS I'M DYING,
SHE CAN STAY
IN THE WAITING ROOM.
DOCTOR:
ARE YOU SURE?
OKAY. WELL, THERE'S NO EVIDENCE
OF PREGNANCY YET.
WE'VE TESTED FOR
THE STANDARD STIS AND HIV.
BUT EVEN IF THE RESULTS
ARE NEGATIVE NOW,
WE'LL HAVE TO RETEST
IN A FEW MONTHS.
IS THAT REALLY NECESSARY?
DOCTOR:
YOUR EXAM SHOWED SIGNS
OF TRAUMA TO THE VAGINAL AREA.
I WAS RAPED?
DOCTOR:
LIKELY NOT INTERCOURSE...
BUT THERE WAS INSERTION.
IF YOU'D COME IN SOONER,
WE COULD HAVE HAD
A CLEARER PICTURE.
HEY, CUTIE!
WHERE ARE WE EATING LUNCH?
FRANKIE:
I WAS HEADED TO THE CAF,
BUT, UM,
MAYBE WE CAN EAT OUTSIDE.
WHY?
PEOPLE ARE MAD AT YOU.
AT ME?
THE PEP RALLY GOT CANCELLED
'CAUSE OF THE ACCUSATIONS.
WHICH I DIDN'T MAKE.
BUT EVERYONE THINKS
YOU DID.
THEY SAY...
WHAT?
THEY SAY YOU HAD SEX
WITH THOSE GUYS
AND REGRETTED IT,
SO YOU CRIED RAPE.
YOU DON'T BELIEVE THAT,
DO YOU?
THAT IS SORTA WHAT HAPPENED
WITH DREW,
AND YOU WERE WALKING
AROUND THAT PARTY
SAYING YOU WANTED
TO MAKE OUT WITH GUYS.
SO WHAT,
I WAS ASKING FOR IT?!
YOU TOO, HUH?
GO AHEAD,
EAT LUNCH WITHOUT ME.
I'LL BE FINE
ON MY OWN.
BECKY:
THESE ARE THE PAIRS OF GUYS
WHO WERE SEEN TOGETHER
AT THE PARTY.
NOW WHAT DO WE DO?
BECKY: I DON'T KNOW.
GRACE: I DO.
DON'T WORRY,
I ALREADY KNOW ABOUT
YOUR LITTLE ROGUES' GALLERY.
UM, WHO ARE YOU?
DEFENDER OF JUSTICE,
FRIEND TO THE LITTLE GUY.
IMOGEN:
WAIT, THAT'S THE WATCHER'S
TWITTER BIO.
YOU'RE THE WATCHER?!
DREW:
YOU'RE A JERK.
YOU'RE THE REASON
I MADE A FALSE ACCUSATION
TO THE POLICE.
I KNOW,
AND I WANNA FIX THAT.
WHY SHOULD WE TRUST YOU?
GRACE:
I'M LETTING YOU KNOW
MY REAL IDENTITY.
DEFEATS THE PURPOSE
OF BEING ANONYMOUS.
OKAY, WHAT DO WE DO?
GRACE:
SEND AN ANONYMOUS EMAIL
TO ONE GUY FROM EACH PAIR.
SAY SOMETHING LIKE,
"I KNOW IT WAS YOU
WHO ASSAULTED ZOE.
YOUR BUDDY ALREADY
RATTED YOU OUT."
THEN WE WAIT
AND WATCH.
WAIT FOR WHAT?
ONE OF THOSE DUDES
TO CONFRONT HIS BUDDY.
NOBODY LIKES A SNITCH.
QUICK LEARNER.
GOLD STAR FOR YOU.
THIS'LL REALLY WORK?
GRACE:
IF NOT, I'VE GOT SOME
OTHER TRICKS UP MY SLEEVE.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
DALLAS: (PA ANNOUNCEMENT)
DUE TO UNFORESEEN CIRCUMSTANCES
THE PLAYOFF PEP RALLY
HAS BEEN CANCELLED,
HOWEVER,
THE GAME GOES ON.
COME OUT
AND CHEER ON OUR BOYS.
GO PANTHERS!
I PAID YOUR PARTNER
TO SWITCH WITH ME.
YOU'RE MINE FOR THE HOUR.
I JUST WANNA WORK
ON MY ASSIGNMENT.
OKAY, LOOK,
I KNOW LIFE SUCKS FOR YOU,
BUT I NEED YOU
TO TELL MAYA
THAT NOTHING HAPPENED
BETWEEN US.
SO YOU WANT ME
TO SEND HER A MEMO?
YEAH,
OR JUST TALK TO HER.
I NEED THINGS
TO GO BACK TO NORMAL.
DO YOU KNOW
WHAT IT'S LIKE
NOT KNOWING
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
IF SOMEONE TOUCHED YOU?
YEAH, I CAN'T IMAGINE,
BUT THAT'S NOT MY FAULT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
KIND OF IS.
(SCOFFS)
I DID NOTHING.
EXACTLY!
YOU SAW HOW DRUNK I WAS
AND YOU DID NOTHING.
LEFT ME SOMEWHERE.
WHAT WAS I SUPPOSED TO DO?
SOMETHING, ANYTHING!
MADE SURE I WAS SAFE.
YOU LET THEM
DO THIS TO ME!
IMOGEN:
SEE ANYTHING WEIRD?
BECKY:
YEAH, THESE TWO,
BUT SO FAR NO REACTION.
IMOGEN:
WELL, MY GUYS LOOKED
REALLY CONFUSED,
SO IT OBVIOUSLY WASN'T THEM.
BECKY:
DON'T WORRY. I'M PRETTY SURE
IT'S THESE TWO DIRTBAGS.
NEIL:
WHAT THE HELL, BRO?!
YOU SAID
WE WERE GONNA KEEP QUIET!
LUKE:
'KAY, DUDE, CHILL OUT!
LOOK, I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING
TO ANYBODY.
WHAT HAPPENED?
NEIL:
SOMEONE EMAILED ME
THIS MORNING
AND THEY'RE SAYING
THAT YOU TOLD THEM.
LUKE: TOLD 'EM WHAT?
NEIL: TOLD THEM WHAT WE DID.
OH MY GOSH.
BECKY...
NO. NO.
LUKE, LUKE COULDN'T HAVE
BEEN INVOLVED.
THOSE ARE THE ONLY TWO
THAT REACTED.
YEAH,
BUT HE'S MY BROTHER.
HE ALREADY TALKED
TO THE POLICE.
HE'S BEEN CLEARED.
SO HAS EVERYONE,
BASICALLY.
IT DIDN'T SOUND LIKE HIM
IN THE VIDEO.
IT DIDN'T SOUND LIKE ANYONE,
IT SOUNDED LIKE A ROBOT.
OKAY, THEN MAYBE
IT WAS A ROBOT.
EVERYONE'S SCARED,
BECKS,
AND THAT GRACE GIRL
IS GONNA FIND OUT ANYWAY.
JUST LET ME
TALK TO HIM, OKAY?
LUKE:
LOOK, DUDE,
I DIDN'T TELL A SINGLE PERSON.
HONESTLY, JUST CHILL OUT.
WE'RE FINE.
NOBODY HERE KNOWS.
JUST... I'LL TALK TO YOU
AFTER SCHOOL, ALL RIGHT?
JUST SHUT UP.
AH! YOU CREEPER,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
UM, I FORGOT
MY SCIENCE PROJECT.
UM, CAN I BORROW YOUR PHONE
TO CALL MOM
TO COME BRING IT?
WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR PHONE?
I FORGOT IT TOO!
(WITH A LAUGH)
I'M SO FORGETFUL.
(SIGHS)
THANKS.
YEAH.
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
(LUKE AND NEIL LAUGH ON VIDEO)
HEY, ISN'T MOM AT A PLAY
WITH GRANDMA THIS AFTERNOON?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
LUKE: (ON VIDEO)
(LAUGHS) DUDE, ONE MORE,
ONE MORE. GO.
LUKE:
HEY, WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
TELL ME
THIS ISN'T YOU.
BECKY-
TELL ME WHAT I'M SEEING
ISN'T REAL.
OKAY, LOOK,
IT'S NOT LIKE IT SEEMS.
SHE KISSED US.
SHE WAS INTO IT.
SHE WAS TOO DRUNK!
SHE KEPT ON ASKING US
IF WE THOUGHT SHE WAS SEXY.
SHE WANTED TO FOOL AROUND
WITH US.
LUKE...
LOOK, BECKY,
I WOULD NEVER HURT ANYONE.
YOU'VE GOTTA BELIEVE ME.
JUST GIVE ME BACK MY PHONE.
CLASS IS GONNA START SOON.
I CAN'T.
WHAT, YOU'D SHOW THE VIDEO
TO THE POLICE?
I'M YOUR BROTHER.
WHOSE SIDE ARE YOU ON?
I HAVEN'T DECIDED YET.
(REPEATED THUDS)
(OUT OF BREATH)
CAN I HELP YOU?
YEAH.
BY DROPPING
THIS WHOLE THING.
I'M NOT ALLOWED
TO WORKOUT NOW?
NO, THE ACCUSATIONS.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO DO
ANYTHING WRONG.
YOU...
LOOK, WE WERE PARTYING,
WE WERE HAVING FUN.
YOU LIKED IT.
I DON'T REMEMBER IT.
SO CAN'T WE JUST FORGET IT?
HOW?
LUKE:
WE JUST...
WE JUST PUT IT BEHIND US,
PRETEND THAT IT NEVER HAPPENED.
LOOK, NO ONE'S GONNA
BELIEVE YOU ANYWAYS.
I'M A GOOD CHRISTIAN GUY,
I'M A HOCKEY STAR,
I'M ON THE BASKETBALL TEAM.
LOOK, YOU'RE GONNA RUIN MY LIFE
IF YOU KEEP THIS UP.
MINE'S ALREADY RUINED!
YEAH, BUT THAT'S BECAUSE PEOPLE
THINK THAT SOMETHING HAPPENED.
I WILL TELL THEM
THAT IT DIDN'T.
I WILL TELL PEOPLE
THAT IT DIDN'T GO ANY FURTHER
THAN THE VIDEO.
LOOK, PEOPLE WILL FINALLY
SHUT UP ABOUT THIS THING,
AND THEN WE CAN FORGET IT
AND MOVE ON.
BOTH OF US.
PLEASE.
(EMOTIONAL BREATH)
DALLAS:
ALL RIGHT, BOYS,
THIS IS IT.
THE PLAYOFFS.
LET'S HUSTLE HARD
OUT THERE!
PANTHERS:
YEAH! (APPLAUSE)
TRISTAN:
I'D HUSTLE A WHOLE LOT MORE
IF WE WERE STILL GETTING
OUR PEP RALLY.
MILES:
WHO CARES ABOUT THE PEP RALLY?
TRISTAN:
I JUST WANTED TO JUMP THROUGH
THAT FLAMING RING
WHILE THE CROWD CHEERED!
MILES:
EVEN WHEN SOMEONE ON THIS TEAM
ASSAULTED ZOE?!
LUKE:
WELL, THERE'S STILL NO PROOF.
MILES:
COME ON,
THE GUY IN THE VIDEO
IS WEARING A BASKETBALL JACKET.
ANYONE COULD'VE PICKED ONE UP.
MILES:
YEAH, THAT IS CRAP
AND YOU KNOW IT!
SO WHO DID IT?
HUH?!
DALLAS:
ENOUGH OF THIS, SHERLOCK.
WE'RE A TEAM!
WE STICK TOGETHER!
SORRY, I CAN'T.
PLAYER:
COME ON, MAN.
DALLAS:
FORGET HIM.
WE'LL CHANGE UP THE OFFENSE.
WE'VE GOT A GAME TO WIN.
(HUM OF CHATTER)
FRANKIE:
MILES! WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
YOU GOING TO THE GAME?
I OVERREACTED EARLIER.
NO, YOU DIDN'T.
'KAY, I SCREWED UP, MAYA.
I KNOW THAT.
I'M SO SORRY.
SHOULDN'T YOU BE
WARMING UP?
(SNORTED CHUCKLE)
NO, I'M NOT PLAYING
WITH THOSE JERKS.
THEY DON'T CARE
WHAT HAPPENED TO ZOE.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
WAIT. DON'T YOU WANT
TO SEE THOSE JERKS
GET THEIR ASSES HANDED TO THEM
WITHOUT YOU?
COME ON.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
HOME. DUH!
WELL, WE JUST WANTED
TO MAKE SURE YOU'RE OKAY.
YOU KNOW, AFTER EVERYTHING
THAT HAPPENED.
ZOE:
IT WAS JUST A JOKE VIDEO, MAYA,
THEN A RUMOUR RAN WILD.
REALLY?
HELL NO!
(CACOPHONY OF CHATTER,
ZOE'S HEELS CLACK QUICKLY)
LUKE:
(STARTLED GRUNT)
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
MAKING AN ANNOUNCEMENT.
EVERYONE WANNA MEET MY CO-STAR
FROM THE VIDEO?
HERE HE IS!
LUKE:
YOU CAN'T JUST ACCUSE
SOMEONE OF...
THIS GIRL'S CRAZY!
ZOE:
I'M CRAZY?!
I WAS DRUNK AND HELPLESS
AND YOU ASSAULTED ME!
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU HAVE
ANY PROOF.
I DON'T NEED ANY PROOF
TO DO THIS!
(FIGHTING GRUNTS)
LUKE:
STOP! CALM DOWN!
LUKE: STOP! HEY!
BECKY: STOP! STOP!
YOU DON'T NEED TO DO THIS!
ZOE:
THERE'S NOTHING ELSE
I CAN DO!
BECKY:
THERE IS.
I HAVE PROOF IT WAS HIM.
LUKE:
BECKY, NO.
BECKY:
I HAVE HIS PHONE.
THERE'S MORE VIDEOS.
GIVE IT TO THE POLICE!
MILES:
HEY, HEY, BUD. STOP.
LUKE:
CHILL OUT FOR A SECOND.
MILES, LET GO.
I'M NOT... HEY!
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING!
SIMPSON:
HEY! THAT'S ENOUGH!
THAT'S ENOUGH! THAT'S ENOUGH!
EVERYONE, FREEZE!
COME ON, ENOUGH!
THAT'S ENOUGH!
CALM DOWN! CALM DOWN!
("Brave"
by Sara Bareilles plays)
♪ You can be amazing ♪
♪ You can turn a phrase
into a weapon or a drug ♪
♪ You can be the outcast ♪
♪ Or be the backlash
of somebody's lack of love ♪
♪ Or you can start
speaking up ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna hurt you
the way that words do ♪
♪ When they settle
'neath your skin ♪
♪ Kept on the inside
and no sunlight ♪
♪ Sometimes a shadow wins ♪
DREW:
HALF-SWEET, FAT-FREE,
MOCHA-FRAPPACINO, RIGHT?
♪ Say what you wanna say ♪
(SUSPICIOUSLY)
RIGHT...
WHAT'S GOING ON?
TRISTAN:
WE'RE HERE TO WALK YOU
TO CLASS,
SIT WITH YOU AT LUNCH,
AND BASICALLY MAKE SURE
NO ONE BUGS YOU.
MILES:
WE WANT YOU TO KNOW
YOU'RE NOT ALONE.
WE'VE GOT YOUR BACK.
♪ I wanna see you be brave ♪
MAYA:
YOU CAN BORROW HIM
FOR THE DAY.
♪ I just wanna see you ♪
THANKS, GUYS.
MEANS A LOT.
♪ I wanna see you be brave ♪
♪ I just wanna see you ♪
ONE SEC.
♪ Just wanna see you ♪
♪ I wanna see you be brave ♪
ZOE:
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I DIDN'T KNOW
HE WAS YOUR BROTHER.
THAT'S AWFUL.
IT'S NOT GONNA BE EASY,
BUT IT'S IMPORTANT
TO DO WHAT'S RIGHT.
♪ ...anything but empty ♪
♪ Why don't you tell them
the truth? ♪
♪ I wanna see you be brave ♪
♪ Just wanna see you ♪
♪ I just wanna see you ♪
♪ I wanna see you be brave ♪
(I wanna see you)