(MOANS)
(APPREHENSIVE BREATH)
(LIGHT KNOCK ON DOOR,
HANDLE CLICKS OPEN)
(STARTLED BREATH)
FRANKIE:
MARCELA SAID
YOU WERE IN HERE.
WHY AM I STILL
AT YOUR HOUSE?
FRANKIE:
I'M NO DETECTIVE,
BUT IT COULD'VE BEEN
ALL THE DRINKING
AT MILES' PARTY.
HUNTER:
UH, OUR HOUSEKEEPER SAID
THAT YOU SHOULD HAVE BREAKFAST.
BELGIAN WAFFLES!
ZOE:
WHAT DID I DO LAST NIGHT?
WHAT DIDN'T YOU DO?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
HERE'S YOU DANCING
ON A TABLE.
THAT'S YOU BARFING
IN THE SHRUBS.
I'M PRETTY SURE
THAT'S A STRIPTEASE.
HUNTER:
WHOA.
I DON'T REMEMBER
ANY OF THAT.
HUNTER:
YEAH, WELL,
EVERYONE ELSE DOES.
AND YOU'RE GETTING
CHIRPED ONLINE, SO.
CAN YOU GO GET READY
FOR SCHOOL
AND LET THE POOR GIRL
GET DRESSED?
SORRY ABOUT
MY DUMB TWIN.
HE WAS FORMED
ON THE DORK SIDE
OF THE WOMB.
PEOPLE NEED TO GET A LIFE.
FRANKIE:
SERIOUSLY.
SO I GUESS
WE'RE NOT PERFORMING
IN THE DEGRASSI SING-OFF
ANYMORE?
WHY?
ARE YOU QUITTING ON ME?
YOU SERIOUSLY THINK
THEY'LL VOTE FOR US AFTER THIS?
REMEMBER WHEN I WAS ALL OVER
THE TABLOIDS
FOR FALLING OFF THAT HORSE
AT THE ROYAL WINTER FAIR?
FRANKIE: NO.
ZOE: EXACTLY!
'CAUSE A WEEK LATER
I WON A TEEN CHOICE AWARD
AND MY DELIGHTFUL SPEECH
ERASED ANY MEMORY
OF MY FACE-PLANT
INTO THE HORSE CRAP.
SO WE STILL HAVE
REHEARSAL?
ZOE:
YES! AND ONCE EVERYONE
SEES ME SINGING
AND DANCING MY HEART OUT,
THEY'LL FORGET ALL ABOUT...
WHATEVER THE HELL I DID
LAST NIGHT!
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ (The best that I can be) ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
BECKY, UM,
I'VE GOT YOU COVERING
THE DEGRASSI SING-OFF!
MUSIC! YAY!
ACTUALLY,
I HAVE A PITCH!
"TEENS AND ALCOHOL -
A BAD MIX!"
BUT YOU'VE NEVER EVEN
HAD A DRINK.
DOESN'T MEAN I DON'T KNOW
HOW BAD IT IS!
BECKY:
I MEAN SHE PRACTICALLY
STRIPPED NAKED AT A PARTY,
IN FRONT OF EVERYONE!
SO YOU WANT TO SCOLD PEOPLE
FOR DRINKING...
ON OUR AIRWAVES.
BECKY:
I WANNA WARN THEM.
GIRLS HAVE TO KNOW
IF THEY GET DRUNK,
THAT THEY'RE RESPONSIBLE
FOR THEIR ACTIONS.
IT'S PRETTY CONTROVERSIAL.
I'D WANT SIMPSON
TO APPROVE IT.
PLEASE, IMOGEN,
I CAN HANDLE THIS.
YOU'RE REALLY READY
FOR PEOPLE TO STOP SEEING YOU
AS BRIGHT AND BUBBLY
BECKY BAKER?
BIG TIME!
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
DALLAS: (PA ANNOUNCEMENT)
CONGRATULATIONS TO THE PANTHERS
FOR MAKING IT
TO THE PLAYOFFS
FOR THE FIRST TIME
IN TWO SEASONS.
YOU ROCK!
I HAVE GOOD NEWS.
I, UH, MADE UP
WITH MY DAD.
SHOULD I BUY YOU A MEDAL?
'KAY, COME ON.
YOU CAN'T STILL BE MAD.
WINSTON:
OH, I THINK SHE'S STILL MAD.
MAYA:
WE PLANNED A ROMANTIC NIGHT
TOGETHER, MILES,
THEN YOU THREW A PARTY!
DIDN'T I ALREADY APOLOGIZE
FOR THAT?
YES, AND IT WAS NOT ACCEPTED.
WAS NOT ACCEPTED...
HOW 'BOUT NOW?
WOW. OKAY, YOU CAN'T JUST BUY
MY FORGIVENESS.
IT'S ALWAYS WORKED ON ME.
MILES:
YEAH. PLEASE, MAYA,
I CAN'T FOCUS ON BASKETBALL
IF YOU'RE MAD AT ME.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
WHAT?
WE'RE IN THE PLAYOFFS!
MAYA:
(ANNOYED SIGH)
COME ON.
ZOE:
♪ LET'S GET PHYSICAL,
PHYSICAL ♪
♪ I WANNA GET PHYSICAL ♪
♪ LET'S GET INTO PHYSICAL ♪
♪ LET ME HEAR
YOUR BODY TALK ♪
♪ YOUR BODY TALK ♪
♪ LET ME HEAR YOUR BODY TALK ♪
FRANKIE:
WOW! YOU'RE, LIKE,
ACTUALLY AMAZING.
HMM. AND IT'S TIME
THE REST OF THE SCHOOL KNOWS IT.
JUST ONE TINY QUESTION.
YOU EXPECT ME
TO LEARN ALL THAT?
KEISHA, TOO,
IF SHE EVER SHOWS.
SORRY, I GOT HELD UP
DEFENDING YOU.
FROM WHAT?
FRANKIE:
PEOPLE ARE SAYING
YOU DID STUFF WITH THIS GUY.
"STUFF"?
ARE WE BABIES?
LIKE SEX.
DO YOU TWO REALLY THINK
I HAVE SEX WITH RANDOM GUYS
AT PARTIES?
ISN'T THAT WHAT YOU DID
WITH DREW?
OKAY, HANDS UP
IF YOU'VE HAD SEX.
SO WHICH ONE OF US
WOULD KNOW
IF SHE HAD SEX LAST NIGHT
OR NOT?
FRANKIE AND KEISHA:
YOU.
ZOE:
AND I ASSURE YOU,
I DID NOT.
GET THESE STUPID RUMOURS
OUT OF YOUR TINY BRAINS,
SO YOU'VE GOT ROOM IN THERE
TO LEARN THIS SONG!
PLACES!
(SNAPS FINGERS) BEHIND ME.
LET'S GO, COME ON!
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT.
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR,
LUKE:
YOU STILL THINKING OF GETTING
THAT TATTOO ON YOUR BUTT,
DALLAS?
(PLAYERS LAUGH)
IT'S TIME FOR THE MIKE DALLAS
SLOP SHOW, ROUND TWO!
DALLAS:
ALL RIGHT, JUST...
JUST WATCH.
FROM ME SITTIN' HERE,
OFF THE SCREEN...
BOOM! DONE.
SHOT, AFTER SHOT, AFTER SHOT,
YOU KNOW?!
HOLLINGSWORTH!
MILES:
MAN, WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
DALLAS:
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
YOU'RE ACTING ALL SPACED OUT.
PLAY LIKE THAT
IN A PLAYOFF GAME,
WE'RE OUT FIRST ROUND.
MILES:
MAN, MAYA'S STILL PISSED AT ME
FOR THROWING THAT PARTY.
LUKE:
HEY, BUT IT WAS AMAZING.
NEIL:
AH, KILLER!
SAW SOMEONE EAT A LIVE FISH
OUTTA YOUR FISH TANK.
LUKE:
(LAUGHING) OH YEAH!
MILES:
WELL, APPARENTLY IT'S NOT
MY GIRLFRIEND'S CUP OF TEA.
SO APOLOGIZE.
MILES:
YEAH, I TRIED.
NEIL:
DID YOU GET HER A GIFT?
MILES:
AN EXPENSIVE ONE.
DIDN'T WORK.
TRISTAN:
(SCOFFS) AMATEURS.
YOU NEED A GRAND GESTURE.
DALLAS AND MILES:
(SNORTED CHUCKLE)
MILES:
A WHAT?
SOMETHING BIG,
SOMETHING PUBLIC,
SOMETHING THAT SAYS
"I'M VULNERABLE,
BUT I LIKE YOU SO MUCH
I'M WILLING TO WORK
FOR YOUR FORGIVENESS."
MMM...
THAT SOUNDS LIKE A LOT OF WORK.
TRISTAN:
WHAT, THERE'S LIKE FIVE OF US?
I SAY WE BRAINSTORM.
MILES?
IF YOU REALLY THINK
IT'S GONNA WORK, SURE.
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, FIVE MINUTES
AND THEN WE PRACTICE.
LUKE:
SERIOUSLY?
WE'RE A TEAM;
WE HELP EACH OTHER OUT.
TRISTAN:
BEST BASKETBALL PRACTICE EVER!
GUYS:
(LAUGH)
BECKY:
WHAT'S THE MOST
YOU'VE EVER HAD TO DRINK?
THIS INTERVIEW
IS FOR DEGRASSI TV, RIGHT?
SO THE WHOLE SCHOOL'S
GONNA SEE THIS?
BECKY:
YEAH!
THEN, ZERO.
ZERO DRINKS.
BECKY:
WOW! WE'RE MORE ALIKE
THAN I THOUGHT.
STAY STRONG, SISTER!
MR. PRESIDENT!
WE'VE ALL HEARD THE STORIES.
WHAT'S THE CRAZIEST THING
YOU'VE EVER DONE ON ALCOHOL?
UH... I-I DON'T DRINK.
BECKY:
OH REALLY, I THOUGHT THAT
ONE TIME WHEN YOU-
UH, CONCUSSIONS!
PEOPLE THINK I'M DRUNK,
BUT I'M STONE SOBER.
BECKY:
EVEN WHEN YOU'RE AT PARTIES,
BEING SO LOUD AND -
NO OFFENSE - DUMB?
I GUESS I'M JUST A LOUD,
DUMB GUY!
BECKY:
THERE'S GOTTA BE SOMEBODY
WHO'LL TALK TO ME
FOR THIS STORY.
AH, DALLAS!
WHAT'S YOUR FAVOURITE THING
ABOUT DRINKING?
WHAT'S THERE NOT TO LIKE?
DREW:
YOU KNOW THIS IS
FOR DEGRASSI TV, RIGHT?
CLARE:
IT'S GONNA AIR
IN FRONT OF THE SCHOOL,
AND ONLINE,
PROBABLY FOREVER.
OH, YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT ALCOHOL?
NEVER TOUCH THE STUFF.
THIS BODY'S A TEMPLE!
(CAMERA BEEPS)
WHY SO GLUM, SIS?
YOU'RE MY BROTHER,
SO I KNOW YOU'LL BE HONEST.
AM I COMPLETELY CLUELESS?
UH, DON'T ANSWER THAT.
I'M TRYING TO GET
THIS SEGMENT FOR DTV
AND I CAN'T FIND
A SINGLE TEENAGER WHO DRINKS.
BECKY,
IF I TOSSED A BALL OUT HERE,
IT WOULD HIT ONE
IN FIVE SECONDS.
BUT I INTERVIEWED
15 PEOPLE!
DREW, DALLAS, CLARE...
(SCOFFS)
I'VE SEEN ALL OF THEM DRINK.
SO THEY LIED TO ME?
LUKE:
WELL, YOU MIGHT NOT BE
THE BEST INTERVIEWER.
YOU'RE TOO NICE.
I WANNA PROVE THAT
I CAN BE A SERIOUS JOURNALIST.
WELL, YOU'VE SEEN
ALL THOSE PICTURES
FROM MILES' PARTY,
RIGHT?
YEAH, EVERYONE HAS.
YEAH, WELL,
THOSE ARE CLEARLY DRUNK PEOPLE.
ESPECIALLY THAT ZOE GIRL.
YES,
SO FIND ONE OF THEM,
CONFRONT THEM,
AND DON'T LET UP
UNTIL THEY GIVE YOU ANSWERS.
OKAY, BUT HOW?
WELL, YOU KNOW HOW ANNOYING
YOU ARE IN THE MORNING
WHEN YOU TRY TO GET ME
OUT OF THE BATHROOM?
JUST... DO THAT.
OH YEAH,
YOU'RE VERY SERIOUS!
(LUKE CHUCKLES)
♪♪♪
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
(HUM OF STUDENTS CHATTERING)
HEY!
I NEED TO TALK
TO YOU.
NOT NOW, ZOE,
I'M BUSY.
DID WE HAVE SEX
AT YOUR PARTY?!
COULD YOU KEEP IT DOWN?
YOU'RE THE LAST PERSON
I REMEMBER TALKING TO,
THEN I WOKE UP
AT YOUR HOUSE... NAKED.
OKAY,
MAYA CANNOT HEAR THIS.
YOU TRIED TO KISS ME,
YOU PASSED OUT.
CHEWY AND I DRAGGED YOU
TO THE POOL HOUSE.
NOTHING ELSE HAPPENED?
PRETTY SURE.
WHAT A RELIEF!
HOW GROSS WOULD
THAT HAVE BEEN?
HEY!
WHATEVER.
I'LL LET YOU GET BACK
TO YOUR COSTUME TRUNK.
OKAY, YOU GOT THIS.
YOU GOT THIS.
JUST BE TOUGH.
(CAMERA BEEPS)
BECKY BAKER, DTV.
HOW MANY DRINKS DID YOU HAVE
AT MILES' PARTY?
YOU HAVE FIVE SECONDS
TO GET THAT THING
OUT OF MY FACE.
ONE...
BECKY:
IS IT TRUE YOU MADE OUT
WITH GUYS
BECAUSE YOU WERE SO DRUNK?
YOU CAN'T JUST ASK PEOPLE
QUESTIONS LIKE THAT ON CAMERA,
ZOE: YOU KNOW.
BECKY: BUT IS IT TRUE?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
HERE'S YOUR STORY:
NOTHING HAPPENED BETWEEN ME
AND ANY GUYS.
AND IF EVERYONE COULD
JUST LET IT GO,
THIS SCHOOL WOULD BE
A HAPPIER PLACE!
SEE? I'M NOT CUT OUT
FOR REAL JOURNALISM.
NO MATTER WHAT I DO,
I CAN'T GET PEOPLE TO TALK.
MAYBE THERE'S ANOTHER ANGLE
FOR YOUR STORY.
A BAD INTERVIEWS
BLOOPER REEL?
IMOGEN:
THIS WAS POSTED
BY AN ANONYMOUS PERSON,
"THE WATCHER."
(GUYS LAUGH IN THE BACKGROUND
ON PHONE RECORDING)
ZOE: (SLURRED SPEECH)
DO YOU THINK I'M SEXY?
THIS WAS AT THE PARTY?
THAT'S WHAT
"THE WATCHER" SAYS.
WHO DO YOU THINK
THOSE GUYS ARE?
I HAVE NO IDEA,
I CAN'T MAKE OUT THE VOICE.
BUT DREW GOT WITH HER
BEFORE, RIGHT?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
TO FINISH MY STORY!
IF THIS WON'T STOP TEEN GIRLS
FROM DRINKING TOO MUCH,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT WILL!
BECKY:
HEY! UH, HI.
CAN I ASK YOU SOME QUESTIONS?
DREW:
ABOUT THE STONE ANGEL?
SURE, BUT I HAVEN'T EXACTLY
FINISHED THE BOOK.
BECKY:
NO, NOT ABOUT HOMEWORK,
SILLY.
DREW:
(HALF LAUGHS)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
DREW:
WHAT IS THIS?
BECKY:
ZOE, FROM THE PARTY.
(MUFFLED CHATTER
AND LAUGHTER ON VIDEO)
WHO DID THIS?
BECKY: IT'S NOT YOU?
DREW: NO!
THIS IS AWFUL.
BECKY:
I KNOW.
DID YOU ASK HER
ABOUT IT?
SHE SWORE
NOTHING HAPPENED.
MAYBE SHE DOESN'T REMEMBER.
HOW COULD SOMEONE
NOT REMEMBER?
BECKY,
SOMETIMES WHEN YOU DRINK,
YOU, YOU BLACK OUT,
LIKE, COMPLETELY.
REALLY?
YEAH, AND...
SHE LOOKS PRETTY
OUT OF IT.
WHICH MEANS SOMEONE
DID THIS TO HER.
OH MY GOODNESS!
IMOGEN:
YOU'RE SAYING
ZOE WAS ASSAULTED?
DREW:
BY TWO GUYS, I THINK.
THE GUY FILMING
AND THE GUY IN THE VIDEO.
IMOGEN:
WHAT HAPPENED TO
"WHEN YOU DRINK,
WHATEVER YOU DO
IS YOUR FAULT."
BECKY:
WATCHING THAT VIDEO
CHANGED MY MIND.
IMOGEN:
DON'T YOU THINK THIS IS GETTING
A LITTLE TOO DEEP FOR DTV?
DTV IS ABOUT STORIES
THAT AFFECT STUDENTS.
WHAT AFFECTS STUDENTS MORE
THAN HAVING SOME GUYS
WHO PREY ON DRUNK GIRLS?!
WHAT GUY EVEN DOES THIS?
I DON'T KNOW,
BUT I WAS AT THAT PARTY.
FIRST, WE NEED TO NAIL DOWN
WHO ALL WAS THERE.
DREW: WAS IT...?
BECKY: THE SKETCHY KIDS?
IMOGEN: THE SWEET NERD?
BECKY: OUR WEIRD CO-WORKER?
DREW:
THE JOCKS?
(EXHALES, THOUGHTFUL)
JENNA:
I WAS AT THE PARTY,
BUT I DIDN'T SEE ANYTHING HAPPEN
TO ZOE.
WELL, DID YOU SEE HER
WITH ANYONE?
WINSTON MAYBE?
I WASN'T THERE LONG.
BUT, YOU KNOW, BE CAREFUL,
SHE IS A KNOWN LIAR.
YEAH, WELL,
THERE'S SORT OF THIS VIDEO.
HAVEN'T YOU SEEN IT?
NO. DON'T FORGET,
SHE'S AN ACTRESS, TOO.
ZOE: (ON RECORDING)
DO YOU THINK I'M SEXY?
THAT'S AWFUL.
DO YOU KNOW
WHO ANY OF THE GUYS ARE?
NO. OF COURSE NOT.
WHAT ABOUT ONE
OF THE BASKETBALL GUYS?
THEY WERE ALL THERE.
EXCEPT ME.
BUT COME ON.
YOU DON'T RECOGNIZE
THE VOICE?
NO. NO ONE ON MY TEAM
WOULD HAVE DONE THAT.
ZIG:
WELL, YEAH,
I'VE SEEN THE VIDEO.
I'M NOT REALLY SURPRISED.
THAT GIRL'S CRAZY.
SO SHE DESERVED IT?
THAT'S NOT WHAT I SAID.
SO NEITHER OF YOU SAW
TWO GUYS ALONE WITH HER?
GRACE:
IF WE HEAR ANYTHING,
WE'LL LET YOU KNOW.
BECAUSE WHOEVER DID THIS
DESERVES A KARMIC BALLS-KICKING.
ZOE, FRANKIE AND KEISHA:
♪ LET'S GET PHYSICAL,
PHYSICAL ♪
♪ I WANNA GET PHYSICAL ♪
♪ LET'S GET INTO PHYSICAL ♪
♪ LET ME HEAR
YOUR BODY TALK ♪
♪ YOUR BODY TALK ♪
♪ LET ME HEAR
YOUR BODY TALK ♪
ZOE:
WOO!
I HONESTLY NEVER THOUGHT
YOU GIRLS WOULD GET THERE,
BUT, WOW!
WE SOUND CRAZY AMAZING.
IN A COUPLE HOURS,
WE'LL WIN THE SING-OFF
AND EVERYONE WILL SEE
THAT YOU'RE A STAR,
(PHONE CHIMES)
NOT A SKANK!
ZOE:
AW! YOU'RE SO SWEET!
FRANKIE:
OH MY GOD.
WHAT?
ANOTHER PICTURE OF ME?
A VIDEO.
ZOE:
I'M A BIG GIRL,
I CAN HANDLE IT.
(MUFFLED CHATTER AND LAUGHTER
ON VIDEO)
I DON'T REMEMBER THIS.
(STUDENT'S PHONE CHIMES)
ZOE:
DO YOU THINK I'M SEXY?
WHO WOULD DO THIS TO ME?
♪ And my heart is here
right next to me ♪
♪ And I'm cold
waiting in the rain ♪
BECKY:
WE'VE INTERVIEWED EVERYONE
AND NO ONE KNOWS ANYTHING?
SERIOUSLY?
DREW:
WELL, OBVIOUSLY
SOMEONE'S LYING.
IMOGEN:
BUT HOW COULD WE EVER
KNOW WHO?
JUST KEEP DIGGING!
IMOGEN:
OKAY, THE SING-OFF
IS ABOUT TO START.
CAN'T YOU JUST COVER IT,
INSTEAD?
IT'S "THE WATCHER."
DREW:
THAT ANONYMOUS PERSON?
"ARE THE PREDATORS
WHO YOU THINK?
TO FIND OUT,
CLICK ON THIS LINK."
WEIRD POEM.
SECURITY FOOTAGE
FROM THE NIGHT OF THE PARTY.
THIS IS BIZARE.
HOW WOULD "THE WATCHER"
GET THIS?
I DON'T KNOW.
HACKERS THESE DAYS,
THEY CAN DO ANYTHING.
BECKY:
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS!
CUTE, LITTLE WINSTON?
YOU REALLY THINK
HE'S CAPABLE OF THIS?
BECKY:
GUYS, LOOK.
MILES IS WEARING
A BASKETBALL JACKET
IN THIS VIDEO,
AND ONE OF THE GUYS
IN THE ASSAULT VIDEO
IS ALSO WEARING
A BASKETBALL JACKET.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
WE MISSED THIS.
GUYS,
WE KNOW WHO DID THIS.
WE HAVE TO FILM THIS STORY.
THIS IS- THIS IS SERIOUS.
I AGREE.
BUT WE CAN'T ACCUSE PEOPLE
WITHOUT REAL PROOF.
YEAH, BUT WHAT DO YOU THINK
I SHOULD DO?
RIGHT NOW...
COVER THE SING-OFF.
SHE'S RIGHT.
MAYA:
I CAN'T BELIEVE TRISTAN DIDN'T
TELL ME HE WAS PERFORMING.
IT'S NOT LIKE HIM.
WHAT'S HE SINGING?
WINSTON:
UH... "THESE BOOTS
ARE MADE FOR WALKING."
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
DREW:
(CLEARS THROAT)
WELCOME, EVERYBODY,
TO THE FIRST ANNUAL
DEGRASSI SING-OFF.
(STUDENTS APPLAUD AND CHEER)
FIRST UP,
WE HAVE MILES HOLLINGSWORTH
AND THE PANTHER PLAYERS.
GIVE IT UP,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
(STUDENTS APPLAUD AND CHEER)
OKAY,
IT'S NOT TRISTAN,
JUST PLEASE WATCH
OR ELSE MILES WILL KILL ME.
MAYA:
I'LL GIVE HIM TWO BARS.
PANTHERS:
♪ DUM, DUM-DUM, DUM-DUM,
DUM-DUM DOO ♪
♪ I GUESS NOW IT'S TIME ♪
♪ FOR ME TO GIVE UP ♪
PANTHERS:
♪ NO, NO ♪
MILES:
♪ I FEEL IT'S TIME ♪
PANTHERS:
♪ NO, NO ♪
MILES:
♪ GOT A FIST OF PURE EMOTION ♪
♪ GET A HEAD
OF SHATTERED DREAMS ♪
♪ GOTTA LEAVE IT ♪
♪ GOTTA LEAVE IT
ALL BEHIND NOW ♪
♪ WHATEVER I SAID,
WHATEVER I DID ♪
♪ I DIDN'T MEAN IT ♪
♪ I JUST WANT YOU BACK
FOR GOOD ♪
PANTHERS:
♪ WANT YOU BACK,
WANT YOU BACK ♪
♪ WANT YOU BACK FOR GOOD ♪
♪ WHENEVER I'M WRONG
JUST TELL ME THE SONG ♪
♪ AND I'LL SING IT ♪
♪ YOU'LL BE RIGHT
AND UNDERSTOOD ♪
PANTHERS:
♪ WANT YOU BACK,
WANT YOU BACK ♪
♪ WANT YOU BACK FOR GOOD ♪
MILES:
♪ I WANT YOU BACK FOR GOOD ♪
PANTHERS:
(HARMONIZE AND HOLD
THE FINAL NOTE)
(STUDENTS CHEER AND APPLAUD)
DREW:
THANK YOU, MILES
AND THE PANTHER PLAYERS.
AH, SO, JUDGES?
CLARE:
UM, SO WE THINK
YOU DESERVE A 9.8!
(STUDENTS WHISTLE,
CHEER AND APPLAUD)
DREW:
ALRIGHTY!
THANK YOU, MILES.
NEXT UP, WE HAVE ZOE,
FRANKIE, AND KEISHA!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
("LET'S GET PHYSICAL"
MUSIC BEGINS)
ZOE, FRANKIE AND KEISHA:
♪ I'M SAYING ALL THE THINGS
THAT I KNOW YOU'LL LIKE ♪
♪ MAKING GOOD CONVERSATION ♪
♪ I GOTTA HANDLE YOU
JUST RIGHT ♪
♪ YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN ♪
♪ I TOOK YOU
TO AN INTIMATE... ♪
(DISTORTED MALE VOICE
FROM RECORDING)
FRANKIE AND KEISHA:
♪ THEN TO A SUGGESTIVE MOVIE ♪
♪ THERE'S NOTHING LEFT
TO TALK ABOUT ♪
♪ UNLESS IT'S... ♪
(SLOW, HEAVY BREATHS
ON RECORDING)
FRANKIE AND KEISHA:
♪ LET'S GET PHYSICAL,
PHYSICAL ♪
ZOE: (ON RECORDING)
♪ DO YOU THINK I'M SEXY? ♪
FRANKIE AND KEISHA:
♪ LET'S GET INTO PHYSICAL ♪
♪ LET ME HEAR
YOUR BODY TALK ♪
♪ YOUR BODY TALK ♪
♪ LET ME HEAR
YOUR BODY TALK ♪
ZOE:
I CAN'T DO THIS.
FRANKIE AND KEISHA:
♪ LET'S GET PHYSICAL,
PHYSICAL... ♪
WINSTON:
HEY, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
AREN'T YOU SUPPOSED TO BE
COVERING THIS FOR DTV?
I HAVE A WAY MORE IMPORTANT
STORY TO FILE, YOU MONSTER.
BECKY:
SO THE SECURITY FOOTAGE SHOWS
MILES AND WINSTON
DRAGGING ZOE TOWARDS
THE POOL HOUSE.
AND MILES IS WEARING A JACKET
THAT MATCHES THE ONE
IN THE ASSAULT VIDEO.
WE MAY NOT KNOW
WHAT EXACTLY HAPPENED TO ZOE,
BUT WE KNOW WHO DID IT.
AND JUST 'CAUSE
SHE WAS DRUNK
DOESN'T MEAN
SHE DESERVED IT.
SO IS IT APPROVED?
CAN I AIR THIS STORY?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
PLEASE, I WORKED SO HARD
ON THIS.
I JUST WANT PEOPLE
TO TAKE ME SERIOUSLY.
DON'T WORRY,
I TAKE THIS VERY SERIOUSLY.
SO WHY CAN'T WE AIR IT?
BECAUSE WE NEED TO GET
THE POLICE INVOLVED.
DREW: (PA ANNOUNCEMENT)
SUPPORT OUR PANTHERS
AT THE PEP RALLY
BEFORE THE GAME THIS WEEK.
WE MADE IT TO THE PLAYOFFS,
FOLKS!
(EXASPERATED SIGH)
DON'T TELL ME THE SINGING
APOLOGY ACTUALLY WORKED.
UH, KIND OF.
HE'S ON PROBATION.
SO AS LONG AS I DON'T SCREW UP,
I'M GOLDEN.
I'M SURE THAT WILL
LAST LONG.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS,
MAYA CHUCKLES)
SIMPSON:
WINSTON. MILES. A WORD.
I'M A LITTLE BUSY.
I THINK YOU CAN SPARE A MOMENT
FOR THESE GENTLEMEN.
THEY HAVE A FEW QUESTIONS
ABOUT SOME EVENTS
THAT TOOK PLACE
AT YOUR PARTY...
REGARDING ZOE RIVAS.
♪♪♪