CLARE:
(PASSIONATE SIGH)
I'M SO GLAD YOU CAME.
I KNEW YOU'D BOOTY TEXT.
I WAS READY.
YOU'RE GONNA GET YOURSELF
INTO SERIOUS TROUBLE.
SWEET LORD,
IT'S HOT IN HERE!
WHO'S IN TROUBLE NOW?
I FEEL LIKE
I'M IN A DREAM.
YOU ARE, CLARE.
IT'S OKAY.
IN A DREAM,
ANYTHING CAN HAPPEN.
YOU CAN FLY, CLARE.
FLY.
FLY!
(CLARE THUMPS ON THE FLOOR)
(GROANS WEAKLY)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ (The best that I can be) ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
MILES:
YEAH, MY FOLKS ARE FLYING UP
TO CALGARY THIS MORNING
TO PICK THEIR MAYOR'S BRAIN
ON ELECTION TACTICS.
MAYA:
AND THEY'RE LEAVING YOU
HOME ALONE?
MIRACLES DO HAPPEN.
WANNA COME OVER?
MAYA:
YEAH, MAYBE WE CAN FIND OUT
HOW THAT SKINNY DIP ENDS.
YEAH, YEAH.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
MILES?
OH, GOTTA GO,
SORRY.
SO YOUR MOM'S ALREADY
IN THE CAR,
AND UM...
WE'RE GONNA MISS YOU.
YEAH,
IT'S ONLY ONE DAY.
NOW, LISTEN,
WE'RE TRUSTING YOU, HERE.
YEAH, YEAH, SURE, DAD.
YOU GUYS BETTER GET GOING.
YEAH, I WILL IN A...
IN A MINUTE,
AND UH...
HEY, MR. HOLLINGSWORTH,
I'M HERE.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
HERE HE IS!
DREW: SORRY I'M LATE, SIR.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH: THAT'S OKAY.
'KAY,
WHAT IS HE DOING HERE?
WELL, WE JUST THOUGHT
IT WOULD BE A GOOD IDEA
TO GIVE YOU SOME BACKUP,
JUST IN CASE.
NOW, I KNOW I DON'T NEED
TO TELL YOU THIS,
BUT NO PARTIES,
NO GIRLS!
YEAH, YEAH,
JUST A GUYS' NIGHT.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
WELL, WE'LL SEE YOU
IN THE MORNING.
I LOVE YOU.
DAD!
HEY, LISTEN,
IF YOU'RE GOOD,
I MIGHT EVEN LET YOU
STAY UP 'TIL TWELVE.
(MILES LAUGHS HUMOURLESSLY,
SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
HE WALKED ME TO SCHOOL,
HE STOOD BY MY LOCKER
WHILE I WAS GETTING MY BOOKS,
WAITED FOR ME
OUTSIDE OF THE BATHROOM,
AND THEN FOLLOWED ME
ALL THE WAY TO CLASS!
DREW'S TAKING HIS BABYSITTING
JOB SERIOUSLY.
HE'S JUST TRYING
TO SCORE POINTS WITH MY DAD!
I GUESS YOUR DAD
DOESN'T TRUST YOU
TO SPEND THE NIGHT ALONE.
YEAH, HE MIGHT AS WELL
SHOVE A SOOTHER IN MY MOUTH
AND THROW A DIAPER ON ME
WHILE HE'S AT IT!
PLEASE LET ME GET
A PICTURE OF THAT!
HEY, IT'S ONLY
FOR ONE NIGHT!
MAN, I'M SO SICK OF HIM
TRYING TO CONTROL MY LIFE.
THEN DON'T LET HIM!
YOU'RE RIGHT.
IF THEY THINK
I NEED A BABYSITTER,
I MIGHT AS WELL ACT
LIKE I NEED A BABYSITTER.
DOES THIS MEAN
WE'RE HAVING A PARTY?
NO, NO, WE'RE HAVING
"THE" PARTY!
YOU REALIZE YOUR DAD
WILL BE FURIOUS
WHEN HE FINDS OUT!
YEAH, WELL,
HE'S CHEATING ON MY MOM,
SO I DON'T REALLY CARE
WHAT HE THINKS.
THEN I'LL SPREAD THE WORD!
NO, NO,
FIRST THINGS FIRST.
WE GOTTA GET RID
OF DREW.
♪♪♪
CLARE:
IT WASN'T JUST KISSING!
IT WAS INTENSE,
AND IT WAS GOING SOMEWHERE!
IN YOUR DREAM.
SO NONE OF THIS
ACTUALLY HAPPENED?
IT FELT LIKE IT DID!
EVEN AFTER I WOKE UP
AND I WANTED IT TO!
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD
OF THE EXPRESSION,
"YOU'RE INNOCENT
WHEN YOU DREAM?"
IT'S A CLASSIC
TOM WAITS SONG.
WELL, IT'S BALONEY!
IT'S YOUR MIND ACTING OUT
YOUR ACTUAL FANTASIES!
I STILL LOVE ELI
AND ONLY ELI.
ALLI:
WELL THEN, I SUGGEST YOU GIVING
DREW SOME DISTANCE.
WE GO TO THE SAME SCHOOL,
WE'RE IN SOME
OF THE SAME CLASSES.
I'M HIS V.P.!
HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO GIVE DREW SOME SPACE?!
WELL, IF YOU CAN'T PRY YOURSELF
OFF OF HIM,
TRY SETTING SOME BOUNDARIES:
NO FLIRTING, NO TOUCHING,
AND NO KISSING.
(SIGHS)
YOU'RE RIGHT.
FROM NOW ON,
I ONLY TALK TO DREW
WHEN I HAVE TO.
(CLEARS THROAT)
DID I KEEP YOU WAITING?
NOPE.
YOU'RE RIGHT ON TIME.
I'M SUPPOSED TO TAKE
YOU HOME, ASAP.
WHATEVER DEAR OLD DAD
WANTS.
DREW:
YEAH.
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
WHICH ONE OF YOUR GIRLS
IS THAT?
NO, IT'S YOUR DAD.
HE NEEDS ME TO GET
SOME LAST MINUTE
CAMPAIGN STUFF PRINTED
ASAP?
OH MY- LIKE MORE LETTERS,
FLYERS, POSTERS?
IT'S GONNA TAKE
ALL NIGHT!
YEAH, YOU KNOW,
I'D HELP
BUT I HAVE TO GO STRAIGHT HOME
AND FINISH AN ENGLISH ESSAY.
LOOK, JUST PROMISE ME
YOU'RE NOT GONNA GET
INTO ANY TROUBLE.
PLEASE?
YEAH, DON'T WORRY,
I'LL BE GOOD.
OKAY, I'LL BE BACK LATER
TO DROP OFF THE MATERIALS.
HE BOUGHT IT?
THE THINGS HE'D DO
FOR MY DAD!
OKAY, WHO'S ON
THE GUEST LIST?
I'VE ALREADY MESSAGED
A BUNCH OF PEOPLE.
WHAT? DUDE, ALREADY?
I JUST GOT RID OF DREW!
I HAD FAITH.
I HOPE MAYA'S
NOT GONNA BE TOO PISSED
THAT YOU GUYS WON'T BE HAVING
ANY ALONE TIME.
I MEAN DOESN'T A RAGER
SOUND LIKE MORE FUN?
ANYWAYS, MY HOUSE
HAS A LOT OF ROOMS
WITH LOCKS ON THE DOORS.
ZOE:
THANKS FOR THE INVITE,
WINSTON!
SEE YOU GUYS LATER.
WOO-HOO!
WHAT, YOU INVITED ZOE?!
MAN, YOU KNOW SHE'S TROUBLE!
ISN'T THAT THE POINT?
WINSTON...
MAN,
YOU ARE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT!
THIS PARTY'S GONNA BE EPIC!
(SIREN WAILS)
(KIDS LAUGH)
(LEO'S KEYS JINGLE)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(KID GIGGLES)
(LOCK CLICKS)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(PHONE RINGS)
ROCKY:
DAD?
ROCKY!
HEY, BUD, HOW ARE YOU?
ROCKY:
GOOD.
WHY DID YOU CALL ME?
SOMETIMES I...
I JUST NEED TO HEAR
YOUR VOICE.
CLARE:
"BREATHING ALIVE" IS ON AT 7:40
AT DUNDAS SQUARE.
ALLI:
OR WE CAN SHOP FIRST
AND CATCH THE 9:15 SHOW
AT METRO CINEMA.
CLARE:
OR WE COULD GO TO THAT PLACE
THAT WE WENT LAST WEEK,
WHICH WAS-
CLARE!
DREW!
UH-OH.
AM I EVER HAPPY
TO SEE YOU!
ACTUALLY,
MAYBE YOU CAN HELP ME.
CLARE: SURE!
ALLI: BOUNDARIES, CLARE.
I MEAN, MAYBE.
UH, I HAVE TO PRINT OFF
THESE MATERIALS,
BUT I CAN'T OPEN
ANY OF THE FILES.
IT'S DRIVING ME CRAZY!
ALLI:
I'M SORRY,
SHE CAN'T HELP.
WE'RE GONNA GO
SEE A MOVIE.
PLEASE, CLARE,
I NEED YOU!
WELL, UH,
MAYBE I COULD-
ALLI: NO, YOU CAN'T.
CLARE: YES, I CAN.
ALL RIGHT!
SWEET!
(BOTH LAUGH)
(SCOFFS INCREDULOUSLY)
SO MUCH FOR DISTANCE.
(SIGHS)
♪ We can smile with love,
make the crowd go wild ♪
♪ We can rock this thing,
we don't need no sleep ♪
(LOUD BUZZ OF EXCITED CHATTER
AND LAUGHTER)
(CHEERING)
♪ We can do this all night ♪
♪ Yeah, everything's all right ♪
♪ We got the keys
to open paradise ♪
♪ Yeah, paradise ♪
♪ It feels like
we can do this all night ♪
MAN, WHO KNEW
YOU WERE SUCH A WHIZ
AT LAST MINUTE
PARTY PLANNING?
THIS IS INCREDIBLE!
POST IT
AND THEY WILL COME.
ZOE:
WHO'S READY TO HAVE
SOME FUN TONIGHT?!
(PARTYGOERS CHEER LOUDLY)
♪ We can rock this thing,
we don't need no sleep ♪
DALLAS:
OKAY, FIND THE AVERAGE
OF 6.12...
DALLAS: 6.15...
ALLI: (GASPS IN PAIN)
DALLAS:
AND 6.19-
WAIT, SLOW DOWN.
AGH!
DALLAS:
SORRY. ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH, IT'S JUST MY WRIST.
SOMETIMES IT STILL HURTS.
YOU'RE STILL IN PAIN,
WHILE LEO GETS TO WALK AROUND
LIKE NOTHING HAPPENED.
ALLI:
NOT FOR LONG.
HE'S BEING DEPORTED
BACK TO FRANCE THIS WEEKEND
AND HIS RECORD WILL FOLLOW.
THE FARTHER AWAY THE BETTER,
RIGHT?
ALLI:
SORTA.
I WISH I COULD'VE SHOWN HIM
JUST HOW MUCH HE HURT ME,
BUT...
I'LL NEVER GET THE CHANCE.
THERE'S GOTTA BE A WAY
TO MAKE HIM
FACE UP TO WHAT HE DID.
LIKE WHAT?!
LET'S TAKE A WALK.
(PARTYGOERS LAUGH AND SHOUT,
LOUD MUSIC PLAYS)
MAYA:
MILES?!
BABE! HEY!
MMMUAH!
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU, ME,
AND A NICE WARM POOL?
MAYA, MY DAD SAID
I COULDN'T HAVE ANYONE OVER.
SO YOU INVITED
THE WHOLE SCHOOL?!
DON'T WORRY, OKAY?
WE'LL FIND SOME TIME ALONE
BEFORE THE NIGHT
IS THROUGH, OKAY?
MAYA:
I'M NOT WORRIED!
I JUST WANNA KNOW
WHAT THE PLAN IS, OKAY?
UPSET YOUR DAD?
GET CAUGHT?
(LAUGHS)
PRETTY MUCH!
MAYA:
AWESOME.
MILES:
OKAY, SHHHH!
COME ON, MAYA,
JUST HAVE SOME FUN.
I MEAN, LOOK, IT'S A PARTY!
HUH?
I THOUGHT YOU'D LIKE IT.
MAYA:
STOP, YOU'RE DRUNK!
COME ON.
OKAY, SINCE WHEN DID YOU
GET SO JUDGE-Y, HUH?
LOOK, I UNDERSTAND
YOU'RE GOING THROUGH SOMETHING!
CAN'T YOU JUST
CALL THIS OFF
BEFORE YOUR WHOLE HOUSE
GETS TRASHED?!
(YELLING ANGRILY)
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND ANYTHING!
NOTHING!
GOOD NIGHT, MILES.
WHAT, YOU'RE LEAVING?!
SERIOUSLY!
(SCOFFS)
(PARTYGOERS CHATTER,
LOUD MUSIC PLAYS)
OOPS! SORRY!
(GIGGLES DRUNKENLY)
AH!
ZOE: FRANKIEEEE! I LOVE YOU!
FRANKIE: HI.
YOU'RE THE BESTEST FRIEND.
YEAH?
YEAH.
MUAH!
AWWW...
LOOK AT LITTLE BOY BLUE
ALL ALONE IN THE CORNER!
HMM! WHERE'S YOUR LITTLE
APPLE-CHEEKED GIRLFRIEND?
SHE WASN'T IN THE MOOD
FOR A PARTY.
DID YOU TWO HAVE A FIGHT?
SHE JUST DOESN'T GET ME,
YOU KNOW?
JUDGE-Y PEOPLE LIKE HER,
WITH THEIR PERFECT
LITTLE LIVES,
THEY HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO BE SOMEONE
WHO HAS REAL PROBLEMS!
AND...
ONCE THEY MAKE UP
THEIR MINDS ABOUT YOU...
THEY'LL NEVER
CHANGE THEM.
WHATEVER PEOPLE LIKE US DO -
GOOD, BAD -
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
SO LET THEM THINK
WHAT THEY WANT.
HMM!
WOW! YOU AND I HAVE MORE
IN COMMON THAN I THOUGHT.
(GIGGLES)
WINSTON:
SAY CHEESE!
(SHUTTER SNAPS)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
PREVENTING A HUGE MISTAKE!
MILES:
OKAY, THIS IS NONE OF YOUR-
THIS IS NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
WINSTON:
YOU HAVE A GIRLFRIEND!
SHE'S AWESOME
IN EVERY POSSIBLE WAY!
WHY WOULD YOU
SCREW THAT UP?!
OKAY, LOOK,
SHE'S THE ONE WHO TOOK OFF!
OKAY, WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO,
RUN AFTER HER OR SOMETHING?
YES!
BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT YOU DO
WHEN YOU SCREW UP!
MILES:
NOW SHE'S PASSED OUT.
(SIGHS)
♪ This is a game
so you know it better ♪
♪ Holdin' me down ♪
♪ Breakin' me down ♪
♪ Breakin' me free ♪
YOU GOTTA...
YOU GOTTA PUT HER
IN THE POOL HOUSE,
OR SOMETHING.
BY MYSELF?!
YEAH.
SHE'S DEAD WEIGHT!
(SIGHS)
OKAY.
♪ Holdin' me down ♪
♪ Breakin' me down ♪
♪ Breakin' me free ♪
LOOK, BUT FIRST-
WHAT?
(CAMERA SHUTTER SNAPS)
YOU NEVER KNOW
WHEN YOU'RE GONNA NEED AMMO.
OKAY, LET'S MAKE THIS QUICK,
COME ON!
OKAY, OKAY-
YOU GRAB HER ARMS.
HUH? OKAY.
GRAB HER ARMS!
YES, I GOT IT.
OH. OKAY.
♪♪♪
(CLARE GIGGLES)
OH, YOU'RE A LIFESAVER!
I NEVER COULD'VE GOTTEN
ANY OF THAT DONE WITHOUT YOU.
ALL I DID WAS TALK YOU
OFF A LEDGE.
AND WHERE WAS THAT,
WHEN WE WERE BUNGEE JUMPING?
(BOTH LAUGH)
UM, WELL,
THANKS FOR THE RIDE.
WE COULD GRAB A COFFEE.
I DON'T THINK
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
WHY, I THOUGHT WE WERE
HAVING FUN TOGETHER.
I'M HAVING TOO MUCH FUN.
SINCE WHEN WAS THAT
EVER A PROBLEM?
(KNOCKING)
ELI! HEY!
CLARE DIANA EDWARDS!
WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN UP TO
THIS FINE EVENING?
OH, WE WERE...
FINISHING STUDENT COUNCIL STUFF
AT SCHOOL.
WHAT ABOUT YOUR SHORT FILM?
I BUSTED MY BUTT
TO GET IT DONE
SO I COULD MAKE IT BACK
FOR OUR BIG BUNGEE JUMPING DATE.
OH, ELI, I...
NO, WE UM...
YOU GUYS ARE GOING
BUNGEE JUMPING?
(LAUGHS) SWEET!
I'LL UM...
SEE YOU AT SCHOOL, EDWARDS.
EDWARDS?
THAT'S MY THING.
EVERYONE WANTS TO BE
LIKE YOU, ELI.
AWW.
COME ON.
(DOOR SLAMS)
♪♪♪
(ELASTICS THWAP)
MILES!
(POSTER CRUMPLES)
DAMN IT!
(KNOCKING)
LEO!
HMPH!
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
WE NEED TO TALK.
ALLI SENT YOU,
IS THAT IT?
IF YOU EVER LOVED HER,
YOU'RE GONNA BE QUIET
AND SIT DOWN.
(SCOFFS)
SIT!
(LEO SIGHS)
ALLI! GOOD, I-
SHUT UP!
THIS IS HOW
THIS IS GONNA HAPPEN.
SHE'S GONNA TALK
AND YOU'RE GONNA LISTEN.
(SIGHS ANGRILY)
(SHAKY SIGH)
I COULDN'T BELIEVE
HOW LUCKY I WAS;
I FOUND LOVE IN
THE MOST ROMANTIC CITY ON EARTH.
BUT IT WASN'T MEANT
TO BE.
BUT WHATEVER HAPPENED,
NOTHING GAVE YOU THE RIGHT
TO HIT ME -
NO EXCUSE,
NO JUSTIFICATION
FOR THE VIOLENCE
YOU PUT ME THROUGH!
YOU HAVE A PROBLEM,
AND IF YOU DON'T FACE IT
YOU'LL END UP
IN A LOT WORSE TROUBLE,
AND OTHER GIRLS
WILL GET HURT.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
YOU BEAT ME...
BUT YOU DIDN'T BREAK ME.
ALLI, WAIT-
GET ON THAT PLANE
AND NEVER CONTACT HER AGAIN!
UNDERSTAND?
(PARTYGOERS CHATTER
AND HOLLER)
WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?!
HEY, IT'S A PARTY.
COME ON, HAVE FUN.
FIRST DRINK'S ON ME.
NO WAY,
YOU ARE NOT LEAVING ME
WITH THIS MESS!
I'M GONNA CALL
YOUR DAD!
OH YEAH?
WELL, THAT WOULD MEAN
WE'D BOTH GET
IN TROUBLE, RIGHT?
BECAUSE IT WAS ON YOU
TO MAKE SURE
THAT THIS DIDN'T HAPPEN.
NOW, MOVE.
NO WONDER HE CAME UP WITH
THE "MILES MANAGEMENT PLAN!"
HE DID WHAT?
THERE'S A WHOLE LIST
OF OPTIONS
JUST IN CASE YOU SCREW UP
THE CAMPAIGN AGAIN!
I SAID, MOVE!
♪♪♪
DREW:
(SHOUTING)
EVERYBODY GET OUT!
(PARTYGOERS LAUGH
AND CHEER)
(SOBBING)
DALLAS:
YOU'RE CRYING?
(SIGHS)
I JUST,
I THOUGHT YOU NEEDED CLOSURE.
YOU SAID YOU DIDN'T GET
THE CHANCE TO CONFRONT HIM,
AND...
I'M SORRY,
I'M SO SORRY.
I SHOULDN'TVE
DONE THIS-
NO, YOU SHOULD'VE.
(SHAKY SIGH)
BUT YOU'RE STILL UPSET.
IT WAS HARD,
BUT...
I NEEDED
TO CONFRONT HIM,
SAY MY PIECE.
SO YOU FEEL BETTER?
YOU'RE ONE OF THE GOOD ONES,
DALLAS.
GLAD I COULD HELP.
(LOUD KNOCKING)
(MAYA SIGHS)
WHY ARE YOU HERE?!
TO APOLOGIZE.
LOOK, I'M SORRY FOR THROWING
THAT STUPID-
SHHHH!
PARTY.
IT WAS IMMATURE,
I SHOULD'VE SHUT IT DOWN
WHEN YOU ASKED.
DO YOU EVEN CARE
ABOUT ME?
WELL, YOU-
WHY ELSE WOULD I BE HERE?
OF COURSE I CARE ABOUT YOU.
YOU'RE THE ONLY THING
I CARE ABOUT!
YOU CARE ABOUT YOUR DAD,
OR ELSE YOU WOULDN'T SPEND
ALL YOUR ENERGY
TRYING TO UPSET HIM!
I JUST WANT HIM TO STOP
TREATING ME LIKE CRAP.
SO DON'T GIVE HIM
A REASON TO!
MILES:
MAYA! MAYA!
MILES, JUST-
MAYA!
FRANKIE:
DID DREW ACCEPT YOUR APOLOGY?
MILES:
NO.
(CAR DOORS SLAM)
THAT'S MOM AND DAD.
GREAT!
I'M TOAST.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH
WE'RE HOME!
WHAT'S THIS?
WHERE'S DREW?
HE ASSURED ME
HE'D BE RESPONSIBLE!
MILES:
DREW HAD NOTHING TO DO
WITH THIS, OKAY?
I THREW THE PARTY.
DREW SHUT IT DOWN
BEFORE IT GOT ANY WORSE.
(SIGHS)
FRANKIE,
IS HE TELLING THE TRUTH?
YEAH, DREW WAS SUPER
ON TOP OF THINGS.
ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT.
HONEY, YOU SHOULD GET READY
FOR SCHOOL NOW, OKAY?
(SIGHS)
I'M SORRY,
I WAS MAD.
WHY?! BECAUSE I ASKED DREW
TO WATCH OVER YOU?
NO, BECAUSE YOU'RE
CHEATING ON MOM.
SHE MIGHT BE OKAY WITH IT,
BUT I'M NOT.
OKAY, LOOK, BUD,
IT'S COMPLICATED.
I DON'T WANT AN EXPLANATION,
I...
I JUST- I WANNA BE LEFT OUT
OF YOUR CAMPAIGN, OKAY?
I CAN'T PASTE ON A SMILE
AND PRETEND
YOU'RE MAN OF THE YEAR.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
OKAY, JUST...
PROMISE, NO MORE STUNTS
LIKE LAST NIGHT?
YEAH.
YOUR MOM AND I,
WE'LL WORK IT OUT.
I'LL BELIEVE IT
WHEN I SEE IT.
OKAY, I'M GONNA CALL A SERVICE
TO FINISH THE CLEANUP.
MILES:
NO, IT'S MY MESS,
I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
♪ It'll be all right ♪
♪ There's gold in the ground
where we're walking tonight ♪
♪ Just sit back ♪
♪ And watch it come to light ♪