(CHURCH BELL TOLLS)
(CROW CAWS)
(PEOPLE MURMUR SOFTLY)
ELI:
SO MANY PEOPLE CAME.
IT WAS AMAZING.
EVERYBODY LOVED
THE DUDE.
BIANCA: THIS IS SUCH CRAP.
ELI: BIANCA!
BIANCA:
WHY COULDN'T THEY SAVE HIM?
HE WAS RIGHT THERE
IN THE HOSPITAL.
WHY DID HE HAVE TO DIE?
I GUESS JESUS
WANTED HIM CLOSE.
WHAT A STUPID THING
TO SAY.
DALLAS:
HEY, BECKS, DO YOU HAVE A RIDE
TO THE RECEPTION?
BECKY:
UH, NOT YET.
DALLAS:
WHY DON'T YOU COME WITH ME?
BECKY:
WHY DO I ALWAYS SAY
THE WRONG THING?
IT'S WHAT YOU BELIEVE,
ISN'T IT?
I SHOULD APOLOGIZE,
TELL HIM IT WAS UNFAIR
HE DIED.
HE WAS TOO YOUNG!
NO, YOU SHOULD LEAVE IT
FOR TODAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I CAN'T!
(BECKY SIGHS HEAVILY)
I'M SORRY ABOUT BEFORE.
I WAS JUST LOOKING
FOR AN ANSWER.
ANY ANSWER.
BUT THERE ISN'T ONE.
WHAT DO YOU ALL KNOW
THAT I DON'T?
HE DIED
BECAUSE OF YOU.
BECKY:
ME?
BUT I WASN'T EVEN THERE!
YOU'RE THE REASON
HE WENT INTO THE VAN -
TO CALL YOU AND BEG
FOR YOUR FORGIVENESS.
(GASPS) NO!
(VEHICLE STARTS UP)
WE SHOULD GO,
YOUR FAMILY'S WAITING.
(BECKY SOBS)
DALLAS:
LISTEN, DUDE'S A MESS, OKAY?
HE DOESN'T KNOW
WHAT HE'S SAYING.
I'LL TAKE YOU
TO THE RECEPTION.
BECKY.
YOU GO AHEAD.
I DON'T THINK
I'M WELCOME.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ (The best that I can be) ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
IT'S DECIDED.
I HATE FUNERALS.
WHO DOESN'T?
UNDERTAKERS,
PROBABLY.
PRETTY MUCH ANYONE
IN THE FUNERAL BUSINESS.
LIKE CEMETERIES,
HEAD STONE MANUFACTURERS...
OKAY, CONNOR,
WE GET IT.
IS IT WRONG TO SAY
I MISS PARIS?
WHAT A WAY
TO END THE SUMMER.
JENNA:
IT'S HIM, ISN'T IT?
ALLI:
SO SHOULD WE HEAD
TO THE RECEPTION?
IS THAT WEIRD?
WE BARELY KNEW ADAM.
YEAH, BUT WE CAN'T JUST
GO ON WITH OUR DAY
LIKE NOTHING HAPPENED,
CAN WE?
(SOBBING)
JENNA:
SWEETIE, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE
AT THE RECEPTION!
NO ONE WANTS ME THERE.
DON'T BE SILLY,
YOU WERE ADAM'S GIRLFRIEND!
NO, WE HAD A FIGHT
AND I SAID
I NEEDED SPACE.
WELL, THAT DOESN'T
MATTER NOW.
IT DOES TO DREW!
YOU BELIEVE ADAM'S
IN HEAVEN, RIGHT?
THEN YOU CAN TALK TO HIM
WHENEVER YOU WANT.
EVEN SAY YOU'RE SORRY.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
CAN ANY OF YOU BUILD
A BONFIRE?
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
(KEYS CLICK)
(SIGHS TEARFULLY)
(MONITOR BEEPS)
HOW DO YOU SAY GOODBYE
TO SOMEONE
WHO CHANGED YOUR LIFE?
BEATS ME,
BUT...
THAT FUNERAL DIDN'T DO
THE TRICK.
HOW WAS IT?
FUNERAL-Y.
DID DREW CRY?
HE WAS QUIET...
BUT EVERYBODY WAS.
SOUNDS LIKE
EVERY FUNERAL EVER.
WHICH IS WHY
IT DIDN'T FEEL LIKE ADAM.
YOU KNOW, HE...
HE WASN'T GLOOMY.
HE WAS THE MOST
POSITIVE PERSON I KNOW.
AND THE BALLSIEST.
(LAUGHS)
I HOPE EVERYONE REMEMBERS HIM
LIKE THAT.
MAYBE WE CAN HELP THEM.
WE'RE MAKING A MEMORIAL VIDEO,
AREN'T WE?
THE BEST MEMORIAL VIDEO.
(LAUGHS)
(BUTTONS CLICK)
EVERYONE'S ASKING ABOUT YOU
UPSTAIRS.
I BROUGHT YOU SOME FOOD.
EGG SALAD,
YOUR FAVOURITE.
DALLAS:
YOU KNOW WHAT EGG SALAD
DOES TO THIS GUY?
DREW DOESN'T FART.
DALLAS:
YEAH, KEEP TELLING YOURSELF
THAT.
(DOOR SQUEAKS)
DAVE:
HEY.
THIS IS WHERE
THE PARTY'S AT?
IMOGEN:
WOW! LOOK AT ALL THE FLOWERS.
LOOKS LIKE SOMEONE ROBBED
A FLOWER SHOP.
CAN YOU IMAGINE?
HANDS UP,
MR. FLORIST.
GIMME ALL YOUR GLADIOLAS.
SORRY, I'M NOT REALLY GOOD
WITH THIS STUFF.
SO, HOW-HOW WAS...
HOW WAS EVERYONE'S SUMMER?
ANYTHING EXCITING HAPPEN?
(SIGHS)
SO STUPID!
DALLAS:
HEY, HEY!
HEY, WE GOTTA GET YOU
OUT OF THIS HOUSE, MAN.
WE'LL GO TO A BAR,
WE'LL GET SOME DRINKS,
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
I JUST WANNA BE ALONE.
NO, MAN, YOU GOTTA BE
AROUND PEOPLE!
(DREW SNIFFLES)
(SIGHS)
ADAM:
(PRETENDING TO BE CLARE)
IF ONLY IT WERE THAT SIMPLE.
DID YOU EVER LOVE ME
AT ALL?
(CLARE LAUGHS)
DID YOU EVEN LOVE ME AT ALL?!
NOW WE JUST NEED A SONG.
HEY.
I HAVE SOME NEWS
THAT MIGHT BRIGHTEN YOUR DAY.
I TALKED TO THE DOCTOR.
YOUR CT SCAN CAME BACK CLEAN.
(GASPS)
W-WHAT?!
CLARE: SERIOUSLY?
HELEN: MM-HMM.
ELI:
THAT MEANS YOU'RE CURED,
RIGHT?
NOT YET,
I'M IN REMISSION.
WHICH MEANS THE CANCER
IS GONE FOR NOW.
SO YOU CAN FINALLY BLOW
THIS POPSICLE STAND, RIGHT?
THEY'RE DISCHARGING HER
TONIGHT.
OH, THANK GOD!
(LAUGHS)
YOU KNOW, PEOPLE WOULD LOVE
TO SEE YOU.
THEY COULD USE
SOME GOOD NEWS.
HELEN:
WE NEED TO GET THIS PLACE
PACKED UP.
(ELI LAUGHS)
♪♪♪
IT'S OKAY TO BE HAPPY.
(SIGHS TEARFULLY)
BIANCA:
HEY.
I WANTED TO GIVE YOU
SOME TIME.
(CRYING)
PLEASE, CAN YOU TALK TO ME?
ANYTHING YOU NEED,
JUST SAY THE WORD.
I NEED MY BROTHER BACK!
HE WAS THE BEST,
THE VERY, VERY BEST.
AND I KILLED HIM.
WHAT?!
IT WAS MY FAULT.
NOT BECKY'S,
MINE.
I KEEP BLAMING
EVERYONE ELSE,
BUT IT WAS ME.
I WAS THE LAST PERSON
TO TALK TO HIM.
IF I WOULD'VE JUST...
DONE SOMETHING DIFFERENT,
I'D JUST...
ANYTHING DIFFERENT,
HE'D STILL BE HERE!
A COUPLE PEOPLE PLANNED
A BONFIRE FOR HIM.
IT MIGHT HELP TO GO.
IS THAT GONNA BRING
MY BROTHER BACK?
(SIGHS)
BECKY:
OKAY. (SIGHS)
(ALLI GRUNTS WITH EFFORT)
WHAT A PERFECT DAY.
IT'S LIKE HE'S WATCHING
OVER US.
OKAY,
NOW FOR THE FINISHING TOUCH.
UH, CONNOR,
CAN I HAVE YOUR HELP?
THANKS.
A LITTLE MORE,
A LITTLE MORE.
CONNOR:
HERE?
BECKY:
YEAH, OKAY.
WHO'S THAT CHAIR FOR?
BECKY:
ADAM.
YOU THINK IT'S STUPID,
DON'T YOU?
STUPID, NO.
A LITTLE CREEPY,
MAYBE.
WHAT IF THIS WHOLE CELEBRATION
WAS A MISTAKE?
I MEAN,
WHAT IF NO ONE COMES?
PEOPLE WILL COME,
YOU POSTED THE INVITATION
ON FACERANGE.
BECKY:
EXACTLY, I POSTED IT!
ADAM'S FRIENDS DON'T LIKE ME
AND DREW HATES ME.
ALLI:
DREW LOST HIS BROTHER
A COUPLE DAYS AGO.
RIGHT NOW
HE HATES THE WORLD.
I JUST WANT TONIGHT
TO BE PERFECT.
FOR ADAM.
(FIRE CRACKLES)
ELI:
MMM... MY LAST HOSPITAL JELL-O.
WHOA.
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE READY
FOR THE BONFIRE.
I'VE BEEN THINKING.
ALWAYS SCARY.
I SHOULDN'T GO
TO THE BONFIRE.
WHY NOT?
YOU'VE BEEN DISCHARGED.
I KNOW, BUT I'M STILL
IMMUNO-SUPPRESSED.
WELL, THE DOCTOR SAID
IT WAS FINE
AS LONG AS THERE'S
NO CLOSE CONTACT.
WELL, WHAT ABOUT
THE HUGGING?
YOU KNOW THAT THERE
WILL BE HUGGING.
I'LL BE YOUR HUG-PROXY.
YOU WANT TO HONOUR ADAM,
DON'T YOU?
YOU KNOW I DO.
THEN WHAT'S WITH
THE STRING OF EXCUSES?
(BREATH CATCHES ON A SOB)
ADAM GOT ME THROUGH
THIS SUMMER.
HOW DO I FACE EVERYONE,
FACE DREW,
WHEN I LIVED AND HE DIED?
WHAT KIND OF WEIRDO GOD MATH
IS THAT?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
YOU CAN'T BLAME YOURSELF
FOR LIVING.
IT'S SO UNFAIR!
I AGREE.
BUT ADAM WOULDN'T WANT US
TO BE SAD,
OR ANGRY, OR GUILTY.
YOU DON'T KNOW THAT.
WOULD YOU?
NO.
(BONFIRE CRACKLES)
ANYONE ELSE REALLY HUNGRY?
BECKY:
WELL, OBVIOUSLY
NO ONE'S COMING.
LET'S JUST PUT THE FIRE OUT
AND PACK UP.
WAIT, MAYBE WE SHOULD
HOLD ON-
NO, IT'S FINE.
IT WAS A SILLY IDEA, ANYWAY!
BECKY!
BECKY:
I JUST WANTED THIS TO BE
WORTHY OF ADAM.
BECKY: (SIGHS)
JENNA: BECKY?
CAN'T WE GET THIS
BANNER DOWN?
NOT UNTIL YOU LOOK
OVER THERE.
(GASPS)
(STUDENTS MURMUR QUIETLY)
(LAUGHS)
(STUDENTS AND FRIENDS
MURMUR QUIETLY)
♪♪♪
THERE ARE MORE PEOPLE COMING.
IT'S GONNA BE
A PACKED HOUSE...
OR A PACKED FIELD.
DAVE:
THIS IS EXACTLY
WHAT PEOPLE NEED.
♪♪♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ♪
♪ In a dream ♪
♪ I was hit so hard ♪
♪ That I woke up ♪
♪ In a room ♪
♪ Beside the empty shell
of beauty ♪
♪ That let me down
the time before ♪
♪♪♪
ELI:
YOU KNOW, THIS REMINDS ME
OF THAT PARTY HE THREW FOR FIONA
AT THE OLD CHURCH.
CLARE:
THAT'S WHERE
WE FINALLY SPARKED.
YOU CALLED ADAM A HERO
THAT NIGHT.
ELI:
WELL, THAT'S 'CAUSE HE WAS!
MINE.
HE TAUGHT ME THE POWER
OF TWINKLY LIGHTS.
WHERE WOULD WE BE
WITHOUT THEM?
ALLI:
CLARE, YOU'RE HERE!
I DIDN'T THINK YOU'D MAKE IT!
ELI:
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
UM, NO GERMS.
YOU CAN HUG THE...
THE HUG-PROXY.
ME.
OKAY, THIS IS WEIRD.
OKAY.
THEY LET YOU OUT
OF THE HOSPITAL?
MY CANCER'S IN REMISSION.
ALLI:
OH MY GOD!
CLARE:
I DIDN'T WANNA SAY
'CAUSE I DIDN'T WANT
TO OVERSHADOW ADAM.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
THAT'S-THAT'S AMAZING!
YEAH, WE NEEDED
SOME GOOD NEWS TONIGHT.
NOW I JUST NEED
TO MAKE SURE
THAT I MAKE
THE MOST OF MY LIFE.
WE ALL SHOULD.
♪♪♪
(CARS RUMBLE)
(SOBS)
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
♪ Take off ♪
♪ Straight up and skywards ♪
♪ You always were
just like a bird in the sky ♪
ELI: (ON VIDEO)
SO, ADAM TORRES,
WHERE DO YOU SEE YOURSELF
IN TEN YEARS?
UH, I DON'T KNOW.
THESE PAST FEW YEARS
I'VE LIVED MORE
THAN I EVER THOUGHT I COULD.
I WENT TO DEGRASSI
AS A NEW PERSON - MYSELF -
AND I HIT ON THE HOTTEST GIRL,
BIANCA -
WELL, THAT WAS BEFORE
MY BROTHER WAS WITH HER -
AND THEN I FELL FOR
THE PERFECT ONE,
WHO OVERCAME SO MUCH
TO BE WITH ME.
SO HANDS OFF, DREW!
ADAM: BECKY, COME HERE.
BECKY: NO!
COME HERE,
I WANT YOU ON VIDEO!
THEN EVERYONE CAN BELIEVE
THAT SOMEONE LIKE YOU
WOULD PICK A GUY LIKE ME.
(DREW SNIFFLES)
ADAM:
ELI, TURN OFF THAT CAMERA
SO I CAN GO MAKE OUT
WITH MY GIRLFRIEND!
(ADAM AND BECKY LAUGH)
♪ We always were just like
two birds in the sky ♪
(LAUGHS)
♪ Ooh... Ooh... Ooh... ♪
♪ Ooh-Ooh... Ooh-ooh...
Ooh... ♪
♪ Let's fly ♪
♪ Above the landscape ♪
(CRICKETS CHIRP)
BECKY:
SO MANY PEOPLE CAME...
JUST NOT THE ONE
I WAS HOPING FOR.
I'M SO LOST WITHOUT YOU.
(SOBS)
GOODBYE, ADAM TORRES.
I LOVE YOU.
♪♪♪
(PEOPLE MURMUR SOFTLY)
(DREW CRIES)
(DALLAS SIGHS HEAVILY)
HOW DO WE MOVE ON?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
WE FIND A WAY
TO SAY GOODBYE.
JENNA:
♪ SO LONG ♪
♪ HERE'S TO THE DAY
WE ARE ALL STRONG ♪
♪ TOGETHER UNITED
WE HOLD ON ♪
♪ FOREVER LET'S JOIN
AND CELEBRATE ♪
♪ GOODBYE... ♪
(SOBS)
YOU DID A STUPID THING.
WHEN YOU LOVED SOMETHING
OR SOMEONE,
YOU WENT AFTER IT,
YOU DIDN'T HESITATE.
THAT'S WHY YOU MADE
SUCH A HUGE MARK
ON THE PEOPLE AROUND YOU.
(SOBS)
THAT'S WHY THERE'S SO MANY
PEOPLE HERE TO SAY GOODBYE.
BUT I'M NOT GOING TO.
BECAUSE TO ME,
YOU'LL NEVER BE GONE.
YOU'LL ALWAYS BE
RIGHT UP HERE.
♪ Let me go ♪
IF YOU DON'T GET
ANOTHER CONCUSSION.
(ALL LAUGH)
(IMOGEN CLAPS)
DREW:
(CLEARS THROAT)
ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
THAT'S ENOUGH STANDING AROUND,
LET'S GET THIS PARTY STARTED!
♪ Your masquerade ♪
♪ I don't wanna be a part
of your parade ♪
DREW: HEY.
BECKY: HI.
I JUST WANTED
TO SAY THANKS.
ADAM LOVED A GOOD PARTY,
IT'S A SHAME
HE HAD TO MISS IT.
HE DIDN'T.
HE'S HERE.
I CAN FEEL IT.
THEN HE'D BE PRETTY MAD
AT THE WAY I TREATED
THE GIRL HE LOVED.
BECKY,
IT WASN'T YOUR FAULT.
IT WASN'T ANYONE'S.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
SO HOW DO WE MOVE ON?
I MEAN, WHAT DO WE DO?
I GUESS MAKE ADAM'S DEATH
MEAN SOMETHING.
♪ Maybe need some protection ♪
♪ But I'm a kid
like everyone else ♪
♪ So let me go ♪
♪ I don't wanna be your hero ♪