♪♪♪
(BOX RATTLES LIGHTLY)
ZIG:
MORNIN', MADAM.
WHOA! WHAT'S WITH
THE TEN GALLON?
IT'S FOR THE WILD WILD WEST
NIGHT.
YOU LIKE?
I LOVE.
IT'S VERY TIM MCGRAW.
ZIG: WHAT'S THAT?
MAYA: WHAT?
OH, IT'S NOTHING.
ZIG:
WELL, NOW I HAVE TO KNOW.
(SIGHS)
ZIG: COME ON, I JUST...
MAYA: NO.
ALL RIGHT, TRUCE.
WHO PUT THAT THERE?
MAYA:
WHAT?
ZIG!
IS THIS ANOTHER GIFT
FROM MILES?
I THOUGHT THAT YOU SAID
THAT YOU TWO WERE THROUGH.
MAYA:
YEAH, WE ARE.
SOUNDS LIKE HORSE FEATHERS
TO THIS COWBOY.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
OH, DID YOU GET
THE SALOON DOORS?
DREW:
INSTALLED IN THE GYM?
YUP. HEY, MIDWAY TICKETS?
PRINTED AND READY TO GO.
WHAT ABOUT THE WILD WEST
BACKDROP?
DREW:
IN THE PROP ROOM.
AND DID YOU GET THE HAY BALES
AND CORN?
CLARE:
CHECK AND CHECK.
AND I GOT EXTRA GUMMY BEARS
FOR THE CANDY TABLE.
DREW:
OH, YES!
ALLI:
UM, IS THIS THE WILD WILD WEST
PLANNING COMMITTEE,
OR THE WILD WILD WEST
PLANNING COUPLE?
UM, I WAS ALSO WONDERING,
DO YOU THINK
THE GRADE 10 MUSIC CLASS
CAN PLAY ANY SQUARE-DANCING
NUMBERS?
THIS ISN'T A DANCE.
BUT THERE COULD BE DANCING.
WHAT TEEN LIKES SQUARE DANCING?
I'LL DANCE WITH YOU,
CLARE.
DALLAS:
OF COURSE YOU WILL.
CLARE:
UM, ACTUALLY, I WAS...
I WAS THINKING ELI.
(CLEARS THROAT)
HE'S COMING?
YEAH, HE'S COMING.
HE'S MY BOYFRIEND.
YOU DON'T REALLY
MENTION HIM ANYMORE.
BECAUSE HE'S BUSY,
AND SO AM I.
AH, BUT WILD WILD WEST NIGHT
IS OUR CHANCE TO-
ALLI:
RIDE THE BUCKING BRONCO?
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
THAT REMINDS ME.
ELI JUST MADE A WESTERN
AT FILM SCHOOL,
SO WE'LL HAVE THE PERFECT HIS
AND HERS COWBOY COSTUMES.
SEE YOU GUYS LATER.
ALLI:
(CLEARS THROAT,
UNCOMFORTABLE)
(HANDCUFFS RATTLE)
LOOK, WHATEVER YOU THINK I DID,
I SWEAR YOU'RE WRONG.
JASON:
SO THAT ISN'T YOUR BAG?
IT IS,
BUT... NOT THE DRUGS.
THEN WHY WERE THEY
IN YOUR BAG?
JUST...
LET ME GO HOME.
BRET BARNETT:
AND SCENE!
GREAT!
REALLY GREAT.
THANKS FOR COMING IN.
ZOE:
I CAN DO THE SCENE AGAIN -
WITH MORE TEARS,
LESS TEARS,
NO TEARS AT ALL?
BRET BARNETT:
NAH, I THINK WE'RE GOOD.
(QUIETLY)
LET'S SEE THE NEXT ONE.
ZOE:
THANKS, BRET.
UH, MR. BARNETT.
I'M A HUGE FAN.
BRET BARNETT:
OH. WELL, HAVE A NICE DAY, UH...
ZOE:
ZOE. ZOE RIVAS.
BRET:
RIGHT. RIGHT, YEAH,
THERE YOU ARE.
I WAS ON WEST DRIVE.
AH.
ANY RECENT PROJECTS?
I TOOK A YEAR OFF...
TO GET SOME REAL LIFE
EXPERIENCE.
BRET:
OKAY. UH, WE'LL LET YOU KNOW.
UH, TOM...
(LOCK CLICKS,
LOCKER RATTLES)
TRISTAN:
MAYA MATLIN, CAT BURGLAR?
I'M NOT BURGLING.
I'M RETURNING.
YOU'RE BREAKING INTO
MILES' LOCKER
TO RETURN HIS GIFT?
WOW!
YOU REALLY DIDN'T LIKE IT.
NO, THE GIFT IS SUPER-SWEET,
TRIS.
THEN WHY AREN'T YOU
SHOWERING HIM WITH KISSES?
BECAUSE...
I'M WORRIED
THAT IF I SEE MILES...
I'LL CRUMBLE
AND TAKE HIM BACK.
WELL, I'M STILL NOT SEEING
A PROBLEM HERE.
I MISS HIM.
A LOT.
BUT ZIG KINDA TOLD ME
HE LIKES ME.
SERIOUSLY?
DO YOU LIKE HIM?
AS A FRIEND, YEAH.
THEN TELL HIM THAT.
THEN YOU AND MILES CAN GO BACK
TO A-COUPLE STATUS!
NO! ZIG WOULD FREAK,
TRIS!
HE WOULD MOVE OUT,
SELL DRUGS,
AND END UP DEAD IN A DITCH
SOMEWHERE!
YOU CAN'T KEEP THEM BOTH
ON THE HOOK.
YOU HAVE TO PICK
A TEAM.
I HAVE.
TRISTAN, MILES AND ZIG:
♪ OH SUSANNAH,
DON'T YOU CRY FOR ME ♪
♪ FOR I COME FROM ALABAMA
WITH A BANJO ON MY KNEE ♪
MS. OH AND STUDENTS:
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
MS. OH:
NICE JOB, EVERYONE!
ALL RIGHT,
WE'RE GONNA TAKE FIVE.
LOOK, I KNOW YOU SAID
NO MORE GIFTS,
BUT I JUST...
I SAW THE HARMONICA
AND I THOUGHT IT WAS PERFECT
FOR YOU.
IT WAS.
IT IS.
BUT YOU'RE GIVING IT BACK.
MILES,
YOU SCARE ME.
THE WAY YOU LASH OUT
AT YOUR DAD.
FRAMING ZIG.
I CAN BE A BETTER GUY.
JUST LET ME SHOW YOU.
PLEASE.
THE ONLY WAY
IT COULD POSSIBLY WORK...
WHAT? ANYTHING.
I'LL DO IT.
EVEN KEEP IT SECRET
FROM ZIG?
SERIOUSLY?
IT'S NOT FOR FOREVER,
JUST...
JUST UNTIL HE GETS HIS LIFE
BACK IN ORDER.
YEAH, YOU THINK
IT'S STUPID.
IT'S STUPID, RIGHT?
NOT IF IT GETS YOU BACK.
MAYA:
OH! SECRET, REMEMBER?
MILES:
YEAH.
PERINO:
TRISTAN.
MISS RIVAS.
ZOE:
FIFTY PERCENT.
CAN MY DAY GET
ANY WORSE?
WHO CARES ABOUT
YOUR SILLY HISTORY GRADE?
YOU'RE GONNA BE BRET BARNETT'S
LEADING LADY.
UNLIKELY.
I BLEW THE AUDITION.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
SORRY, TRIS.
I JUST WANNA GO HOME
AND CURL UP
WITH A GIANT MINT TEA.
PERINO:
NOT SO FAST, LITTLE LADY.
YOU BLEW YOUR HISTORY TEST.
ZOE:
I WAS BUSY PREPARING
FOR AN AUDITION.
PERINO:
YOU KNOW WHAT'S WEIRD?
YOU GOT 50% OF THE TEST
100% RIGHT.
I HAVE A PHOTOGRAPHIC MEMORY.
PERINO:
SO USE IT!
BRIGHT SPARKS COULD USE
AN EXTRA MEMBER.
YOU'LL GET EXTRA CREDIT
AND IT'LL HELP YOU PASS
THIS COURSE.
TRISTAN:
YOU WANT ZOE TO JOIN
THE NERD SQUAD?
IT'S A CHAMPIONSHIP
QUIZ TEAM.
TRISTAN:
YOU'RE NOT HELPING YOUR CASE,
MR. P.
(SHARP INHALE)
WE PRACTICE AT LUNCH.
LET ME HAVE A LOOK
AT THAT BOOK.
CLARE:
HEY, THANKS FOR PUSHING
FOR THIS EVENT.
I THINK IT'S GONNA BE
A FUN NIGHT.
DREW:
OH, YEAH, DON'T MENTION IT.
ALL RIGHT, SO WHAT DO THESE
MATCHING COSTUMES LOOK LIKE?
ACTUALLY, I DON'T KNOW YET.
ELI HASN'T CALLED ME BACK.
CLARE, YOU'VE GOTTA GRAB
THE BULL BY THE HORNS.
I CALLED HIM!
I TEXTED LIKE NINE TIMES!
WHAT MORE CAN I DO?
I WAS TALKING ABOUT
THIS BULL.
OH.
(HALF LAUGHS)
SORRY.
(CLARE'S PHONE RINGS)
HOWDY, PARDNER.
GOT YOUR COWBOY BOOTS
ALL SHINED UP?
ELI:
LOOK, I GOT BAD NEWS.
I CAN'T COME.
YOU'RE BAILING.
AGAIN.
LOOK, CLARE,
DON'T BE MAD.
WE KNEW LONG-DISTANCE
WAS GONNA BE HARD.
CLARE:
YEAH, BUT I THOUGHT
WE'D BOTH WORK AT IT.
I TOLD EVERYONE YOU WERE COMING.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO SAY?
THAT I'M AT SCHOOL,
IN NEW YORK,
MISSING YOU.
NOT EVEN I BUY THAT.
(PHONE BEEPS,
ENDING CALL)
(EXHALES FORCEFULLY)
YOU OKAY?
I WILL BE AS SOON AS WE GET
THIS THING DOWN TO THE GYM.
I'VE HAD ENOUGH BULL
FOR ONE DAY.
COME ON.
(BELL DINGS)
COGNITIVE DISSONANCE!
PERINO:
CORRECT, ALLI!
ANCIENT EGYPTIANS USED
THIS PLANT TO MAKE PAPER.
ALLI: PAPYRUS!
PERINO: CORRECT!
ARE YOU SURE YOU HAVE
A PHOTOGRAPHIC MEMORY?
YOU HAVEN'T ANSWERED
A SINGLE QUESTION.
PERINO:
WHICH GREEK GOD WORE WINGED
SANDALS AND A WAIST POUCH?
(BELL DINGS)
HERMES.
LIKE THE HANDBAGS.
PERINO:
ACTUALLY, IT'S HERMES,
LIKE THE GOD,
BUT CLOSE ENOUGH!
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
SO HOW MANY EXTRA MARKS
DO I GET
FOR BEING ON THIS TEAM?
ALLI:
AH, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
IT TAKES MORE THAN ANSWERING
ONE QUESTION
TO GET ON THE TEAM.
ZOE:
COME ON, GUYS,
I NEED THIS,
OR I'LL BE STUCK
AT DEGRASSI FOREVER.
MR. PERINO,
YOU SAID I'D BE GOOD!
PERINO:
ALLI'S THE CAPTAIN.
(SIGHS)
WELL...
YOU NEED THIS
AND WE NEED YOU,
SO AS LONG
AS YOU GET STUDYING.
WE PRACTICE AGAIN
IN THE MORNING.
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
UNGH! TRISTAN...
OH, SORRY.
BRIGHT SPARKS?
ZOE, NO.
PEOPLE WILL JUDGE.
PEOPLE LIKE ME.
IF MY ACTING CAREER
IS A BUST,
I MAY AS WELL
GET A DECENT GRADE.
BECAUSE EVEN THOUGH EVERYONE
AT DEGRASSI
SEES ME AS A VICTIM,
I'M APPARENTLY
NOT GOOD ENOUGH
TO PLAY ONE
FOR BRET BARNETT.
THAT'S IT.
WAIT.
DOES BRET KNOW ABOUT
YOUR ASSAULT?
THE AGONIZING WAIT
FOR THE TRIAL?
NOT EXACTLY SOMETHING
I WANNA TRUMPET AROUND.
IF IT GETS YOU THE PART...
YOU THINK I SHOULD PLAY
THE VICTIM CARD?
SOMETHING TERRIBLE
HAPPENED TO YOU.
USE IT.
YOU DESERVE
A HAPPY ENDING.
(DIALLING BEEPS)
TRISTAN:
REMEMBER, I GET TO BE HEAD
OF YOUR ENTOURAGE!
GUYS, ARE YOU DONE YET?
MILES:
FIVE MORE MINUTES, PLEASE.
KEEP WATCHING FOR ZIG.
I'VE MISSED YOU
SO MUCH.
ME TOO.
WINSTON:
THE CROW FLIES AT MIDNIGHT!
MAYA:
HUH?
WINSTON:
THE BLACK DOG APPROACHES!
MILES:
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT,
CHEWY?
WINSTON: ZIG IS COMING!
MAYA: OH NO!
MAYA:
UM... THANKS.
WINSTON:
FOR THE LAST TIME,
STOP WITH THE BICKERING!
AM I INTERRUPTING SOMETHING?
NO.
NO, NO.
MM-MM.
NO.
NO!
OKAY.
UM...
MAYA, DO YOU THINK
WE COULD TALK?
IN PRIVATE.
MAYA:
YEAH.
WHY NOT?
SO WHAT'S UP, ZIG?
ZIGMUND?
ZIGGY MCZIG-ZIG.
ZIG:
I JUST WANTED TO APOLOGIZE
FOR BEING AN ASS THIS MORNING.
MAYA:
OH, DON'T...
DON'T SWEAT IT.
ZIG:
UM, THERE'S MORE, ACTUALLY.
UM...
SO THIS MORNING WHEN YOU SAID
THAT YOU AND MILES ARE THROUGH,
WERE YOU BEING SERIOUS
OR...?
YEAH.
TOTALLY SERIOUS.
WELL, THEN, UM...
I DON'T KNOW,
MAYBE IT'S TIME THAT...
THAT FOR YOU GAVE US
A CHANCE.
MAYA:
UM...
ZIG:
WHAT'S WRONG?
MAYA, I LIKE YOU.
WELL, UM...
WHAT ABOUT MY MOM
AND HER HOUSE RULES?
RIGHT.
AND I'LL RESPECT
THE RULES.
BUT I'M NOT GONNA BE LIVING
AT YOUR HOUSE FOREVER.
I JUST NEED TO KNOW
THAT YOU'LL WAIT FOR ME.
(MUMBLES)
OF COURSE.
ZIG:
I CAN'T LOSE YOU
TO ANOTHER GUY.
ALLI:
THAT LYING, CHEATING, DIRTBAG!
I'M SO TIRED OF HIM
MAKING ME FEEL LIKE CRAP.
WHAT ARE WE TALKING HERE?
BREAKING UP?
IS THIS ABOUT DREW?
NO!
I... I THINK I'M IN LOVE WITH
THE IDEA OF ELI FROM BEFORE.
FROM BEFORE WE HAD TROUBLE
COMMUNICATING.
BEFORE LENORE...
OH YEAH,
I FORGOT THAT NEW YORK ELI
WAS SUCH A DIRTY-
RAT! AGGHHH!
EXACTLY!
NO, NO, LIKE AN ACTUAL RAT
JUST RAN ACROSS MY FEET!
ALLI:
EW! WELL, IS YOUR MOM HOME?
CLARE:
NO! THEY'RE AWAY AT SOME
WOOD-WORKING CONFERENCE.
CAN YOU COME OVER?
I LOVE YA, CLARE,
BUT I AM NOT KILLING A RAT
FOR YOU!
IF ELI WERE HERE-
HE'D MAKE A DOCUMENTARY
ABOUT IT?
WELL, I NEED SOMEONE!
(RAT SQUEAKS,
CLARE YELPS)
ZOE:
WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO DO TO ME?
BRET BARNETT:
ZOE!
ZOE RIVAS.
READY FOR YOUR SCREEN TEST?
ZOE: OF COURSE.
BRET: GREAT.
THANKS AGAIN FOR GIVING ME
THIS CHANCE, BRET.
BRET:
YEAH.
UM, SO, LIKE BEFORE,
FROM THE TOP?
BRET:
YEAH. THIS IS GONNA BE
THAT MOMENT
WHEN SHE REALIZES
ALL HOPE IS LOST.
AND SHE'S SCARED,
SHE'S DESPERATE,
SHE'S ALONE,
AND I WANT YOU TO TAP
INTO THE FEELING YOU FELT
WHEN YOU WERE ASSAULTED.
OKAY?
ACTION.
HELP!
CAN ANYONE HEAR ME?!
JASON:
OH... THEY DIDN'T TELL ME
YOU WERE SO PRETTY.
STAY AWAY.
JASON:
OH...
DON'T WORRY.
I PROMISED YOUR PARENTS
I WOULDN'T HURT YOU
ONCE THEY PAID THE RANSOM.
LUCKY FOR ME,
THEY HAVEN'T PAID.
(DEEP, RASPY INHALE)
WHAT TO DO WHILE WE WAIT...
DO YOU ANY IDEAS?
NEIL:
(ON VIDEO) NICE.
OH, DUDE!
JASON:
'CAUSE, UM...
(SMACKS LIPS)
I GOT ONE.
GET YOUR HANDS OFF ME.
JASON:
OH NO, NO, NO.
DON'T WORRY.
NEIL:
(ON VIDEO)
OH, DUDE!
LUKE:
WE WERE PARTYING.
WE WERE HAVING FUN.
YOU LIKED IT.
JASON: (PAINED YELP)
CREW: OH MY GOSH!
JASON:
OWWW! WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
ZOE:
OH MY GOD!
I'M SO SORRY.
THAT'S GONNA LEAVE A MARK!
BRET BARNETT:
ZOE, WHAT'S HAPPENING?
I'M SO- I'M SORRY.
IT'S JUST...
(STAMMERING, EMOTIONAL)
CAN I TAKE A MINUTE?
BRET:
YEAH, TAKE FIVE.
GET HER...
GET HER OUTTA THERE.
COME ON, JASON.
GET YOU SOME ICE FOR THAT.
JASON:
YEAH, WE'RE GONNA NEED
A LOT OF ICE.
BRET:
I'M SURE IT WAS JUST
HEAT OF THE MOMENT.
YOU KNOW, IT WAS METHOD.
MAYBE SHE'S METHOD.
(SET DOOR CLOSES)
CLARE:
YOU GOT IT?
NO, IT'S GOING...
DREW:
OH NO! OH, IT'S UNDERNEATH
THE THINGAMAJIG.
CLARE: WHERE'S IT GOING?
DREW: WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
CLARE: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
DREW: IT'S COMING BACK TO YOU.
CLARE: NO! AHHH!
DREW: COMING BACK. HE'S COMING!
DREW:
THE STOVE! OKAY, COME ON.
COME ON, LITTLE GUY.
COME ON.
OH... NO, NO!
CLARE:
NO, NOT UNDER THE FRIDGE!
DREW:
(CLEARS HIS THROAT)
WELL, I GUESS HE LIVES HERE NOW.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
FINE, I'LL MOVE THE FRIDGE
AND YOU CHASE OUT THE RAT.
(RELUCTANT WHIMPER)
READY?
NOT EVEN A LITTLE.
THREE...
TWO...
(DREW GRUNTS,
FRIDGE RATTLES)
(DREW AND CLARE
YELP AND SQUEAL)
DREW:
GO, GO, GO, GO, GO, GO, GO!
CLARE:
(RELIEVED GASP)
DREW:
AH. WE MAKE A PRETTY GOOD TEAM,
EDWARDS!
(LAUGHS,
GASPS FOR BREATH)
DREW:
WOO!
(EMOTIONAL BREATHS)
DREW:
WHAT'S WRONG?
OH, NOTHING.
I'M FINE.
LOOK,
YOU DON'T DESERVE THIS.
WHAT, A RAT IN MY HOUSE?
NO, TO FEEL LIKE THIS.
YOU DESERVE A GUY
WHO MAKES YOU FEEL GOOD, CLARE.
A GUY WHO SHOWS UP.
LIKE YOU?
LOOK,
YOU'RE ALL ALONE TONIGHT.
I... I CAN STAY.
NO.
NO, YOU CAN'T.
NOT WHILE I'M STILL WITH ELI.
THEN MAYBE YOU SHOULDN'T
BE WITH ELI ANYMORE.
WHERE'S JASON?
BRET:
SENT HIM HOME.
I THINK WE'RE DONE
FOR THE DAY.
ZOE:
I'M SORRY,
I REALLY DIDN'T MEAN TO DO THAT.
WHAT, HEADBUTT YOUR CO-STAR
DURING A SCREEN TEST?
I SHOULD HOPE NOT.
I WAS TRYING TO CHANNEL
MY ASSAULT LIKE YOU ASKED,
BUT I JUST... OVERLOADED.
LIKE I WAS RIGHT BACK THERE.
YEAH, I SAW THAT.
I DIDN'T KNOW
IT STILL AFFECTS ME THIS MUCH.
BRET:
SO, MAYBE INSTEAD
OF THIS ROLE,
YOU'LL FOCUS
ON SOME THERAPY, HUH?
ZOE:
WAIT, NO, NO, NO.
YOU'VE GOTTA GIVE ME
ANOTHER CHANCE.
PLEASE!
EVER SINCE THAT NIGHT,
EVERYTHING IN MY LIFE
FEELS TAINTED.
I WANT THIS GIG.
I NEED A WIN.
I PROMISE I CAN DO IT.
YOU SAW I CAN MAKE IT REAL.
LET ME THINK ABOUT IT,
OKAY?
ELI:
YOU'VE REACHED ELI'S MESSAGES!
LEAVE ONE.
(PHONE BEEPS)
HEY, ELI, IT'S ME.
I JUST...
I REALLY, UH...
I REALLY NEED
TO TALK TO YOU.
SO PLEASE CALL ME BACK
AS SOON AS YOU CAN.
NO, ACTUALLY,
THAT'S NOT GOOD ENOUGH.
I NEEDED YOU, ELI,
AND YOU DITCHED ME.
I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU IN WEEKS...
AND I HAVE FELT SO ALONE.
I'VE TRIED TO CONVINCE MYSELF
THAT THINGS ARE FINE,
BUT...
MAYBE WE'VE BEEN FIGHTING
TOO HARD
TO KEEP SOMETHING ALIVE
THAT'S ALREADY GONE.
♪ Drain the blood
before you go ♪
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
I...
I GUESS WHAT I'M SAYING IS...
IT'S OVER, ELI.
MAYBE IT HAS BEEN
FOR A WHILE
BUT WE BOTH JUST DIDN'T
REALIZE.
(PHONE BEEPS)
PHONE RECORDING:
END OF VOICE MESSAGE SPACE.
TO RE-RECORD, PRESS ONE.
TO DELETE, PRESS TWO.
IF YOU ARE SATISFIED
WITH YOUR MESSAGE,
PRESS THREE.
♪ Drain the blood
before you go ♪
PHONE RECORDING:
VOICE MESSAGE SENT.
(SHAKY EXHALE)
♪ So we can watch... ♪
PERINO:
IN WHAT CITY WOULD I FIND
WESTMINSTER ABBEY?
ZOE: LONDON!
PERINO: CORRECT!
SOMEONE'S BEEN STUDYING!
HAD TO KEEP MY MIND BUSY.
WAITING TO HEAR BACK
ABOUT A ROLE.
PERINO:
WHAT FREUDIAN TERM
REFERS TO URGES
THAT ARE SATISFIED
AND PLEASURABLE?
(BELL DINGS,
ZOE'S PHONE VIBRATES)
YOU ONLY GET FIVE SECONDS.
YES!
PERINO:
I'M SORRY,
THAT ANSWER IS INCORRECT.
IT'S LIBIDO.
YOU HAVE TO PAY
BETTER ATTENTION.
ACTUALLY,
I DON'T HAVE TO DO ANYTHING
WITH YOU NERDS ANYMORE.
BECAUSE BRET BARNETT
JUST CAST ME
IN HIS NEW MOVIE!
SO YOU'RE JUST DITCHING
THE TEAM?
THEY ASKED ME TO START
RIGHT AWAY.
ZOE RIVAS IS BACK, BABY.
(COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYS)
♪ I SAW YOU AT THE MOVIE SHOW ♪
♪ JUST THE OTHER DAY ♪
♪ BUT I WAS WITH
MY OTHER LOVE ♪
♪ SO I LOOKED THE OTHER WAY ♪
♪ I DIDN'T WANT TO HURT HIM ♪
♪ COULDN'T BEAR FOR HIM
TO SEE ♪
♪ THE WAY THAT I WOULD
LOOK AT YOU ♪
♪ AND THE WAY
YOU'D LOOK AT ME ♪
♪ TRA LA LA LA,
TRIANGLE ♪
♪ WHAT'LL I DO ABOUT YOU? ♪
♪ WHAT'LL I DO ♪
♪ ABOUT YOU? ♪
(TRIANGLE DINGS,
MS. OH AND STUDENTS CHEER)
YOU GUYS ARE GONNA ROCK TONIGHT.
GREAT JOB, MAYA.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
GOOD CLASS, EVERYONE.
ZIG:
SO I GUESS ALL OUR LATE NIGHT
PRACTICES REALLY PAID OFF, HUH?
YOU WANNA GO GRAB LUNCH?
MAYA:
UM, I THINK I'M JUST GONNA
STICK AROUND,
REHEARSE SOME MORE.
WELL, I CAN WAIT.
NO, I'LL BE PROBABLY
A LONG TIME.
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
SEE YOU IN THE RUBBER ROOM,
I GUESS.
(SCOFFS LIGHTLY)
MAYA:
HEY.
MILES:
I CAN'T DO THIS.
MAYA:
WHAT? WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
MILES:
THIS.
WATCHING YOU AND ZIG...
HIM GRINNING LIKE HE'S WON!
I'M WITH YOU.
YOU KNOW THAT.
I KNOW,
BUT HE DOESN'T.
LOOK, MILES,
I KINDA NEED YOU
TO BE THE BIGGER PERSON HERE,
OKAY?
I CAN'T.
I MEAN,
HE'S BASICALLY MARKED YOU.
YOU'VE BEEN STRINGING HIM
ALONG FOR A YEAR, MAYA.
WHY?
(SCOFFS)
I'M...
I'M JUST TRYING TO MAKE SURE
NO ONE GETS HURT.
YEAH,
TOO LATE FOR THAT.
Maya:
♪ What'll I do ♪
♪ About you? ♪