♪♪♪
TECHNICIAN: (OVER SPEAKER)
CLARE, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
YES.
TECHNICIAN:
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
OTHER THAN TERRIFIED?
TECHNICIAN:
IT'S NORMAL TO BE SCARED
BEFORE AN MRI.
YOU'LL BE FINE.
RIGHT.
JUST A MASSIVE MACHINE
BLASTING MY BRAIN
TO SEE IF THE CANCER'S SPREAD.
WHY WORRY?
TECHNICIAN:
IT'S CRITICAL YOU DON'T MOVE
DURING THE SCAN.
LIE STILL.
WAIT!
WHAT IF I HAVE TO SNEEZE?
TECHNICIAN:
TELL ME, AND I'LL PRESS PAUSE.
AND IF I GET ITCHY?
TECHNICIAN:
CLARE, ARE YOU STALLING?
IS IT THAT OBVIOUS?
TECHNICIAN:
TAKE A DEEP BREATH FOR ME.
YOUR BOYFRIEND AND YOUR MOM
ARE RIGHT OUTSIDE.
YOU'RE NOT ALONE, OKAY?
NOW, JUST LET ME KNOW
WHEN YOU'RE READY.
(CLARE SIGHS)
(TAKES A DEEP BREATH)
LET'S DO IT.
(MRI MACHINE WHIRS
AND BEEPS)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ (The best that I can be) ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(ALLI SIGHS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
CAN I GET ONE OF THOSE LITTLE
"PETIT NOIR" THINGS
YOU GAVE ME THE OTHER DAY?
AS YOU WISH.
ANYTHING ELSE, MADEMOISELLE?
UH, THAT'S IT.
MERCI!
(BOTH LAUGH)
(SIGHS)
AGGHHH!
OH!
WHAT ARE YOU,
A GRAVEDIGGER NOW?
NO, CONNOR BOUGHT IT
FOR ME
WHEN WE VISITED
THE CATACOMBS
FOR OUR FRENCH PROJECT.
MMM... ROMANTIC.
JENNA:
DO YOU KNOW THEY MOVED
SIX MILLION BONES THERE
FROM ALL OVER PARIS?
(GIGGLES)
OKAY, WHAT ABOUT YOU?
DID YOU HAVE FUN
AT THE LOUVRE?
I HAVEN'T EXACTLY
MADE IT THERE YET.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT,
BECAUSE YOU'VE BEEN
FLIRTING
WITH THAT SUPER HOT WAITER
ALL DAY!
THAT'S LEO,
THE GUY THAT SAVED ME.
ALLI BHANDARI,
YOU'RE BLUSHING!
I'VE NEVER SEEN YOU
LIKE THIS BEFORE!
I KNOW,
BUT WHEN I'M NEAR HIM,
MY HEART STARTS RACING,
AND MY STOMACH
DOES FLIP-FLOPS.
AND HE'S JUST A STRANGER,
JENNA!
JENNA:
THEN GET TO KNOW HIM BETTER.
ALLI:
I KNOW, I'M TRYING.
I'VE BEEN HERE ALL DAY
AND HE HASN'T EVEN
ASKED ME OUT YET.
SO WHY DON'T YOU TRY
ASKING HIM OUT?
ALLI:
(CLEARS THROAT)
LEO?
UN PETIT NOIR
POUR LA BELLE FILLE.
ALLI:
LEO, WAIT!
WOULD YOU MAYBE WANNA DO
SOMETHING WITH ME?
I'M DONE AT THREE.
SOUNDS GREAT.
OH NO, WHAT ABOUT
YOUR PRESENTATION?
RIGHT.
UH... HOW'S FOUR?
YOU'RE DEFINITELY WORTH
THE WAIT.
(SURPRISED GASP)
(BOTH GIGGLE)
TRISTAN:
WAIT, SO HOW DO YOU SAY "ECLAIR"
IN FRENCH?
MILES: ECLAIR.
TRISTAN: OH! (GIGGLES)
TRISTAN:
OH, WHAT A BEAUTIFUL DAY!
THE SUN IS SHINING,
THE BOYS ARE STUNNING,
THE ECLAIRS, PERFECT!
SO YOU'RE EATING
CARBS NOW?
OH, NOT A CHANCE.
THIS IS LIKE 400 CALORIES.
BUT MILES GOT IT FOR ME.
SO CUTE, RIGHT?
TRIS, YESTERDAY MILES
WAS ENEMY NUMERO UNO,
AND NOW YOU GUYS ARE
BEST FRIENDS?
AND HOPEFULLY SOON,
BFS.
AS IN BOYFRIENDS,
ROMANTIC PARTNERS.
OH, HE HUGGED ME IN HIS BOXERS
LAST NIGHT, MAYA!
IT LINGERED.
I KNOW!
YOU'VE ONLY TOLD ME
LIKE FIFTY TIMES!
BUT I'M STILL NOT CONVINCED
HE'S INTO GUYS.
WINSTON?
OH NO, MILES.
WE'RE GONNA BE BFS.
NOT IF I GET TO HIM FIRST.
HE PLAYS FOR MY TEAM.
DON'T UNDERESTIMATE
THE POWER OF GATSBY GARCIA.
(BELL RINGS)
MME. CLIQUET:
BONJOUR, LES ELEVES!
AUJOURD'HUI, JE VOUS DONNE
UN DEVOIRS SAVEUR!
VOUS AVEZ ACHETER D'ALIMENTS
D'EPICERIES LOCALE,
ET VOUS ALLEZ PREPARER
UN REPAS FRANCAISE
POUR VOS CAMARADES.
ICI, VOTRE LISTE DE COURSE!
MILES:
(CLEARS HIS THROAT)
SHE WANTS US TO BUY
FRENCH FOOD
FOR THE CLASS TO SAMPLE.
YEAH, I'LL TAKE A HANDOUT.
MME. CLIQUET:
TRES BIEN.
EN GROUPS DE DEUX,
S'IL VOUS PLAIT.
GROUPS OF TWO!
TRISTAN AND ZOE:
PARTNERS?
SURE, TRIS.
HMPH!
ANNOUNCEMENT ON PA:
DR. CARTER TO ADMITTING,
PLEASE.
DR. CARTER TO ADMITTING.
IF THE CANCER HAS SPREAD
TO MY BRAIN,
REGULAR CHEMOTHERAPY
WON'T FIX IT.
THEN THEY'LL TRY
SOMETHING ELSE.
CLARE:
RADIATION, EVEN SURGERY,
IF THE TUMOR'S OPERABLE.
CLARE, PUT DOWN
THE COMPUTER.
WHY DON'T WE WATCH A MOVIE?
I BROUGHT "LIFE OF PI."
(KNOCKING)
MARIELLE:
KNOCK, KNOCK.
CHEMO'S ALL DONE FOR THE DAY.
CLARE:
SO NO MRI RESULTS?
MARIELLE:
LAST I HEARD, THE RADIOLOGIST
IS REVIEWING YOUR SCANS
WITH THE ONCOLOGY TEAM
THIS AFTERNOON.
THAT SOUNDS BAD.
IS THAT BAD?
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, CAN'T YOU
SNEAK A PEEK?
DON'T PESTER THE NURSE.
IF I'M DYING,
I HAVE A RIGHT TO KNOW!
ELI:
WHOA! OKAY, NOBODY'S DYING HERE!
HELEN:
ELI'S RIGHT.
YOU DON'T KNOW THAT!
ELI:
CLARE!
WELL, SHE DOESN'T!
I'LL TRY AND GET AN ETA
ON THE MRI RESULTS.
SO "LIFE OF PI?"
NO. ACTUALLY,
I THINK I'D LIKE
TO VISIT A FRIEND.
SOMEONE I MET IN GROUP.
♪♪♪
UH, DEUX BAGUETTES,
ET UN CAMEMBERT,
S'IL VOUS PLAIT.
SHE'S CUTE, HUH?
UH, NOT REALLY MY TYPE.
(RAP SONG PLAYS)
OH! MY! GOD!
I LOVE THIS SONG!
OH, I ACTUALLY KNOW
THIS SONG.
I UH...
NEVER MIND.
OKAY, NOW YOU HAVE
TO TELL ME!
(SIGHS)
I DID A DANCE TO IT.
EXCUSE ME,
LOUDER PLEASE?
I DID A DANCE TO IT.
MILES HOLLINGSWORTH THE THIRD
DANCER?
DETAILS, STAT!
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
I TOOK A CLASS FOR A BIT.
TRISTAN:
WHAT, LIKE BALLET?
MILES:
YEAH, I-I DID BALLET
TO THIS SONG.
NO, IT WAS HIP HOP.
MY SISTER WAS IN TAP
NEXT DOOR,
SO IT WAS EITHER I SAT AROUND
BORED THREE NIGHTS A WEEK,
OR I LEARNED.
I LEARNED.
TRISTAN:
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR,
SHOW ME!
MILES:
(LAUGHS)
I DON'T REMEMBER IT.
WHEN MY DAD FOUND OUT
THAT I WAS IN THE CLASS,
HE PULLED THE PLUG.
OH, WELL, YOU'RE LIKE
A REAL LIFE BILLY ELLIOTT!
WELL, MINUS THE BRITISH
AND MINING.
WERE YOU FURIOUS
WITH YOUR DAD?
HE-HE JUST DOESN'T GET ME.
NEVER HAS.
I GET IT.
I'M SORRY, MILES.
YEAH, BOO-HOO RICH KID,
RIGHT?
BUT, UH, YOU KNOW,
THANKS, TRIS.
YOU'RE...
YOU'RE EASY TO TALK TO.
I AM SO SORRY!
I SENSED A MOMENT, AND-
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
IT'S FINE, ALL RIGHT?
IT'S COOL.
COME ON, I KNOW A PLACE
THAT HAS GREAT FOIE GRAS.
(TRISTAN HALF LAUGHS)
ALLI:
ET EN FAIT,
J'AI VU LA GRANDE DAME -
LE MONA LISA.
ELLE ETAIT GRANDE
ET SPLENDIDE.
JE N'AI POURVU ADMIRE
CONCLUT AUX CETTE JOURNEE
SPECIALE
AU MUSEE DE LOUVRE.
MERCI, ALLI.
MAINTENANT, VOS NOTES.
ALLI BHANDARI,
ASSEZ BIEN.
HENRI, TU FAIRE A LA PROCHAINE
PRESENTATION?
ALLI:
ASSEZ BIEN?!
"GOOD ENOUGH?"
WHAT'S THE LETTER GRADE
FOR THAT?
UH...
I GOT A C?!
UM...
EXCUSE ME, MADAME,
THERE MUST BE A MISTAKE
WITH MY GRADE.
YOU SHOULD BE HAPPY WITH
ASSEZ BIEN, MADEMOISELLE.
IT'S CLEAR YOU DID NOT
GO TO THE LOUVRE.
YOU DESCRIBED THE MONA LISA
AS "BIG."
OKAY, LOOK, MADAME,
I KNOW I MESSED UP,
BUT IS THERE ANY WAY
I CAN HAVE A REDO?
FIVE HUNDRED WORDS
ON THE LOUVRE BY TOMORROW,
AND THIS TIME, GO!
PAS DE PROBLEME!
JENNA:
ACTUALLY,
THAT IS A TRES BIG PROBLEME.
YOU HAVE A DATE!
RIGHT.
WELL, WHAT'S MORE ROMANTIC
THAN A MUSEUM?
(MONITORS BEEP)
CLARE, WHAT'RE YOU
DOING HERE?
I WAS LOOKING
FOR PAULA.
I SWEAR SHE SAID 423.
I MUST HAVE THE WRONG ROOM.
MARIELLE:
THIS WAS PAULA'S ROOM.
SHE'S OUT ALREADY,
LUCKY DUCK!
WHEN?
MARIELLE:
EARLY THIS MORNING.
I'M SORRY, CLARE!
WE HAD THE SAME CANCER.
HEY, I GOT YOUR TEXT,
WHAT'S THE EMERGENCY?
WE NEED TO TALK
"WELCOME BACK DAY" AT DEGRASSI,
MR. PRESIDENT.
YOU TOOK ME AWAY
FROM CAMP
TO TALK ABOUT SOMETHING
THAT'S TWO MONTHS AWAY?
LET'S START BY DISCUSSING
ORIENTATION FOR NEW STUDENTS.
I WAS UM,
I WAS THINKING THAT
WE COULD PAIR THE NINERS WITH-
(DOG WHINES)
WHAT WAS THAT?
UH...NOTHING.
(DOG WHIMPERS)
(BARKS)
(LAUGHS)
YOU BROUGHT A DOG
TO A HOSPITAL?!
NO, I WAS BRINGING HIM
TO CAMP,
AND YOU RUSHED ME
OVER HERE!
(SIGHS)
OH NO.
THERE ARE CLEANING SUPPLIES
IN THE BATHROOM.
UH, AREN'T YOU
GONNA HELP?
(SCOFFS) CANCER!
CAN'T GET AN INFECTION.
URINE'S STERILE.
COME ON, BUDDY!
THE ONE SCIENTIFIC FACT
YOU KNOW!
(DREW LAUGHS)
SO WHAT WAS THIS "MEETING"
REALLY ABOUT?
WELL, ANY MINUTE, A DOCTOR'S
GONNA WALK THROUGH THAT DOOR
AND TELL ME IF MY CANCER
HAS GOTTEN WORSE.
SCARY.
I'M NOT READY.
I DON'T WANT THESE FOUR WALLS
TO BE THE LAST ONES I SEE.
YOU COULD ALWAYS LEAVE.
♪♪♪
LEO:
ET VOILA!
WOW! THAT IS BEAUTIFUL.
LEO:
IT'S MY FAVOURITE SPOT
IN PARIS.
ALLI:
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN
TO THE LOUVRE?
LEO:
MANY TIMES.
WHAT'S YOUR FAVOURITE
PAINTING?
THE LAST SUPPER,
OF COURSE.
BUT MOSTLY I LOVE
THE INTERIOR -
THE GLASS, THE LIGHTS.
I WILL SHOW YOU SOMETIME.
WELL, HOW ABOUT NOW?
WE SHOULD HURRY THOUGH,
BECAUSE IT CLOSES IN AN HOUR.
ALLI, I'M SORRY
IF THIS PICNIC DATE
IS A DISAPPOINTMENT
TO YOU.
NO, THE PICNIC ISN'T
THE PROBLEM.
I FLUNKED
AN ASSIGNMENT TODAY.
OH, LET ME GUESS,
ON THE LOUVRE?
YEAH, AND I'VE BEEN GIVEN
A CHANCE TO REDO,
SO I THOUGHT MAYBE
WE COULD-
I WOULD DO IT
FOR YOU?
YOU ASKED ME OUT ON A DATE
SO I WOULD DO YOUR HOMEWORK?
NO! NO, THAT'S NOT
WHAT I MEANT AT ALL,
I WAS-
IT SURE LOOKS THAT WAY
TO ME!
BON APPETIT.
(GROANS)
LEO, I-
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
CLARE, YOU ALMOST READY?
HMM.
SO THE NURSES ARE GONNA
THINK YOU'RE SLEEPING.
I'VE GOT A STRETCHER
OUT IN THE HALL.
ALL YOU GOTTA DO IS
THROW OVER YOUR HEAD AND...
PRETEND LIKE YOU'RE UM...
DEAD?!
YEAH!
IS THAT GONNA BE WEIRD?
THIS ISN'T A PRISON, DREW!
AS LONG AS THE NURSES DON'T SEE,
WE'RE GOOD.
OH. OKAY.
WELL, I GOTTA DROP
WAFFLES OFF AT CAMP
AND THEN WE CAN GO
ON AN ADVENTURE.
WHAT DID YOU WANNA DO?
OH WAIT, NO,
UH... ROCK CLIMBING?
NO, BUNGEE JUMPING!
OH, I GOT IT.
SKYDIVING!
S-SKYDIVING?
YEAH.
THAT COULD ACTUALLY
KILL ME.
I JUST WANT TO BE
A REGULAR GIRL FOR A DAY,
AND ALL OF MY FRIENDS
ARE AT CAMP.
TO DEGRASSI!
TELL ME THE TRUTH DOCTOR,
AM I GONNA DIE?
NOT ON MY WATCH!
(BOTH LAUGH)
♪ You've got everything ♪
♪ When you're close to me ♪
♪ You're all around ♪
OMLG!
MAYA, I HAVE NEWS!
OMLG?
"OH MY LADY GAGA."
GUESS WHAT THE NEWS IS
ALREADY!
OKAY, UM...
DOES IT INVOLVE MILES?
HEY, YOU'RE GUESSING
TOO SLOW!
WE KISSED!
SERIOUSLY?
OH, MY HEART EXPLODED!
W-WOW. SO ARE YOU GUYS
LIKE DATING NOW?
I DON'T KNOW,
I MEAN,
I GUESS I HAVE TO ASK HIM OUT
ON AN OFFICIAL DATE FIRST.
UNLESS HE ASKS ME FIRST!
(GASPS) OH MY GOSH!
ALL MY DREAMS
ARE COMING TRUE,
NOW I JUST NEED
THAT BLAZER!
(LAUGHS)
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
OKAY, GIRAFFES HERE
AND IGUANAS HERE!
DREW:
WELCOME TO SPORTS DAY, CLARE!
I-I THOUGHT IT WAS
ANIMAL DAY.
WHAT, BECAUSE OF THE DOG?
NO, NO, NO, NO,
IT'S THE PRIZE FOR THE WINNER.
THEY GET TO PLAY
WITH HIM.
UH, THEY LET YOU OUT
OF THE HOSPITAL?
I WOULDN'T SAY "LET."
MADISON:
I DON'T WANT TO BE
YOUR PARTNER, COLTON!
I WANT TO WIN!
MIND IF I TRY COUNSELORING?
I CAN BE YOUR PARTNER.
I'M CLARE.
YOU DON'T LOOK VERY FAST.
WELL, I'M FASTER THAN HIM.
ADAM:
YOU SURE YOU'RE OKAY?
NEVER BETTER!
NOW, ON WITH THE RACE!
OKAY, COLTON, MADISON,
AND... PINK,
LET'S SEE HOW FAST
YOU GUYS ARE.
READY? SET?
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
CLARE:
GO, COLTON!
YOU CAN DO IT!
YEAH, MADISON!
WOO!
HUH?
♪ Starlight shines bright
in my eyes ♪
♪ I see you,
I want, I want you tonight ♪
(GAGS)
♪ And I know it's too late ♪
I-I JUST NEED A MINUTE.
YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU'RE GOING TO PUKE.
(RETCHES)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
GUYS, WATER BREAK!
KIDS:
YEAH! WOO HOO!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(GUITAR PLAYS)
OH NO.
WHAT HAPPENED?
LEO DITCHED ME
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE DATE.
JENNA:
OKAY, START AT THE BEGINNING.
HE TOOK ME
TO THE MOST BEAUTIFUL SPOT.
JEALOUS!
WE COULD SEE
THE WHOLE CITY.
MORE JEALOUS.
ALLI:
HE BROUGHT CHEESE
AND BREAD,
AND SPARKLING WINE,
BUT HE COULD TELL THAT
I WAS OBVIOUSLY DISTRACTED.
JENNA:
THE ASSIGNMENT.
SO I SUGGESTED
WE GO TO THE LOUVRE
SO I COULD FINISH IT.
MAYA:
SERIOUSLY?
YOU WERE ON LIKE,
THE MOST ROMANTIC DATE EVER!
WITH THE DREAMIEST GUY.
AND YOU TOLD HIM
YOU'D RATHER DO HOMEWORK?
I KNOW, I KNOW.
I MESSED UP.
WELL, YOU WIN SOME,
YOU LOSE SOME.
ALLI:
YEAH, BUT THE PROBLEM IS,
I DON'T WANT TO LOSE LEO.
(SIGHS)
(KIDS SHOUT)
COLTON: WHAT DID IT LOOK LIKE?
MADISON: IT WAS JUST GROSS.
YOU LIE,
YOU'RE NOT FAST.
WELL, AT LEAST
WE GOT A TROPHY!
EVERYONE GOT A TROPHY.
COLTON:
WHY DID YOU THROW UP?
WERE YOU NERVOUS?
CLARE:
NO, I'M SICK.
HOW SICK?
I WISH I KNEW.
(COUGHS LOUDLY)
YOU JUST COUGHED
IN MY FACE!
I HAVE A COLD.
YOU HAVE A COLD?!
AN INFECTION COULD KILL ME!
DREW:
HEY, GUYS, WHY DON'T YOU GO
FIND ADAM?
HE'S RIGHT OVER THERE.
WHAT AM I DOING HERE?
WHAT IF I CAUGHT
SOMETHING?
THAT WOULD PROBABLY
BE BAD.
YOU HAVE TO TAKE ME
BACK TO THE HOSPITAL NOW!
OKAY.
I'LL GO GET THE CAR.
♪♪♪
BONJOUR.
LEO.
I AM WORKING, ALLI.
VERY BUSY.
WELL, CAN WE TALK?
I ONLY HAVE LIKE TEN MINUTES
UNTIL CURFEW.
OKAY, LAST YEAR,
I HAD AN AMAZING OPPORTUNITY.
BUT AFTER ONE FUN NIGHT
WITH A GUY,
I THREW IT ALL AWAY.
LEO:
WHAT DOES ANY OF THAT
HAVE TO DO WITH ME?
ALLI:
BECAUSE I LET GUYS MESS ME UP.
ALWAYS!
INSTEAD OF GOING TO THE LOUVRE
TO DO MY ASSIGNMENT,
I SAT IN THIS CAFE
HOPING YOU WOULD ASK ME OUT!
YOU COULD HAVE
EXPLAINED THAT.
INSTEAD OF RUINING
OUR DATE?
I KNOW.
I JUST...
LIKE YOU SO MUCH
AND I WANTED YOU
TO LIKE ME.
WHAT DO YOU WANT NOW?
I DON'T KNOW!
MY BRAIN'S TELLING ME
TO RUN, FAST.
BUT YOUR HEART?
IT'S RACING.
(LAUGHS)
YOU MUST THINK I'M SOME CRAZY,
LOVESTRUCK GIRL.
NO.
DOES THIS MEAN
I GET A SECOND CHANCE?
YOU STILL HAVE YOUR PROJECT
TO FINISH, NO?
DUE TOMORROW.
THEN LET'S VISIT
THE LOUVRE.
(LAUGHS)
YOU'RE BACK!
WHERE WERE YOU?!
UM, WINNING
A PARTICIPATION TROPHY.
THEY ALMOST CALLED
A CODE YELLOW ON YOU!
THAT MEANS SENDING
THE POLICE OUT!
I'M OKAY, ELI,
SERIOUSLY.
BUT WHAT IF YOU
CAUGHT SOMETHING?
I KNOW.
WHAT IF YOU STARTED
TO BLEED?
I KNOW!
WHAT IF YOU REACTED
TO THE CHEMO?!
IT WAS STUPID, OKAY?
I KNOW.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
I DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH TIME
I HAVE LEFT-
CLARE, STOP.
NO, JUST-
JUST LET ME FINISH.
SO I HAVE TO SPEND IT
IN THE BEST WAY POSSIBLE.
(SIGHS)
I WAS REALLY WORRIED TODAY.
I WOULD BE WORRIED
IF YOU WEREN'T.
WHAT'S WRONG?
IS IT MY MRI?
(CRYING)
IT CAME BACK CLEAR.
(RELIEVED SIGH)
NOW, THE DOCTOR SAYS
YOU'RE NOT OUT OF THE WOODS YET,
BUT-
BUT NOTHING!
I AM GONNA FIGHT THIS.
I AM GONNA WIN!
OKAY, COME HERE!
(ALL LAUGH)