♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ Hey ♪
(MUFFLED MUSIC PLAYS
THROUGH HEADPHONES)
IF HE ASKS ABOUT COMPUTERS,
TELL HIM WE'RE WAITING
ON THE SCHOOL BOARD.
HELLO? DREW?
HEY, I'M TRYING
TO GET PSYCHED!
BECKY:
UH, SIT STILL,
SQUIRMY WORMY!
YOU'RE DOING YOUR FIRST
INTERVIEW WITH DEGRASSI TV,
REPRESENTING STUDENT COUNCIL,
AND YOU NEED TO BE READY.
CLARE,
I WAS BORN READY.
CLARE: OH, REALLY?
DREW: REALLY.
WHAT ARE THIS YEAR'S STATS
ON CLUB ENROLLMENT?
HIGHEST IN FIVE YEARS.
AND UPCOMING PEP RALLIES?
FOR BOTH BOYS'
AND GIRLS' SPORTS.
DEGRASSI DOESN'T DISCRIMINATE.
THANK YOU.
ADMIT IT, CLARE,
YOU'RE IMPRESSED.
SURPRISED IS MORE LIKE IT.
THAT'S WHY I BOOKED
THE INTERVIEW:
TO SHOW EVERYONE
I'M A GOOD PRESIDENT.
AND IT'S THE PERFECT TIME
TO ANNOUNCE THE-
AH! DON'T SPOIL IT.
(SIGHS)
BECKY:
OKAY, JUST-
REALLY?
YEAH.
OKAY, THANK YOU...
IT'S A LITTLE MUCH.
THANK YOU.
(SIGHS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
GOOD MORNING,
DEGRASSI.
TODAY, MY GUEST
IS DEGRASSI'S PRESIDENT,
DREW TORRES.
LET'S TALK ABOUT
YOUR TERM SO FAR.
WHY DON'T WE START
WITH THE BUDGET?
OUR TREASURER,
CONNOR DELAURIER,
TELLS US WE HAVE SOME CASH
TO SPEND.
A GREAT OPPORTUNITY
TO GIVE BACK TO THE SCHOOL.
WHAT'S YOUR PLAN?
WE ARE PLANNING
A FALL CARNIVAL!
SOUNDS FUN,
DOESN'T IT?
BUT WHAT ABOUT THE TEAMS
WHO CAN'T AFFORD NEW EQUIPMENT?
OR THE CLUBS
THAT ARE SHORT ON SUPPLIES?
YOUR PRESIDENT HAD THIS
TO SAY:
I'M THE PRESIDENT,
I KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT THE STUDENTS WANT.
PEOPLE, THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU ELECT SOMEONE
BASED ON THEIR LOOKS,
INSTEAD OF THEIR PLATFORM.
DO WE EVEN KNOW
WHAT HIS PLATFORM WAS?
OR IS?
IT SEEMS ALL OUR PRESIDENT
WANTS TO DO
IS BLOW OUR BUDGET...
THE WHOLE SCHOOL
IS SEEING THIS.
WHO CARES WHAT SOME ANGRY
LITTLE NERD SAYS?
HE'S JUST TRYING TO MAKE
A NAME FOR HIMSELF.
BY BRINGING ME DOWN.
THERE WOULDN'T EVEN BE
A DEGRASSI TV WITHOUT ME!
HE WHO GIVETH...
CAN ALSO TAKETH AWAY.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I THINK WINSTON JUST AIRED
HIS FINAL BROADCAST.
(LAUGHS)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ (The best that I can be) ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
MR. TOWNSEND:
AND NOW YOUR LEGS ARE ENCASED
IN CONCRETE!
VERY HEAVY.
GOOD, GOOD!
BUT NOW WE'RE FLOATING -
EXCELLENT -
LIGHT AS A FEATHER.
FLOATING...
FALLING FROM THE SKY,
THE WIND IS BLOWING...
AND NOW WE ARE SITTING DOWN.
OKAY,
NOW THAT WE'RE WARMED UP,
LET'S TALK
MONOLOGUE ASSIGNMENTS.
NOW I'VE HAND-SELECTED
EACH MONOLOGUE
TO FIT THE STUDENT
PERFORMING IT.
PLEASE HAMLET, PLEASE HAMLET,
PLEASE HAMLET,
PLEASE HAMLET-
YOU... HAMLET?
EMPHASIS ON
THE "HAM."
SIGH.
PREDICTABLE.
MAYA'S RIGHT;
YOU ARE A BULLY.
MR. TOWNSEND:
MS. RIVAS. MY FAIR LADY.
WHICH BRINGS US
TO MR. MILLIGAN.
TRISTAN:
OH, UM, IS HAMLET
STILL AVAILABLE?
YOU'RE IN THE RIGHT BALLPARK,
I HAVE GIVEN YOU SHAKESPEARE.
OH, UH... MACBETH?
MR. TOWNSEND: MM-MM.
TRISTAN: NO? UH, KING LEAR?
BOTTOM.
MR. TOWNSEND:
YES, FROM "A MIDSUMMER
NIGHT'S DREAM."
IT'S ONE OF THE BARD'S
GREATEST COMEDIC ROLES.
NOW, HE FALLS ASLEEP
IN THE FOREST A MAN
AND WAKES UP A DONKEY!
NOW, I'M COUNTING ON YOU
TO DELIVER
A FLAMBOYANT PERFORMANCE.
(BELL RINGS)
CLARE:
THAT IS FANTASTIC NEWS!
YEAH, I CAN PICK UP
THE PROJECTOR THIS AFTERNOON.
GREAT. THANK YOU.
ALLI:
ARE YOU DELIVERING PIZZAS
TO THE MOON?
THIS IS GOOD, OLD-FASHIONED
SIXTEEN MILLIMETER FILM.
A CINEPHILE'S DREAM COME TRUE.
I'VE ORGANIZED
A ROMANTIC OUTDOOR SCREENING.
WELL, IT CAN'T BE FOR ELI
'CAUSE HE'S IN NEW YORK.
HE'S COMING HOME
FOR A WHOLE WEEK!
WE KNOW, WE KNOW.
IT'S ALL YOU'VE TALKED ABOUT
FOR THE PAST COUPLE DAYS.
WELL, YOU CAN'T BLAME ME
FOR BEING EXCITED!
BOTH YOUR BOYFRIENDS
ARE HERE.
I HAVEN'T SEEN MINE
IN SIX WEEKS.
YEAH, BUT HAVEN'T YOU TALKED
TO HIM LIKE EVERY DAY?
WE DID, AT FIRST,
BUT LATELY ELI'S JUST BEEN
SO BUSY WITH SCHOOL.
WHICH IS WHY TONIGHT
HAS TO BE PERFECT.
WELL, DON'T PUT TOO MUCH
PRESSURE ON YOURSELF.
YOU FORGET, PRESSURE TURNS COAL
INTO DIAMONDS.
THEN I GUESS TONIGHT'S DATE
WILL BE SPARKLING!
(ALLI AND CLARE LAUGH)
IN SUMMARY,
FACULTY URGE STUDENTS
TO PRACTICE PROPER
LOCKER HYGIENE,
TO STAVE OFF
INSECT INFESTATION...
DREW:
CAMERA'S CONFISCATED.
STUDENT COUNCIL PROPERTY.
OKAY, GREAT.
AND WE DON'T HAVE
A BATTERY FOR THAT,
SO WE JUST LOST THAT TAKE.
YOU SHOULD'VE THOUGHT OF THAT
BEFORE YOU EMBARRASSED ME.
WINSTON:
LAST TIME I CHECKED,
YOU EMBARRASSED YOURSELF.
THERE'S VIDEO TO PROVE IT!
IMOGEN, YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO FIND
A NEW ON-AIR PERSONALITY.
WINSTON'S OUT.
IMOGEN:
YOU CAN'T DO THAT!
IF YOU CENSOR US,
YOU MAY AS WELL SILENCE US,
DREW!
DREW:
WELL, SILENCE SOUNDS GOOD.
REALLY, REALLY GOOD.
CHECK OUT THE CHARTER,
IMOGEN.
STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT
HAS FINAL SAY
OVER ALL CLUBS
AND COMMITTEES.
WELL, IF YOU FIRE WINSTON,
I QUIT TOO!
DREW:
THEN IT LOOKS LIKE BECKY'S
THE NEW HEAD OF DTV.
HALLELUJAH!
♪♪♪
(PROJECTOR WHIRS)
CLARE:
THIS MOVIE'S SO WELL WRITTEN,
I'M FEELING KIND OF INSPIRED!
ARE YOU WATCHING THROUGH
YOUR MIND'S EYE,
MR. FILM STUDENT?
SORRY.
I'VE BEEN WORKING DOUBLE TIME
TO GET THIS WEEK OFF.
I'M EXHAUSTED.
I NOTICED.
YOU BARELY SAID A WORD
ON THE WAY BACK
FROM THE AIRPORT.
WELL, IF YOU MISS
THE THIRD ACT,
I CAN'T IN GOOD CONSCIENCE
LET YOU CROSS THIS OFF
YOUR MUST-SEE MOVIES LIST.
NO WAY, THE THIRD ACT'S
THE BEST PART.
YOU'VE ALREADY SEEN THIS?
YEAH,
I HAD TO FOR SCHOOL.
DIDN'T I TELL YOU?
NO.
(SIGHS)
(CELL PHONE BUZZES)
WHO IS IT?
UH, NEW YORK.
MY EDITOR.
ANSWER IT.
YOU SURE?
YOU'RE A BIG TIME
MOVIE DIRECTOR.
YOU'RE IN DEMAND,
GO!
(ELI SIGHS)
HELLO?
YUP. ONE SECOND.
WHAT'S UP?
NO, NO, IT NEEDS TO BE DONE
BY THURSDAY.
OKAY.
CAN I CALL YOU BACK?
YEAH. OKAY, BYE.
TRISTAN:
I SEE THEIR KNAVERY:
THIS IS TO MAKE AN ASS OF ME;
TO FRIGHT ME, IF THEY COULD.
BUT I WILL NOT STIR
FROM THIS PLACE,
DO WHAT THEY CAN.
HEE-HAW.
(BOTH LAUGH)
DON'T LAUGH.
BUT ISN'T IT SUPPOSED
TO BE FUNNY?
TRISTAN:
YES, BECAUSE MR. TOWNSEND THINKS
THE ONLY THING I CAN PLAY
IS AN ASS.
NOT THAT I CARE,
BUT WHAT MONOLOGUE DID ZOA GET?
THE ONE SHE WANTED.
MEANWHILE, TOWNSEND SAID
I WAS "FLAMBOYANT."
YOU KNOW HOW THEY SPELL THAT?
G-A-Y.
HE THINKS
I CAN'T HANDLE DRAMA.
MILES:
SO WHY DON'T YOU JUST GIVE HIM
A PIECE OF YOUR MIND?
YOU KNOW,
LIKE MAYA DID TO ZOA.
AND GET SUSPENDED
AND PUT UNDER HOUSE ARREST?
COME ON, TRIS!
WE COULD HAVE AT LOT OF FUN...
TOGETHER!
I'M NEVER GONNA GET
THE LEADING MAN PARTS.
I'M THE FOOL FOR LIFE.
SO, GO IN THERE
AND SHOW HIM YOU DESERVE
TO DO SOMETHING...
DRAMATIQUE!
THANK GOD WE CAME
TO GIVE YOU YOUR HOMEWORK.
MYMAT, I LOVE YOU!
OH!
DREW:
WE DON'T HAVE ENOUGH MONEY
FOR BOTH A COTTON CANDY MACHINE
AND A PETTING ZOO,
SO I WAS THINKING...
SUGAR: BAD;
CUTE LITTLE CHICKIES: GOOD!
WE'RE STILL DOING
THE CARNIVAL,
EVEN WITH PUBLIC OPINION
AT AN ALL-TIME LOW?
DON'T WORRY, CLARE,
WHILE YOU WERE PLANNING
YOUR PERFECT LITTLE DATE
WITH ELI,
I GOT EVERYTHING
UNDER CON...TROL.
STUDENTS:
(CHANTING) OCCUPY DEGRASSI!
OCCUPY DEGRASSI!
WINSTON:
DOWN WITH DREW "FASCIST" TORRES!
FREEDOM OF THE PRESS
FOREVER!
DOESN'T LOOK
UNDER CONTROL TO ME!
THEY CAN'T STAY HERE ALL DAY,
THEY'VE GOT CLASS!
THEY'RE ROTATING,
SO PEOPLE ON SPARES
CAN KEEP TAKING OVER.
MR. SIMPSON:
EXCUSE ME, PARDON ME,
SORRY, SORRY, SORRY.
SO-SO-SO THIS IS HAPPENING.
PLEASE TELL ME STUDENT COUNCIL
HAS A SOLUTION.
YEAH...
ISN'T THAT YOUR JOB?
YOU FIRED WINSTON
FROM DEGRASSI TV!
SERIOUSLY?!
BECAUSE HE WAS SPREADING
LIES ABOUT ME!
ALL I DID WAS SHOW THE PEOPLE
WHAT TYPE OF PRESIDENT YOU ARE!
WHAT WOULD THAT BE?
A TERRIBLE PRESIDENT!
WHICH IS WHY WE'RE ASKING YOU
TO RESIGN.
YOU SEE WHAT I'M DEALING
WITH HERE, SIR?
YES, AND I'M CONFIDENT
THAT YOU CAN RESOLVE IT
BY THE END OF THE DAY.
AND IF I DON'T?
PROTESTORS:
DOWN WITH DREW!
MAYBE THE PROTESTERS
HAVE A POINT!
PROTESTORS:
HECK NO, WE WON'T GO!
TRISTAN:
I SEE THEIR KNAVERY:
IT IS TO MAKE AN ASS OF ME;
TO FRIGHT ME,
IF THEY COULD.
BUT I WILL NOT STIR
FROM THIS PLACE
DO WHAT THEY CAN.
I WILL WALK UP
AND DOWN HERE,
AND I WILL SING
THAT THEY SHALL HEAR
I AM NOT AFRAID.
MR. TOWNSEND:
OKAY, I AM GONNA STOP YOU
RIGHT THERE.
NOW, I KNOW THIS IS
JUST A REHEARSAL,
BUT THAT'S NOT QUITE
WHAT I HAD IN MIND.
IT'S A COMEDIC ROLE.
♪ THE OUSEL-COCK,
SO BLACK OF HUE, ♪
♪ WITH ORANGE-TAWNY BILL ♪
HEE-HAW!
(STUDENTS LAUGH)
YOU KNOW, FUNNY!
BUT I DON'T WANT
TO DO IT THAT WAY.
HMM... THEN YOU'LL BE
RECEIVING A ZERO
ON THIS ASSIGNMENT.
(TRISTAN SIGHS)
(DREW SIGHS HEAVILY)
BIANCA: HEY.
DREW: HEY.
BIANCA:
I'M IN THE MIDDLE
OF A STUDY SESH,
CAN WE TALK LATER?
WHAT'S THE TOPIC?
THE GEOPOLITICAL RAMIFICATIONS
OF THE MARGARET THATCHER
PREMIERSHIP.
DREW:
YIKES, IT SOUNDS COMPLICATED.
NO, IT'S PRETTY SIMPLE.
IT'S A MEAN LADY
WHO RAN BRITAIN
AND SHE DID A LOT OF GOOD STUFF,
BUT A LOT OF PEOPLE
STILL HATED HER.
I FEEL THAT.
BIANCA:
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
NO, NO.
WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME MORE
ABOUT THIS THATCHER LADY.
WHAT'S HER STORY?
WELL, MY THESIS IS THAT
HER MONETARIST ECONOMIC POLICIES
WERE RECALCITRANT
WHEN IT CAME TO THOSE
OF LOWER SOCIOECONOMIC VALUE.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
ANY OF THOSE WORDS.
SHE DIDN'T DO
WHAT THE PEOPLE WANTED
AND THEY GOT UPSET.
DREW:
OKAY, SO WELL,
WHAT COULD SHE HAVE DONE
ANY DIFFERENT?
BIANCA:
I DON'T KNOW,
COMPROMISED?
DREW,
MY PAPER'S DUE TOMORROW.
OKAY, OKAY, I GOTTA GO BACK
TO CLASS, ANYWAYS.
DREW: GOOD LUCK, B.
BIANCA: THANKS. BYE.
LOVE YOU.
♪♪♪
ALLI:
OH, REHASHING YOUR PERFECT DATE?
MY DATE WAS ANYTHING
BUT PERFECT.
ELI AND I ARE
SO OUT OF SYNC.
SO YOU'RE A LITTLE RUSTY.
HE'S KEEPING SECRETS
FROM ME.
I FOUND CIGARETTES
IN HIS BAG.
AFTER HIS GIRLFRIEND'S
CANCER?
CLASSY MOVE,
GOLDSWORTHY.
YOU AND LEO WERE
HAVING TROUBLE, RIGHT?
WHAT COUPLE DOESN'T?
HOW'D YOU GET OVER IT?
WE TALKED, A LOT.
WE'RE STILL TALKING.
ELI AND I NEED TO TALK.
HE'S NOT THE ONLY ONE
KEEPING SECRETS, CLARE.
YOUR MAGAZINE ARTICLE?
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED
TO SAY?
I BLEW MY CHANCE
AT GETTING INTO COLUMBIA
AND HAPPY ANNIVERSARY!
YOU'RE SO OBSESSED
WITH BEING PERFECT
THAT YOU'RE TOO SCARED
TO BE HONEST!
YOU SHOULD WRITE
A RELATIONSHIP BOOK.
(SCOFFS)
"CHEATERS, LOSERS,
AND PERVS:
HOW TO PICK A GUY
THE BHANDARI WAY."
(LAUGHS)
DREW:
SO...
I THINK WE CAN COME
TO A COMPROMISE.
CONTINUE.
YOU CAN COME BACK
TO DEGRASSI TV,
BUT UNDER SOME GROUND RULES.
RULE NUMBER ONE:
DEGRASSI CLUBS AND COMMITTEES
MUST SHARE EQUAL AIR TIME.
ACCOMPLISHABLE.
RULE NUMBER TWO:
DEGRASSI TV MUST NOT PORTRAY
STUDENT COUNCIL
IN A NEGATIVE LIGHT -
OR ITS EVENTS,
OR ITS PRESIDENT.
SERIOUSLY?!
NOW I REALLY WANNA SEE YOU
GET IMPEACHED!
WHY DO YOU HATE ME
SO MUCH?
BECAUSE IT'S GUYS LIKE YOU
WHO'VE BEEN PICKING ON ME
MY ENTIRE LIFE.
SO THIS IS A PERSONAL THING.
YOU HAVE TO ADMIT,
I'M NOT A BAD PRESIDENT.
NO, I DON'T THINK
YOU'RE A BAD PRESIDENT.
REALLY?
WINSTON:
NO, I THINK YOU'RE
A TERRIBLE PRESIDENT!
WINSTON,
THAT'S ENOUGH!
NO, IT'S NOT!
I MEAN, WHAT WERE
PEOPLE THINKING
WHEN THEY ELECTED
AN IDIOT LIKE YOU
INTO OFFICE?
WHAT, DID THEY FEEL
SORRY FOR YOU?
(TRAY CLATTERS)
FEMALE AND MALE PROTESTOR:
DOWN WITH DREW!
ARE YOU OKAY?
ZOA:
THAT DONUT WILL GO
STRAIGHT TO YOUR HIPS.
THAT'S WHY I'M EATING IT
WITH MY EYES
AND NOT WITH MY MOUTH.
I KNOW YOU'RE NOT
MY BIGGEST FAN RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE YOU'RE MAYA'S PET,
BUT HERE'S SOME ADVICE-
IS THAT HOW YOU
GIVE ADVICE -
BY INSULTING PEOPLE?
FINE.
DON'T LISTEN TO ME.
HAVE FUN FAILING
DRAMA CLASS!
YOU'VE BEEN DOING THIS
SINCE YOU WERE AN EGG,
WHAT'S YOUR ADVICE?
DO THE MONOLOGUE
AS SCRIPTED.
I CAN'T.
YES, YOU CAN.
YOU'D KILL IT!
OBVIOUSLY,
BUT I DON'T WANNA BE
THE FUNNY GUY,
OR THE FOOL,
OR THE SIDEKICK.
I WANNA SHOW PEOPLE
THAT I CAN BE A LEADING MAN.
RIGHT NOW,
ALL YOU'RE SHOWING
IS THAT YOU CAN'T
DO ANYTHING.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
HEY, DALLAS,
WAIT UP, MAN!
I NEED YOUR HELP.
I DID SOMETHING BAD.
I KNOW,
IT'S ALL OVER SCHOOL.
YOU ATTACKED WINSTON?!
I LOST CONTROL.
WHAT DO I DO?
SHOULD I RESIGN?
WHY ARE YOU TAKING THIS
WINSTON THING SO PERSONALLY?
BECAUSE WINSTON'S RIGHT!
HE SEES I'M JUST STILL
THE SAME SCREW-UP
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN.
SOON EVERYONE ELSE
IS GONNA SEE IT, TOO.
AND BY "EVERYONE"
YOU MEAN BIANCA.
SHE'S OFF AT UNIVERSITY,
TAKING ALL THESE
SMART CLASSES,
I JUST... I WANT HER
TO SEE I'VE CHANGED.
YOU HAVE!
YOU'RE JUST SAYING THAT.
I DON'T KNOW ANYONE
WHO DESERVES TO BE PREZ
MORE THAN YOU.
YOU'RE ONE OF
THE BEST GUYS I KNOW.
AND MOST HANDSOME?
DON'T PUSH IT.
(BOTH LAUGH)
I JUST WANNA GIVE 'EM
WHAT THEY WANT.
IF THEY DON'T WANT
A CARNIVAL,
FIGURE OUT
WHAT THEY NEED INSTEAD.
IS THIS STILL
YOUR POST MOVIE RITUAL?
EAT PIE
AND TALK ABOUT IT?
ARE WE GONNA ACT LIKE
LAST NIGHT WASN'T WEIRD?
I'M SO GLAD
YOU FELT IT TOO.
I THINK I KNOW WHY.
YOU DO?
HOW LONG HAS IT BEEN
GOING ON?
IT WAS JUST ONCE.
WHY'D YOU START?
I MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
I WAS MISERABLE
AND FEELING A VOID.
AND THAT'S HOW YOU COPE
WITH MISSING ME...
BY SMOKING CIGARETTES?
I FOUND THEM
IN YOUR BAG.
THOSE DON'T BELONG
TO ME.
I WAS HOLDING ONTO THEM
FOR LENORE.
I MUST'VE FORGOT.
SHE'S YOUR EDITOR,
RIGHT?
♪ Open up,
let you in ♪
♪ Don't wanna fall again ♪
♪ Original sin ♪
♪ Same story again ♪
YOU SAID IT WAS
"JUST ONCE"
BECAUSE "YOU MISSED ME."
I'M SO SORRY,
CLARE.
SHE CALLED
DURING OUR DATE!
SHE WANTED TO TALK!
IT WAS LATE,
WE WERE WORKING
IN MY DORM ROOM.
NO! NO, NO!
I DON'T WANNA HEAR THIS!
NEW SCHOOL, OKAY?
NEW PEOPLE.
IT WAS SO HARD DEALING
WITHOUT YOU!
OH, SO THIS IS
MY FAULT?!
NO, NO, NO!
THAT'S NOT
WHAT I'M SAYING!
JUST- CAN YOU PLEASE
JUST LET ME EXPLAIN?
NO, I'VE HEARD ENOUGH!
I WANT YOU TO GO!
NO! OKAY, NO, NO!
WE JUST NEED TO TALK
THIS THROUGH!
NO, WE DON'T!
JUST GO!
♪ This war I conceded ♪
♪ I doubted you believed it ♪
♪ You're all that I needed
in this war of hearts ♪
(HARPSICHORD MUSIC PLAYS)
(AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
TRISTAN:
WHY DO THEY RUN AWAY?
I SEE THEIR KNAVERY:
THIS IS TO MAKE AN ASS OF ME;
TO FRIGHT ME,
IF THEY COULD.
BUT I WILL NOT STIR
FROM THIS PLACE
DO WHAT THEY CAN;
I WILL WALK UP
AND DOWN HERE,
AND I WILL SING,
THAT THEY SHALL HEAR
I AM NOT AFRAID.
♪ THE OUSEL-COCK,
SO BLACK OF HUE, ♪
♪ WITH ORANGE-TAWNY BILL ♪
HEE-HUH!
HEE-HAW!
(LAUGHS)
HEEEE-HAAAAW!
(AUDIENCE LAUGHS
AND CLAPS)
BRAVO!
DARE I SAY,
THAT WAS DELIGHTFUL!
(BELL RINGS)
ARRIVEDERCI,
MY LITTLE ACTORS!
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
YOU KILLED IT,
TRISTAN!
OH! DUH.
HOW WOULD YOU LIKE
TO KEEP KILLING IT?
WHATEVER IT IS
YOU'RE TRYING TO SAY,
SPIT IT OUT,
MISS MYSTERY.
I'M PUTTING TOGETHER
A COMEDY TROUPE -
IMPROV, SKETCHES,
WE'LL DO IT ALL -
AND I'D LIKE YOU
TO BE IN IT.
OH.
COME ON,
IT'LL BE FUN!
I KNOW, THERE'S JUST ONE
ITSY BITSY PROBLEM.
MAYA STILL HATES ME.
BINGO.
I CAN KEEP A SECRET.
CAN YOU?
(UNCERTAIN GRUNT)
WINSTON:
WHY IS ALL OUR EQUIPMENT SET UP?
SO YOU CAN SMASH IT
RIGHT IN FRONT OF US?
NO, I SET IT UP
SO I CAN DO ANOTHER INTERVIEW
WITH DEGRASSI TV.
OH, WELL,
YOU FIRED US, REMEMBER?
UM...
WELL, TECHNICALLY,
HE FIRED YOU.
I QUIT IN SOLIDARITY.
BECKY:
YEAH, ME TOO.
DEGRASSI TV NEEDS YOU,
SO LET'S NEGOTIATE.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
A NEW BATTERY
FOR THE VIDEO CAMERA?
THAT'S DOABLE.
WINSTON:
COMPLETE JOURNALISTIC FREEDOM
TO SAY WHATEVER WE WANT,
WHENEVER WE WANT.
NO STRINGS ATTACHED.
IF SIMPSON'S COOL WITH IT,
I'M COOL WITH IT.
FREE SPEAK AWAY.
IMOGEN:
WAIT A SECOND.
WHAT EXACTLY IS THIS INTERVIEW
GONNA BE ABOUT?
THE CARNIVAL.
STILL WITH THIS
CARNIVAL?!
(LAUGHS)
I TOOK A POLL
ON THE DEGRASSI BLOG
ASKING THE STUDENTS
HOW THEY WANTED THE MONEY SPENT.
GUESS WHAT WON?
IMOGEN: EW!
WINSTON: WE CAN'T DO THAT!
I KNOW.
THAT POLL MADE ME REALIZE
THAT DEGRASSI STUDENTS
DON'T ACTUALLY NEED
ANYTHING.
THEY ALREADY HAVE A LOT.
BUT WHAT THEY CAN DO
IS GIVE SOMETHING BACK,
SO STUDENT COUNCIL
IS GOING TO HOST
A THANKSGIVING FEAST
FOR NEEDY FAMILIES
OVER THE HOLIDAY WEEKEND.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE
YOU'RE GOING OUT OF YOUR WAY
TO MAKE SURE
I DON'T TELL SIMPSON
YOU PUSHED ME.
NO, NO, I DID PUSH YOU.
IT WAS WRONG
AND I'M SORRY.
YOU SHOULD TELL SIMPSON.
NAH.
I CAN'T INTERVIEW YOU
IF YOU'RE IN DETENTION,
AND WELL,
THIS IS ONE HELL OF A STORY!
BEFORE WE GET STARTED,
I JUST...
I WANNA SAY,
I THINK I MISJUDGED YOU.
WELL,
IT'S ALL IN THE PAST.
ALL THAT MATTERS
IS THAT WE MOVE FORWARD.
DEAL?
DEAL.
READY WHEN YOU ARE,
CAM-OP!
UH, IT'S PRODUCER.
SOUND, SPEED,
AND WE'RE ROLLING.
WINSTON:
FOR DEGRASSI TV,
I'M WINSTON CHU.
WE'RE BACK ON THE AIRWAVES,
BABY!
(STUDENTS CLAP AND CHEER)
I'M JOINED AGAIN
BY STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT,
DREW TORRES -
HOLD YOUR HECKLES -
WITH A VERY SPECIAL
ANNOUNCEMENT.
MR. TORRES,
I'D LIKE TO HUMBLY THANK YOU
FOR REINSTATING THE DTV TEAM...