DALLAS:
BREAKFAST? CHECK.
DREW:
WE ARE T-MINUS TWENTY
'TIL THE RUGRATS ARRIVE.
WE GOT EVERYTHING?
DALLAS:
CAMP ACTIVITY CENTERS?
CHECK.
DREW:
T-SHIRTS AND WELCOME KITS?
CHECK.
COUNSELORS GETTING BUSY?
CHECK, CHECK, AND CHECK.
DREW:
RETRIEVE YOUR TONGUE, BRO,
THE CAMPERS
ARE ABOUT TO ARRIVE.
BECKY LEAVES
FOR FLORIDA TODAY.
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
FIVE MORE MINUTES.
PLEASE DON'T GO.
I'LL BE HOME BEFORE
YOU KNOW IT.
BESIDES, YOU HAVE YOUR
COUNSELOR JOB TO KEEP YOU BUSY.
I'LL ALREADY BE BUSY
MISSING YOU!
IMOGEN:
INCOMING!
OH! AM I LATE?
OH HEY, BECKY.
READY?
I SHOULD GO.
UM, BUT UM,
BEFORE YOU DO,
ONE THING.
IMOGEN.
YEAH?
YOU CAN'T BE
AROUND HER ANYMORE.
SHE'S MY FRIEND.
BUT YOU HAVE OTHER FRIENDS!
YOU DON'T TRUST ME?
I TRUST YOU.
BUT STILL...
PROMISE YOU'LL STAY AWAY
FROM IMOGEN.
I PROMISE.
THANK YOU!
IMOGEN:
COME ON, CO-COUNSELOR,
WE'RE GONNA BE LATE!
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(The best that I can be)
♪ Ooh... ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(PHONE RINGS, PATIENTS CHATTER)
(SIREN WAILS DISTANTLY)
NOT EXACTLY A VIEW
OF THE EIFFEL TOWER.
HMM.
CLARE:
SO, WHERE'S THE ROOM
SERVICE MENU?
IS THERE A HAIR DRYER
IN THE BATHROOM?
ACTUALLY, I- NEVER MIND,
I PROBABLY WON'T NEED THAT.
JUST TRYING TO KEEP
THINGS LIGHT.
MARIELLE:
DO YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS
ABOUT THE TREATMENT, CLARE?
NO, UM...
SIX WEEKS OF INPATIENT
TREATMENT,
FOLLOWED BY MONTHS
OF ORAL CHEMO MEDICATION.
AND IF ALL GOES WELL,
IT'S A 70% SURVIVAL RATE.
YIPPY-SKIPPY.
WE'LL PROBABLY HAVE MORE
QUESTIONS AS WE GO ALONG.
MARIELLE:
IN THE MEANTIME,
HERE'S SOME LITERATURE
YOU CAN READ THROUGH.
UH, SORRY.
THE PATIENTS ARE OFTEN
MUCH YOUNGER THAN YOU ARE.
NO, THAT'S OKAY, IT'S A
CHILDREN'S HOSPITAL, AFTER ALL.
SO, WHERE ARE THE CRAYONS?
YOU'LL NEED TO CHANGE.
WE'LL WANT TO PREP YOU
RIGHT AWAY.
WHAT'S FIRST ON THE OLD
ITINERARY?
GETTING A CATHETER INSERTED
INTO YOUR CHEST.
THAT'S HOW THE CHEMO
WILL BE DELIVERED.
ROGER THAT.
LET'S DO THIS.
♪ You come around
and light up everything ♪
♪ You stun me
with your smile ♪
♪ And all you bring ♪
♪ Oooh ♪
♪ You come around
and make me wanna sing ♪
♪ And make me wanna sing ♪
♪ My fears away ♪
PLEASE TELL ME YOU GOT UP
EARLY THIS MORNING
AND WENT FOR A RUN
OR SOMETHING,
AND DIDN'T SNEAK OUT
LAST NIGHT!
MAYA:
I SLEPT OVER AT TRISTAN'S.
KATIE:
OKAY WELL, COME HOME NOW,
'CAUSE MOM IS GIVING ME
THE THIRD DEGREE!
YOU KNOW THIS ISN'T HELPING
YOUR CASE FOR PARIS.
WHAT CASE?
MOM AND DAD AREN'T GOING
TO LET ME GO TO PARIS.
THAT'S PRETTY CLEAR.
YOU KNOW, YOU COULD TRY
APOLOGIZING FOR SAYING,
"I HATE YOU."
GOODBYE, KATIE.
KATIE:
DON'T YOU DARE HANG-
TRISTAN:
ANY NEWS FROM THE HOME FRONT?
NOT GOOD NEWS.
TWENTY MINUTES LATE
FOR CURFEW,
AND YOUR MOM WON'T
LET YOU GO TO PARIS?
SHE WOULDN'T EVEN LISTEN
TO MY SIDE OF THE STORY.
YEAH, IT'S SO UNFAIR!
MM.
OH, YOU STILL HAVE THAT
CARD FROM THAT GUY.
HIS NAME'S MILES.
HE'S TROUBLE,
ONE HUNDRED PERCENT.
MAYBE I SHOULD RETURN
THE CARD IN PERSON, THEN.
WHAT?
MY MOM THINKS I'M TURNING
INTO SOME KIND OF BADASS,
SO...
WHY NOT BE A BADASS?
(KIDS CHATTER)
MAN,
ROCKY WOULD'VE LOVED THIS.
TOO BAD HE'S UP AT THE COTTAGE
WITH HIS MOM.
DREW:
YEAH.
MADISON GRANT,
YOU ARE AN IGUANA!
I DON'T WANNA BE AN IGUANA.
OH, BUT YOU'LL LOVE IT!
HERE'S ONE OF YOUR IGUANA
LEADERS RIGHT NOW!
I DON'T WANT TO BE
AN IGUANA.
IMOGEN AND I CAN'T
WORK TOGETHER.
IT'S A PERSONAL ISSUE.
YOU KNOW AH,
FOR SECOND THERE,
I THOUGHT YOU HAD
A REAL REASON.
DREW, PLEASE.
NO.
DALLAS AND I SPENT HOURS
MAKING THESE GROUPS,
YOU CAN'T SWITCH.
YOU TWO ARE IGUANAS.
YOU'RE GONNA LOVE IT, GO!
OH! HI.
HI, OKAY.
MY FELLOW IGUANAS!
GRR- NO. ROAR- NO.
IT DOESN'T MATTER,
BECAUSE WE'RE ALL GONNA HAVE
THE BEST SUMMER TOGETHER!
WE HAVE ONE LITTLE PROBLEM.
BECKY.
SHE THINKS YOU LIKE ME.
SHE DOESN'T WANT US
TO HANG OUT.
I CAN FIX THIS, THERE MUST
BE SOMETHING I CAN DO.
HELP ME CONVINCE DREW
WE CAN'T WORK TOGETHER?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
ALL CAMPERS TO YOUR
ANIMAL GROUPS,
IT'S TIME FOR THE FIRST
ACTIVITY!
MY NAME'S COLTON,
AND I'M AN IGUANA!
HISSSS!
AN IGUANA SOUND!
IMOGEN AND KIDS:
HISSSSSSS!
I GUESS WE'LL TALK
TO DREW LATER?
YEAH, I GUESS.
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYS)
(GUESTS CHATTER)
(SIGHS)
OH HI, UM EXCUSE ME,
UH, SORRY.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH: THAT'S OKAY.
IS MILES HERE?
MILES?
WELL, IF I KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT MY SON,
HE'S PROBABLY...
STEALING BOOZE FROM THE BAR.
COME.
MILES, MAKE SURE NO ONE
ELSE SEES.
AYE AYE, FATHER.
OH MY GOD,
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOUR LIFE!
I HAVE SO MANY QUESTIONS!
YEAH, I ONLY HAVE ONE.
WHY ARE YOU RANDOMLY
AT MY HOUSE?
RIGHT. UM, I WANTED
TO RETURN THIS.
SO...
YOU'RE PROBABLY WONDERING WHY
I'M NOT AT HOME RIGHT NOW,
PACKING FOR PARIS.
WELL, I WAS LATE FOR CURFEW
BY A FEW MINUTES,
AND NOW MY MOM
WON'T LET ME GO.
OH, BOO HOO.
OH COME ON, I HAD BIG
PLANS FOR THE SUMMER.
NOW, I NEED A MENTOR
IN TROUBLEMAKING.
WANT TO APPLY?
RIGHT THIS WAY,
GRASSHOPPER.
(LAUGHS)
SO, WHAT ARE WE CELEBRATING?
UH, DAD IS RUNNING
FOR MAYOR IN THE FALL.
OH.
OH, LOOK.
A FELLOW DEGRASSIAN.
CHEWY, THIS IS MAYA.
MAYA, CHEWY.
MILES, SCOTCH.
IT'S WINSTON.
WINSTON CHU.
(LAUGHS)
(MUFFLED MUSIC PLAYS)
MARIELLE: (KNOCKS)
OH, WHY AREN'T YOU
IN YOUR GOWN YET?
IT WAS ITCHY,
AND I WAS COLD.
YOU NEED TO PUT ON YOUR GOWN,
CLARE.
CLARE:
I'M WAY MORE COMFORTABLE
IN MY SWEATS.
IT'S HOSPITAL POLICY.
I DON'T WANT TO,
I FEEL FINE.
WE NEED TO PUT
THAT STENT IN!
FOR THE CHEMO.
IF YOU SUFFER ANY
SIDE EFFECTS,
WE NEED FAST ACCESS.
EVERY MINUTE COUNTS.
SO, WHAT KIND OF TROUBLE
ARE WE GONNA GET UP
TO THIS SUMMER?
FIRST LESSON,
YOU CAN'T PLAN TROUBLE.
SECOND LESSON?
HANG OUT WITH MILES,
AND TROUBLE FINDS YOU.
WHOA!
(COUGHS)
IT'S AH,
MORE OF SIPPING DRINK.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
COULD I HAVE EVERYONE'S
ATTENTION, PLEASE?
FIRST OF ALL, I WANNA THANK
YOU ALL FOR COMING OUT TODAY.
(MAYA'S PHONE BEEPS)
AND I THINK MOST OF YOU KNOW
WHAT I'M ABOUT TO SAY.
SO I AM HERE TODAY TO ANNOUNCE
TO YOU, MY FAMILY,
AND MY CLOSEST FRIENDS,
MY CANDIDACY FOR MAYOR!
(BOTTLE SHATTERS)
GUESTS: (STARTLED) OH! OH!
(SIGHS)
JEEZ, WELL, WHO INVITED
THE TEENAGERS?
WAS THAT MY CUE
TO WRAP THINGS UP?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
SMOOTH MOVE, MATLIN.
WINSTON:
I-I DON'T THINK HE'LL BE MAD.
WHAT?
WHAT'S WRONG?
WE'VE BEEN FRIENDS SINCE
WE WERE FIVE, CHEWY.
YOU KNOW BETTER.
CAN I HAVE A WORD WITH YOU?
YOU REALLY WANNA DO
THIS RIGHT NOW?
YES, COME ON! COME!
MILES, STOP IT!
STOP IT!
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
ONE THING. ONE THING TODAY!
MILES:
I TOLD YOU I DIDN'T WANT
TO BE HERE!
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
AND I TOLD YOU THAT
I DIDN'T CARE!
SO I WANT YOU TO COME
DOWNSTAIRS NOW,
AND APOLOGIZE!
MILES:
YOU'RE JOKING.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
HOW DARE YOU RUIN EVERYTHING!
MILES:
I DON'T CARE ENOUGH TO RUIN
ANYTHING OF YOURS!
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
YOU-YOU'RE SUCH A DELINQUENT!
I DON'T KNOW
WHY I EVEN BOTHER!
MILES:
THEN DON'T!
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
WHY CAN'T YOU BE MORE
LIKE YOUR SIBLINGS?!
MILES:
BECAUSE IT'S MORE FUN
BEING A DISAPPOINTMENT!
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
THERE'S MORE IMPORTANT THINGS
IN LIFE, MILES!
NICE POOL, HUH?
YOU KNOW, AFTER THE RECEPTION,
WE COULD GO FOR A SWIM?
THIS IS AWFUL.
IT WILL BE OVER SOON.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
WASTE OF TIME!
MILES:
I HATE YOU!
(DOOR SLAMS)
HOW'D YOU ENJOY THE SHOW?
ARE YOU OKAY?
THIS IS NORMAL FOR
THE HOLLINGSWORTH CLAN.
DO YOU WANNA TALK?
ABOUT WHAT?
I'M GREAT!
NOW, WHAT SHOULD WE DO
FOR AN ENCORE?
SWIM?
MAYA:
I SHOULD GO.
WINSTON:
OH, BAD IDEA, MAN.
DON'T POKE THE BEAR,
YOU'RE GONNA MAKE THINGS WORSE!
MILES:
THEY CAN'T GET WORSE.
MAYA:
MILES! MILES!
DON'T DO ANYTHING STUPID!
YOU WANTED TO GO,
SO GO!
♪ This night
is gonna be electric ♪
♪ So never pick a fight
in my home ♪
♪ Take a shot if you think
you've really got it ♪
WHOO! (SPLASH)
♪ You want it
you need it ♪
♪ You can't stop
can't stop me ♪
♪ From breaking you down ♪
♪ You want it
you need it ♪
IDIOT.
WE BETTER GO FISH HIM OUT.
NO, I CAN'T BE HERE.
I CAN'T BE AROUND GUYS
LIKE HIM.
♪ You can't stop us now! ♪
COLTON:
MY NAME IS COLTON,
AND I LIKE CARS.
HIS NAME IS COLTON,
AND HE LIKES CARS,
MY NAME IS ADAM,
AND I LIKE APPLES.
HE'S COLTON,
HE LIKES CARS,
HE'S ADAM,
HE LIKES APPLES,
I'M MADISON,
AND I LIKE...
MONKEYS!
HIS NAME IS COLTON,
AND HE LIKES CARS,
HER NAME IS MADISON,
AND SHE LIKES MONKEYS,
AND UM...
MY NAME'S IMOGEN,
AND I LIKE IGUANAS!
YOU FORGOT SOMEONE.
I DID? WHO?
MADISON:
ADAM.
WHO'S THAT?
NEVER HEARD OF HIM.
MOVING ON.
THAT WAS PRETTY RUDE!
"THAT WAS PRETTY RUDE!"
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
"WHAT ARE YOU DOING?"
DID YOU FEEL THAT?
IT WAS LIKE,
THE WIND OR SOMETHING?
WHY ARE YOU BEING
SUCH A JERK?
COLTON AND MADISON:
UH OH!
YOU'RE THE JERK!
OW!
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
HEY! GUYS, THAT'S ENOUGH!
SORRY, MAMA AND PAPA IGUANA
NEED TO TAKE A LITTLE TIME OUT.
I TOLD YOU, DREW,
NOW WILL YOU SWITCH US?
STOP! IF SIMPSON HEARS,
WE'RE ALL GONNA BE IN TROUBLE.
SO WILL YOU QUIT?
YOU QUIT!
I'M NOT QUITTING!
YOU TWO GO OUTSIDE,
DON'T COME BACK IN
UNTIL YOU WORK THINGS OUT!
GO!
HEY, GUYS.
I'M DREW,
AND I LIKE DOGS.
(MUFFLED ANNOUNCEMENTS ON PA)
(MACHINES BEEP)
(PHONE BEEPS)
(RINGING)
ELI:
YOU'VE REACHED ELI,
WAIT FOR THE BEEP.
(BEEPS)
HI. HI, IT'S ME.
I'M AT THE HOSPITAL,
I WAS JUST KINDA HOPING
TO HEAR YOUR VOICE.
IT JUST KIND OF HIT ME
HOW SCARED I AM.
AND I KNOW I SAID
NOT TO COME HOME,
(SOBS)
CAN YOU COME HOME PLEASE?
ELI:
ASK AND I APPEAR.
YOU CAME.
YEAH, I LEFT RIGHT AFTER
YOU TOLD ME THE NEWS.
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT MAD.
(SOBS)
WHAT'S GOING ON,
ARE YOU-
ARE YOU LEAVING, OR?
ARE YOU OKAY?
I FEEL FINE!
AND EVERYONE JUST KEEPS
TELLING ME THAT I'M SICK.
I THINK I'M ONLY GOING
TO GET A LOT SICKER.
I DON'T WANT TO GO
THROUGH THIS, ELI.
(SIGHS)
MRS. MATLIN:
WELL, SHE'S NOT HERE,
SO JUST PLEASE CALL ME
IF SHE SHOWS UP.
THANK YOU.
OH! OH, THANK GOD!
I'M OKAY.
YOU'RE OKAY?!
YOU IGNORED ALL MY MESSAGES!
OKAY MOM, SORRY.
THANK YOU, I...
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW SCARED WE WERE,
IMAGINING ALL
THE TERRIBLE THINGS
THAT COULD'VE HAPPENED TO YOU?
I'M SORRY.
FOR EVERYTHING, I-
GOD, I WAS SUCH A BITCH!
I MESSED UP,
AND I TOTALLY UNDERSTAND
WHY I DON'T GET
TO GO TO PARIS.
MAYA, HONEY-
I SHOULDN'T HAVE SAID
I HATE YOU.
I DON'T HATE YOU,
I LOVE YOU!
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH,
AND YOU'RE THE GREATEST MOM.
(KIDS SHOUT DISTANTLY)
ADAM:
CAN WE JUST PRETEND
THAT WE MADE UP,
SO WE CAN GO BACK TO WORK?
NOT UNTIL YOU SAY SORRY.
ME, SAY I'M SORRY?!
YOU'RE THE ONE TRYING
TO BREAK UP MY RELATIONSHIP!
I AM NOT!
THEN WHY WOULDN'T YOU
SWITCH GROUPS?
THE SILENT TREATMENT.
REAL MATURE.
OKAY!
I DON'T MAKE FRIENDS
THAT EASILY.
AND I WRECK EVERYTHING
I TOUCH.
FIRST WITH FIONA,
AND NOW WITH YOU.
DALLAS IS ALWAYS AVAILABLE.
(RETCHES)
YOU'LL FIND ANOTHER GIRL.
OR BOY, OR WHATEVER
IT IS YOU'RE INTO.
I LIKE PEOPLE.
I LIKE YOU.
WELL, MAYBE WE COULD BE
SECRET FRIENDS.
AND STAY CO-COUNSELORS?
BUT WE HAVE TO PRETEND
TO HATE EACH OTHER
FOR BECKY'S SAKE.
YAAAY!
UH, THAT MEANS NO TOUCHING!
UH...
OH, THAT'S TOUCHING TOO.
UM, OKAY.
IMOGEN MORENO REPORTING
FOR DUTY.
THIS IS GONNA BE A SUMMER
FOR THE BOOKS, ISN'T IT?
WELL, AT LEAST
IT WON'T BE BORING.
COME ON, FRIEND, LET'S TELL
DREW THAT WE HATE EACH OTHER,
BUT WE'RE WILLING
TO WORK TOGETHER.
FOR THE KIDS!
OH, AND ADAM, UM...
I HOPE BECKY REALIZES
HOW LUCKY SHE IS.
ME TOO.
YOU ALL DONE PACKING
FOR SOCCER CAMP?
YEAH, PRETTY MUCH.
MOM SAID YOU WERE UPSET.
YEAH.
I FELT BAD FOR WHAT
I SAID TO HER,
AND I REALIZED THAT I'M LUCKY
TO HAVE THE PARENTS THAT I DO.
SO YOU GONNA BE OKAY
WITHOUT ME HERE THIS SUMMER?
OF COURSE I WILL.
IT'S JUST...
I DON'T KNOW.
EVERYBODY LEAVES ME.
YOU, TRISTAN, TORI.
MAYBE ONE DAY I WON'T
GET LEFT BEHIND.
(SIGHS)
(MRS. MATLIN CLEARS THROAT)
YOUR FATHER AND I HAVE BEEN
TALKING ABOUT PARIS.
YEAH?
THIS YEAR HAS BEEN
AWFUL FOR YOU,
AND WE DON'T FEEL VERY GOOD
ABOUT KEEPING YOU HERE
WHEN YOU HAVE THIS AMAZING
OPPORTUNITY.
YOU HAVE TO PROMISE
TO FOLLOW THE RULES,
AND THE CURFEWS.
I EXPECT AT LEAST AN B PLUS
IN THE COURSE,
YOU EMAIL ME ONCE A DAY,
AND YOU PHONE THREE TIMES
A WEEK, MINIMUM!
PROMISE!
ARE YOU SAYING I CAN GO?
YAAAY!
I CAN GO!
(MAYA AND KATIE LAUGH)
MARIELLE:
OKAY CLARE,
THIS ISN'T GONNA HURT A BIT,
I'M JUST MAKING SOME
LAST MINUTE ADJUSTMENTS.
WOW, UM...
THAT GOWN IS REALLY,
REALLY SEE THROUGH.
STOP, I'M NERVOUS ENOUGH
AS IT IS,
I HATE NEEDLES.
THEN GOOD THING THERE
ARE NO NEEDLES.
JUST A DIRECT LINE PLUNGING
DEEP INTO YOUR CHEST.
NOT HELPING.
DID IT HURT
WHEN THEY PUT THAT IN?
I'LL SURVIVE.
MARIELLE:
OKAY, CLARE.
THE CARBOPLATIN DRIP
IS ALL SET UP.
GET YOURSELF IN A COMFORTABLE
POSITION,
AND TELL ME
WHEN YOU'RE READY.
I'M READY.
♪ This all ♪
♪ We could bleed
Or break ourselves ♪
MADAME JEAN-AUX:
ECOUTEZ!
EVERYONE MAKE SURE
YOU HAVE YOUR PASSPORTS
BEFORE WE LEAVE
FOR THE AIRPORT.
WHERE'S CLARE?
CONNOR:
YEAH, SHE'S USUALLY
SO PUNCTUAL.
(ALLI SIGHS)
SHE WANTED ME TO WAIT UNTIL
THE LAST POSSIBLE MINUTE.
IT'S-IT'S CANCER,
ISN'T IT?
CONNOR:
IS SHE GONNA DIE?
CONNOR!
WHAT?
IT'S A VALID QUESTION!
ALLI:
THE PROGNOSIS IS GOOD.
BECAUSE IF IT WASN'T, NO ONE
COULD TEAR ME AWAY FROM HER.
TRISTAN:
OH, IT'S SO GOOD YOUR MOM
AND DAD CHANGED THEIR MINDS.
MAYA:
YEAH, MY PARENTS ARE AWESOME
LIKE THAT.
WELL YEAH, SUMMER WOULD HAVE
BEEN A BUMMER WITHOUT YOU.
MADAME JEAN-AUX:
EVERYONE, WE HAVE SOME LAST
MINUTE ADDITIONS TO OUR GROUP.
MAYA AND TRISTAN:
YES!
MADAME JEAN-AUX:
PLEASE MAKE WINSTON
AND MILES FEEL WELCOME.
TRISTAN:
UH, ISN'T THAT THE GUY
FROM THE CONCERT?
OH MY GOD.
HEY, HOW'D YOU GET
ON THIS TRIP?
MILES:
UH, WELL, MY FATHER WANTED
TO SEND ME AWAY,
AND CHEWY HERE
HAS TO BABY-SIT, RIGHT?
YEAH, PARIS,
WHAT A DRAG.
YEAH, SO, IT LOOKS LIKE WE CAN
SPEND THE SUMMER TOGETHER,
AFTER ALL.
MAYA:
WELL, I'M SPENDING IT
WITH MY BEST FRIEND,
NOT YOU.
YOUR LOSS.
SO, YOU TWO HOOKING UP,
OR WHAT?
NO, NO,
DEFINITELY NOT.
AWESOME.
LET'S KEEP IT THAT WAY.
(SCOFFS)
I HAVE A FEELING THIS SUMMER'S
GONNA BE CRAY-CRAY.
THEN WE BETTER STICK TOGETHER.
BON! BIEN!
ALLONS-Y A PARIS!
(STUDENTS CLAP AND CHEER)