ZOE:
I CANNOT WAIT FOR THIS DANCE!
FRANKIE:
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA WEAR?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT DO NORMAL PEOPLE
NORMALLY WEAR?
YOU'VE NEVER BEEN
TO A SCHOOL DANCE?
I WAS PROM QUEEN
ON "WEST DRIVE,"
BUT SPENDING ALL MY TIME
ON SET,
I MISSED OUT
ON THE REAL THING.
I WANNA LOOK GOOD
FOR MY DATE.
YOUR DATE?
WHO ARE YOU GOING WITH?
IT BETTER NOT BE MILES.
DON'T YOU DARE TAKE
MY STUPID OLDER BROTHER BACK.
COME ON, SPILL.
WHO IS IT?
FINE, I'M GOING
TO THE DANCE WITH-
MILES:
FOUR TICKETS, PLEASE.
MILES: HEY, SIS.
FRANKIE: THAT'LL BE $40 DOLLARS.
SIXTY!
THERE'S A JERK TAX.
OH, ZOE, STILL CARRYING
THAT TORCH FOR ME.
SO SAD.
SINCE DUMPING YOUR ASS,
I'VE FOUND MY GIRLS.
MILES:
SERIOUSLY, SIS?
I THOUGHT YOU'D HAVE
BETTER TASTE IN FRIENDS.
I'VE GOT AN AUDITION
TONIGHT
AND I PRETTY MUCH HAVE
A NEW BOYFRIEND.
OOH! HOT GOSS ALERT!
WHO'S THE GUY?
IT'S... DREW TORRES.
WHOA.
WAIT. SCHOOL PRESIDENT,
DREW TORRES?
LIKE SENIOR DREW TORRES?
WHAT'S HE DOING
WITH YOU?
ANYTHING I WANT HIM TO.
AND WE'RE GOING
TO THE DANCE TOGETHER.
TRISTAN:
UH, WON'T HIS GIRLFRIEND MIND?
WHAT GIRLFRIEND?!
BIANCA. I'M PRETTY SURE
SHE'S AT UNIVERSITY.
WELL,
THEY MUST BE OVER.
COOL.
WELL, I GUESS WE'LL SEE YOU TWO
AT THE DANCE.
COUNT ON IT.
(MAYA AND TRISTAN LAUGH)
(LAUGHS)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ (The best that I can be) ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(SIGHS)
(GLASS CLINKS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
(MIXTURE FIZZES)
CLARE:
OKAY, THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
WHAT, JENNA TRYING
TO DO LAB WORK?
NO, YOU TWO NOT TALKING.
WHAT'S UP?
SHE DOESN'T APPROVE OF ME
DATING LEO.
OH, THE GUY
WHO HURT YOU?
THE GUY WHO CREEPILY
FOLLOWED YOU HERE?
ACROSS AN OCEAN,
FOR LOVE!
IT'S LIKE A NICHOLAS
FRICKIN' SPARKS MOVIE!
COME ON, CLARE,
HELP ME OUT!
YOU ARE A SMART,
BEAUTIFUL GIRL.
YOU COULD DATE
PRACTICALLY ANYONE.
BUT I WANT TO DATE HIM.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
MAYBE I SHOULD TRANSFER
TO FRANCE
FOR MY SENIOR YEAR!
HIS FRIENDS WOULD
SUPPORT US.
WHY DON'T YOU BRING HIM
TO THE DANCE?
WHAT, SO YOU GUYS
CAN JUDGE HIM?
SO WE CAN GET TO KNOW HIM,
SEE THE LEO YOU SEE.
AND COME ON,
DON'T YOU WANNA SEE
HOW BADLY DREW SCREWED UP
THIS DANCE
WITHOUT OUR HELP?
OKAY, FINE.
CLARE:
THANK YOU!
(BELL RINGS)
WHOA! AGH!
PRESIDENT TORRES,
HARD AT WORK.
SHOULD I BRING MY SURFBOARD
TOMORROW?
DREW:
BEACH BASH IS ALMOST READY,
SIR.
MR. SIMPSON:
EXCELLENT.
I'M ASSUMING THAT YOU FOLLOWED
ALL THE DANCE GUIDELINES
IN THE HANDY DANDY
STUDENT HANDBOOK.
YEAH, THE-THE HANDBOOK.
YEAH, YEAH, OF COURSE.
SO YOU'VE BOOKED THE APPROPRIATE
SECURITY PERSONNEL?
DREW:
SORRY, THE WHAT-
THE WHAT NOW?
TWO POLICE OFFICERS.
DEFINITELY...
DEFINITELY DID THAT.
AND YOU'VE TALKED
TO THE CAFETERIA LADIES?
ABOUT?
FOOD! YOU CAN'T JUST BUY
A BAG OF CHIPS, DREW.
UH, IT'S A UNION THING.
OBVIOUSLY, 'CAUSE IT'S, UH,
IT'S IN THE HANDBOOK.
YEAH, AND YOU'VE RENTED
A SOUND SYSTEM?
WELL, THE GYM HAS ONE.
IT WAS BLOWN DURING
THE WELCOME BACK ASSEMBLY.
LOOK, MAYBE I SHOULD
JUST TALK TO CLARE.
I MEAN, MAYBE SHE'S TAKEN CARE
OF THIS STUFF.
DON'T WORRY, SIR.
I ASSURE YOU,
I'VE GOT IT ALL UNDER CONTROL.
I TRUST YOU.
HANG TEN.
TELL ME YOU'RE NOT
THE WORLD'S BIGGEST LIAR!
E-EXCUSE ME?
WE ARE GOING TO THE DANCE
TOGETHER, RIGHT?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
OH MY GOD!
IT'S TRUE,
YOU HAVE A GIRLFRIEND!
A FIANCEE.
FI-
BUT... YOU CALL ME
EVERY NIGHT
SAYING SOME PRETTY
SEXY STUFF.
OH LOOK, I'M SORRY,
IT'S MY MEDS.
UH, ZOLPI- SOMETHING.
SLEEPING PILLS?
YEAH, THEY MAKE ME DO SOME
PRETTY WEIRD THINGS SOMETIMES,
INCLUDING CALLING PEOPLE.
BUT I THOUGHT
YOU LIKED ME!
WELL, DON'T WORRY,
I'M ALL OUT
AND THE DOC WON'T GIVE ME
ANY MORE.
BOO-HOO!
I TOLD ALL THE HATERS
IN MY CLASS WE'RE TOGETHER!
WHAT DO I DO NOW?!
TELL THEM WE'RE NOT.
(GIRLS GIGGLE)
ALLI:
THE SOLUBILITY OF A GAS
IN A LIQUID IS PROPORTIONAL
TO THE PRESSURE OF THE GAS
ABOVE THE LIQUID.
WHICH MEANS...
LEO:
AH, HENRY'S LAW.
THINK OF COLA.
WHEN YOU OPEN THE CAN,
THE PRESSURE CHANGES,
AND - PSSSH! - GAS ESCAPES.
WHY DO I EVEN NEED
TO GO TO CLASS
WHEN I HAVE YOU?
(LEO LAUGHS)
OH, I HAVE SOMETHING
FOR YOU
FOR BEING
SUCH A GOOD TUTOR.
(BOTH LAUGH)
DARWIN.
AN EARLY EDITION.
I THOUGHT
YOU MIGHT NEED IT
FOR WHEN YOU START
YOUR CLASSES AT T.U.
BUT THERE'S MORE,
CHECK THE BOOKMARK.
TICKETS TO MY SCHOOL DANCE.
COME WITH ME.
AND YOUR FRIENDS?
WE CAN ALL HANG TOGETHER.
BUT YOU SAID
THEY DIDN'T LIKE ME.
THEY DON'T KNOW YOU.
THEY JUST SEE YOU AS THE GUY
THAT GAVE ME BRUISES.
YOU TOLD THEM THAT?!
AND IT WASN'T YOU!
I KNOW THAT,
THEY DON'T.
SO COME AND SHOW THEM
THAT YOU'RE A GREAT GUY!
NO, I DON'T WISH
TO BE TESTED!
LEO,
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT!
GREAT, THEN...
NO ONE WILL MIND
IF I DON'T COME.
(BALL THUDS)
(DALLAS GROANS)
DALLAS:
DUDE, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
IT'S 3:00 IN THE MORNING
AND THOSE AREN'T EXACTLY
SOOTHING OCEAN SOUNDS.
YOU UP
THINKING ABOUT ADAM?
NO, I'M FREAKING OUT ABOUT
HOW MUCH I HAVE TO DO
FOR THIS DANCE.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA TAKE
ANY MORE PILLS?
I WISH.
DOC WON'T GIVE ME ANYMORE,
HE SAYS THEY'RE HABIT FORMING.
THEN STAY UP
AND WORK ON THE DANCE STUFF.
I'M TOO TIRED,
THERE'S TOO MUCH,
AND I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHERE TO START.
IS THAT THE LIST?
YEAH.
(YAWNS)
OKAY, I'LL TAKE THE FOOD,
THE COPS,
AND THE DECORATIONS.
AND THE NINER GIRLS
CAN TAKE THE CLEAN-UP.
REALLY?
YOU'D DO THAT?
YEAH. YOU JUST TAKE CARE
OF THE MUSIC.
THANKS, BRO.
YOU CAN THANK ME
BY CHILLING OUT
AND MAKING THIS DANCE HAPPEN.
(BALL THUDS)
AND BY GIVING ME
THAT DAMN BALL!
♪♪♪
(ZOE CLEARS HER THROAT)
I NEED SOME HELP.
ZIG:
YOU'RE FROM THAT SHOW.
ZOE:
I WAS.
YOU WERE MEAN
ON THE SHOW.
I'M NICER IN PERSON.
ARE YOU THE KIND OF GUY
I CAN...
"GET" THINGS FROM?
WELL, SURE.
I GOT LOTS OF THINGS.
I'LL BET YOU DO,
BUT I'M NOT TALKING
ABOUT HERPES!
LISTEN, IF YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO ASK POLITELY,
THEN YOU CAN FORGET IT.
(SIGHS)
PARDON MY MANNERS.
HOW'S THIS?
I THINK I KNOW A GUY
WHO CAN HELP YOU.
WHAT KIND OF "THINGS"
DO YOU NEED?
(ZOE CLEARS HER THROAT)
LOOK, IF YOU'RE HERE
TO YELL AT ME AGAIN-
I'M NOT.
GOOD, BECAUSE I DON'T
HAVE THE TIME.
I'VE STILL GOTTA SET UP
THIS SOUND SYSTEM,
GO HOME, MAKE THE PLAYLIST
FOR THE DANCE,
GET MYSELF READY-
AND YOU HAVEN'T SLEPT
AND YOU'RE FREAKING OUT.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
IS THAT-
YOUR PRECIOUS
SLEEPING PILLS?
YES!
AND THEY CAN ALL BE YOURS
IF... YOU GO TO THE DANCE
WITH ME?
LOOK, I TOLD YOU,
I HAVE A FIANCEE!
I DON'T CARE.
SHE NEVER HAS TO KNOW!
AND AT THE END OF THE NIGHT
YOU CAN HAVE THE BEST SLEEP
OF YOUR LIFE.
DREW:
OKAY, FINE.
GREAT!
PICK ME UP AT EIGHT.
(SIGHS)
(CRICKETS CHIRP)
COME ON, DREW, FOCUS!
(FEW BARS OF A SONG PLAYS)
TOO SLOW.
TOO SLOW!
♪♪♪
♪ Tell me where,
tell me when ♪
♪ I'll be there ♪
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
♪♪♪
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
MAYA:
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY IS IT SO QUIET?
TRISTAN:
MAYBE IT'S SUPPOSED
TO BE RELAXING?
LIKE A VACATION?
IF THERE'S NO MUSIC,
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO BUST
MY SWEET MOVES?
NOPE, STOP.
SEE, THIS IS PRECISELY
WHY YOU DON'T HAVE A GIRLFRIEND.
OH MY GOSH,
IT FEELS LIKE FLORIDA.
DALLAS:
HEY, BECKY!
ANY CHANCE YOU WERE
A SECRET MIAMI CLUB DJ?
OH YEAH,
DJ SHAKE 'N' BAKES!
SERIOUSLY?
NO, SILLY!
MUSIC'S THE DEVIL'S NOISE.
WOW! I KNEW YOU WERE
RELIGIOUS, BUT...
UGH! PEOPLE NEVER
GET MY JOKES!
(SIGHS)
DREW:
ALL ALONE?
I, UH, GUESS SO.
DALLAS:
I HEARD YOU WERE GONNA BRING
YOUR DUDE TO THIS.
YOU KNOW,
I WANTED TO SIZE HIM UP.
OH YEAH, HE CAME DOWN
WITH THAT THING
THAT'S GOING AROUND.
THAT'S TOO BAD.
BUT IT DOES MAKE YOU
AVAILABLE...
NOT REALLY.
TO HELP OUT.
DREW'S AWOL
AND HE DIDN'T SET UP
THE SOUND SYSTEM.
GREAT DANCE SO FAR.
NO MUSIC,
NO BOYFRIEND.
YOU SPEAK TOO SOON.
YOU CAME!
I OVERREACTED.
I KNOW THIS
IS IMPORTANT TO YOU,
AND I WANT TO MEET
YOUR FRIENDS.
YOU ANY GOOD WITH
SOUND SYSTEMS?
WHO'S THIS?
UM, LEO LAUZON,
MEET... MIKE DALLAS.
DALLAS.
WHO TEXTED YOU
IN PARIS?
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU.
LET ME SEE
WHAT I CAN DO.
(ALLI LAUGHS)
♪♪♪
(KNOCKING)
DREW!
IDIOT!
DREW, WAKE UP!
MMM, I DON'T WANNA GO
TO CAMP TODAY.
SNAP OUT OF IT!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN MY HOUSE?
YOU FORGOT TO PICK ME UP!
I'M YOUR DANCE DATE,
REMEMBER?
NO, I CAN'T GO.
I TOOK THE PILLS ALREADY.
YEAH, OBVIOUSLY.
NOW, GET UP!
BUT I WANNA SLEEP,
THEY'RE SLEEPING PILLS!
ZOE:
WE HAD A DEAL!
I'M NOT LETTING MILES AND MAYA
SEE ME
WALK INTO THAT DANCE ALONE.
MM...
I CAN'T GO LIKE THIS!
ZOE:
OF COURSE YOU CAN!
IT'S YOUR FIRST EVENT,
MR. PRESIDENT.
NOW PUT ON
YOUR BIG BOY PANTS!
THE MUSIC!
I NEVER MADE
THE PLAYLIST!
I'M SURE THEY FIGURED
SOMETHING OUT.
♪ We can dance if we want to ♪
♪ We can leave
your friends behind ♪
♪ 'Cause if friends don't dance
and if they don't dance ♪
ALLI:
THANK GOODNESS LEO
AND DALLAS FIGURED OUT
THE SOUND SYSTEM, HUH?
THIS STUFF IS SO '80S.
SO, LEO,
IS THIS WHAT YOUR DANCES
WERE LIKE IN FRANCE?
OH NO, EN FRANCE,
NO ONE WOULD BE STANDING
AGAINST THE WALL.
I-I JUST MEAN,
THE EMPHASIS AT A DANCE
IN FRANCE
IS, YOU KNOW, DANCE.
CONNOR, AM I LOSING SOMETHING
IN THE TRANSLATION?
I'M NOT SUPPOSED TO BE
WARM TO YOU.
WHAT IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
DON'T LOSE YOUR TEMPER!
OKAY!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
I CAN'T WIN
WITH THESE PEOPLE.
IT'S NOT A SPRINT,
IT'S A MARATHON,
SO JUST KEEP TRYING,
PLEASE?
FIND SOME COMMON GROUND.
♪♪♪
LEO:
HEY, I'M NOT A BAD GUY.
I KNOW IT'S GONNA TAKE SOME TIME
TO PROVE IT TO YOU,
BUT PLEASE GIVE ME A CHANCE.
DANCE WITH ME.
♪ If you disrespect
everybody that you run into ♪
♪ Tell me why do you think
anybody's gonna respect you ♪
♪ Oh, respect yourself ♪
DID YOU KNOW
HE COULD DO ALL THAT?
I HAD NO IDEA!
♪ If you won't
respect yourself ♪
♪ Ain't nobody gonna give
a whoop-de-whoop ♪
♪ No, no, no ♪
♪ Respect yourself ♪
♪ Na-na na-na ♪
♪ Do-do do-do ♪
THE COLOURS...
ALL RIGHT,
STAY WITH ME.
MILES:
SLOW SONG.
CRIMINAL THAT NEITHER OF US
ARE DANCING WITH ANYONE.
MAYA:
YEAH, BUT WHO WOULD
WE DANCE WITH?
WHOLE LOTTA PEOPLE HERE,
YOU'D THINK THERE'D BE
SOMEONE FOR US.
MAYBE NO ONE'S
GOOD ENOUGH.
COME ON,
DANCE WITH ME.
BUT-BUT THE COLOURS!
OH! HEY, GUYS.
YOU KNOW MY DATE.
WOW,
IT ACTUALLY IS TRUE.
DREW: WHOA!
ZOE: WHAT?!
WHAT IS IT?
DREW:
CLARE!
I DIDN'T THINK
YOU'D DANCE WITH ME
AFTER WHAT I DID.
MILES:
YOUR, UH, BOYFRIEND,
DOESN'T EVEN KNOW YOUR NAME!
HE'S JUST TIRED.
HE PLANNED THIS WHOLE DANCE,
YOU KNOW.
DREAM CLARE:
AND THE DANCE IS REALLY GREAT.
YOU KNOW
WHO WOULD'VE LOVED IT?
ADAM!
WH-WHY WOULD YOU SAY THAT?!
ADAM! ADAM!
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE!
IS HE ON DRUGS?!
MILES:
I GUESS THAT'S WHAT IT TAKES
FOR ZOE TO SECURE A DATE
THESE DAYS.
WHY DON'T YOU TWO
JUST HAVE SEX ALREADY!
CLARE:
OKAY, THAT WAS REALLY FUN,
BUT A LITTLE DANCING DOES NOT
PROVE THAT YOU'RE A GOOD GUY.
I KNOW, BUT I DON'T PLAN
ON STOPPING HERE.
YOU'LL SEE I'M GOOD,
AND I'M GOOD FOR ALLI.
I HOPE SO.
SO YOU GUYS ARE TALKING NOW?
WE'RE STARTING TO SEE
WHAT YOU SEE IN HIM.
JENNA:
YEAH, BUT DON'T THINK
WE AREN'T WATCHING YOU, BUDDY.
(ALLI LAUGHS)
SO DOES THIS MEAN
I PASSED THE FRIEND TEST?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WOW!
CONNOR:
GUYS, YOU'VE GOTTA SEE THIS!
DREW'S GETTING NAKED!
ALLI:
WHAT?!
LET'S GO IN,
YOU GUYS!
DUDE, WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?!
THE OCEAN!
IT'S BEAUTIFUL!
CLARE: WHAT'RE YOU DOING?!
DREW: AHHHH!
GETTING AWAY FROM YOU!
I'M DIVING IN
AND SWIMMING AS FAR AS I CAN GO.
(SIGHS BRACINGLY)
CANNONBALL!
(SPLASHES)
(STUDENTS LAUGH)
WH-WHAT THE HELL?
(STUDENTS HOLLER COMMENTS)
TEN POINTS! NICE ONE, DREW!
YOU ANIMAL!
DALLAS:
DUDE, THAT WAS HILARIOUS!
THAT "DUDE" IS NOT OKAY!
JENNA:
(GIGGLES)
('80S STYLE MUSIC PLAYS)
(STUDENTS LAUGH
AND CHATTER)
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ You break the chain of hope
to get somewhere someday ♪
♪ To feel just what
I want you to feel ♪
IT MAKES YOU SICK,
DOESN'T IT?
WHATEVER.
EVERYONE THINKS THAT
SHE'S THE SWEETHEART
AND I'M THE BITCH.
BUT SHE STOLE
MY BOYFRIEND.
I TOLD HER I'D WAIT
UNTIL SHE'S READY.
I GUESS NOW SHE'S READY
FOR THIS IDIOT.
I'M GONNA TEACH HER
A LESSON.
HOW?
I'LL THINK OF SOMETHING.
ZIG:
WELL, GOOD LUCK WITH THAT.
♪ Looking at the past ♪
♪ And trying to push
the words away ♪
HEY!
I'M SORRY ABOUT DREW.
ARE YOU?
YOU SEEMED TO GET
QUITE A LAUGH
OUT OF IT EARLIER.
I SHOULD'VE WARNED YOU
HE'S SUCH A JERK.
HE TOTALLY SCREWED OVER
MY SISTER LAST YEAR.
WHY ARE YOU BEING
SO NICE TO ME?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU'RE NEW HERE.
I GUESS I DON'T REALLY HAVE
ANY GIRLFRIENDS.
ME NEITHER.
GROWING UP ON SET,
ALL THE GIRLS WERE ALWAYS
OUT TO GET EACH OTHER.
WELL, I'M NOT OUT
TO GET YOU.
FRIENDS?
FRIENDS.
I THINK THIS IS GOING TO BE
A GREAT START
TO A NEW YEAR.
(MUFFLED DANCE MUSIC PLAYS)
DREW:
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THAT.
WHAT ARE YOU ON?!
A COUCH.
I'M SERIOUS,
I'M CONCERNED.
PLEASE DON'T TELL BIANCA.
I'LL LEAVE THAT
UP TO YOU,
IF YOU EVEN REMEMBER THIS
IN THE MORNING.
SO HOW WORRIED
SHOULD I BE?
ARE WE TALKING WEED?
MDMA?
HELP ME OUT,
I DON'T REALLY KNOW MANY DRUGS.
I'M SO SICK
OF MISSING HIM.
THIS IS ABOUT ADAM.
HE WAS MY ROCK...
MY MORAL COMPASS.
WITHOUT HIM,
I'M TOTALLY LOST.
WE ALL ARE.
I THINK ABOUT HIM
EVERY DAY.
WHAT DO WE DO WITHOUT HIM?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
I'LL COME BACK
TO COUNCIL.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
I WAS TERRIBLE.
ADAM WOULD WANT ME
TO WATCH OUT FOR YOU.
(LAUGHS)
I COULD HANDLE THAT.
AND WHEN YOU'RE READY,
ONLY WHEN YOU'RE READY,
WE'LL DO SOMETHING
IN HIS MEMORY.
I'D LIKE THAT.
(YAWNS)
SERIOUSLY,
WHAT DID YOU TAKE?
JUST A COUPLE
OF SLEEPING PILLS.
UM, ALL THIS
FROM A SLEEPING PILL?!
I'M AS SURPRISED
AS YOU ARE.
(GROANS SLEEPILY)
♪♪♪