(LOW RUMBLING,
BIRDS CHIRP)
(LOUD THUNDERCLAP)
(WIND HOWLS)
(RATTLING)
IMOGEN:
IF WE DON'T REDUCE
GREENHOUSE GASES,
THE DEVASTATING EFFECTS
OF CLIMATE CHANGE
WILL ONLY GET WORSE!
SUPERSTORMS THAT USED
TO BE RARE
HAVE BECOME COMMON OCCURRENCES
AROUND THE GLOBE.
THANK YOU.
(DRAMATIC SOUND EFFECTS PLAY)
MR. PERINO:
THANK YOU, MS. MORENO.
ANY QUESTIONS?
DALLAS.
THAT CAN'T HAPPEN HERE,
RIGHT?
IMOGEN:
HAVEN'T YOU BEEN WATCHING
THE WEATHER NETWORK?
THERE'S LIKE A HUGE STORM
COMING RIGHT NOW!
COMING TO NEW YORK,
OR MAYBE NEW BRUNSWICK.
SO NOT HERE.
COOL?
WHY DOES NO ONE EVER
TAKE ME SERIOUSLY?!
MR. PERINO:
ANY MORE QUESTIONS?
OKAY, THAT'S ALL I'VE GOT
FOR THE TERM.
ENJOY YOUR BREAK!
DREW:
SWEET! WE CAN FINALIZE
THE PLAYLIST
FOR THE END
OF THE TERM DANCE!
YEAH, WHEN DOES THE DANCE
END AGAIN?
TEN? ELEVEN?
NEXT SUNDAY?
HER PARENTS HAVE BEEN
PRETTY UPSET
SINCE HER BROTHER
GOT SENTENCED.
YEAH, WELL,
TWO YEARS IN THE SLAMMER,
COULD YOU IMAGINE?
N-NO!
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, STOP!
UM, BE HAPPIER!
MUSIC! MUSIC!
♪ One, two, three-four-five ♪
♪ Everybody in the car
so come on let's ride ♪
♪ To the liquor store
around the corner ♪
♪ The boys say they want
some gin and juice ♪
♪ But I really don't wanna ♪
♪ Beer bust like
I had last week ♪
♪ I must stay deep
'cause talk is cheap ♪
♪ I like Angela, Pamela,
Sandra, and Rita ♪
♪ And as I continue ♪
♪ You know they're gettin'
sweeter ♪
IMOGEN:
WHAT GIVES?
THAT'S LIKE THE HAPPIEST SONG
ON EARTH!
SHE AND HER BROTHER USED TO DO
A DANCE ROUTINE TO THAT
WHEN THEY WERE KIDS.
HOW DO YOU EVEN KNOW THAT?!
BECKY AND I TALK,
WE'RE TIGHT.
I SHOULD GO CHECK ON HER.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I GOT THIS ONE.
DREW TORRES IS "JUST FRIENDS"
WITH A GIRL RIGHT NOW?!
YOU BELIEVE THAT,
BUT NOT GLOBAL WARMING?!
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ (The best that I can be) ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(BELL RINGS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
ZIG, YOU HAVE TO GO
TO THIS DANCE WITH ME!
SCHOOL EVENTS AND I
DON'T EXACTLY MIX.
COME ON,
I NEED SOME FUN!
MILES IS THE WORST
AND TRISTAN HATES ME!
I NEED MY BEST FRIEND
RIGHT NOW!
SINCE WHEN AM I
YOUR BEST FRIEND?!
I DON'T KNOW,
BUT THINK ABOUT IT.
I MEAN
AREN'T I YOURS, TOO?
YEAH, I GUESS SO.
YES! YOU'RE THE BEST!
AND I PROMISE,
WE WILL HAVE FUN TONIGHT!
OKAY.
ZIG: OH, SORRY!
ZOE: TOTALLY MY FAULT!
I WASN'T LOOKING.
SO, UH, SO YOU'RE GOOD?
NO MORE WRESTLING MATCHES
WITH REPORTERS?
I'M TRYING TO LAY LOW
FOR A WHILE.
HEY, ARE YOU GOING
TO THE DANCE?
UH, I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE. WHY?
WELL, I THOUGHT IT MIGHT BE FUN
IF YOU AND I...
HUNG OUT THERE TOGETHER?
ZIG:
YEAH! YEAH,
THAT WOULD BE FUN.
I GUESS.
AWESOME.
COOL.
♪ Come on,
be proud of who you are ♪
♪ Shout it out ♪
YOU DUMBASS!
WHAT?
DID YOU JUST AGREE
TO GO TO THE DANCE
WITH BOTH THOSE GIRLS?
YEAH, WHY?
IS THAT BAD?
(SNICKERS)
WHAT?!
WE ARE GOING TO TEAR UP
THE DANCE FLOOR TONIGHT!
ACTUALLY, I'M KIND OF
GOING WITH ZIG.
BUT YOU SAID YOU WOULD HELP
KEEP MY MIND OFF
ALL THINGS YATES.
SORRY, TRIS!
YOU COULD COME WITH.
WHAT? NO, I'M IN A FIGHT
WITH MAYA,
WHO LIVES WITH ZIG.
WHICH MEANS WE'RE ENEMIES,
ONCE REMOVED.
AW!
BUH-BYE.
(SCOFFS)
CAN YOU BELIEVE
I'M BEING DITCHED FOR ZIG?
OH, SORRY,
STORY OF YOUR LIFE.
SO ARE YOU GOING
TO THE DANCE TONIGHT?
NOPE.
TRISTAN:
WHY NOT?
RHYMES WITH SCHMAYA SCHMATLIN.
GOTCHA.
WELL, MAYBE WE COULD HANG OUT?
ACTUALLY, MY PARENTS ARE STUCK
IN COLORADO
AT LIKE A COUPLES RETREAT
OR SOMETHING.
MOVIE MARATHON!
YOU'RE NOT GAMING
WITH WINSTON?
THE GUY WHO BETRAYED ME
IN COURT
AND NOW MAKES OUT
WITH MY LITTLE SISTER?!
NO!
SO JUST YOU AND ME,
HANGING OUT ALONE,
LIKE A BRO-DATE?
YEAH,
NOBODY CALLS IT THAT.
WELL, YOU KNOW, I MAKE
A KILLER BAG OF POPCORN!
THE SECRET IS DILL SPICE.
BEST BRO-DATE EVER!
ALLI: IF YOU WANT TO CALL HIM-
CLARE: CALL YOU.
IF YOU SEE HIM ANYWHERE-
CALL YOU.
IF YOU EVEN THINK
THE WORD ELI-
I GET IT, AL!
YOU KNOW, I MANAGED TO BOOK
AN EARLIER FLIGHT TO NEW YORK,
SO I COULD GET THERE
BEFORE THE STORM.
WILL YOU LET ME CATCH IT?!
YEAH, BUT AN EARLIER FLIGHT
EQUALS EXTRA TIME TO KILL
BEFORE YOUR COLUMBIA INTERVIEW,
AND I'M JUST WORRIED ABOUT
WHAT YOU'RE GONNA DO!
I DON'T KNOW,
IT'S MY FIRST TIME IN NEW YORK.
ANY ADVICE?
THE THREE B'S:
BARNEYS, BENDEL AND BERGDORF!
ALL SHOPPING,
OF COURSE.
AND NO E'S!
CLARE:
IT'S A BIG CITY, ALLI.
I DON'T WANNA SEE ELI,
I WON'T SEE ELI.
NOW, WILL YOU LET ME GET
TO THE MOST IMPORTANT INTERVIEW
OF MY LIFE?
OKAY, FINE. GO.
KILL IT!
♪ Come on,
be proud of who you are ♪
♪ Shout it out ♪
(WIND HOWLS)
(SOBBING)
IT'S GETTING WINDY
OUT HERE.
YOU SHOULD COME INSIDE,
HELP GET THE DANCE READY.
UH, I DON'T THINK
I'M GONNA GO.
HOW DID YOU FIND ME
IN HERE, ANYWAY?
BECAUSE.
I KNOW WHERE YOU GO
WHEN YOU'RE UPSET.
(BECKY SNIFFLES)
YOU'VE BEEN SO NICE TO ME
THESE PAST COUPLE WEEKS.
WHY?
'CAUSE I KNOW
WHAT IT'S LIKE...
TO LOSE A BROTHER.
THAT'S WHY I'M NOT LEAVING
UNTIL YOU CRACK A SMILE.
SO, UM...
HERE'S A LITTLE PREVIEW
OF WHAT YOU'RE GONNA GET
IF YOU COME TO THE DANCE
TONIGHT.
OH! GREAT!
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
(SIGHS)
♪ He buried her heart still ♪
DREW:
BECKY BAKER?
WILL YOU GIVE ME
A LITTLE SQUEEZE?
(BOTH LAUGH)
DREW!
IT'S A STRESS BALL.
IT WORKS FOR ME
WHEN I'M GOING THROUGH STUFF.
HERE, TRY.
(BOTH LAUGH)
IT FEELS GOOD, HUH?
YOU GONNA COME TONIGHT?
I JUST NEED A BIT MORE TIME
TO MYSELF.
OF COURSE.
YOU'LL SAVE ME THAT DANCE
THOUGH, RIGHT?
AS LONG AS IT'S NOT
THE RUNNING MAN.
(BOTH LAUGH)
(WIND HOWLS VIOLENTLY)
ZIG:
YOU HAVE TO HELP ME!
WHO ASKED YOU FIRST?
MAYA.
THEN TELL ZOE
YOU CAN'T GO.
DO YOU EVEN KNOW HER?
EW! YOU LIKE HER!
I NEVER SAID THAT!
THEN TELL BLONDIE
YOU'LL SEE HER AT HOME,
OR WHATEVER.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
AFTER EVERYTHING MAYA
HAS DONE FOR ME?
AND BESIDES,
ZOE JUST ASKED ME
AS LIKE A FRIEND, RIGHT?
GIRLS DON'T ASK GUYS TO DANCES
AS FRIENDS.
DOES THAT MEAN
MAYA'S INTO ME?
NO, SHE JUST WANTS
TO BE YOUR FRIEND.
BUT YOU JUST SAID
THAT-
THAT'S AN EXCEPTION!
OKAY, BUT YOU CAN'T DATE ZOE,
IT WOULD KILL MAYA!
BUT YOU JUST SAID-
MAYA DOESN'T "LIKE"
LIKE YOU, OKAY?
THAT DOESN'T MEAN
SHE'D BE OKAY
WITH YOU DATING
HER NEMESIS.
TRY TO KEEP UP,
IT'S NOT THAT COMPLICATED!
SO IF EITHER GIRL FIGURES OUT
THAT I PICKED ONE OF THEM
OVER THE OTHER...
YOU'RE DEAD MEAT.
GREAT. SO THE ONLY WAY THAT
I CAN MAKE IT THROUGH THIS...
IS IF I FIND A WAY
TO MAKE THEM GET ALONG.
MY RECOMMENDATION?
PEACH SCHNAPPS.
THE ULTIMATE
SOCIAL LUBRICANT.
(CHUCKLES)
(ROMANTIC FRENCH MUSIC PLAYS)
(WIND HOWLS)
(DOOR SHUTS QUIETLY)
(CHUCKLES)
(FRANKIE AND WINSTON GASP)
HEY! WE WERE WATCHING THAT!
YEAH, BUT I'M OLDER.
FRANKIE:
YEAH, BUT I'M SMARTER
AND FASTER!
MILES:
WHOA! WHOA!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
FRANKIE: GIMME THE REMOTE!
MILES: GET OFF!
MILES: AH! WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
(LOUD THUD, GLASS BREAKS)
FRANKIE:
I'M TRYING TO GET THE REMOTE!
MILES: NOPE. THIS IS SO-
FRANKIE: I WAS HERE FIRST!
MILES, JUST BECAUSE MAYA
BROKE YOUR HEART
DOES NOT MEAN
YOU HAVE TO BE A HUGE JERK!
MILES:
WE'LL PLAY FOR THE GOOD TV.
GUYS!
NO, FRANK, LET'S JUST GO.
SIT!
OKAY.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WINSTON:
THE CLASSIC HOLLINGSWORTH
FAMILY WAY
OF SETTLING SOMETHING.
FRANKIE: CHARADES!
MILES: CHARADES!
OH, I LOVE CHARADES!
YOU WON'T
THE WAY THEY PLAY IT.
♪♪♪
NEW YORK IS FREAKING AWESOME,
ALLI!
ALLI:
DON'T WANNA SAY
"I TOLD YOU SO,"
BUT... I TOLD YOU SO!
CLARE:
THE MOMA WAS BEAUTIFUL,
TIMES SQUARE WAS MENTAL,
AND I FOUND THE MOST AMAZING
BOOKSTORE IN THE WEST VILLAGE.
I COULD SPEND DAYS THERE!
ALLI:
CLARE EDWARDS
ALREADY A NEW YORKER?
ALMOST. ALL I HAVE TO DO
IS NAIL MY INTERVIEW, AND-
WHOA!
ALLI:
WHAT? DID YOU SEE A CELEBRITY?
IT'S CHANNING TATUM, ISN'T IT?
IS HE HOT?
IS HE TALL?
HE'S... ELI.
ALLI:
THERE'S NO WAY!
CLARE:
RUFFLED HAIR, BLACK COAT,
BLACK CHUCKS.
W-WHAT DO I DO?
ALLI:
WALK AWAY BRISKLY!
FOCUS ON YOUR INTERVIEW.
EYES ON THE PRIZE, GIRL!
YEAH!
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT, AL.
THANKS.
(RELIEVED SIGH)
(LOUD CLANG)
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYS)
HAVE A GOOD DANCE!
HOW DO I LOOK?
THERE'S NO MIRRORS
IN THE COUNCIL OFFICE.
YOU LOOK GOOD.
I KNOW, I JUST WANTED
TO HEAR YOU SAY IT.
SO IS THE GYM READY?
YOU HAVE TO ANSWER A RIDDLE
BEFORE YOU PASS.
DO YOU LIKE BECKY?
(GASPS) WHAT?
SERIOUSLY?!
YOUR BROTHER'S OLD GIRLFRIEND?
LOOK, THAT'S ONE
OF THE MANY REASONS
I KNOW I CAN'T LIKE HER,
SO CAN I GO NOW?
NOPE, BECAUSE YOU SAID,
"YOU CAN'T LIKE HER,"
NOT "YOU DON'T LIKE HER."
LOOK, BECKY IS SWEET,
BUT I'M HONESTLY
JUST TRYING TO BE A GOOD FRIEND!
SO SHE GOT UPSET,
YOU FOUND HER, AND YOU...
CHEERED HER UP,
CONVINCED HER TO COME,
AND PROMISED HER A DANCE.
THIS ONLY ENDS ONE WAY,
MY MAN,
IN HEARTBREAK.
YOU KNOW WHAT? FINE.
JUST TO PROVE TO YOU TWO
THAT I'M GONNA DO
THE RIGHT THING HERE WITH BECKY,
YOU KNOW WHAT?!
I'M GONNA SKIP THE DANCE!
NO MORE ACCIDENTAL FLIRTING,
NO MORE SEXY DANCE MOVES
GETTING ME IN TROUBLE!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
NO MORE DREW TORRES!
(CREAKING,
TREE CRASHES)
(GIRLS SCREAM)
(WIND HOWLS VIOLENTLY)
(RAIN PATTERS)
UNTIL FURTHER NOTICE,
NO ONE'S GOING ANYWHERE!
IF I REQUEST
THE NEW BEYONCE SONG TONIGHT,
WILL YOU DANCE WITH ME?
UH, YEAH.
YEAH, SURE.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
EXPECTING SOMEONE?
WHO?!
UM...
STARTS WITH A "Z."
ZOE?!
SERIOUSLY?
I JUST THOUGHT
THE MORE THE MERRIER,
AND SHE ASKED ME
IF I WANTED TO HANG OUT.
I DON'T KNOW, I JUST DIDN'T
REALLY THINK YOU'D MIND-
I MIND A LOT!
YOU KNOW, WE HAVEN'T EVEN SPOKEN
SINCE THE TRIAL,
AND SHE'S THE WORST!
YEAH, WELL,
I THOUGHT MILES WAS THE WORST!
MAYA:
THEY'RE BOTH TERRIBLE, OKAY?!
YOU KNOW, THEY BASICALLY
GOT IT ON AT THAT PARTY
WHILE MILES AND I WERE
STILL TOGETHER!
ZIG:
OKAY, LOOK, EVERYTHING'S GONNA
BE FINE, OKAY?
AND TO MAKE SURE OF IT...
I GOT MYSELF
A LITTLE HELPER.
OH MY GOD,
YOU LIKE HER!
ZOE:
HELLO, PARTY PEOPLE!
OKAY, I THINK I MANAGED
TO SAVE MY HAIR!
WHO'S READY
TO HAVE SOME FUN?
(LAUGHS FALSELY)
♪♪♪
♪ Let's go ♪
♪ Woo ♪
OKAY, WELL, IT'S OFFICIAL,
THE DANCE IS CANCELLED.
SO UH... TWEET,
OR WHATEVER YOU KIDS DO
THESE DAYS.
COME ON, SIR,
IT'S ABOUT TO LET UP!
DID YOU ALREADY FORGET
WHAT HAPPENED OUT THERE?!
THE STORM HAS TURNED,
IT'S HEADING RIGHT FOR US.
WE'RE GONNA GET HAMMERED
FOR THE NEXT COUPLE HOURS!
I'M GOING TO SOUND
THE EMERGENCY ALARM;
I NEED YOUR HELP TO MAKE SURE
THAT EVERY STUDENT
WHO IS STILL HERE
IS IN THE GYM AND ACCOUNTED FOR,
GOT IT?
ALL RIGHT,
WE'RE ON IT, SIR.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
HEY, EVERYONE,
AT LEAST I WASN'T THE ONE
TO RUIN EVERYONE'S DANCE
THIS TIME!
(CHUCKLES)
(THUNDER RUMBLES,
SIRENS WAIL)
NURSE:
(FRUSTRATED SIGH)
IT NEVER FAILS:
STORM OUTSIDE, CHAOS INSIDE.
REMEMBER TO KEEP
THE STITCHES CLEAN,
AND WHATEVER YOU DO,
DON'T SCRATCH 'EM.
THOSE DIRTY LITTLE PAWS
OF YOURS
CAN CAUSE AN INFECTION.
UH, IS-IS THAT
THE REAL TIME?
YUP! YOU GOT A DATE?
YEAH, WITH THE COLUMBIA
OFFICE OF ADMISSIONS!
OKAY, WELL,
WE'VE DONE THE BLOODWORK
TO MAKE SURE
THERE'S NO UNDERLYING REASON
YOU PASSED OUT,
ESPECIALLY CONSIDERING
YOUR RECENT MEDICAL HISTORY.
YOU SHOULD GET RESULTS
WITHIN 24 HOURS.
SO A DOCTOR JUST HAS
TO LOOK AT YOU,
RULE OUT A CONCUSSION,
THEN YOU CAN JET!
NO, YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND,
I HAVE TO GO NOW!
YOU PASSED OUT
IN THE STREET.
THIS IS SERIOUS!
SO IS COLUMBIA!
MY ENTIRE FUTURE,
MY LIFE IN NEW YORK,
RESTS ON THIS INTERVIEW!
I HAVE TO GET OUT OF HERE,
PLEASE!
(GROANS)
IF ANYONE ASKS,
I TRIED TO STOP YOU,
YOU BIT ME!
YOU ARE A LIFESAVER!
WINSTON:
UH, UH, TWO WORDS!
UH... BABY!
UH, BABY- BABY DADDY?
UH, DAD?
DADDY! DAD!
AND... TIME'S UP!
BASTERDS!
THE MOVIE WAS
"INGLOURIOUS BASTERDS!"
TRISTAN:
YOU KNOW, FOR TWO PEOPLE
IN LOVE,
YOU SURE DON'T HAVE
MUCH OF A CONNECTION!
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY?!
TRISTAN:
THAT YOU'RE GONNA LOSE.
OBVI!
OKAY, LET'S DO THIS.
OPEN.
UH, BOOK!
BOOK? BOOK?
BOOK!
FOUR WORDS...
SHOOT.
UM... SHOTGUN, FLYING, BIRD-
OH! OH! UM,
"TO KILL A MOCKINGBIRD!"
YES!
WELL, WE STUDIED THE BOOK
IN CLASS,
AND SIR SNOOZE-A-LOT HERE
FELL ASLEEP.
MILES:
THAT CREEPO YATES CAUGHT ME.
HE WAS SO MAD.
UM, 'CAUSE HE TRIED
TO GROPE ME!
NO WAY!
GRANT WOULD NEVER DO THAT.
I WAS THERE, DUDE!
WHY ARE YOU DEFENDING HIM?
WHOA! TRIS, HE DIDN'T TRY
TO TOUCH YOU TOO, DID HE?
NO, NO, I JUST...
WE...
OH MY GOD, YOU HAD A THING
WITH THE PERVY TEACHER?!
WE HAD A CONNECTION!
A CONNECTION?
GET REAL, TRIS!
IF I'VE LEARNED ANYTHING
THIS YEAR,
IT'S THAT NO ONE WILL EVER
TRULY LOVE YOU.
(SIGHS)
COLD, MAN!
(DOOR CLICKS OPEN,
THUNDER RUMBLES)
(DOOR SLAMS)
NEVER HAVE I EVER-
MM-HMM?
SHOPLIFTED MAKEUP
FROM A STORE!
ZIG:
I'VE NEVER DONE THAT,
I SWEAR!
ZOE:
OH, GOOD FOR YOU!
ZIG:
YOU'VE NEVER DONE THAT EITHER,
YOU DIRTY LIAR!
YES I HAVE!
ZIG:
YOU'RE JUST A GOODY TWO-SHOES
AND EVERYONE KNOWS IT!
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW ME!
ZOE:
OH YES, I DO!
YOU- WHATEVER.
IT'S MY TURN.
(GIGGLES)
OKAY.
NEVER HAVE I EVER...
UM, SKINNY DIPPED!
I'VE TOTALLY SKINNY DIPPED!
ZIG:
WHOA THERE!
ZOE:
YOU'RE JUST SAYING THINGS
YOU'VE DONE
SO YOU CAN KEEP DRINKING!
MAYA:
OKAY, I'LL DO SOMETHING
I HAVEN'T DONE!
NEVER HAVE I EVER...
COME ON TO ANOTHER GIRL'S
BOYFRIEND AT A PARTY!
HMM?
UM... OKAY.
UH, MAYBE YOU'VE HAD ENOUGH.
OH, COME ON!
ZOE, DRINK UP!
OKAY, UH, IT'S MY TURN,
ACTUALLY!
MY TURN.
SO NEVER HAVE I EVER-
MAYA:
CYBERBULLIED SOMEONE BY PUTTING
FAKE NAKED PICTURES OF HER
ALL OVER THE INTERNET?
(GIGGLES)
I DON'T THINK SHE UNDERSTANDS
HOW TO PLAY!
ZIG:
OKAY, MAYA, CALL OFF YOUR DOGS!
WHY?
IF IT WASN'T FOR HER,
I'D STILL BE WITH MILES
RIGHT NOW.
CAN WE TALK ABOUT THIS
LATER?
NO, I WANNA TALK
ABOUT IT NOW!
YOU'VE BEEN SUCH
A BITCH TO ME, ZOE!
YOU'RE THE REASON
I SPENT THE ENTIRE YEAR
IN THE RUBBER ROOM,
AND YOU KEEP STEALING
ALL MY PEOPLE:
MILES, TRISTAN,
AND NOW ZIG?!
MUAH!
GET YOUR OWN PEOPLE!
(GROANS)
SCREW THIS!
I'M GOING TO THE DANCE
ON MY OWN!
OKAY, UM...
IT'S PRETTY BAD OUT THERE
AND SHE'S PRETTY DRUNK.
ZIG: I'M GONNA GO AFTER HER.
ZOE: NO, LET ME.
ARE YOU SURE
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA?!
WE OBVIOUSLY HAVE SOME STUFF
TO WORK OUT.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
(SIGHS)
(SIRENS WAIL)
(CLARE PANTS)
NO, NO, NO, PLEASE TELL ME
YOU'RE NOT PACKING UP!
CAN I HELP YOU,
MISS?
EDWARDS, CLARE EDWARDS!
I- I HAVE AN INTERVIEW!
HAD AN INTERVIEW.
I AM SO SORRY
THAT I'M LATE,
BUT THERE'S GOTTA BE
ANOTHER SLOT LEFT!
THE ADMISSION TEAM
HAS LEFT.
IT'S NOT MY FAULT!
PLEASE, YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND
THE DAY I'VE HAD!
SAVE IT!
I'VE HEARD EVERY EXCUSE,
MS. EDWARDS.
NO, BUT I-
I WAS IN THE HOSPITAL!
LOOK, I WAS IN A HIT AND RUN
WITH... A POLE.
I CAN SHOW YOU
THE STITCHES!
I BELIEVE YOU.
NO ONE WOULD LIE ABOUT
SOMETHING SO EMBARRASSING.
I COULD PROBABLY FIT YOU IN
FIRST THING TOMORROW MORNING.
EIGHT A.M.
MY FLIGHT HOME
IS TONIGHT!
PLANES ARE GROUNDED,
YOU'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
OKAY!
GOT ANY HOTEL
RECOMMENDATIONS?
LOTS, BUT THEY'LL BE FULL
WITH STRANDED TOURISTS.
KNOW ANYBODY IN THE CITY
YOU CAN STAY WITH?
ONE PERSON.
(WIND HOWLS,
RAIN SPLASHES)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
UH, HEY, TRISTAN!
TRISTAN, COME INSIDE,
IT'S DANGEROUS OUT HERE!
JUST LEAVE ME
TO THE STORM!
(GROANS)
DID YOU REALLY HAVE A THING
WITH YATES?
I THOUGHT WE WERE IN LOVE.
BUT OBVIOUSLY
IT'S JUST A BIG JOKE!
WHO COULD EVER
TRULY LOVE ME, RIGHT?
COME ON, TRIS,
YOU'RE THE MOST LOVEABLE GUY
I KNOW!
I DIDN'T MEAN
NO ONE COULD LOVE YOU.
I MEANT LIKE ANYONE.
YOU KNOW, I... I MEANT ME!
YOU?!
RIGHT!
YOU'RE A GOD AMONG MEN!
YOU GET EVERY GIRL YOU WANT!
UNTIL THEY GET TO KNOW ME,
THEN THEY RUN FOR THE HILLS!
TRISTAN:
YEAH, WELL, MAYA'S A DUMMY!
AND ZOE ISN'T EXACTLY
GOOD AT BOYS.
YOU KNOW, I TOTALLY FELL FOR YOU
IN PARIS.
(WIND HOWLS,
METAL CLANGS)
LOOK OUT!
(CLANGING)
(PANTING)
YOU KNOW,
IF THIS WERE A ROM-COM,
THIS IS WHERE
WE'D KISS.
(LOUD THUNDERCLAP)
ALL RIGHT, COME ON,
LET'S GET INSIDE!
SOMEONE'S GOTTA KEEP FRANKIE
AND WINSTON IN CHECK!
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
DREW:
ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
FIND YOUR NAME ON THE LIST
AND CHECK IT OFF!
HAVE YOU TRIED
TO CALL HOME YET?
I CAN'T GET THROUGH!
THE STORM PROBABLY TOOK
THE TOWERS DOWN.
HEY, UM, HAVE YOU SEEN BECKY?
ME? NO.
WH-WHY WOULD I HAVE SEEN BECKY?
WHY WOULDN'T YOU HAVE
SEEN BECKY?!
I THOUGHT YOU TWO
WERE TIGHT?
TIGHT? NO!
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE LOOSE!
OKAY, SUPER LOOSE!
OKAY, WEIRDO!
WELL, WE CAN'T FIND HER
ANYWHERE.
WE THOUGHT WE'D SEE HER
WHEN WE WERE GETTING DRESSED,
AND NO ONE'S SEEN HER
SINCE YOU WENT TO TALK TO HER!
HAVE YOU TRIED
TO CALL HER?
THERE'S NO CELL SERVICE!
WHERE'D YOU SEE HER LAST?
UM, THE GREENHOUSE.
DREW...
THE GREENHOUSE WAS DESTROYED
BY THAT UPROOTED TREE!
(LOUD THUNDERCLAP)
DREW, IMOGEN, AND JACK:
(YELLING) BECKY! BECKY! BECKY!
BECKY! BECKY! BECKY!
OH MY GOD!
IMOGEN:
BECKY!
JACK: HEY!
IMOGEN: BECKY!
DREW:
COME ON! BECKY!
BECKY!
IMOGEN:
BECKY! OH MY GOD!
THANK GOD
SHE'S NOT IN HERE!
THEN WHERE IS SHE?!
SHE PROBABLY JUST WENT
BACK INSIDE.
WHICH IS WHAT
WE SHOULD BE DOING!
WHY? IT LOOKS LIKE
IT'S CLEARING UP!
ARE YOU SERIOUS,
DREW?!
THIS IS THE FIRST WAVE
OF THUNDERCLOUDS
OF WHO KNOWS HOW MANY!
WE NEED TO GO BACK
IN THE GYM, NOW!
COME ON!
I HOPE SHE'S SAFE!
IMOGEN:
RUN! COME ON!
COME ON!
(WIND HOWLS,
METAL CLANGS)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
(TRANSFORMERS EXPLODE)
(SIRENS WAIL IN THE DISTANCE)