♪♪♪
PLEASE GIVE IT UP
FOR LEXTACY!
(CHEERING)
MEL:
HOW WAS IT?
HONESTLY?
THE MOST TERRIFYING EXPERIENCE
OF MY LIFE.
ANNOUNCER:
GENTLEMEN,
GET READY TO CELEBRATE
THE SCINTILLATING
SHERRY JUBILEE...
I THINK I'M GONNA
THROW UP.
PAIGE CALLED.
SHE WANTS YOU
TO CALL HER BACK.
MEL?
THIS NEVER HAPPENED,
OKAY?
PAIGE:
HEY SWEETS.
I BROUGHT FALAFEL.
IS THAT THE ONLY REASON
YOU COME OVER?
TO FATTEN ME UP?
NO. UM...
IN FACT, IT'S NOT.
I THOUGHT ABOUT
WHAT YOU SAID,
ABOUT LABELS -
STRAIGHT, BI,
LESBIAN, WHATEVER.
I REALLY, REALLY CARE
ABOUT YOU
AND I'VE DECIDED TO TRY
TO GET OVER MY FEARS.
SO MS. NUNEZ,
WILL YOU BE
MY SWEETHEART?
THERE'S YOUR ANSWER,
SWEETHEART.
♪♪♪
MORNING.
IRREGULAR COOKIE?
MOM...
GOD, HOW CAN YOU STOMACH
THOSE THINGS
AFTER A NIGHT SHIFT?
HEY, EACH COOKIE
I MECHANICALLY ASSEMBLE
GETS US ONE STEP CLOSER
TO KEEPING A ROOF
OVER OUR HEADS.
WILL THIS HELP?
HOLY!
DID YOU ROB A BANK?
A JOB AT A SCHMANCY BISTRO
EQUALS BIG TIPS.
THAT'S FOR
THE RENT FUND.
THANK YOU SO MUCH,
HONEY.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE THE ONE
THING I'VE EVER DONE
THAT TURNED OUT RIGHT?
DON'T BE SO SURE.
RIGHT NOW
I'VE GOT AN EXAM.
TEACHER:
(CLEARS THROAT)
JAY:
EEYORE, HAVE YOU SEEN MY FRIEND
SEAN AROUND?
I'M SORRY, MAN.
IT'S JUST...
EVERYTHING'S ABOUT
TO CHANGE.
WELL, IT'S ABOUT TIME
YOU GOT SOME FRESH GITCH.
I'M TALKING ABOUT
MY LIFE, JACKASS.
EMMA THINKS
SHE'S PREGNANT.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?!
CONGRATULATIONS, MAN!
SCORE!
SCORE?
WHAT, HAVE YOU BEEN
DRINKING BRAKE FLUID?
YOU HAVE GOT HER, BRO,
FOREVER.
NOW THIS WAY EMMA
CAN'T DITCH YOUR ASS
WHEN SHE COMES
TO HER SENSES!
YOU KNOW, GIMMIE A BREAK,
ALL RIGHT?
KNOCKING HER UP
WAS NEVER PART OF THE PLAN.
THIS IS YOUR TICKET,
SEANY.
READY-MADE FAMILY,
LIFE AT THE GARAGE...
YOU'RE SET FOR LIFE!
ISN'T THAT WHAT
YOU ALWAYS WANTED?
♪♪♪
DID YOU TIP?
OR IS EVERY LAST DIME
STILL GOING TO YOUR DAD?
TIP I DID,
GLOOMY ONE.
I ALSO HAVE ONE
FOR YOU:
WHEN BOY HUNTING,
TRY TO LOOK LIKE
YOU'RE HAVING FUN.
JESSE!
YOU LOOK GREAT,
ELLIE.
SO WHAT'S IN THE BAG?
A GESTURE OF SWEET,
SWEET ROMANCE?
PAIGE:
THIS?
A LITTLE POST-EXAM GIFT
FOR MY BELLE.
SUPER ON SALE.
(GIGGLE)
OH...
SEXY!
IT'S PERFECT FOR WORK!
HILARIOUS, MEL!
SHE'S, SHE'S JOKING.
GOOD.
BUT AS FAR AS JOKES GO,
HON?
NOT SO FUNNY.
THE THOUGHT OF YOU WEARING
A PARKA IN THAT PLACE
GIVES ME AN EMOTIONAL BOIL.
WELL, THEN I GUESS
I'LL JUST HAVE TO PERFORM
AN EMOTIONAL LANCING.
TOMORROW NIGHT,
I'LL QUIT;
I'LL FIND A NEW JOB.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?!
BEST PRESENT EVER!
I SUDDENLY FEEL
LIKE DANCING!
NEW JOB?
AS FAR AS PAIGE KNOWS?
YOU BET.
A BIG, FAT LIE.
NOW THERE IS
A SOLID FOUNDATION
FOR A RELATIONSHIP.
ALEX:
YEAH, A COMPLICATED ONE.
AND IF SHE FINDS OUT
I'M AN EXOTIC DANCER?
THERE WON'T BE ONE
AT ALL.
JAY:
WELL GOOD LUCK WITH THAT,
LEXTACY.
YOU SEE,
WHEN A HOT GIRL
SHAKES HER NAKED TA-TAS
FOR A LIVING,
WORD GETS AROUND.
MS. HATZILAKOS:
ALEX, DO YOU HAVE A MINUTE?
YEAH.
PEOPLE ARE TALKING
ABOUT YOU.
WHATEVER.
IT'S ALL LIES.
THESE PEOPLE
ARE YOUR TEACHERS.
THEY'RE ALL VERY IMPRESSED
ON HOW YOU'VE HAD A MAJOR
TURN-AROUND THIS YEAR.
HOWEVER, I DID HEAR ABOUT
YOUR ORGANIC CHEM EXAM.
IT'S NOT EXACTLY
YOUR BEST WORK.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
YEAH, COULDN'T BE
BETTER, MS. H.
I'LL STUDY HARDER
NEXT TIME, OKAY?
LISTEN, I WANTED TO TALK
TO YOU ABOUT UNIVERSITY.
YEAH.
UNIVERSITIES COST MONEY.
THERE ARE SCHOLARSHIPS
OR LOANS.
I'LL WRITE YOU
A GLOWING REFERENCE,
AND WITH SOME
PART-TIME WORK...
IS THAT ALL?
HOW WAS YOUR EXAM?
I MANAGED.
THANKS FOR THE STUDY HELP.
OKAY...
IF YOU'RE PREGNANT,
LET'S KEEP THE BABY.
IF THAT'S OKAY
WITH YOU?
(SIGHS)
YES, YES.
YES, IT'S OKAY
WITH ME.
JUST US DOING THIS TOGETHER
MAKES IT OKAY WITH ME.
AH, JUST PROMISE ME
YOUR PARENTS WON'T KILL ME.
WELL THERE WILL BE
SERIOUS DRAMA,
BUT IT'S BETTER
THAN BOOTCAMP!
I'M STILL GOING
TO ENLIST, EMMA.
WHAT?
I'D SEND MONEY.
I'D SEE YOU ON LEAVE.
IT'S BEST FOR EVERYONE.
LEAVING ME ALONE?
IT'S THE WORST IDEA,
SEAN!
IT'S RIDICULOUS!
I WOULDN'T BAIL ON YOU,
EMMA.
I, I JUST WANT
TO GET A CAREER!
I WANT A CHANCE
TO BECOME SOMETHING.
AND I'M STUCK
BEING A TEEN MOM.
WELL, THAT'S FANTASTIC.
WHY ARE GUYS
SO TYPICAL?
(EXOTIC MUSIC)
♪♪♪
ALL BY YOURSELF,
SWEETHEART?
YEAH,
I DIDN'T WANT TO JOIN
THE DRESSING ROOM
NOSE-CANDY PARTY.
SMART GIRL.
BUT THAT TELLS ME
YOU NEED THE MONEY
FOR SOMETHING ELSE.
YEAH, I'M JUST NOT SURE
DANCING TOPLESS
FOR A BUNCH OF LONELY PERVS
IS WORTH IT.
NO OFFENCE.
ALLAN HERE IS ONE
OF MY BEST CLIENTS.
LEXTACY, IS IT?
IS THAT FRENCH?
LOOK, VLAD,
I DON'T THINK
I CAN DO THIS ANYMORE.
IF YOU STILL NEED A WAITRESS,
I CAN-
BUT YOU ARE A NATURAL,
ALEX.
I LIKE YOU.
MY CLIENTS LIKE YOU.
SO I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU
THE WEEKEND SHIFTS.
HUGE MONEY.
CASH...
EVERY NIGHT.
WHAT'S THE CATCH?
ASIDE FROM TAKING
MY CLOTHES OFF.
JUST BE SEXY.
ANNOUNCER:
LEXTACY TO THE STAGE,
PLEASE.
MEL!
WHERE'S ALEX?
I WANT TO WISH HER
A HAPPY LAST NIGHT
IN THE CESSPOOL.
YOU SHOULD GO,
PAIGE.
ANNOUNCER:
AND NEXT UP?
ONE HAND MEETS THE OTHER
FOR THE SEXY LEXTACY...
(EXOTIC MUSIC)
(AMBULANCE WAILING)
(CHEERING)
PAIGE!
WHAT ARE YOU-?
OH, I JUST THOUGHT
I'D DROP IN,
CHECK OUT
SOME NAKED CHICKS,
AND SURPRISE!
ONE OF THEM WAS YOU.
IT'S NOT WHAT
YOU THINK.
I SAW YOU STRIPPING!
DEVOID OF CLOTHING!
WHAT IS THERE
TO THINK?
WHAT ELSE AREN'T YOU
TELLING ME?
HOW BAD IS IT THAT
YOU HAVE TO DO THIS?
I'M DOING WHAT
I HAVE TO DO, OKAY?
JUST DON'T WORRY.
AND DON'T BE MAD,
PLEASE.
HOW CAN I NOT WORRY?
WHAT IS ALL THIS?
YOUNG LADY,
IF YOU WANT A JOB,
AUDITIONS ARE
ON THURSDAYS.
GOODBYE.
(SOBBING)
DARCY:
SO, YOUR VOTES
FOR WINTERFEST ICE QUEEN...
ARE YOU TAKING BRIBES?
YOU'RE OUR GIRL,
DARCY.
THANKS FOR HELPING
SET UP.
IT'D BE A WINTERY NIGHTMARE
WITHOUT YOU.
I HAD A NIGHTMARE -
MR. ARMSTRONG CHASED ME
OFF A CLIFF.
MUST'VE BEEN
THAT FUNCTIONS EXAM.
EMMA, HELP,
I'M FALLING!
STOP IT.
I'M SORRY.
I'M JUST TRYING TO SKIP OVER
THE WHOLE FUNCTIONS MEMORY.
SPEAKING OF FUNCTIONS,
WHEN WE LIVED TOGETHER,
WE WERE IN SYNC.
LAST WEEK I ASKED YOU
FOR A TAMPON,
BUT YOU WEREN'T...
YOU KNOW.
I THINK SEAN AND I
HAD AN ACCIDENT.
OH, NO!
ARE YOU SURE?
I THINK SO.
I DIDN'T KNOW IT WAS POSSIBLE
TO BE THIS SCARED.
BUY YOU A DRINK,
LEXTACY?
WAIT TEN MINUTES,
ALLAN.
SHOW'S FREE.
SORRY.
YOU HAVE A GOOD NIGHT.
WHO ARE YOU?
FIVE WORDS OR LESS.
ENTREPRENEUR, GOLFER,
DIVORCED - TWICE,
OLD, AND... LONELY.
THAT'S SEVEN.
WHAT YOU'RE COUNTING
THE "AND"?
OKAY, MY TURN.
I'M A LESBIAN.
AH...
I JUST WANTED
TO TALK.
SUPER.
THING IS UH...
MY PARTNER WANTS ME
TO QUIT WORKING HERE,
AND IT'S GETTING HARD
TO FIND REASONS NOT TO.
YOU KNOW,
IT TAKES A...
BRAVE,
SUPREMELY CONFIDENT WOMAN
TO DO WHAT YOU DO.
IF SHE CAN'T HANDLE IT,
IT'S HER LOSS.
YEAH, THING IS,
I DON'T WANT TO LOSE HER.
I BET SHE DOESN'T WANT
TO LOSE YOU EITHER.
HERE.
FOR YOUR TIME.
ELLIE!
RISE AND SHINE,
SLEEPY HEAD.
EL? HALF HOUR
'TIL CLASS.
HEY, COME ON.
ELLIE:
NO, NO, NO.
STAY DOWN.
WHAT? WHAT?
LISTEN...
I JUST WANNA SAY...
SORRY,
YOU FIRST.
I'M SORRY YOU HAD TO FIND OUT
THE TRUTH LIKE THAT.
THE LOOK ON YOUR FACE
AT THE BAR...
YOU NEED HELP.
SO I'LL FORGIVE YOU,
ERASE THAT IMAGE
FROM MY MEMORY,
AND WE'LL CELEBRATE
YOUR NEW JOB AT THE DANCE.
THERE'S ALSO AN INTERNSHIP
AT MY MOM'S COMPANY-
PAIGE,
I HAVE A JOB, OKAY?
EXPLOITING YOURSELF
IS NOT A JOB.
SO SWALLOW
YOUR STUPID PRIDE
AND ACCEPT HELP
WHEN IT'S OFFERED.
MY MOM AND I ARE THIS CLOSE
TO BEING EVICTED.
I DO THIS
BECAUSE I HAVE TO.
GET IT?
NO. I WILL NEVER,
EVER GET
WHY YOU WOULD TAKE
YOUR CLOTHES OFF FOR MONEY.
FOR ANY REASON,
EVER.
I DON'T KNOW,
FEMALE EMPOWERMENT?
THAT'S BOVINE FECAL MATTER
AND YOU KNOW IT, ALEX!
I'LL HAVE ENOUGH
IN A WEEK OR TWO.
UNTIL SOMETHING ELSE
COMES UP!
EVERY NIGHT THAT
YOU DO THIS,
IT KILLS ME.
WHEN DOES IT STOP?
MAYBE WHEN I MAKE ENOUGH
FOR TUITION.
OR WHEN I GET MOMMY'S
MAGIC CREDIT CARD, LIKE YOURS!
THIS IS MY REALITY,
PAIGE.
AND IF YOU CAN'T BE THERE
FOR ME,
WE HAVE NO FUTURE.
SORRY... ALEX.
I CAN'T.
HAVE FUN
AT THE STUPID DANCE.
PREGNANT?
EVERYTHING WE'VE
TALKED ABOUT
WAS SUPPOSED
TO PREVENT THIS!
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT,
MOM.
OKAY,
FIRST THING'S FIRST,
TAKE THE TEST.
IF IT'S POSITIVE,
WE'LL MAKE YOU
A DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENT.
EMMA:
OKAY.
BUT REMEMBER, THESE TESTS
ARE ONLY 99% ACCURATE.
HERE WE GO AGAIN.
EMMA:
(SQUEALS)
IS EVERYTHING OKAY,
HONEY?
YEAH.
IT'S MORE THAN OKAY.
I GOT MY PERIOD!
YES!
(SINGSONGY)
GO EMMA!
YOU GOT YOUR PERIOD!
AND YOU'RE NOT PREGNANT!
WE'RE GOING DANCING!
LET'S PICK A DRESS OUT,
WE'RE GOING DANCING.
HEY, GOLFER.
GLAD TO SEE YOU.
ALLAN:
SO, THINGS WITH
THE GIRLFRIEND ARE...?
BIG, HUGE,
APOCALYPTO FIGHT.
THIS SO-CALLED
CONFIDENT WOMAN
IS FEELING PRETTY
PATHETIC RIGHT NOW.
LOOK, LEXTACY -
WHATEVER YOUR NAME IS -
COME TO VEGAS
WITH ME.
VEGAS?!
OKAY, WHAT PART
OF I'M A LESBIAN
DIDN'T YOU GET?
I'M NOT ASKING YOU
TO FALL IN LOVE WITH ME.
THINK OF IT
AS ANOTHER JOB.
NAME YOUR PRICE.
ALEX:
YOU PIG!
IF YOU EVEN LOOK AT ME-
CONTROL YOURSELF
OR THERE WILL BE PROBLEMS.
ARE WE CLEAR?
I'VE GOT MY OWN PROBLEMS,
SCUMBAG.
I QUIT!
♪♪♪
SURPRISED YOU'RE HERE.
WHY WON'T YOU
RETURN MY CALLS?
'CAUSE THERE'S NOTHING
TO TALK ABOUT.
I GOT MY PERIOD.
FALSE ALARM.
REALLY?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?!
IT'S NOT SOMETHING
I JOKE ABOUT.
WOW. THAT'S AWESOME,
RIGHT?
SO, WHAT NOW?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU'RE OFF
TO BASIC TRAINING.
I'M GOING TO UNIVERSITY
NEXT YEAR.
WHEN I GET BACK...
STOP.
MAYBE WE SHOULDN'T MAKE
ANY PLANS RIGHT NOW.
CAN I AT LEAST
HAVE A DANCE?
♪♪♪
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
WE DON'T HAVE TO MOVE.
I QUIT MY JOB.
WHAT CAN WE SELL?
YOU QUIT?
THAT WAS GOOD MONEY,
ALEX!
THAT WAS...
THAT WAS MONEY
WE ALL NEED.
GUESS WHO MADE BAIL?
OH, PERFECT.
HOW, EXACTLY?
YOU KIND OF...
HELPED.
YOU USED THE MONEY
FOR HIM?
ASK ME WHERE THE CASH
CAME FROM, MOM!
ASK ME!
DO YOU KNOW WHAT
I HAD TO DO?
ALEX, WE'RE ALL GOING
TO GET OUT OF THIS TOGETHER.
WRONG!
YOU'RE PATHETIC, MOM.
FROM NOW ON,
YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN.
ALEX...
♪♪♪
TOBY:
THINK JT WOULD'VE LIKED
MY CROWN?
LIBERTY:
YEAH, TOBY ISAACS,
ICE KING?
YOU NEVER WOULD'VE
LIVED THAT DOWN.
SPINNER:
LOST YOUR DATE?
IT'S A SOLO FLIGHT
TONIGHT.
I GUESS IT'S
JUST US FRIENDS.
ME GOING STAG, I GET.
BUT YOU?
DUDE, I DON'T GET
THIS CRAZY WORLD.
♪♪♪
(SLOW SONG PLAYING)
DO YOU KNOW THIS IS
MY FIRST DEGRASSI DANCE?
DO YOU LIKE MY DRESS?
SHOULDN'T IT BE
ON THE FLOOR AT WORK?
OKAY.
I'VE SCREWED UP A LOT,
BUT IF I LET YOU GO
IT'LL BE THE BIGGEST
SCREW-UP OF MY LIFE.
SO I QUIT STRIPPING.
FOR REAL.
HON,
THIS IS HAPPY NEWS.
CHAD'S BACK.
I CAN'T GO HOME.
I HAVE NOTHING.
JUST HELP ME,
PLEASE?
SWEETIE,
YOU HAVE ME.
(DANCE MUSIC STARTS)
HOW ABOUT A LITTLE
FAUX-SNOW DANCE THERAPY?
IT'S THE ONLY DANCING
I'LL BE DOING FROM NOW ON.
♪♪♪