(SOBBING)
JT'S GRANDMA:
IT WAS A BEAUTIFUL SERVICE,
THANK YOU.
JT WAS JUST
THE SWEETEST BOY.
I CAN'T UNDERSTAND WHY ANYONE
WOULD WANT TO HURT HIM.
SEAN:
TELL YOU WHAT
I KEEP THINKING ABOUT.
GETTING IN A ROOM
WITH THE GUY WHO DID THIS
AND MAKING HIM PAY.
HE'S IN JAIL, SEAN.
I KNOW.
I'M PISSED.
I MEAN, KILLING JT FOR NO...
(CHOCKING UP)
THE GUY'S A PSYCHO.
HOW'RE YOU FEELING,
SWEETIE?
YEAH. WE'RE WORRIED
ABOUT YOU, LIB.
YOU HAVEN'T SAID
A THING.
I HAVE NOTHING TO SAY,
EMMA.
EXCUSE ME.
PLEASE LEAVE ME
ALONE, TOBY.
LOOK...
I UNDERSTAND
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO TALK.
I'LL JUST...
STAND HERE.
EVERYONE EXPECTS ME
TO BE LIKE MIA.
CRYING MY EYES OUT.
I CAN'T.
TOBY:
JT WOULDN'T WANT YOU TO.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS-
THIS IS ALL WRONG.
ALL THESE FLOWERS
AND ORGAN MUSIC,
AND PEOPLE BAWLING.
JT WOULD HATE THIS.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
JT WOULD PROBABLY PUT
WHOOPEE CUSHIONS
ON EVERY SEAT,
IF HE COULD.
(CHUCKLES)
WE NEED TO DO
LIKE A MEMORIAL
OR SOMETHING
AT SCHOOL.
YOU'LL HELP ME,
RIGHT?
YOU CAN FIND LOADS
OF VOLUNTEERS.
YEAH,
BUT I'M ASKING YOU.
'CAUSE I DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN DO IT WITHOUT YOU.
♪♪♪
SAUVE:
GRIEF IS A LONG PROCESS,
JUST GIVE IT TIME.
UH...EMMA?
ARE YOU READY TO SEE
THE PSYCHOLOGIST?
TOBY?
I HEARD YOU WERE THE LAST ONE
TO SPEAK TO JT
BEFORE HE DIED.
WHAT DID HE SAY?
IT WAS JUST TALK.
NOTHING IMPORTANT.
NO...
JUST TELL ME,
PLEASE?
HONESTLY?
WE TALKED ABOUT OATMEAL
AND HOW HE REALLY
WANTED A BOWL.
SO, HE DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING
ABOUT ME?
AT ALL?
I'M SORRY, MIA.
IT WAS JUST OATMEAL.
TOBY?
IS THAT REALLY WHAT
JT TALKED ABOUT?
WELL, NO.
I MEAN, YEAH,
BUT BY OATMEAL HE MEANT...
HE TOLD ME HE WAS
STILL IN LOVE WITH HER.
OH MY GOSH.
POOR LIBERTY.
HE WAS ON HIS WAY
TO TELL HER WHEN...
YOU KNOW.
SO LIBERTY DOESN'T KNOW?
YOU HAVEN'T TOLD HER?
I WAS JUST ABOUT TO.
SHE'S IN SHOCK.
MAYBE A FEW WEEKS
SHE CAN HANDLE IT,
BUT NOT NOW.
(STUDENT CHATTER)
ASHLEY:
I FEEL SO BAD FOR MIA.
LOSING HER BOYFRIEND
LIKE THAT?
I MEAN,
WHAT IF WERE JIMMY?
I JUST...
I JUST LOVE HIM SO MUCH,
I JUST COULDN'T DEAL
WITH LOSING HIM.
IS THAT OKAY?
ARE MY ANSWERS LAME?
NO. NO.
THEY'RE GREAT.
I JUST HAVE A LOT
ON MY MIND RIGHT NOW.
YOU KNOW JT,
THE ARTICLE...
JESSE.
SO I'M GUESSING
IT DIDN'T GO WELL
TELLING HIM ABOUT
THE CRAIG INCIDENT.
IT WENT FINE,
'CAUSE I DIDN'T.
EL.
I CAN'T DO IT, ASH.
I CAN'T TELL HIM
THAT I KISSED CRAIG.
IT'LL BE OVER.
MAYBE.
NOT MAYBE;
WILL BE.
YOU DON'T KNOW THAT,
EL.
JUST...
HAVE A LITTLE FAITH.
HE MIGHT SURPRISE YOU.
YOU'RE GONNA BE OKAY,
LIBERTY.
I'M NOT.
I CAN'T FEEL A THING.
I MEAN, ONE MINUTE JT'S
AT MY BIRTHDAY,
AND THE NEXT,
HE'S GONE.
FOREVER.
YOU KNOW WE'RE GONNA GET
THROUGH THIS TOGETHER.
I PROMISE.
TOBY, WHY ARE YOU BEING
SO NICE TO ME?
BECAUSE I KNOW HOW HARD
THIS IS FOR YOU.
I KNOW THAT YOU STILL
HAD FEELINGS OR WHATEVER
FOR JT.
FEELINGS THAT WERE NOT
RETURNED.
IT APPEARS MIA WAS THE OWNER
OF JT'S HEART.
FOR THE BEST, I SUPPOSE.
YEAH.
FOR THE BEST.
TOBY:
JT'S LOCKER -
ARE YOU READY FOR THIS?
LIBERTY:
WOW.
IT'S JUST LIKE
HE LEFT IT.
TOBY: (EXHALES)
THIS IS KIND OF FREAKY.
OH MY GOD!
THE TAPE HE MADE.
WE HAVE TO SHOW THIS TAPE
AT THE MEMORIAL -
JT PLAYING WITH ISABELLA.
EVERYONE WILL REALLY LOVE IT!
YEAH, IT JUST SOUNDS
RATHER PRIVATE;
SOMETHING FOR YOU
AND ISABELLA.
THAT'S YOUR OPINION.
TOBY, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
MR. SIMPSON'S MAKING
A TRIBUTE VIDEO.
LET'S JUST GET THIS DONE.
FINE.
WAIT.
MIA, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING?
I THOUGHT WE WERE GOING TO GO
THROUGH HIS STUFF TOGETHER.
YEAH? AND I THOUGHT THAT YOU
WANTED TO GET THE JOB DONE.
BUT YOU'RE TAKING
EVERYTHING.
SO?
I WAS HIS GIRLFRIEND.
MIA, YOU'RE NOT
BEING REASONABLE.
JT DIED FRIDAY NIGHT
AND I DIDN'T GET A CHANCE
TO SAY GOODBYE TO HIM.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
HOW DIFFICULT THIS IS.
EXCUSE ME?
I THINK I DO.
I'M JUST AS SAD
AS YOU ARE.
REALLY?
YOU COULD'VE FOOLED ME!
I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU
SHED A SINGLE TEAR.
MIA, STOP IT!
MIA:
YOU'RE A ROBOT, LIBERTY.
A WALKING,
TALKING COMPUTER!
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
TOBY:
WE'RE NOT DOING THIS, MIA.
NOT UNTIL WE'RE READY.
WHATEVER, TOBY.
WHO MADE YOU BOSS?
THIS SUCKS!
TOBY:
HEY. MIA WANTED ME
TO TELL YOU
THAT SHE'S SORRY
AND SHE DIDN'T MEAN IT.
SHE DID MEAN IT.
AND SHE'S RIGHT,
I AM A TALKING
COMPUTER.
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
SHE'S JUST UPSET.
WE ALL ARE.
TELL YOU WHAT,
WHY DON'T WE GET AWAY
FROM THIS
FOR A COUPLE OF HOURS?
CERTAINLY.
BUT HOW?
ROAD TRIP.
EXCUSE ME?
YOU HEARD ME.
COME ON!
♪♪♪
WHAT'S THIS?
FREE STUDY-PARTNER
FOR ONE HOUR.
ONE FREE NECK RUB.
FREE MIXED CD.
ONE FREE MEAL
OF MY CHOOSING.
ANYWHERE YOU WANT,
FROSH.
JUST AS LONG AS
IT'S PIZZA PIZZA.
(CHUCKLES)
JESSE STEFANOVICH,
THE LAST OF THE BIG SPENDERS.
HEY,
THAT'S JUST HOW I ROLL.
ELLIE:
WOW... (CHUCKLES)
I MEAN... WOW!
VERY ARTICULATE.
CAN I QUOTE YOU?
ANYTHING ELSE TO SAY?
THERE'S KIND OF AN EXPECTED
RESPONSE HERE.
THREE WORDS?
BEGINS WITH I?
I KISSED CRAIG.
YOU WHAT?
I'M SORRY, JESSE.
I HAD TO TELL YOU.
PLEASE DON'T BE MAD.
WHEN I SAW HIM
ALL THESE FEELINGS
CAME RUSHING BACK.
BUT IT'S TOTALLY,
COMPLETELY OVER BETWEEN US.
I GET IT.
CRAIG MEANT A LOT TO YOU.
I'M NOT MAD.
SHOULDN'T YOU BE?
I MEAN...
EVEN JUST A LITTLE?
THOSE WHO LIVE
IN GLASS HOUSES...
LOOK, I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU
IN WEEKS, ELLIE.
I DIDN'T KNOW
WHICH WAY WAS UP.
THE OTHER NIGHT
I WAS AT A BAR AND...
THERE WAS THIS GIRL...
LET'S JUST SAY
I MADE A MISTAKE.
WHAT...
WHAT KIND OF MISTAKE?
HOW BAD?
NOT THE WORST,
BUT... BAD.
LOOK,
YOU WERE HONEST WITH ME,
I FELT I OWED IT TO YOU.
I DON'T NEED
YOUR GUILT PRIZE.
ARE YOU SURE
ABOUT THIS?
YOU KNOW,
CUTTING CLASS?
LIBERTY, COME ON!
IT'LL BE LIKE
A MINI-VACATION!
JUST ME AND YOU!
(ENGINE ROARS,
CAR STALLS)
DAMN YOU,
BUBBIE'S CAR!
YOU STUPID PIECE
OF JUNK!
EVERY SINGLE TIME
I DRIVE YOU...
YOU BREAK,
GODDAMN YOU!
THIS IS FUNNY TO YOU?
ACTUALLY, IT REALLY IS.
(GIGGLES)
LOOK, I JUST THOUGHT
THAT WE COULD GET AWAY,
MAYBE YOU'D FEEL BETTER.
WELL, IT WORKED.
MAYBE NOT FOR THE REASONS
YOU INTENDED...
YEAH, YOUR BUBBIE'S GOING TO BE
REALLY MAD AT YOU FOR THIS.
(CHUCKLES)
SEE?
YOU'RE LAUGHING.
THAT'S GOOD.
AT LEAST I DIDN'T
TOTALLY FAIL.
NO, YOU DIDN'T FAIL.
YOU'RE AMAZING,
TRULY.
(NERVOUS CHUCKLE)
GOTTA THANK YOU, DUDE,
FOR LOOKING AFTER LIBERTY.
LAST NIGHT, SHE KEPT GOING ON
ABOUT YOUR LITTLE ROAD TRIP.
AH, IT WAS NO BIG THING.
IT WAS TO HER.
MORNING, TOBY.
MORNING.
IF I DIDN'T KNOW
ANY BETTER,
I'D THINK SOMETHING
WAS GOING DOWN
BETWEEN YOU
AND MY SISTER.
WHAT? NO. COME ON!
THAT'S CRAZY TALK.
GOOD. CAUSE IF NOT,
DANNY WOULD HAVE
TO CHOKE A DUDE.
DOES DANNY HAVE TO CHOKE
A DUDE, TOBY?
RELAX, MAN.
WE'RE JUST FRIENDS.
(RELIEVED EXHALE)
TELL ME HE'S BEING
A PARANOID FREAK.
FREAK, YES.
PARANOID?
NOT SO MUCH.
I KISSED LIBERTY.
OWWW!
ARE YOU CUCKOO-BANANAS?
NO! WELL, YEAH.
I DON'T KNOW.
AM I?
YES!
TOBY:
WHAT? WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHY ON EARTH
WOULD YOU DO SOMETHING
SO RIDICULOUSLY STUPID?
TOBY:
BECAUSE I LIKE HER, MANNY.
BECAUSE SHE'S CUTE
AND SHE'S SWEET AND SAD
AND SHE NEEDS ME.
AND YOU WANNA BE HER KNIGHT
IN SHINING ARMOR.
WELL, IT'S WRONG.
BOTH OF YOU ARE
A MESS RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS THE WORST
POSSIBLE TIME.
TOBY...
YOU JUST BURIED
YOUR FRIEND.
A FRIEND WHO STILL
HAD FEELINGS
FOR THE GIRL
YOU JUST KISSED.
I KNOW, MANNY.
I KNOW.
AND I COULDN'T FEEL GUILTIER,
BELIEVE ME.
BUT WHAT NOW?
WHAT CAN I DO?
TAKE THE KISS BACK.
WHAT?!
H-HOW?
GET IN A TIME MACHINE?
TELL HER
YOU DIDN'T MEAN IT.
TELL HER YOU WERE ON CRACK,
WHATEVER.
JUST TAKE IT BACK.
FINE. FINE.
I WILL.
I'LL ISSUE AN OFFICIAL
KISS RETRACTION.
HAPPY?
WHAT'S THAT?
GUESS.
ELLIE, WAIT!
HEY! HEY!
HOLD ON!
DON'T JUST THROW THIS AWAY,
OKAY?
WE BOTH MADE A MISTAKE.
REALLY?
I KISSED SOMEONE.
YOU HAD A RANDOM HOOKUP
WITH SOME BAR SKANK.
I DIDN'T HAVE SEX
WITH HER, OKAY?
I DON'T CARE.
IT WAS STILL MORE
THAN A KISS.
WAY MORE.
YOU KISSED SOME GUY
THAT YOU'VE BEEN CRUSHING ON
SINCE FOREVER.
RIGHT? YOU THINK THAT
DOESN'T HURT, HM?
I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY, TOO.
OKAY?
SO COULD WE JUST GET
PAST THIS, OKAY?
JUST MOVE ON?
NO, IT'S NOT THAT SIMPLE,
JESSE.
IT CAN'T BE
THAT SIMPLE.
SAYS WHO, HM?
LOOK...
DO YOU LOVE ME?
I...WHAT KIND OF QUESTION
IS THAT?
AN IMPORTANT ONE.
MAYBE THE ONLY ONE
THAT MATTERS RIGHT NOW.
I HAVE TO GET
TO THE MEMORIAL.
LIBERTY?
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
WHAT HAPPENED YESTERDAY
WAS NICE AND EVERYTHING,
BUT WRONG.
AND I WAS WONDERING
IF I COULD TAKE IT BACK?
THE KISS, I MEAN.
IT'S NOT A LIBRARY BOOK,
TOBY.
YOU CAN'T JUST RETURN IT.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I WAS JUST HOPING THAT,
IN THIS CASE,
WE COULD MAKE
A SPECIAL EXCEPTION?
TOBY,
DO YOU LIKE ME?
YEAH.
A LOT, ACTUALLY.
WELL, I LIKE YOU, TOO.
PROBLEM SOLVED.
(SIGHS)
SO I'VE HEARD
THERE WAS A WAR
BETWEEN LAKEHURST
AND DEGRASSI.
DO YOU THINK JT
WAS A VICTIM OF THAT?
NO.
I THINK THAT PSYCHO, DRAKE,
WAS A TICKING TIME BOMB,
AND IF IT WASN'T JT,
IT WOULD'VE BEEN
SOMEBODY ELSE.
IT'S JUST SO
IMPOSSIBLY RANDOM.
THING IS,
LIFE IS RANDOM.
SOMETIMES IT'S TRAGIC
AND TOTALLY MESSED UP.
BUT THERE IS ONE THING
THAT MAKES ALL THE DRAMA
AND THE TEARS WORTHWHILE:
IF YOU'RE LUCKY ENOUGH
TO FIND SOMEONE YOU LOVE
WHO LOVES YOU BACK,
IT'S A GIFT.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYIN'?
YOU'RE A WISE MAN,
JIMMY BROOKS.
DON'T FORGET
GOOD-LOOKING.
HATZILAKOS:
ATTENTION STUDENTS,
PLEASE MAKE YOUR WAY
TO THE GYMNASIUM.
THE JT YORKE MEMORIAL
IS ABOUT TO BEGIN.
SIMPSON:
EVERYONE, MAY I HAVE
YOUR ATTENTION?
WELCOME TO THE JT YORKE
MEMORIAL.
THERE'S A LOT OF US
THAT ARE AFFECTED BY THIS,
BUT UH...
WE'RE NOT HERE TO MOURN JT,
WE'RE HERE TO CELEBRATE HIM.
AND I'D LIKE TO START
WITH A SLIDE SHOW
THAT I PUT TOGETHER
WITH THE HELP OF PETER STONE
AND GAVIN MASON.
♪♪♪
♪ If I were to die today ♪
♪ My life would be
more then okay ♪
♪ For that time
I spent with you ♪
TOBY...
I WANT TO SHOW MY VIDEO,
BUT LIBERTY SAYS
WE DON'T HAVE TIME.
SHE'S RIGHT.
I'M SORRY, MIA.
GOD! WHY ARE YOU ALWAYS
TAKING HER SIDE?
IT'S NOT ABOUT SIDES,
OKAY?
WHY ARE YOU GETTING
SO UPSET ABOUT THIS?
BECAUSE IT'S THE PRINCIPLE.
WHY DOES LIBERTY GET A SAY
IN ANYTHING TO DO WITH JT?
HE COULDN'T STAND HER.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
MIA:
OH, REALLY?
YOU KNOW WHAT HE USED TO CALL
HER BEHIND HER BACK?
LIBERTY 3000.
HE TOLD ME HATED HER.
FUNNY, BECAUSE I SEEM
TO REMEMBER
HIM TELLING ME
THE EXACT OPPOSITE.
WHAT?
WHEN?
WHEN DID HE SAY THIS?
JUST FORGET I SAID ANYTHING,
PLEASE?
NO, NO.
I CAN'T JUST FORGET IT.
I NEED TO KNOW, TOBY.
WHEN?
RIGHT BEFORE HE DIED.
THE THING ABOUT OATMEAL?
HE MEANT LIBERTY.
I'M SORRY, MIA,
BUT HE STILL LIKED HER.
YOU SUCK, ISAACS.
YOU SUCK SO BAD.
GIVE ME THE TAPE.
YOU'RE GOING
TO PLAY IT?
LIBERTY,
WHAT DID YOU HEAR?
EVERYTHING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU.
LIBERTY!
JUST TELL ME WHY?
WHY WOULD YOU WANT
TO HURT ME LIKE THIS?
I DIDN'T WANT
TO HURT YOU.
I WANTED TO HELP YOU!
TOBY, YOU KNEW HOW
I FELT ABOUT JT,
AND YOU KNEW HOW MUCH
IT WOULD MEAN TO ME
TO KNOW HE FELT
THE SAME WAY.
LIBERTY, I WAS TRYING
TO PROTECT YOU!
AND THAT INVOLVES
KISSING ME?!
THAT'S IDIOTIC!
I KNOW!
AND I KNOW
IT'S TOTALLY WRONG,
BUT OVER THE LAST
FEW DAYS
I'VE DEVELOPED...
FEELINGS.
BUT I KNOW NOW
IT'LL NEVER HAPPEN.
YEAH, WELL...
I WISH I HAD JT.
BUT THAT'LL NEVER
HAPPEN EITHER.
PLAY THIS.
♪ All the time
that I was holdin' back ♪
♪ Just trying
to protect myself ♪
♪ I want you to know
I loved you ♪
JT:
GOOD GIRL.
SAY HELLO TO THE CAMERA!
♪ Say what you will ♪
♪ Before it's too late ♪
(SOBBING)
♪ If I were to die today ♪
♪ My life would be
more than okay ♪
ARTICLE'S GOOD,
FROSH.
REALLY?
REALLY.
BEST THING YOU'VE WRITTEN.
FISHED THAT OUT
FROM THE TRASH, HUH?
YOU KNOW ME.
ALWAYS BEEN A SUCKER
FOR THE HAWAIIAN SLICE.
HAM AND PINEAPPLE
SHOULD NOT WORK TOGETHER,
BUT SOMEHOW THEY DO.
I'M GLAD YOU CAME,
MIA.
NO PROBLEM.
I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
I THINK WE'RE READY
TO DEAL WITH THIS.
LOOK, WHAT YOU SAID
ABOUT JT-
FORGET WHAT I SAID
ABOUT JT.
NO, 'CAUSE DEEP DOWN,
I THINK I ALWAYS KNEW -
ABOUT LIBERTY.
I JUST DIDN'T WANT
TO BELIEVE IT.
LIBERTY...
HOW'RE YOU DOING?
LET'S JUST DO THIS,
SHALL WE?