ANNOUNCER:
ATTENTION PASSENGERS
ON FLIGHT 672...
CRAIG:
WAITING FOR SOMEONE?
MANNY:
NOBODY IN PARTICULAR.
OH.
JUST THIS GUY...
TALL, CURLY HAIR,
PRETTY CUTE.
CRAIG:
MM-HMM.
YEAH.
HE'S LIKE YOUR
BOYFRIEND?
I DON'T KNOW,
HAVEN'T SEEN HIM
FOR MONTHS
AND HE HARDLY
EVER CALLS.
WOW.
GUY SOUNDS LIKE
A REAL JACKASS.
YOU SURE YOU WANNA
KEEP SEEING HIM?
LIKE I SAID,
HE'S PRETTY CUTE.
I MISSED YOU,
YOU JERK.
I KNOW,
I MISSED YOU, TOO.
IT'S SO GOOD
TO SEE YOU AGAIN,
I JUST WISH I COULD
STAY LONGER.
WELL, I'M SURE
WE CAN PACK A LOT
INTO THE NEXT
FEW DAYS TOGETHER.
SURE.
TOTALLY!
LET'S GO BY
MARCO AND ELLIE'S.
THEY'VE GOT THIS WELCOME HOME
PARTY OR SOMETHING.
(APPLAUSE)
THAT WAS AWESOME.
DID YOU WRITE THAT?
THAT ONE I WROTE
ON A FERRY
TO VANCOUVER ISLAND.
IT'S A LONG STORY.
I LOVE THE ALLUSIONS
TO MELVILLE.
CRAIG:
WOW. YOU PICKED UP ON THAT?
THE NIGHT'S YOUNG.
LET'S HEAR ANOTHER.
YEAH, MAN,
FOR SURE.
(CRAIG PLAYS GUITAR)
♪ I KNOW YOU SAY
YOU'VE BEEN ♪
♪ PASSIN' BY ♪
♪ BUT I JUST SAW
YOU DROWNIN' ♪
♪ ON A SHIP TONIGHT ♪
♪♪♪
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO
RUN LINES LAST NIGHT
AND I FORGOT.
WELL,
YOU WERE PRETTY BUSY.
EVERYONE NEEDS
SOME CRAIG.
WELL, I DON'T CARE
ABOUT EVERYBODY.
I CARE ABOUT YOU.
SO, CAN I HELP?
I DON'T KNOW?
TOO LATE!
AHEM...
"I JUST DON'T WANT
YOU TO GET HURT."
"I ALREADY GOT HURT,
REMEMBER?
HE LEFT,
AND HE HASN'T COME BACK."
OKAY.
WHAT IF YOU TRY IT
ANGRIER?
WELL, THAT WAS
MY FIRST INSTINCT,
BUT I THOUGHT I COULDN'T
PULL IT OFF.
OF COURSE YOU CAN.
JUST TRY IT.
"HE LEFT,
AND HE HASN'T COME BACK!"
DON'T EVER DOUBT
YOUR INSTINCTS, MANNY.
YOU'RE GOOD.
I GOTTA GO.
I'LL COME WITH YOU.
I'M SURE YOU HAVE MORE
IMPORTANT MUSIC STUFF
YOU NEED TO DO.
WELL, I GOT A SOUND CHECK
FOR A SHOW TONIGHT,
BUT THIS IS MORE
IMPORTANT.
COME ON,
LET'S GRAB A CAB.
ACROSS TOWN?
IT'LL COST A FORTUNE.
IT'S ON ME.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
MIA:
JT!
ISABELLE IS SICK.
THEY SENT HER HOME
FROM DAYCARE.
I SPENT ALL NIGHT
WRITING THIS
"WAITING FOR GODOT"
PRESENTATION
AND NOW THE PERIOD'S
HALF OVER.
IT'S TOO BAD
THE DAYCARE'S SO FAR.
BUT I MEAN, KWAN WILL
GIVE YOU AN EXTENSION.
YEAH, SHE MIGHT.
IF SHE HADN'T HAVE ALREADY
GIVEN ME 2 ALREADY.
LISTEN UM,
LEAVE ISABELLA WITH ME.
I HAVE A SPARE
THIS MORNING.
JT, ARE YOU SURE?
I WOULDN'T USUALLY
DO THIS,
BUT IT'S NOT LIKE THERE'S
ANY DAYCARES NEAR HERE
I CAN BRING HER TO.
AND I WISH THERE
WAS ONE HERE,
BUT I MIGHT AS WELL
KEEP DREAMING.
SERIOUSLY MIA,
GO BEND IT
LIKE BECKETT.
WE'LL BE GREAT.
YOU'RE NOT LIKE
ANY BOY I KNOW.
WELL, THEN YOU CAN
MAKE IT UP TO ME.
HOT DATE TONIGHT
AT THE DOT?
(LAUGHS)
GOOD.
HEY, THERE.
YOU KNOW THE BEST PART
ABOUT BEING SICK?
POPSICLES!
BYE, HONEY.
JT:
ALL RIGHT!
YOU LIKE POPSICLES?
(DOOR OPENS)
GUYS?
YOU ARE LOOKING
AT A FUTURE ACTING LEGEND.
MANNY JUST NAILED
HER AUDITION.
THANKS TO MY ACTING GURU,
CRAIG!
HEY,
IF YOU LAND THAT PART,
THAT'S A BIG DEAL.
"WEST DRIVE" IS HUGE.
ELLIE:
IF YOU LIKE EARNEST
TEEN MELODRAMAS
FILLED WITH WOEFULLY
BAD WRITING.
MARCO:
WELL, IT AIN'T NO
"SAVED BY THE BELL", HUH?
AND SPEAKING OF WHICH,
EL?
I THINK IT'S TIME WE WENT
TO GET OUR SCREECH ON.
I WISH I COULD'VE
SEEN THAT AUDITION.
I BET YOU KILLED IT.
I JUST WISH I COULD
DO IT AGAIN
SO I CAN GET MORE
OF THIS BUZZ.
MAN,
I LIVE FOR THAT BUZZ.
SOMETIMES WHEN
I'M ON STAGE I THINK,
IT'S MY JOB JUST TO MAKE THEM
REMEMBER JUST ONE CHORD,
ONE MOMENT.
THAT'S EXACTLY
HOW I FEEL!
THAT'S WHY
YOU'RE MY GIRL!
(DOOR CHIMES JINGLE)
MIA,
YOU LOOK PRETTY.
OH, THANKS.
DO YOU WANNA
SIT DOWN?
JT HASN'T COME YET.
SO, WHERE'S ISABELLA?
UH... SHE'S AT HOME
WITH MY MOM.
SHE SURE IS CUTE.
CHARMS EVERYONE.
WELL, EXCEPT FOR WHEN
SHE'S BEING A NIGHTMARE.
ANYWAY,
UH, HOW ARE YOU?
YOU SEEM A LITTLE
BIT TENSE.
OH UM, JUST IN A QUIET MOOD,
YOU KNOW?
SURE,
IT'S NOT USUALLY
QUIET ENOUGH IN MY HEAD!
YEAH, IT'S UH,
FAR TOO QUIET IN MY LIFE.
ALTHOUGH, A CHILD
WOULD CHANGE THAT.
LIKE WHEN YOU'RE
A PARENT SOMEDAY?
OH UH, NO.
I ALREADY AM.
GAVE HIM UP FOR
ADOPTION LAST YEAR.
OH... I... WOW.
I-I DIDN'T KNOW.
YEAH, I DON'T USUALLY
TALK ABOUT IT MUCH.
AFTER JT SOLD DRUGS
TO SUPPORT US AND...
(DEEP BREATH)
ALMOST COMMITTED SUICIDE,
I-I HAD NO CHOICE,
BUT TO GIVE HIM UP.
YOU... WHA-WHAT?!
(LAUGH OF DISBELIEF)
OH, HE DIDN'T TELL YOU?
TYPICAL.
TOBY:
OUCH!
(DOOR BELL RINGS)
ARE YOU OKAY?
HOW'S BELLA?
I WA- I WAS SO WORRIED,
AND THEN YOUR CELL
WASN'T ON!
SOLUTION?
DON'T CALL.
WAIT, MIA!
AT LEAST TELL ME
WHAT'S WRONG!
YOU COULDN'T TELL ME
THE TRUTH ABOUT YOUR LIFE?
ABOUT YOUR BABY?
LIBERTY TALKED TO YOU.
AND YOU DIDN'T.
YOU STOLE DRUGS?
LOOK UH, YOU DON'T KNOW
THE WHOLE STORY.
I TRUSTED YOU
WITH MY DAUGHTER!
JT:
AND YOU STILL SHOULD.
OKAY, LIBERTY AND HER PARENTS
GAVE UP THE BABY
AND IT STILL MAKES ME CRAZY.
IS THE DRUG STUFF TRUE?
PRESCRIPTION.
BUT LIBERTY DIDN'T WANT
TO STAY AT HOME
SO WE HAD TO GET
SOME EXTRA CASH.
LIBERTY'S NOT
THE PROBLEM HERE, JT.
YOU ARE.
(UPSET EXHALE)
(SIGHS)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
MANNY:
HE MUST BE SO EXCITED.
I BET HE'S GOING TO BE
SO GREAT TONIGHT!
EMMA:
HE'S MUSIC PERSONIFIED,
YA-DEE-DAH, I KNOW.
BUT EM, WE SO COMPLETELY
GET EACH OTHER.
IT'S SO GOOD!
COUPLE OF DAYS AGO
YOU WERE PRETTY DOWN
ON THE GUY.
WHAT CHANGED?
WE JUST...
RECONNECTED.
I CAN'T EXPLAIN IT,
SEAN.
IT'S MAGIC.
OH... GREAT.
SHE'S HERE.
CRAIG'S SHADOW.
EMMA:
YOU WORRY TOO MUCH
ABOUT HER.
WELL, NOT TONIGHT!
TONIGHT, NO ONE CAN
BRING ME DOWN,
NOT EVEN SMELLY
MCSNOOTY-PANTS.
(KNOCKS)
SPECIAL DELIVERY!
I HAVE THAT MANUELLA SANTOS
YOU ORDERED...
(CRAIG INHALES DEEPLY)
HEY!
I'M SO HAPPY TO SEE YOU!
ALL RIGHT MAN,
YOU'RE UP!
AREN'T YOU GONNA
SAY ANYTHING?
BREAK A LEG.
I GUESS.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
(CRAIG PLAYS GUITAR)
♪ I FLY TOO CLOSE
TO THE SUN ♪
♪ I CHASE THE WHALE
ON THE RUN ♪
♪ BUT I'M... ♪
♪ I'M JUMPIN' FROM MOUNTAINS ♪
♪ AND I'M JUMPIN' FROM SKIES ♪
♪ TRY TO REALIZE MY SIZE. ♪
ARE YOU OKAY?
YOU WERE A BOUNCY
LOVE-BUNNY 10 MINUTES AGO.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I CAN'T SEE.
I'M GONNA MOVE UP.
♪ WHAT YOU FEEL ♪
♪ WHEN YOU SEE ♪
♪ DROWNING IN THE SEA ♪
♪ DROWNING CLOSE TO ME ♪
♪ OOOOH! ♪
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
CRAIG:
THANK YOU!
MARCO:
HEY, CRIAG.
HEY THAT WAS AWESOME,
MAN. CONGRATULATIONS!
CRAIG:
THANKS MAN!
(LAUGHS)
ELLIE:
YOU'RE A GENIUS!
(LAUGHS) WAS THAT WHY
YOU WERE ASKING
ABOUT DROWNING
ALLEGORIES LAST MONTH?
OH!
YOU-YOU CAUGHT IT!
AGAIN!
MAN, I CAN'T GET ANYTHING
PAST YOU, ELLIE.
YOU'RE JUST SO...
MMM!
YOU'RE SO KEYED IN
TO WHAT I'M DOING.
WELL, IT WAS PERFECT.
ESPECIALLY IN THAT
MELANCHOLY KEY.
LISTEN, I'M GOING
TO DO A PROFILE ON YOU
FOR THE CORE!
YEAH, HANG ON, EL.
MANNY, ARE YOU OKAY?
WE DIDN'T GET
A CHANCE TO TALK,
AND IT WAS SO GREAT
THAT YOU CAME BACKSTAGE,
AND NOT FOR A SECOND
DID I WANT YOU TO THINK
THAT I DO THAT.
IT'S FINE.
I JUST HAVE
A SPIRIT SQUAD
AT THE CRACK OF DAWN.
I COULDN'T STAND IT
IF YOU WERE UPSET.
I COULD SEE YOUR EYES
SHINING THE WHOLE TIME
I PLAYED.
YOU WERE INCREDIBLE.
GO GET CONGRATULATED.
OKAY.
HEY.
WE NEED TO TALK.
YOU SHOULD'VE THOUGHT
ABOUT THAT WEEKS AGO.
MIA, I'M SORRY.
I SHOULD'VE TOLD YOU
THE WHOLE TRUTH,
BUT I WAS JUST SCARED
YOU'D BAIL ON ME.
YOU KNOW
I'M NOT JUDGMENTAL.
I KNOW!
THAT'S ONE OF THE THINGS
THAT I LOVE ABOUT YOU.
YOU JUST... YOU NEED
TO FORGIVE ME, PLEASE?
LOOK...
I CAN'T DO THIS
RIGHT NOW.
I'M TIRED,
AND I'M STRESSED.
ISABELLA'S SICK AGAIN.
I HAD TO LEAVE HER
WITH MY AUNT.
(SIGHS)
I'VE BEEN THINKING.
I THINK THERE SHOULD BE
A DAYCARE AT DEGRASSI.
AND I SHOULD BE
LINDSAY LOHAN.
NO, I'M SERIOUS.
YOU SAID YOURSELF
IT WOULD BE A GOOD IDEA.
I REALLY THINK THAT'S
WHAT THE SCHOOL NEEDS.
AND THIS ISN'T ABOUT YOU
TRYING TO SUCK UP TO ME?
NO.
IT'S ABOUT ME DOING
THE RIGHT THING.
AND I'M GONNA DO IT!
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
(EXASPERATED SIGH)
THE POUT IS OFFICIALLY
OUT OF FASHION, SO SPEAK.
WHAT IS UP?
"WEST DRIVE" WENT
IN ANOTHER DIRECTION.
WHICH PROBABLY MEANS
THEY CAST
SOME TALL BLONDE
WITH LONG LEGS.
WEST DRIVE,
SMEST DRIVE.
THAT SHOW IS SO
ISSUE OF THE WEEK.
I HAVE MY OWN
CRAIG...
HE'S NOT THE SAME.
SEEMS LIKE THE SAME
OLD ROCK STAR TO ME,
JUST MORE SURE
OF HIMSELF.
YEAH,
THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
EGO? GROUPIES?
IS THIS AN ELLIE
THING?
NO,
IT'S DEFINITELY CRAIG.
WELL, I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT I'VE LEARNED:
IF YOU WANT THE GUY,
YOU TAKE THE FLAWS.
SEE CAMERON,
COMMA SEAN.
THIS IS A DIFFERENT
PROBLEM
THAN YOU HAD WITH SEAN.
WAY.
WELL, CRAIG IS CRAZY
ABOUT YOU
AND YOUR SHINING EYES,
REMEMBER?
MAYBE I NEED
TO REMIND HIM.
TRUE LOVE?
IT'S WORTH FIGHTING FOR.
(PLAYS GUITAR)
(HUMS A NOTE)
HEY.
I NEED TO SAY
SOME STUFF.
SAY AWAY.
LAST NIGHT WITH THE...
YOU SAID IT DIDN'T
BOTHER YOU.
I LIED.
CRAIG, IT DOES.
WHY?
WHY DO YOU DO IT?
(MUMBLES)
WHEN I GET NERVOUS
IT'S LIKE MY SYNAPSES
HAVE A PARTY.
I NEED A LITTLE
CONFIDENCE BOOST SOMETIMES.
HOW OFTEN IS SOMETIMES?
CRAIG:
PLEASE I'VE DONE IT
LIKE TWICE.
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
BELIEVE ME.
I DIDN'T GET THE PART
ON "WEST DRIVE".
OH MAN...
THEIR LOSS.
YOU'RE A STAR.
LISTEN, UH...
ELLIE'S HAVING A DINNER
PARTY TONIGHT
AND I WANT YOU
TO COME.
IF ELLIE SEES ME HERE,
SHE'LL PROBABLY
POISON THE FOOD.
MANNY,
YOU GOTTA GET OVER HER.
SHE MAKES ME FEEL DUMB
WHEN I SPEAK.
I'M NOT SMART
LIKE SHE IS.
YEAH, YOU ARE!
YOU'RE JUST NOT
BOOK SMART.
WHO CARES?
I MEAN, SERIOUSLY.
YOU'RE, YOU'RE BRILLIANT
IN EVERY OTHER WAY.
SO COMFORTED
RIGHT NOW.
MANNY,
I'M CRAZY ABOUT YOU.
THAT SHOULD BE ALL
THE COMFORT YOU NEED.
FINE.
A DONATION WILL BE MADE
IN DEGRASSI'S NAME.
AND UH...
COUNCIL WILL NOW
HEAR NEW BUSINESS.
JT:
I PROPOSE THAT DEGRASSI
SHOULD HAVE AN ON-SITE
DAYCARE.
BENEFITS WOULD BE PLENTIFUL
FOR BOTH STAFF AND STUDENTS
WITH CHILDREN-
THAT'S PREPOSTEROUS.
NEXT?
JU- WAIT A MINUTE!
I HAVEN'T EVEN
FINISHED MY PITCH.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
I ALREADY KNOW
IT IS FOOLISH
AND ILL-CONCEIVED.
WHAT ABOUT BUILDING
CODES, JT?
WHAT ABOUT ER...
CHILD HEIGHT COUNTERS,
FACILITIES,
A PLAYGROUND?
COME ON...
TOBY...
HELP ME OUT.
UM, MAYBE YOU SHOULD
LET HIM FINISH HIS PITCH.
OR NOT.
NEXT!
MOVING ON.
WAIT!
JUST HEAR ME OUT.
OUR COMMUNITY CAN
BENEFIT FROM THIS.
YOU MEAN YOUR
GIRLFRIEND CAN.
JT:
YEAH, AND?
LIBERTY:
AND SO THIS ISN'T
PRACTICAL FOR DEGRASSI,
ESPECIALLY SINCE
A DAYCARE
WOULDN'T EVEN OPEN
FOR 2 YEARS!
LOOK THIS IS PERSONAL,
NOT SERIOUS.
NEXT?
IS THIS EARTH?
YOU'RE THE ONE
MAKING IT PERSONAL.
IT'S A GOOD IDEA!
WE DON'T TAKE PITCHES
FROM IRRESPONSIBLE SLACKERS
WITH ILL-RESEARCHED
SCHEMES!
I GUESS NOT.
SINCE JUDGMENTAL ROBOTS
MAKE THE DECISIONS!
A DEGRASSI DAYCARE
COULD MAKE LIFE EASIER
FOR STUDENTS.
FOR ONE STUDENT.
LIBERTY, YOU OF ALL PEOPLE
KNOW I'M NOT ALONE.
IT COULD HELP...
EVENTUALLY.
JT:
SO JUST TO CLARIFY HERE,
THE REASON YOU WON'T SUPPORT
A DEGRASSI DAYCARE
IS PURELY SELFISH.
IS THAT RIGHT,
MS. PRESIDENT?
ELLIE:
YEAH, BUT IT WAS HIS CHOICE!
(SATISFIED EATING SOUNDS)
WELL, ROUSSEAU DID SAY,
"MAN'S CHOICES
ARE LIMITED."
YOU KNOW,
"MAN IS BORN FREE,
BUT EVERYWHERE
IS IN CHAINS."
ONLY TRUE
IF HE'S PART OF SOCIETY!
HMM.
CRAIG:
YEAH, BUT YOU CAN'T
NOT BE THOUGH!
IT'S NOT EXACTLY OPTIONAL.
(POLITE LAUGHTER)
SO TRUE.
MANNY,
YOU'VE STUDIED ROUSSEAU?
UM... NOT EXACTLY.
HE WAS UH...
HE WAS A BIG
18TH CENTURY THINKER.
ELLIE SENT ME
ONE OF HIS BOOKS
WHEN I WAS ON THE ROAD.
UM, HOW NICE.
MARCO:
WELL, ELLIE AND I HAVE BEEN
TAKING INTRO TO PYSCH?
AND AH, JUNG SAYS
THAT WE ALL HAVE LIKE,
MASSIVE COMPLEXES.
HMM. NO KIDDING!
NEUROSIS RULES!
(ALL GIVE FAKE CHEERS)
(LAUGHTER)
MANNY,
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
UM... SOMEONE TOLD ME
THAT WOODY ALLEN
WAS A PERFECT ONSCREEN
NEUROTIC.
UH HUH...
WELL, I DON'T HAVE
ANY NEUROSES, OF COURSE.
(LAUGHS)
REALLY.
BECAUSE I THOUGHT BEING
CONSTANTLY REJECTED BY GUYS
WOULD MESS YOU UP,
ELLIE.
YEAH.
(CHUCKLES)
YEAH, I FEEL BAD THAT
I TAKE TIME TO MEET GUYS
WHO ACTUALLY LIKE ME.
OH, DEAR.
ELLIE:
IN FACT,
I DON'T KNOW HOW I MADE IT
THROUGH HIGH SCHOOL
WITHOUT HAVING MY BREASTS
SHOWN ONLINE.
WHERE ARE YOU
GOING?
DID YOU HEAR
WHAT SHE SAID?
YEAH,
BUT YOU STARTED IT.
I MEAN, WHY CAN'T YOU
JUST GET OVER HER?
BECAUSE-
SHE'S SMARTER THAN ME,
SHE'S FUNNIER THAN ME,
SHE'S EVERYTHING
THAT I'M NOT.
KEEP BELIEVING IT,
MANNY.
IT'S REAL ATTRACTIVE.
THEY WON'T LET ME
INTO THEIR LITTLE CLUB.
MANNY,
YOU'RE SPONTANEOUS.
YOU'RE BRIGHT.
AND YOU'RE MY GIRL.
WHY CAN'T YOU
JUST BE YOURSELF?
MAYBE I JUST
NEED A LITTLE BOOST.
WHERE IS IT?
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
WHOA.
SHOW ME.
WHAT?
NO.
WHY?
'CAUSE THEN I CAN TALK
WITH ALL YOUR
SMART FRIENDS.
THESE ARE THE PEOPLE YOU
WANNA SPEND TIME WITH, RIGHT?
COME ON...
THIS IS YOUR CLUB.
I WANT IN.
MANNY:
ANYWAYS, IT DOESN'T REALLY
MATTER IF I GET THE PART
BECAUSE IT ALL THAT
IS HOW I PRESENT MYSELF
IN THE LONG TERM.
THAT'S WHAT
MY AGENT SAYS.
YEAH, YEAH, NO.
I MEAN, YOU HAVE TO GET
THEM TO REMEMBER YOU.
YEAH!
BECAUSE WHO WANTS TO BE YET
ANOTHER DUMB BORING ACTRESS,
RIGHT, ELLIE?
(CHUCKLES)
ANYWAYS,
I TOLD HER JUST CAST ME
AS THE FUNNY GIRL,
YOU KNOW.
I SAID THAT TO HER.
IT'S SMART, YOU HAVE
TO GET NOTICED, RIGHT?
MANNY:
OH MY!
(CRAIG LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
(GLASS SHATTERS)
CRAIG:
OH! (LAUGHS)
MANNY:
OH MY... (LAUGHS)
OH MY GOSH!
GET IT... OH.
(LAUGHTER)
MARCO: (STAMMERING)
THIS... MANNY IT'S...
YOU KNOW MANNY,
IT'S REALLY FINE. IT'S...
I AM SO SORRY.
(MANNY AND CRAIG LAUGH)
MANNY:
OH BABY!
JT:
LIBERTY!
WHAT THE HELL
WAS THAT YESTERDAY?
YOU DISMISSED
EVERYTHING I SAID
VERY PROFESSIONAL,
AND THEN YOU BAILED.
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT
WORDS LIKE THAT MEAN,
MAN-CHILD!
WHAT WAS IRRESPONSIBLE?
SUPPORTING YOU?
BEGGING YOU TO GO
TO THE DOCTORS?
BACKING YOU WHEN
YOU GAVE HIM UP
EVEN THOUGH
HE WAS MY SON TOO?
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING.
WHAT I'M SAYING
IS THAT I'M HAPPY.
AND THAT MAKES YOU BURN.
WHY?
YOU'RE RIDICULOUS.
NO, I'M RIGHT.
OKAY, I HAVE A RIGHT
TO BE HAPPY.
SO STOP TRYING TO MAKE ME
AS MISERABLE AS YOU ARE.
GOOD MORNING.
MANNY:
I'M LATE.
AND SO MUCH LESS CHATTY
THAN YOU WERE LAST NIGHT.
SHOCKING.
(EXHALES AND SNIFFS)
(BLOWS NOSE)
COFFEE?
IT WAS A LATE NIGHT.
YEAH.
THANKS.
IS... WHAT IS THIS?
EL, I DON'T KNOW
HOW THIS HAPPENED.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I NEVER THOUGHT
IT WOULD GET BAD SO FAST.
CRAIG, ARE YOU DOING COKE?
MANNY IS.
EMMA:
YOU WORRY TOO MUCH
ABOUT HER.
WELL, NOT TONIGHT!
TONIGHT, NO ONE CAN
BRING ME DOWN,
NOT EVEN SMELLY
MCSNOOTY-PANTS.
(KNOCKS)
SPECIAL DELIVERY!
I HAVE THAT MANUELLA SANTOS...
HEY!
I'M SO HAPPY TO SEE YOU!
ALL RIGHT MAN,
YOU'RE UP!
AREN'T YOU GONNA
SAY ANYTHING?
BREAK A LEG.
I GUESS.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)