SPINNER:
'KAY, AND THE RECEIPT'S
IN THE BAG.
SALE'S ON ALL WEEK.
SPREAD THE WORD.
MR. DEL ROSSI:
ONE-SIX-THREE-SEVEN.
YOU HAVE TWENTY SECONDS
TO PUNCH IT IN.
YOU GOT THAT, MARCO?
HUH?
YEAH, YEAH.
I GOT THAT, PA.
THANKS.
GETTING ROBBED ONCE
WAS ENOUGH, YOU KNOW.
AND THE NEW SIGNAGE
LOOKS GREAT, MR. D. R.
YEAH.
CASH ONLY, RIGHT?
HEY,
YOU CAN'T TRUST BANKS.
THE SERVICE FEES,
LOW INTERESTS...
TALK ABOUT
GETTING ROBBED.
HEY, ME AND UNCLE LOUIE
ARE GONNA PLAY THE PONIES;
YOU BOYS WANNA COME
WHEN YOU CLOSE UP?
SPINNER:
YEAH!
NO, NOT TONIGHT.
YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES
YOU WORRY ME, MARCO.
THIS IS LIFE.
YOU GOTTA LIVE IT.
DUDE, COME ON.
YOU'VE BEEN
JOHNNY LONGFACE ALL WEEK.
OH...
SO IT'S BEEN A WEEK
SINCE DYLAN LEFT?
'CAUSE YOU KNOW
WITH CONSTANT PHONE TAG
AND NO EMAILS,
IT'S LIKE -
POOF! -
MY BOYFRIEND
JUST DISAPPEARED
OFF THE FACE
OF THE EARTH.
LAST I HEARD,
SWEDEN WAS STILL ON EARTH.
FOR THE LAST TIME, SPINNER,
SWITZERLAND.
WHATEVER.
LOOK, DYLAN'S GOT
PRACTICE EVERY DAY,
ROAD TRIPS WITH THE TEAM,
WORKOUTS WITH THE TEAM...
LONG, HOT SHOWERS
WITH THE TEAM.
DUDE, YOU HAVE AN ACTIVELY
GAY IMAGINATION.
SPIN, DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW HARD IT IS
TO GO FROM ALWAYS HAVING
SOMEBODY THERE
TO BEING TOTALLY ALONE?
LOOK,
WHEN DYLAN WAS HERE,
NOBODY EVER SAW YOU.
YOU TWO JUST
PLAYED HOUSE 24/7.
DON'T HERMIT-OUT
WITH YOUR LAPTOP
NOW THAT HE'S GONE.
(LAUGHS)
WHATEVER, BUDDY.
I JUST WON
TWO HUNDRED BUCKS.
ARE YOU FINISHED
WITH YOUR LECTURE?
♪♪♪
MARCO:
HEY, DYLAN.
IT'S THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT,
YOUR TIME.
I'M CALLING YOU,
SO... CALL ME BACK.
LOVE YOU. BYE.
HEY, MARCO.
SPIN.
HOW'S FORTRESS
SQUATCH DESIGNS?
THE ALARM IS ARMED
AND READY.
WHAT'S WITH
THE HUSH-HUSH?
WELL, WHEN ELLIE GAVE ME
THE GREEN LIGHT
TO DATE HER EX,
I'D SAY SHE WAS JUST
A TOUCH COLOURBLIND.
ELLIE:
I HEARD THAT!
IF JESSE CALLS,
I'LL BE HIDING
IN MY ROOM.
SPINNER:
OH, FUN TIMES AT THE DEL ROSSI-
MICHALCHUK-
NASH-TANAKA-OCHI
ABODE.
SPIN,
THIS IS DRIVING ME NUTS.
DUDE, COME ON,
YOU'RE COOPERED UP INSIDE.
IT'S COLD, WET,
WINTER YUCK OUT THERE.
YOU NEED A CHANGE
OF SCENERY.
YOU KNOW WHAT, BUD?
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WHAT'S THE OPPOSITE OF COLD,
WET, WINTER YUCK?
HOT, DRY, SUMMER... YUM?
EXACTLY.
SO, I'M THINKING VAYCAY.
ME, YOU, DAYTONA BEACH.
DAYTONA?
YEAH.
I WOULD'VE EXPECTED
SWEDEN-
SWITZERLAND,
TO VISIT YOUR
SWISS-TER MISTER.
FOR WHAT?
IT'S A LONG-DISTANCE
RELATIONSHIP, SPIN.
EMPHASIS ON DISTANCE.
HE'S HAVING FUN.
I JUST...
I WANT TO HAVE MINE.
SPRING BREAK, EH?
YEAH.
HOTTIES ON TOP
OF HOTTIES...
THAT, MY FRIEND,
IS YUM.
WHAT?
DUDE, EVERY CENT I HAD
WENT INTO THE STORE.
NO. NO.
DON'T WORRY,
I HAVE A PLAN.
SPINNER:
WAIT, THIS IS YOUR PLAN?
PLAYING ONLINE POKER?
YOU'VE GOT
A BETTER ONE?
OH?!
YES, YES!
HE FOLDED; I WIN AGAIN!
YES!
ELLIE:
I'M READING CHEKHOV
OVER HERE!
SORRY ELLIE!
HEY, GUYS,
LET'S HIT A CLUB!
COME ON,
IT'S ON ME.
WAIT, W-W-WHAT ABOUT
OUR TRIP MONEY?
I'LL WIN MORE.
IT'S WHAT I DO.
OH, THANKS GUYS,
FOR HANGING OUT TONIGHT;
I NEEDED THIS.
AH, NO PROBS,
MAN.
ME AND SPIN CAN STUDY
FOR OUR TESTS NEXT WEEK.
JAY:
YO, GANGSTAS,
WHAT'S THE HAPS?
JUST CELEBRATING MARCO'S
BIG ONLINE POKER SCORE.
YOU MUST BE QUITE
THE SHARK, DEL ROSSI.
WELL, I USED TO PLAY
WITH MY BOYFRIEND.
YES, YOU'RE GAY.
SUPER.
YOU WANNA MAKE
SOME REAL COIN,
ME AND THE GUYS AT WORK
HAVE A LITTLE SOMETHING
GOING ON.
DEFINE A LITTLE
SOMETHING.
TEXAS HOLD 'EM.
$20 GETS YOU
IN THE DOOR,
$100 GETS YOU
IN THE GAME.
OUR CHARITY TURKEY DINNER
GAVE OVER 100 PEOPLE
A HOT, TASTY MEAL.
KIM:
AND WE'RE ORGANIZING
ANOTHER EVENT
FOR THE END-OF-SEMESTER DANCE.
SO SUGGESTIONS ANYONE?
NECKMAN:
UH, USED GLASSES DRIVE?
PETER:
GREAT IDEA, NECKMAN.
DARCY,
MY MOM'S ASKING FOR YOU.
IT'S ACTUALLY
KIND OF IMPORTANT.
I'D BETTER NOT KEEP
THE BOSS LADY WAITING.
PETER:
I LIED.
OH, REALLY?
SCREW MY MOM'S
NO GIRLFRIENDS POLICY.
I'VE BEEN THINKING
ABOUT YOU ALL WEEK.
SOMEONE MIGHT
SEE US.
IT'S THE KEY
TO MY HEART.
DON'T SAY
WHERE YOU GOT IT.
IT CAN BE OUR SECRET.
IT'S ADORABLE,
PETER.
THANKS.
ELLIE:
LOTS MORE CLOSET SPACE
IN MY ROOM.
PAIGE:
ELLIE, I KNOW YOU HAD YOUR EYE
ON DYLAN'S ROOM,
BUT HE GAVE IT TO ME.
WELL, WE SHOULD HAVE
HAD A VOTE.
PAIGE:
NOT A BIG FAN OF DEMOCRACY,
HON.
MARCO, TELL HER YOU DON'T MIND
IF I TAKE DYLAN'S ROOM.
ELLIE:
DON'T LET PRINCESS
ALWAYS-GETS-HER-WAY BULLY YOU,
OR MANIPULATE YOU.
SHE HAS A WAY
WITH MEN.
PAIGE:
YOU AND JESSE BROKE UP!
YEAH, JUST.
MARCO, TELL HER-
SHUT UP!
I'M NOT GONNA REFEREE
YOUR CATFIGHTS
ABOUT THE ROOM, OR JESSE,
OR ANYTHING.
JUST WORK IT OUT
YOURSELVES!
GET ME OUT OF HERE.
SIMPSON:
OKAY, MONDAY MINDS,
LAST WEEK,
WE STARTED TALKING ABOUT
ONLINE COMMUNITY MODERATION.
ANY THOUGHTS?
IS IT GOOD? BAD?
IT'S CENSORSHIP.
IT'S ABOUT KEEPING THE INTERNET
SAFE FOR EVERYBODY.
YEAH, WELL, WHO GETS
TO DECIDE WHAT'S SAFE
AND WHAT'S NOT, KIM.
YOU?
I'M NOT SURPRISED
YOU'D SAY THAT,
YOU ONLY CARE
ABOUT YOURSELF.
YEAH?
WELL, YOU ONLY CARE ABOUT
WHAT PEOPLE THINK
ABOUT YOU.
AT LEAST I HAVE
A CONSCIENCE.
PETER:
AT LEAST I CAN THINK
FOR MYSELF.
SUBMIT TO PEER PRESSURE MUCH?
GUYS...
DARCY:
SUBMIT TO UGLINESS, MUCH?
CAN YOU TELL THROUGH
ALL THAT EYE FAT?
DARCY:
EYE FAT?
THAT IS SO PATHETIC.
SERIOUSLY, ENOUGH!
THANK YOU.
HERE. FLOAT OUR POKER
DREAMS ON THIS.
AND IF WE LOSE?
WE WON'T,
I KNOW WHAT I'M DOING.
DUDE, IT'S NOT MONEY
IN THE BANK.
JAY'S FRIENDS
ARE POKER NINJAS.
YEAH, EXACTLY.
THAT'S WHAT MAKES
IT FUN -
HIGH RISK,
HIGH REWARD.
COMING FROM YOU?
THAT'S BONKERS.
SPIN,
YOU AND JIMMY
OPENED UP A STORE, RIGHT?
ELLIE HOOKED UP
WITH HER BOSS.
EVEN FLAME-OUT PAIGE
IS STARTING OVER.
AND DYLAN...
DYLAN IS OFF ON HIS EUROPEAN
HOCKEY ADVENTURE.
WHAT HAVE I DONE?
KEPT YOUR MARKS UP?
OH, WOW!
WHOOP-DEE-DOO!
I'M MASHED POTATOES,
MAN.
I'M BORING
AND I'M BORED,
AND I JUST-
I NEED A RUSH.
COME ON.
HOW'D YOU GET IN HERE?
TELL YOU A SECRET?
IT'S NEVER LOCKED.
OH, NEXT TIME
WE'RE FAKE FIGHTING,
CAN YOU TONE DOWN
THE "YOU'RE UGLY" STUFF?
YOU SAID
I HAVE EYE FAT.
IT WAS ALL I COULD
THINK OF.
YOUR EYES
ARE BEAUTIFUL.
AND YOU'RE NOT UGLY,
STUPID.
PETER STONE.
I WONDER IF YOUR MOM
WOULD LIKE TO HEAR ABOUT THIS?
SPINNER:
FOLD.
JAY:
(SIGHS)
ME, TOO.
CAN'T LOSE WHAT YOU DON'T
PUT IN, RIGHT?
YEAH, CAN'T WIN MUCH,
EITHER.
RAISE A HUNDRED.
GOING VEGAS ON ME,
BOSS?
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S DOUBLE IT.
AGGRESSIVE.
I'M IN.
I'M ALL IN.
YOU WITH ME?
(CHUCKLES)
WELL, IF YOU CAN'T SPOT
THE SUCKER,
YOU ARE THE SUCKER.
THE QUESTION IS,
WHAT'S HIS TELL?
IF YOU FIGURE IT OUT,
YOU LET ME KNOW.
IT'S ALL YOURS,
BOSS.
YES!
MONEY FOR NOTHING!
JAKE:
HEY, THIS IS HOW IT WORKS.
WE GET A CHANCE
TO WIN IT BACK,
TOMORROW.
ALL RIGHT.
IF YOU WANT TO KEEP
GIVING ME YOUR MONEY,
I'M GONNA GLADLY
KEEP TAKING IT.
SPINNER:
DAYTONA.
♪♪♪
OH, UH, HELLO.
MARCO LEFT A MESSAGE;
SOME URGENT
NEED TO RAGE?
OH, THERE'S BEEN
RAGING.
MARCO:
HEY, HEY!
FUN PATROL'S HERE!
NO CATFIGHTING TONIGHT,
LADIES. PROMISE?
YEAH, FINE.
WHAT IS UP?
I AM, BABE!
TONIGHT, I AM SO WIRED.
HE PRETTY WELL BANKRUPTED
THESE HARDCORE POKER DUDES.
I HAD THEM EATING
OUT OF MY HANDS!
LOOK AT YOU,
MR. HIGH ROLLER.
NEXT STOP,
THE MATADOR.
COME ON, VAMOS!
ELLIE:
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
THE AFTER HOURS CLUB?
I CAN'T.
I HAVE AN ESSAY.
MARCO:
ELLIE!
ELLIE, YOU CAN'T FIND
LOVE IN AN ESSAY!
YOU GOTTA LIVE!
AND I GOT A TEST.
COME ON,
PUT IT AWAY.
SPIN,
WE'RE RICH.
WE'RE CELEBRATING.
I'M HAPPY.
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM HERE?
YOU, DUDE.
YOU'RE BEING AN ASS.
SPIN, THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
I'VE HAD FUN IN AGES.
AND IT'S ALL THANKS
TO MY TRIPLE "P":
PERFECT POKER PARTNER!
COME ON, MAN,
LET'S JUST ROLL WITH THIS.
LET'S SEE HOW MUCH MONEY
WE CAN MAKE! PLEASE?!
FOLD AGAIN.
SURPRISE.
JAY:
RAISE IT FIFTY.
SHARK BOY?
MARCO:
FUNNY THING ABOUT POKER,
NOBODY REMEMBERS
HOW YOU BUILT YOUR FORTUNE;
JUST HOW YOU LOST IT.
WELL, WE'RE MAKING MEMORIES
TONIGHT, RIGHT BOSS?
CALL.
I THINK I'M GONNA GO
ANOTHER FIFTY.
MARCO?
MARCO:
I'M ALL IN.
SPINNER:
DUDE...
THAT'S EVERYTHING.
YEAH, NOT THIS TIME,
BLUFF-MEISTER.
I'LL SEE YOU.
LET'S HAVE 'EM.
JAY:
YOU ARE TOAST,
SHARK BOY.
YES!
OKAY. IT'S FINE.
IT'S FINE.
I JUST- I NEED A LOAN
TO BUY BACK IN.
I'LL WIN IT BACK, OKAY?
YEAH? HOW MUCH?
MARCO:
UM...
TONY:
WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON?
HEY, TONY,
YOU WANT IN?
TONY:
DON'T GET SMART.
YOU GUYS WANT TO KEEP
YOUR JOBS,
THIS ENDS NOW.
EVERYBODY OUT!
MARCO:
LOOK, EVERYBODY GOES BUST,
OKAY?
MY LUCK WILL TURN.
JUST TRUST ME.
TRUST YOU?
MARCO, YOU'VE JUST
LOST $1100.
KISS IT GOODBYE;
I DID.
WHAT?
WHAT ABOUT OUR TRIP, MAN?
THE HOTTIES?
DUDE, IT'S OVER.
GO HOME,
WATCH TV WITH YOUR DAD.
MAYBE HE CAN TALK
SOME SENSE INTO YOU.
YOU'VE JUST GOT
TO STOP.
HEY, POP.
HEY, SON.
CAN'T STAY AWAY FROM
YOUR MOM'S COOKING, EH?
HOW DID YOU AND UNCLE LOUIE DO
AT THE TRACK?
EH, WE HAD FUN.
DID YOU GUYS
WIN ANY MONEY?
WE HAD FUN, MARCO.
WHY?
NO, NO.
JUST MAKING CONVERSATION.
MR. DEL ROSSI:
YEAH?
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT
GOES WITH THAT?
SOME OF YOUR MOM'S
HOMEMADE CANNELLONI.
SHE PUT SOME IN THE FREEZER
BEFORE SHE WENT TO BINGO.
NAH, SIT.
KIM:
EMAILING YOUR BOYFRIEND?
(SCOFFS)
VERY FUNNY, KIM.
I'M JUST KIDDING!
ALL SET TO WORK ON
OUR DRAMA PROJECT AFTER SCHOOL?
OH, UM, I HAVE GRANDMA'S
BIRTHDAY THING.
CAN WE RESCHEDULE?
FINE.
THAT'S THE LAST TIME
I CANCEL MAJORETTE'S FOR YOU.
ANYONE SEE YOU?
NO, NOT THAT THIS IS
THE PERFECT HIDING PLACE.
HOW SNEAKY DID YOU
HAVE TO BE?
DARCE, I'M SORRY
IT HAS TO BE LIKE THIS -
SNEAKING AROUND,
LYING.
WHAT WE'RE DOING
ISN'T REALLY BAD.
IT'S KINDA FUN.
YOU'RE FUN.
SO ARE YOU.
SO MUCH FUN.
DARCY?!
KIM?
WISH YOUR GRANDMA
A HAPPY BIRTHDAY FOR ME.
OH, SUGAR.
JAKE:
I WIN THIS HAND,
I'LL BUY EVERYONE
A T-SHIRT.
JAY:
MUST SAY,
MR. DEL ROSSI,
YOU HAVE SOME
NICE DIGS HERE.
NO GIRLFRIENDS,
NO GREASEMONKEY BOSSES.
COULD BE A REGULAR GIG, HUNH?
YEAH, RIGHT.
IF ANYBODY FINDS OUT
WE'RE USING THE STORE,
I'M DEAD.
CALL.
JAY:
OH...
RAISE A HUNDRED.
THERE'S NO WAY YOU GOT
THE STRAIGHT FLUSH,
BLUFF-MEISTER.
JAY:
WELL, THE BEAUTIFUL THING IS,
THERE'S NO SUCH THING
AS A LOCKED HAND.
SO, JAKE,
YOU IN OR OUT?
I'M IN, BOSS.
(SIRENS)
FEMALE OFFICER:
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WE GOT A BREAK
AND ENTER CALL.
NO. NO, NO, NO.
MUST BE SOME MISTAKE,
I WORK HERE.
NO. JUST LET ME FINISH
THIS HAND.
FEMALE OFFICER:
GAME'S OVER, FELLAS.
MARCO:
WHAT?! ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
DON'T YOU GUYS HAVE
SOME KIND OF MURDER
YOU COULD BE SOLVING?
FEMALE OFFICER:
YOU'RE UNDER ARREST
FOR TRESPASSING.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
MAYBE IF YOU'D ANSWERED
YOUR PHONE
OR RETURNED MY MESSAGES?
KIM TATTLED TO MY MOM.
KIM SHOULD MIND
HER OWN BEESWAX.
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG
WITH US BEING TOGETHER.
WE'RE NOT GOING
TO BE TOGETHER.
MY PARENTS ARE
TALKING ABOUT
SENDING ME
TO BOARDING SCHOOL.
WHAT?!
SHE CAN'T.
SHE ALSO SAID,
IF YOU KNOW WHAT'S
GOOD FOR YOU,
YOU'LL KEEP
YOUR DISTANCE.
YOUR MOM CAN'T KEEP US APART,
PETER.
DO YOU BELIEVE THAT
LOVE CONQUERS ALL?
I DON'T THINK
IT'S GOING TO BE ENOUGH.
THERE'S ALWAYS SOMETHING
IN OUR WAY.
I'LL BE AT OUR
SECRET PLACE TOMORROW.
PROVE TO ME THAT YOU'RE
NOT THE TYPE TO GIVE UP.
(SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER
OVER RADIO)
MARCO:
SPINNER! SPINNER!
THANK GOD.
TELL HER...
TELL HER THAT I-
WHAT IS GOING ON HERE,
MARCO?
DUDE, I PRESSED
THE ALARM CODE.
IT DIDN'T EVEN GO OFF.
IT'S A SILENT ALARM,
IDIOT.
OFFICER:
IS THIS A FRIEND
OF YOURS?
HE'S A PART-TIME
EMPLOYEE.
OFFICER:
WITH PERMISSION
TO BE HERE?
NO.
OFFICER:
I'M GONNA HAVE
TO TAKE HIM IN.
COME ON.
(DOOR SQUEAKS AS IT OPENS)
IF THEY'RE SENDING ME
AWAY,
I HAVE NOTHING TO LOSE,
EXCEPT YOU.
PETER,
YOU'VE GOT ME.
ELLIE LET ME IN.
UNCLE LOUIE TALKED
TO HIS COP BUDDY AT 54.
YOU HAD TROUBLE
AT THE STORE?
YEAH.
I WAS HOPING YOU WOULDN'T
FIND OUT ABOUT THAT.
YEAH, WELL, UNCLE LOUIE
MENTIONED A POKER GAME.
THE POLICE CONFISCATED
THE MONEY,
SO I HAVE A BUNCH OF MECHANICS
FOR ENEMIES NOW.
BUT SPINNER DROPPED
THE TRESPASSING CHARGES.
IT'S FINE.
I GUESS YOU'RE LUCKY.
SO, DO YOU KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT THE $600 I'M MISSING?
UH...
I WAS IN THE HOLE, DAD.
MARCO, HOW COULD YOU?
MARCO:
I NEEDED IT.
COME ON,
YOU KNOW HOW IT IS.
YOU GAMBLE EVERY WEEKEND.
MARCO,
YOU STOLE FROM FAMILY!
ARE-ARE YOU IN TROUBLE
OR SOMETHING, MARCO?
IS THERE SOMETHING
YOU'RE NOT TELLING ME?
NO!
IT'S DYLAN, DAD.
WELL, HOW'S DYLAN
THE PROBLEM, MARCO?
I FEEL EMPTY WITHOUT HIM,
DAD.
I'M LOST.
HE'S MY BOYFRIEND.
YOU THINK I'M STUPID?
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
YOU ABUSED YOUR FRIENDS
AND YOUR FAMILY
BECAUSE PLAYING CARDS
WAS MORE IMPORTANT.
NOW, NO MATTER
WHAT DYLAN IS TO YOU,
HE'S NOT A PART OF THIS
AND YOU KNOW THAT.
I'M DONE.
I'M DONE WITH IT,
OKAY?
PROMISE.
I UNDERSTAND
IF YOU HATE ME FOR IT.
MARCO...
YOU'RE MY SON.
I'M GOING TO WATCH YOU.
JUST...
GO TO SCHOOL.
AND IF YOU HAVE
ANY HONOUR,
YOU'LL COME AND SEE ME
AT THE SHOP;
YOU CAN WORK OFF
WHAT YOU STOLE.
PEOPLE LEAVE, MARCO.
YOU HAVE TO LIVE
YOUR OWN LIFE.