SIMPSON:
I WANT YOU TO DISCUSS
THE DIFFERENT WAYS
MEDIA LAYERS ITSELF.
NOW WE'VE TALKED ABOUT
CROSS-PROMOTION...
AND CONGLOMERATES.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THE WAY
THAT PRINT AND BROADCASTING
INFORM ONE ANOTHER.
(SOUND OF KEYS TAPPING)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
DARCY,
CAN YOU SEE ME,
PLEASE?
MYROOMPAGE
IN CHAT FUNCTIONS.
I KNOW WE'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO USE THEM IN SCHOOL.
THEN WHY WERE YOU?
DARCY, ALL YOUR ACTIVITY
IS LOGGED.
I CAN SEE IT HERE
ON MY MONITOR.
YOU CAN?
BUT IT'S PRIVATE.
YOU SHOULDN'T READ IT.
THAT'S WRONG.
IT'S NOT WRONG.
IT'S SCHOOL POLICY.
AND BESIDES, WE'VE SPOKEN
ABOUT THE DANGERS
OUT THERE IN CYBERLAND.
PLEASE,
I'M NOT A LITTLE KID.
WELL, YOU'RE KIND OF
ACTING LIKE ONE.
AND QUITE FRANKLY,
YOUR MARKS ARE STARTING
TO SLIP.
THIS ISN'T LIKE YOU.
FINE. I'LL TRY HARDER,
OKAY?
CAN I GO?
♪♪♪
GRAPHING TRIG FUNCTIONS!
NOW YOU FOOTBALL PLAYERS
WILL HAVE AN ADVANTAGE
BECAUSE YOU KNOW THE SHAPES
WE'RE LOOKING FOR.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
NEXT CLASS.
BET ADAMS KNOWS THE SHAPE
HE'S LOOKING FOR.
YOURS.
WHY ARE YOU ALWAYS
SO GROSS?
JOKE? HUMOUR?
HEARD OF IT?
LOOK,
COME OVER TONIGHT.
MY MOM'S NEXT DOOR
AT HER FRIEND'S.
WE CAN DO OUR LITTLE
PHOTO SHOOT.
WITHOUT MANNY?
MM-MM.
COME ON,
WE DON'T NEED HER.
YEAH, WE DO.
WITHOUT MANNY,
IT'S JUST ME AND YOU
AND A CAMERA.
ICK.
THANKS, THAT'S SO
NICE TO HEAR.
LOOK, YOU GOT SOMETHING
PEOPLE WANNA PAY FOR.
DON'T YOU WANNA
MAKE SOME CASH?
YOU'RE NOT MY PIMP,
OKAY?
I JUST MEANT...
YOU COULD STILL USE
SOME MONEY FOR SPIRIT SQUAD.
SOME COOL UNIFORMS
FOR THE BOYS?
I'LL THINK ABOUT IT.
(CLEARS THROAT)
YOU NEED TO WATCH OUT
FOR PETER.
SURE HAS HIS CREEPY
EYE ON YOU.
DARCY:
I'M WITH SPINNER,
REMEMBER?
I DON'T THINK OF PETER
THAT WAY AT ALL.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT YOU THINK OF HIM.
IT MATTERS WHAT
HE THINKS OF YOU.
YOU NEED TO WATCH OUT
FOR HIM.
DARCY:
WHAT I NEED IS TO CHANGE OUT
OF THESE STINKY GYM CLOTHES
SO I CAN GO OUT
WITH MY BOYFRIEND,
WHOSE NAME ISN'T PETER.
NINA:
THAT'S IT FOR ME.
SEE YOU.
THREE,
TWO...
ONE.
(GIGGLES)
WHY MR. BOSSMAN,
THIS IS SO...
SO INAPPROPRIATE
FOR THE WORKPLACE.
MMM...
WHICH IS WHY WE WAIT
FOR THE DOORS TO SHUT
FOR US TO BE ALONE.
(GIGGLES)
THE SEXIEST KIND
OF ALONE THERE IS.
NOT TOO SEXY,
MR. BOSSMAN.
I NEED TO MAKE
THIS DEADLINE
OR YOU MIGHT HAVE
TO FIRE ME.
DEADLINE'S EXTENDED.
BUT WHAT IF UM...
NINA COMES BACK?
OR ERIC?
OR ONE OF THE OTHER
WRITERS?
WELL...
THEN WHY DON'T WE TAKE
THIS ACT ON THE ROAD?
SAY LIKE MY PLACE?
(GIGGLES)
REALLY AM WORRIED
ABOUT MY WORK.
MAYBE I'LL JUST UM...
I'LL BUCKLE DOWN HERE
AND WRITE THE ROCKINGEST
REVIEW EVER.
THAT'S COOL.
LATER, FROSH.
ASHLEY:
SO... WHAT'S HE LIKE?
CUTE,
FUNNY,
UM, SEXY, SMART.
INTIMIDATINGLY SO.
DON'T KNOW
WHAT HE SEES IN ME.
OH, COME ON, EL.
ASH, HE'S 22,
WITH TONS OF EXPERIENCE.
I'VE ONLY HAD
TWO BOYFRIENDS.
ONE WAS MARCO.
GAY.
AND THE OTHER
WAS SEAN,
AND WE NEVER...
YOU KNOW.
YOU THINK HE WANTS TO?
UM, HE'S A GUY.
YEAH, GOOD POINT.
SO HAVE YOU KNOW,
TALKED ABOUT...
DOING IT?
CAN WE NOT SAY "DOING IT?"
AND NO.
NO, WE HAVEN'T TALKED
ABOUT IT.
NOT YET. I MEAN...
I FIND IT A LITTLE
EMBARRASSING AND...
BY A LITTLE
I MEAN HUGELY.
WELL, IF YOU CAN'T
TALK ABOUT IT,
YOU SHOULD AT LEAST
BE PREPARED.
IN CASE, YOU KNOW,
IT JUST... HAPPENS.
I HATE WHEN
YOU'RE RIGHT.
LUCKY FOR YOU
THERE'S A HEALTH CLINIC
AT THE UNIVERSITY.
WHOA...
WHOA-WHOA-WHOA-WHOA!
EASY THERE, TIGER.
(SIGHS)
DARCE, THESE DAYS,
IT'S LIKE YOU'RE GONNA
JUMP OUT OF YOUR OWN SKIN.
DO YOU WANNA TALK
AND TELL ME
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I DON'T WANT TO TALK.
I WANT TO SHOW YOU
SOMETHING.
DARCY:
HI CLARE.
BYE CLARE.
MOM SAID NO BOYS IN OUR ROOM
WHEN SHE'S NOT HERE.
DON'T BE
A GOODIE-GOODIE.
GO DOWNSTAIRS.
COME LOOK.
YOU BRING ME UP HERE
TO HELP YOU STUDY?
DO...DO YOU WANNA FAIL?
SPINNER:
WHOA. THESE ARE...HOT.
DARCY:
TELL ME WHICH ONES YOU LIKE.
I THINK THAT ONE'S GOOD.
I LOOK TALL
AND MY LEGS LOOK TAN.
I TOOK THOSE MYSELF,
LAST NIGHT.
SPINNER:
DARCE, WHY DOES IT SAY
MYROOMPAGE IN THE CORNER?
WELL, THEY'RE LINKED
TO MY PAGE.
BUT IT'S PRIVATE.
PASSWORD PROTECTED.
WELL, WHATEVER.
THESE PHOTOS
ARE STILL ONLINE.
WHY?
WHO ELSE HAS SEEN THESE?
I THOUGHT YOU'D THINK
THEY'RE SEXY.
I WAS SEXY.
WILL YOU ANSWER
THE QUESTION?
HAVE OTHER GUYS
SEEN THESE PICTURES?
NO. YEAH.
BUT NOT MANY.
IT'S A REALLY
PRIVATE WEB PAGE.
THERE IS NO SUCH THING
AS PRIVACY ON THE WEB, DARCY.
GUYS ARE LOOKING
AT YOU.
BUT THEY'RE JUST LOOKING.
THAT'S ALL THEY'RE DOING.
THAT'S NOT ALL
THEY'RE DOING, DARCY.
SPIN.
SPIN, DON'T.
I JUST, I WANTED
TO FEEL BEAUTIFUL
AND SEXY AND LIKE...
FREE.
JUST, I THOUGHT IF I
SHOWED IT TO YOU THEN...
YOU'D UNDERSTAND.
WELL, I DON'T.
YOU HAVE TO TAKE
THIS DOWN.
I-I DON'T WANT TO.
I CAN'T EVEN DEAL WITH THIS
RIGHT NOW.
I GOTTA GO.
(EXHALES)
OH.
JESSE:
WOW. THAT'S UH...
A LOT OF BIRTH CONTROL.
IN SO MANY FORMS
AND COLOURS.
YEAH, WELL UM...
I TOLD THE WOMAN
I DON'T ACTUALLY WANT
ANY BIRTH CONTROL,
JUST...JUST THE INFORMATION
PLEASE.
AND SHE LOOKED AT ME
LIKE I HAD FOUR NOSES
AND INSISTED
I TAKE ALL THIS
WHEN I WAS LIKE,
PLEASE, I JUST WANT
THE INFORMATION.
THAT IS ALL.
YOU KNOW,
I LIKE TO READ.
I'M A RESEARCHY TYPE.
NINA:
(LAUGHING)
JESSE:
I'LL UH...
CATCH YOU LATER.
SO HOW NAKED
ARE WE GETTING HERE?
NAKED?
I DON'T DO THAT, THANKS.
JOKING.
SO YOU GOT INTO A FIGHT
WITH SPINNER?
UH, WAS IT A FIGHT?
OR THE FIGHT?
DID YOU GUYS BREAK UP?
I DON'T KNOW YET.
YET?
THAT'S NOT SOUNDING GOOD.
I COULDN'T BELIEVE IT
WHEN EMMA DUMPED ME.
HURT LIKE HELL.
STILL DOES.
WHICH IS WHY THIS HAS
BEEN SO GREAT.
SOMEONE TO HANG WITH
AND TO TALK TO.
SOMEONE COOL...
LIKE YOU.
LET'S GET ON WITH IT.
I WANT GET THESE PICTURES
ONLINE BY TONIGHT.
PETER:
NICE.
WOW!
THAT ONE'S GORGEOUS.
CAN YOU FLIP
YOUR HAIR A LITTLE?
WOW! DARCY!
THAT'S GOOD.
PETER:
CAN YOU JUST SIT UP?
TILT YOUR HEAD
JUST A LITTLE BIT.
WE SAW.
THE RING?
A SHOOTING STAR?
YOUR FUTURE LIVES
AS LONELY OLD DORKS?
DEREK:
YOUR MYROOMPAGE.
HOT STUFF.
OH, AND WE DON'T MEAN
THE BLOG.
DANNY:
WE MEAN THE PRIVATE PAGE.
SEX-AY.
WHAT?!
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
IT'S PASSWORD PROTECTED!
WHAT CAN I SAY?
YEARS OF COMPUTER CAMP
PAID OFF.
MY MAN IS LIKE THE OBI-WAN
OF PASSWORD HACKS.
DUDE IS LIKE SCARY.
YOU HACKED IN?
WHY?
WHY WERE YOU EVEN
ON MY PAGE TO BEGIN WITH?
BOTH:
CAUSE YOU'RE HOT.
JUST TELL ME YOU PERVS
DIDN'T SHOW THE PICTURES
TO ANYONE?
DANNY:
NOT YET.
OH, WE WANT $20.00.
WHOA!
I FORGOT
MY LUNCH MONEY TODAY.
AND WE ALSO WANT A SHOT
OF YOUR BAZOONGAS BY FRIDAY.
BAZOONGAS ARE OFF
THE TABLE.
YOU TWO LITTLE WEIRDOS
FORGET YOU EVER SAW
THAT PAGE
BECAUSE IT IS COMING DOWN
IN OH,
ABOUT 5.7 SECONDS.
BAZOONGAS?
DUDE, YOU'RE SO LAME.
LET'S JOIN HANDS.
LORD,
THERE ARE THOSE AMONG US
WHO HAVE BENEFITTED FROM
YOUR LESSONS OF FORGIVENESS
IN THE PAST.
AND IT IS OUR HOPE
THAT THEY WILL EXTEND
FURTHER FORGIVENESS,
UM, TO THOSE WHO REALLY
BADLY NEED IT.
AMEN.
DARCY:
SPINNER!
SPINNER, STOP!
PLEASE!
I TOOK THE PAGE DOWN.
IT'S ALL OVER.
YOU'RE RIGHT, DARCY.
IT IS ALL OVER.
SPIN,
I KNOW YOU'RE FURIOUS?
BUT YOU HAVE TO KNOW
THAT THESE PICTURES
MEAN NOTHING.
THEY MEAN EVERYTHING,
DARCY.
YOU PUT ME THROUGH THE RINGER
ON REVIRGINIZING.
AND THAT WHOLE THING
WITH PAIGE-
THAT WAS CHEATING!
YOU SLEPT WITH HER.
AND THIS IS
SO MUCH BETTER?
YOU'RE POSING FOR RANDOM GUYS
ON THE INTERNET?
IT WASN'T RANDOM.
I MEAN, I KNOW THE GUY.
HE'S A FRIEND.
SO YOU WERE CHEATING.
WHICH MAKES YOU THE BIGGEST
HYPOCRITE THAT EVER LIVED.
JUST TELL ME WHO SENT YOU
THOSE PICTURES?
WAS IT DANNY? DEREK?
WHO?
IT WAS PETER.
EXCUSE ME, SIR?
HI, CAN I HELP YOU?
I'M JUST LOOKING
FOR SOMEBODY.
OH, OKAY.
CAN YOU TELL ME WHO?
SIR, THIS IS A SCHOOL.
WE CAN'T JUST LET STRANGERS
WALK OFF THE STREET.
RIGHT.
I UNDERSTAND.
I'LL GO.
WHY?!
JUST TELL ME WHY!
WHY WOULD YOU DO
SOMETHING SO HORRIBLE?
I DIDN'T THINK
IT WAS SO HORRIBLE.
YOU TWO WERE GONNA
BREAK UP ANYWAY.
I NEVER SAID THAT!
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO.
COME ON, DARCY,
YOU AND SPINNER
WERE NEVER GONNA LAST.
EXCUSE ME?
WHY WOULD YOU WANNA BE
WITH A BORING CHRISTIAN GUY?
WHEN INSIDE OF YOU
THERE'S A SEXY CHICK
TRYING TO BUST OUT?
I WAS TRYING TO HELP YOU,
DARCY.
SPINNER JUST DOESN'T
GET YOU.
AND YOU DO?
YOU'RE NOTHING TO ME,
PETER.
NEVER HAVE BEEN.
YEAH,
NOT LIKE ADAMS.
DID YOU REALLY BUY THAT CRAP
I TOLD YOU ABOUT HIM?
I MET ADAMS IN A CHATROOM.
HE'S JUST SOME BORED,
LONELY LOSER...
WITH MONEY.
BUT I THOUGHT...
HE SAID...
LIES.
A LOT OF LIES.
HE PLAYED YOU, DARCY.
JUST LIKE YOU
PLAYED ME.
YOU'RE QUIET TODAY.
IS IT ABOUT
THE PICTURES?
CLARE, YOU DIDN'T
LOOK AT THEM?
THEY WERE ON
OUR COMPUTER.
IF YOU DIDN'T WANT ME
TO SEE THEM...
JUST PROMISE,
DON'T EVER DO SOMETHING
LIKE THAT, OKAY?
WHAT DO YOU THINK I AM,
FIVE?
ADAMS:
DARCY?
HI.
WHO'S HE?
ADAMS:
IT'S ME. ADAMS.
GO INSIDE.
CLARE:
I DON'T LIKE THIS.
GO INSIDE.
HI.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
HOW'D YOU FIND
WHERE I LIVE?
ADAMS:
JUST A LITTLE DETECTIVE WORK.
YOUR CHEERLEADING PHOTO
HAD THE DEGRASSI LOGO
SO I...
I KINDA FOLLOWED YOU HOME.
I JUST WANTED US
TO MEET.
I THOUGHT WE COULD
GET TO KNOW EACH OTHER,
JUST ONE-ON-ONE?
(REALIZING SIGH)
THAT'S A NICE BRACELET.
THANKS, MY BOYFRIEND MADE IT.
(MOUTHS 911)
ADAMS:
OH, SPINNER?
DARCY:
I TOOK DOWN MY PAGE.
OH, I WAS SO SAD.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHY DID YOU DO THAT?
HELLO, 911?
(LAUGHING)
NEXT PITCH...
ELLIE.
UH... OKAY.
UM...
AS MOST OF YOU KNOW,
AND LOVE TO BUG ME ABOUT,
I'M A FIRST YEAR.
AND I'M A LITTLE FASCINATED
BY THAT OFFICE DOWN THE HALL.
THE SEXUAL HEALTH
OFFICE?
(LAUGHS)
UM, SO...
FOLLOWING IN THE GREAT,
THOUGH FICTIONAL,
STEPS OF CARRIE BRADSHAW,
I'D LIKE TO PITCH A SERIES
ON SEXUAL HEALTH
ON CAMPUS.
JESSE:
PASS.
NEXT?
HANG ON,
I'VE DONE RESEARCH.
JESSE:
IT'S OKAY.
WE GET IT.
NEXT?
ELLIE:
I... (NERVOUS LAUGH)
I-I JUST UM...
THINK IT'S IMPORTANT THAT
WE'RE ALL INFORMED ABOUT SEX.
JESSE:
OUR READERS ARE INFORMED,
FROSH.
BUT...
JESSE:
IT'S DEAD, OKAY?
STOP PITCHING IT.
FREDDIE,
WHAT DO YOU GOT?
DARCY:
I... I SHOULD REALLY GO.
WE HAVEN'T EVEN TALKED.
HOW IS SCHOOL?
DO YOU LIKE IT?
YOU MUST HAVE
SO MANY FRIENDS.
I GUESS SO.
I KNOW YOU WOULD.
PRETTY GIRL LIKE YOU,
EVERYONE WANTS TO BE
AROUND YOU.
WAIT! DARCY, COME BACK!
OFFICER:
SHOW ME YOUR HANDS, SIR.
ADAMS:
WE WERE JUST TALKING!
SHOW ME YOUR HANDS!
DARCY,
I THOUGHT YOU LIKED ME?
WE'RE INVESTIGATING A REPORT
OF A TRESPASSER IN THE AREA.
I'M GONNA NEED
TO SEE SOME ID.
DARCY!
OFFICER:
SIR, YOU NEED TO STAY HERE.
NO! NO, I DON'T!
SHE'S MY FRIEND.
TELL THEM THAT
YOU KNOW ME!
DARCY, TELL THEM
I'M YOUR FRIEND!
OFFICER:
YOU'RE COMING WITH ME!
ADAMS:
DARCY!
I WANT TO RESIGN -
FROM THE PAPER
AND US.
SO... GOODBYE.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
CAN WE DISCUSS THIS?
JESSE, I JUST MADE
A COMPLETE ASS OF MYSELF
AND YOU JUST SAT THERE
WITH NINA AND WATCHED.
NO, I DID NOT.
I WAS TRYING
TO HELP YOU.
WHY DO YOU THINK
I WAS TRYING TO STOP YOU?
BUT YOU JUST KEPT GOING
AND GOING AND GOING.
I DO HAVE
THAT TENDENCY.
WHAT WERE YOU DOING
WITH ALL THAT STUFF ANYWAY?
I MEAN...
HOW MUCH BIRTH CONTROL
DO YOU NEED?
NO, JESSE, DON'T.
IT'S NOT FUNNY
AT ALL.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE CUTE
WHEN YOU'RE MORTIFIED.
WELL, REMIND ME TO MORTIFY
MYSELF MORE OFTEN.
REMIND ME WE NEED
TO HAVE A TALK,
ABOUT US.
WHERE WE'RE GOING.
THAT IS, IF THERE...
STILL IS AN US?
RESIGNATION CANCELLED.
GOOD.
'CAUSE I WASN'T GONNA
ACCEPT IT ANYWAY.
YOU'RE STUCK WITH ME,
FROSH.
FOR A LONG TIME,
I HOPE.
SO, UM, THEY'RE GONNA
TAKE OUR COMPUTER AWAY
FOR EVIDENCE.
SO IF YOU HAVE ANYTHING
ON THERE...
IT'S OKAY.
DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING?
EMAILS FROM SPINNER
OR SOMETHING?
I DON'T WANNA REMEMBER.
IT'S OKAY, DARCE.
NO.
NO, EVERYONE'S GONNA KNOW,
AT SCHOOL,
ABOUT HOW I'M A HYPOCRITE.
NOBODY'S GONNA FIND OUT.
I'LL PUNCH THEM.
YOU'RE GOOD, CLARE.
YOU'RE REALLY GOOD.
YOU ARE TOO, DARCE.
YOU JUST GOT A LITTLE
TURNED AROUND IS ALL.
I THINK IT'S A TEENSY BIT
MORE COMPLICATED THEN THAT.
I'M PRETTY MIXED-UP.
A PERSON CAN BE GOOD
AND MIXED-UP
ALL AT THE SAME TIME.
YEAH?
OKAY.
I HOPE YOU'RE RIGHT.