DARCY:
YOU CALL THAT A KISS?
SPINNER:
I CAN FEEL YOUR MOM'S EYES
WATCHING US
FROM INSIDE THE HOUSE.
YEAH AND CLARE'S PROBABLY
HIDING IN THE BUSHES
VIDEOTAPING FOR EVIDENCE.
NO. NO, NO, NO.
THAT WOULD BE WRONG.
AND YOU AND YOUR SIS
NEVER DO ANYTHING WRONG.
YOU'RE LIKE
REGULAR SAINTS.
CLARE IS A SAINT.
I'M NOT.
I CAN BE BAD
SOMETIMES TOO.
DON'T JUDGE A BOOK
BY ITS COVER.
CLARE:
WHY ARE YOU SO ADDICTED
TO WRITING A DUMB BLOG
NO ONE READS?
I'M NOT ADDICTED,
AND PEOPLE DO READ IT.
THERE'S A WHOLE ONLINE
COMMUNITY OF PEOPLE
WHO ARE ONE HUNDRED
ZILLION TIMES
LESS ANNOYING
THAN YOU ARE.
IT'S GOOD YOU'VE GOT
FRIENDS SOMEWHERE,
EVEN IF THEY
ARE INVISIBLE.
UGH.
♪♪♪
CHANTAY:
THE NEW UNIFORM WOULD BE
A DARKER BLUE
THAN THE PANTHER BLUE
WE HAVE NOW.
THAT'S OKAY.
I HATE PANTHER BLUE.
US TOO.
AND THEY COME IN
ULTRA-FASHIONABLE,
MODERN, ATHLETIC,
CROP-TOP STYLE!
CROP-TOPS?
COME ON, WE'RE NOT
FLASHING OUR ABS
AT THE ENTIRE SCHOOL.
OKAY, FORGET ABOUT
THE CROP-TOPS.
HOW ABOUT AT LEAST
GETTING US
SOME NEW SHORT-SHORTS?
THOSE SHORTS-SHORTS
ARE A LITTLE TOO SHORT.
WAY TOO MUCH LEG.
THE LAKEHURST SQUAD
WEARS THEM.
AND DARCY,
THEY'D BE SO MUCH EASIER
TO MOVE AROUND IN.
WHICH WE'LL NEED
FOR THE ATHLETIC ROUTINES
MANNY'S WORKED OUT
TO GET US TO THE REGIONALS?
THEN CHANGE
THE ROUTINES.
LOOK, WE CAN'T EVEN AFFORD
TO GET NEW UNIFORMS,
SO CAN WE JUST DROP IT?
BESIDES,
I HAVE MY OWN ANSWER
TO GETTING US
INTO REGIONALS.
BOYS.
NOT THAT I HAVE ANYTHING AGAINST
THAT ANSWER GENERALLY,
BUT PARDON?
MORE LIFTS,
MORE THROWS.
I THOUGHT OF IT YESTERDAY
WHEN I WAS WATCHING
SOME PRO-STYLE ON TV.
SO YOU JUST DECIDED
WITHOUT TALKING
TO THE CHOREOGRAPHER?
THAT'S WHY I LOVE
BEING CAPTAIN.
MANNY:
IS IT POSSIBLE THAT
I'M ACTUALLY MISSING
PAIGE MICHALCHUK?
GOOD MORNING,
EMMA.
NOTHING ABOUT YOU
IS GOOD,
AND DON'T TALK
TO ME.
OFF TO CLASS,
PETER MICHAEL.
PLEASE FOCUS ON YOUR STUDIES
INSTEAD OF GIRLS.
EMMA'S MORE
THAN JUST A GIRL.
I SAID,
OFF TO CLASS.
HI, THIS IS TOBY ISAAC
WITH YOUR MORNING
ANNOUNCEMENTS.
UH, WE WANT TO REMIND
ALL STUDENTS
ABOUT THE UPCOMING...
HEY LIBERTY,
GUESS HOW MANY PIECES
OF GUM
I HAVE IN MY MOUTH?
OKAY. I'M TRYING TO WATCH
THE ANNOUNCEMENTS?
TOBY:
LOCAL TV STATION CKJH
IS LOOKING FOR A "PJ" TO HOST
THEIR KIDS PROGRAMMING.
AUDITIONS TO BE HELD TODAY
AT NOON.
SUCCESSFUL CANDIDATES ARE-
ME!
SUCCESSFUL CANDIDATES
ARE ME!
I'LL GET MY OLD
JOB BACK!
YEE-HAW!
THE CHILDREN NEED ME,
LIBERTY.
MATURE, JT.
REALLY MATURE.
TOBY:
AND NOW, WE HAVE
AN ANNOUNCEMENT
FROM DARCY EDWARDS,
CAPTAIN OF YOUR SPIRIT SQUAD.
DID YOU KNOW GEORGE W. BUSH
USED TO BE A CHEERLEADER?
SO WHY NOT YOU TOO?
YOUR SQUAD NEEDS NEW SHOULDERS
TO LEAN ON.
BROAD SHOULDERS.
THAT'S RIGHT GUYS,
IT'S YOUR TURN
TO SHOW SCHOOL SPIRIT!
GOOD ANNOUNCEMENT.
THANKS.
WHAT DO YOU HAVE
AGAINST SHORT-SHORTS?
DON'T YOU THINK SPIRIT SQUAD
HAS AN IMAGE TO MAINTAIN?
A "WE'RE NOT DIRTY"
KIND OF IMAGE?
SHORTS AREN'T DIRTY.
CORRECT ME IF I'M WRONG,
BUT AREN'T YOU WEARING SHORTS
IN YOUR MY-ROOM-PAGE?
THEY SHOW LIKE
THIS MUCH MORE THIGH.
SO?
YOU HAVE GOOD THIGHS.
ANYONE WHO GOES TO YOUR
MY-ROOM-PAGE WOULD KNOW.
CAN YOU STAY OUT
OF THIS?
I'M JUST SAYING
YOUR BLOG IS GOOD.
THOSE QUIZZES YOU DO
ARE FUN.
SIMPSON: (UNENTHUSIASTIC)
IT'S HARD-DRIVE MAINTENANCE DAY.
CAN YOU STAND THE EXCITEMENT?
I CAN'T.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
JT:
AND THEN?
THEN SHE GAVE ME
THAT LIBERTY LOOK.
THAT LOOK THAT SAYS
"YOU'RE SO IMMATURE
AND PATHETIC
THAT I CAN'T EVEN FIND
THE WORDS TO DESCRIBE IT."
YOU MEAN,
THAT LOOK THAT SAYS,
"MY PASSION FOR YOU
BURNS BRIGHT, JT.
IT IS AN ETERNAL FLAME
OF MUCH LOVENESS."
TOBES, STOP IT.
YOU'RE MAKING ME ILL.
LOOK, IT'S NOT
JUST YOU, JT.
IT'S... IT'S HER.
YOU NEVER STOP
TALKING ABOUT HER.
YOU'RE LIKE, OBSESSED.
JT:
TOBES, OBSESSING OVER LIBERTY
WOULD BE LIKE...
OBSESSING OVER LINT
OR OATMEAL.
MIA:
OHMIGOD, THAT'S IT!
YOU'RE PJ JT!
MY KID LOVES YOU.
YOU HAVE A KID?
HER NAME'S ISABELLA.
SHE'S YOUR BIGGEST FAN.
AND SHE WON'T EVEN LET ME
TURN OFF THE TV
WHEN THEY'RE RERUNNING YOU.
YEAH?
YEAH.
REMIND ME TO GET YOUR AUTOGRAPH
FOR HER.
I THINK YOU'RE HER
FIRST CRUSH.
THAT IS NOT OATMEAL.
THAT IS A HOMEMADE
MEATBALL SUB
WITH EXTRA CHEESE
AND SPICY SAUCE.
LOOK, TELL MR. PERINO
THAT UH...
THAT I CAUGHT BIRD FLU.
I'VE GOT AN AUDITION
TO GO TO!
(STAINING GRUNTS)
SO THAT'S YOUR
GREAT IDEA.
TURNING SPIRT SQUAD
INTO DORKWAD CENTRAL?
SOMEHOW IT LOOKED A BIT
DIFFERENT IN MY HEAD.
SORRY I'M LATE!
THIS WHOLE BOY IDEA
IS OFFICIALLY DEAD.
THEY'RE ALL GOING HOME.
HOME! GO!
WAIT-WAIT-WAIT-WAIT.
PETER MIGHT ACTUALLY
BE OKAY AT THIS.
"OKAY" IS NOT A PETER WORD.
TRY UM...
"PSYCHO, SERIAL KILLER-Y."
UH..."SATANIC"
IN YOUR LANGUAGE.
I'M RIGHT HERE,
MANNY.
I DO HAVE EARS,
YOU KNOW?
SO IT'S JUST A SOUL
YOU'RE MISSING?
UM, WHERE'S THE PART
WHERE I GET TO GRAB
MANNY'S INNER THIGHS?
AS IF I'M LETTING
YOU PICK ME UP.
I'VE SEEN MORE
GRACEFUL CAMELS.
MAYBE.
BUT I GOT TWICE THE HUMP.
(CHUCKLES)
YEAH-HOO!
DARCY:
OKAY, GUYS,
LET'S GET THESE
TRY-OUT STARTED.
UM, I WANT TO START
WITH SOME LIFTS
BECAUSE WIMPS LIFT WEIGHTS
AND CHEERLEADERS LIFT PEOPLE.
AMEN, SISTER.
TESTIFY.
DARCY:
YEAH. AMEN.
UM, PETER,
YOU CAN HELP ME DEMONSTRATE.
UH, DO YOU MIND SPOTTING?
GIRL:
SURE.
DARCY:
STAND BEHIND ME HERE.
I'LL STAND HERE.
GRAB MY WAIST.
I'LL HOLD YOUR WRISTS.
I'M GONNA COUNT.
READY?
1, 2, DOWN, UP.
PERFECT!
RIGHT, MANNY?
I FEEL REGIONALS.
DARCY:
(CLEARS THROAT)
DARCY! HEY!
I HAVE A BOYFRIEND
YOU KNOW.
OH, IT'S NOT
LIKE THAT.
I JUST WANT TO THANK YOU
FOR IN THERE.
WHATEVER.
I JUST BELIEVE THAT SOMETIMES
PEOPLE DESERVE FORGIVENESS.
YOU REALLY WANT
TO BE A CHEERLEADER?
HATZILAKOS:
PETER MICHAEL,
TWO MINUTES, OKAY?
OKAY, MOM!
I'M STUCK IN THIS HOUSE
ARREST THING.
BUT IF I JOIN A CLUB-
YOU GET AN EXCUSE
TO STAY OUT LONGER.
I GET IT.
I'VE BEEN WARNED
ABOUT YOU.
I'M BORED, OKAY?
I'M GETTING A'S
IN EVERYTHING.
I'VE READ THE BLOG
OF EVERY BORING KID
IN THIS ENTIRE
BORING SCHOOL.
INCLUDING MY BORING BLOG?
NO, I ACTUALLY
LIKED YOURS.
YOU'RE NOT WHO
I THOUGHT YOU WERE.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
YOU'RE COOLER
THAN I THOUGHT.
AND SMART AND FUNNY.
LOOK PRETTY CUTE
IN SHORTS.
GOOD NIGHT,
MS. HATZILAKOS!
I THINK PETER'S READY
TO GO HOME, NOW.
HATZILAKOS:
THANKS, DARCY.
GOOD NIGHT!
I'M GONNA LINK YOU UP
TO MY BLOG, ALL RIGHT?
I KNOW A LOT
OF PEOPLE.
COME ON.
TIME TO GO HOME.
JT:
AND THAT'S IT FOR TODAY.
SO REMEMBER,
IMAGINE ALL WEEK LONG.
AND DON'T EAT THE GLUE!
BYE-BYE!
(WEAK APPLAUSE)
SO AM I... AM I FIRED
FOR CUTTING MY FINGER
WITH THE SAFETY SCISSORS
OR WHAT?
YOU COVERED WELL.
NOW, CAN YOU TELL US WHY
YOU WANT YOUR OLD JOB BACK?
WELL,
IT'S FOR THE CHICKS.
(GIGGLES)
VERY FUNNY, JT.
BUT SERIOUSLY?
JT:
WELL, RESPECT, I GUESS.
YEAH.
I KNOW IT SOUNDS WHACKO,
BUT MAKING ARTS AND CRAFTS
AND WEARING DRESS-UP COSTUMES,
IT HELPS ME GAIN IT.
FEEL RESPECTED...LIKE.
WELL THEN,
PREPARE FOR RESPECT.
SEE YOU TOMORROW,
BABY.
THAT'S IT?
OKAY,
WHAT'D I FORGET?
UM, ENJOY YOUR DINNER.
REMEMBER TO PRAY.
WHAT?
YOU DON'T WANT
TO KISS ME MORE?
I MAKE OUT WITH YOU
TOO MUCH,
I'M A HORN DOG;
I DON'T MAKE OUT
WITH YOU,
AND I'M IN TROUBLE?
HOW CAN I WIN?
IT'S NOT ABOUT WINNING.
IT'S ABOUT RESPECTING
EACH OTHER'S NEEDS.
I DO RESPECT YOU,
DARCE.
THAT'S WHAT ALL
THIS IS ABOUT -
RESPECT,
ABSTINENCE,
CHASTITY,
BEING GOOD.
DON'T YOU GET TIRED
OF BEING GOOD?
WHAT'RE YOU SAYING,
DARCY?
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME
TO DO?
JUST TELL ME.
I CAN'T...
'CAUSE I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST...
I NEED MORE...SOMETHING.
FORGET IT,
OKAY?
CAN WE JUST FORGET IT?
FINE.
IT'S FORGOTTEN.
IS YOUR BRA
STILL DONE UP?
IT'S EXACTLY
WHERE IT SHOULD BE.
CLARE:
YOUR EMAIL SOUND
KEEPS GOING.
MOM:
CLARE, COME AND SET THE TABLE!
MOM SAID SHE NEEDS HELP
WITH DINNER. GO.
BUT...
GO.
GO!
(GIGGLES)
WHAT'S THE STORY,
MORNING GLORY?
THE STORY IS
YOU'RE CUTE.
HEY, I HAVE SOMETHING
FOR YOU.
THANK YOU.
I MADE IT OUT OF
THIS LEATHER JACKET
THAT I USED TO WEAR
WHEN I WAS A KID.
SO...
I'M SO LUCKY I HAVE YOU.
(GIGGLES)
AW...
LOOKS LIKE I MADE YOU
PRETTY POPULAR.
IN THE ONLINE WORLD
ANYWAY.
I LINKED YOUR BLOG UP
TO MY WEBSITE.
SENT A LOT OF MY FRIENDS
YOUR WAY.
WHO'S THAT ADAMS GUY?
IS HE A FRIEND OF YOURS?
YEAH, WE'RE TIGHT.
REALLY.
SO... WHAT'S HE LIKE?
YOU MEAN WHAT DOES
HE LOOK LIKE?
I KNOW WHERE
THIS IS GOING.
NO YOU DON'T.
AND DON'T BE A CREEP.
ADAMS IS COOL.
HE'S AN OLD BUD
FROM PRIVATE SCHOOL.
HIS DAD'S SUPER RICH.
HE PLAYS SOCCER.
GIRLS SAY HE'S CUTE.
HE'S DEFINITELY A BIG FAN
OF YOURS RIGHT NOW.
ALL RIGHT, FOLKS!
POP QUIZ ON MOTHERBOARDS.
'CAUSE LET'S FACE IT,
WHO DOESN'T LOVE
A GOOD MOTHERBOARD.
HANDS ON HIPS,
RIGHT?
1, 2...
OKAY, UM...
TRY THE LIFT AGAIN,
SPAGHETTI ARMS.
AND DON'T TICKLE HIM
THIS TIME.
I WANT TO LIFT
A LADY.
MANNY:
WELL, NONE OF THEM WANT
TO COME NEAR YOU,
WHICH I DON'T THINK
IS IN YOUR FAVOUR
FOR THE WHOLE
MAKE-THE-TEAM THING.
HAVE YOU SEEN THIS?
HOLY KAMOLEY.
HE DID RESEARCH.
HE PRACTICED.
YEAH, THIS IS BETTER
THAN HALF THE GIRLS
ON THE TEAM.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
GUY MIGHT BE THE TWISTED-UP
SPAWN OF SATAN,
BUT HE ALSO MIGHT BE OUR TICKET
TO THE REGIONALS.
DARCY:
YEAH.
HE'S FULL OF SURPRISES.
WELL...
SEE, LOOK AT THAT!
LOOK AT THAT!
PJ JT.
OH HI.
HAS ANYONE EVER TOLD YOU
THAT'S A LOT OF LETTERS
FOR ONE LITTLE GUY?
LITTLE?
WHAT DID YOU HEAR?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
FORGET IT.
I-I GOT MY JOB BACK!
CONGRATS!
JT:
OH! OOH. THANKS!
UH...
UM...YEAH...
YOU SHOULD COME
TO THE SHOW!
OH, I WOULDN'T WANT
TO GET IN THE WAY.
OH, NO.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
JUST COME TO A TAPING
WITH YOUR DAUGHTER.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
SHE'D LOVE THAT.
YEAH.
COME TONIGHT.
IT'S THE PREMIERE.
IT'S GONNA BE LIKE
TEN TIMES THE EXCITEMENT.
THE CATERERS HEAT THE COFFEE
TO LUKEWARM INSTEAD OF TEPID.
IT'S REALLY...
ISABELLA WOULD
DEFINITELY LOVE THAT!
WE'LL BE THERE
FOR SURE.
COOL. OKAY, SO UM...
(GIGGLING)
THAT WAS GREAT TODAY,
PETER.
PETER:
YEAH. I GUESS I WAS BORN
FOR SPIRIT SQUAD.
RIGHT MANNY?
JUST BECAUSE YOU HELP
WITH THE EQUIPMENT
AND YOU CHEER CIRCLES
AROUND THOSE OTHER LOSERS
DOESN'T MEAN I SUDDENLY THINK
YOU'RE MOTHER THERESA.
I'M NOT MOTHER THERESA.
DARCY IS.
I'M NOBODY'S MAMA,
THANK YOU.
ADAMS SAYS
YOU'RE A HOT MAMA.
MANNY:
MMM, WHO'S ADAMS?
THIS GUY WHO GOT HER TO POST
SOME SEXY SHOTS ONLINE.
YEAH, RIGHT.
DARCY'S IDEA OF A SEXY POSE
IS LIKE...
(ANGELIC SOUND)
PETER:
HEY, SOME GUYS LIKE A HOT NUN.
DARCY:
THAT IS NOT FUNNY.
I WEAR A ROSARY THONG
UNDER MY HABIT.
EWW!
CAMERAS?
I DON'T THINK SO.
THERE IS A BIG POLICY
AGAINST YOU AND PHOTOS.
PETER:
COME ON, JUST FOR POSTERITY.
MANNY:
HEY, I WANT REVENGE.
GIVE IT TO ME!
OH, YES! YES!
♪♪♪
THAT'S SO GOOD.
DARCY:
DEGRASSI PANTHERS.
HERE.
PETER:
I'LL TAKE IT.
MANNY:
OKAY. OKAY.
PETER:
ALL RIGHT, GIRLS,
TAKE YOUR JACKETS OFF.
YO GUYS,
COWGIRL STYLE!
YOU WANT TO SEE A COWGIRL,
DO YOU?
(LAUGHING)
HEY YOU!
OKAY. YEAH.
ABOUT THAT.
YOU ARE NEVER GOING
TO GET YOUR HANDS ON THESE.
NEVER. NO.
MANNY:
HEY! HEY! HEY! HEY!
NOT A CHANCE.
OKAY.
YOU ROCK.
PETER:
PRINT SOME OFF FOR ME.
(GIGGLES)
OH SUGAR.
YOU KNOW MANNY LEFT
LIKE AN HOUR AGO?
OKAY. WELL, IF YOU END UP
IN THAT KIND OF MOOD...
THERE'S MORE WHERE
THAT CAME FROM.
BUT I CAN'T STAY OUT LONG.
GOT A LOT OF EMAILS
WAITING FOR ME.
JT:
AND THAT'S ALL FOR TODAY.
SO REMEMBER,
BE BIGGER THAN YOU ARE
AND DON'T EAT ORANGE PIE!
(APPLAUSE)
BRIANNA!
I'M GONNA GET YOU!
(GROANS)
OH, THANK YOU.
GOOD JOB!
HIGH FIVE ON THAT ONE!
ALL RIGHT!
HEY!
SO...HOW DID IT LOOK?
SHE THINKS YOU'RE
A COMIC GENIUS.
WELL, SOMEBODY HAS TO.
SO DO YOU WANNA GET
SOMETHING TO EAT?
WHO? ME?
YEAH YOU.
MAYBE UM... CHEESIES?
TACO CHIPS?
ORANGE POP?
(NERVOUS LAUGH)
UH...
WELL, I...
OH, IT'S OKAY.
UH... NEVER MIND.
IT'S PAST BELLA'S
BEDTIME ANYWAY.
BYE.
NO, NO. THAT'S NOT-
WAIT!
MANNY:
I LAUGHED SO HARD,
EM CAME DOWN TO SEE
WHAT I WAS DOING.
DID SHE SEE?
NO. BUT THANKS
FOR MAKING THE PAGE
PASSWORD PROTECTED.
THAT PAGE BETTER
STAY PRIVATE.
UM YEAH,
ABOUT THAT.
WHO'D YOU SHARE
THE PASSWORD WITH?
TELL ME IT'S NOT
SOMEONE I KNOW?
NO, NO, NO.
IT'S AN ONLINE FRIEND.
SOMEONE WHO HAPPENS TO HAVE
A LOT OF MONEY.
HIS NAME'S ADAMS.
AND HE LOVES HIM
SOME DARCY!
HE SENT ME A THANK YOU
GIFT LAST NIGHT.
$200 BUCKS BY EMAIL.
$200?
I THOUGHT WE'D GET
TWENTY AT MOST.
AN ONLINE ADMIRER
PAYING FOR PHOTOS.
THAT'S NOT CREEPY AT ALL.
SO HOW WAS
THE BIG PREMIER?
UH...
IT WAS OKAY.
JT, I WAS THINKING,
THE OTHER DAY-
HI.
SORRY TO INTERRUPT.
COULD I UM...
SPEAK TO JT?
LIBERTY:
COURSE. SPEAK AWAY.
LOOK, I HAVE A KID,
AND I KNOW IT
FREAKS GUYS OUT.
AND I JUST WANT
TO LET YOU KNOW...
I GET IT.
JT:
NO, YOU DON'T GET IT, OKAY?
I LOVE KIDS.
MIA:
YEAH. GUYS ALWAYS SAY THAT.
JT:
NO. I MEAN IT.
YOU GOTTA TRUST ME ON THIS ONE,
MIA, OKAY?
I DO LOVE KIDS.
SO IT'S JUST ME
YOU DON'T LIKE?
YOU KINDA BLEW ME OFF.
I KNOW.
I'M SORRY.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S WRONG WITH ME?
I GUESS ORANGE PIE
IMPAIRS YOUR THINKING.
WELL, LISTEN UH...
HOW ABOUT I TAKE YOU AND BELLA
OUT FOR ICE CREAM?
MAYBE TONIGHT?
MIA:
WE'D LOVE THAT.
I'D LOVE THAT.
JT:
OKAY.
ALL:
TA-DA!
OKAY. YOU GUYS CAN GO
HAVE A SODA.
OR A NICE COLD GLASS
OF TALENT.
DARCY:
NEW UNIFORMS!
GIVE ME AN S!
GIVE ME AN H!
GIVE ME AN O, R, T!
MANNY, LOOK AT THESE.
HOLY HOT-TASTIC.
THIS IS EXACTLY
WHAT WE WANTED.
PAIGE ALWAYS PROMISED US
NEW UNIFORMS,
BUT NEVER CAME THROUGH.
UH, THESE ARE WAY
TOO SHORT.
PROBLEMS WITH HIS
BIKINI LINE.
I KEEP ON TELLING HIM
TO GET A BRAZILIAN.
MANNY:
THEY'RE FOR GIRLS,
LOSERS.
THESE MUST HAVE COST
A FORTUNE.
YEAH, WELL, I'VE BEEN
SELLING CHOCOLATE BARS
DOOR TO DOOR.
AMAZING, THE SUPPORT
FROM THE COMMUNITY.
HM.
SO,
BY SELLING CHOCOLATE BARS,
DO YOU MEAN POSTING
SEXY PHOTOS ON THE WEB
FOR CASH?
SEXY?
THEY WERE JUST SILLY.
WHATEVER.
WHAT HAPPENS IF PRINCIPAL H.
SEES THEM OR SIMPSON?
OR TOBY?
OR THE JANITOR?
PETER:
THEY WON'T.
NOBODY WILL.
PHOTOS ARE ON
A SECRET PAGE.
OH, THAT'S SO COMFORTING.
MANNY,
YOU SHOULD BE HAPPY.
YOU WANTED NEW UNIFORMS
AND NOW WE'VE GOT THEM.
PETER:
AND THINK OF WHAT ELSE
WE CAN GET?
I SAY WE DO ANOTHER
PHOTO SHOOT TODAY.
PAPA NEEDS
A NEW PAIR OF SHOES.
NO, PAPA NEEDS A LIFE,
AND I NEED TO GO HOME.
THIS IS OVER, GUYS.
OVER.