(CLOCK TICKING)
(STUDENT COUGHS)
PROFESSOR JANES:
AND TIME.
NEXT QUESTION.
(COUGHING)
EWW!
(TAPPING)
PROFESSOR JANES:
AND TIME.
NEXT QUESTION.
WHAT?
SHHH! SHHH! SHHH!
(CLOCK TICKING)
AND TIME.
NEXT QUESTION.
TIME.
AND TIME.
(DIFFICULTY BREATHING)
(HYPERVENTILATING)
(GASPING FOR BREATH)
(BREATHING HARD)
GOD,
I'M SUCH AN IDIOT!
♪♪♪
(ROCK MUSIC BLARES)
(PARTY CHATTER)
PAIGE:
HI, ALEX'S VOICEMAIL,
UH...
SORRY I HAVEN'T CALLED.
I WANTED TO,
BUT...
OKAY,
HAVE YOU EVER FELT
LIKE THE SUBWAY
IS RUNNING OVER YOUR LUNGS?
LIKE YOU'RE TRYING
TO BREATHE,
BUT THE ENTIRE TRAIN
IS JUST CRUSHING YOUR RIBS?
OKAY, UM,
I'M RAMBLING.
I JUST...
I REALLY, REALLY,
REALLY HOPE
THAT YOU'RE STILL GOING
TO MARCO AND DYLAN'S
THIS WEEKEND.
BYE.
(SIGHS)
PROFESSOR JANES:
THAT'S IT.
OH, AND I'LL HAVE
YOUR EXAM MARKS NEXT WEEK.
UH, PAIGE...
MICK-HAIL-CHOOKE?
A WORD, PLEASE?
UM, PROFESSOR JANES.
I WAS HOPING
WE COULD TALK, ACTUALLY.
UM...
I GUESS YOU THOUGHT
I LEFT THE MID-TERM.
WELL, I MEAN, I DID,
BUT NOT LIKE...
WHEN SOMEONE WALKS OUT
ON AN EXAM,
I LIKE TO KNOW WHY.
I SLEEP BETTER.
WELL, THAT'S PART OF IT -
SLEEPING.
I HAVEN'T BEEN.
AH! PARTYING.
NO, I SWEAR.
THOUGH THE REST
OF MY DORM HAS.
A LOT.
I JUST HAVE...
SO MUCH WORK
ALL THE TIME.
WELCOME TO COLLEGE.
IT'S STRESSFUL.
AND WHO KNEW THERE'D BE
SO MUCH MATH IN MARKETING?
PROFESSOR JANES:
PAIGE,
YOU NEED TO PASS
THIS COURSE
TO STAY IN
THE PROGRAM.
HELP ME TO,
PLEASE?
I AM SECONDS FROM LOSING
MY SCHOLARSHIP.
I DON'T WANT
TO DISCOURAGE YOU,
BUT NOT EVERYONE
IS CUT OUT FOR BANTING.
PROFESSOR JANES,
MY MOM WAS A BANTING GIRL
AND I AM A BANTING GIRL.
I JUST HAVE TO GET BETTER
AT DOING... BANTING.
(SIGHS)
TAKE HOME MID-TERM.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
I KNOW I CAN DO BETTER
THIS TIME.
PROFESSOR JANES:
ALONG WITH YOUR
TWENTY PAGE ESSAY
ON INTERNATIONAL BRANDING,
AND THE CHAPTER SUMMARIES
YOU'RE LATE ON.
THANK YOU,
PROFESSOR JANES.
DON'T WORRY,
I WON'T LET YOU DOWN.
MAKES NO DIFFERENCE
TO ME.
JUST DON'T LET
YOURSELF DOWN.
5:00 P.M. MONDAY.
HAVE A GREAT WEEKEND.
HEY...
HEARD YOU NEEDED TO GET
INTO THE CAF KITCHEN.
I'M WAITING FOR MY MOM
TO DRIVE ME HOME,
SO I THOUGHT I MIGHT
HELP A FRIEND.
FUNNY,
I DON'T SEE ONE.
OUCH.
I GUESS I COULD JUST GO
TO MEDIA IMMERSION
AND SCROLL THROUGH
SOME OF YOUR HOT PICS,
IF YOU'D EVER PUT
THEM BACK UP ONLINE.
(SNORTS)
DREAM ON.
I DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR PEOPLE
WHO MANIPULATE OTHERS
FOR THEIR OWN FUN.
"AND IF HE SINS AGAINST YOU
SEVEN TIMES A DAY,
AND RETURNS TO YOU
SEVEN TIMES SAYING,
I REPENT,
FORGIVE ME."
YOU SHOWED
MY PRIVATE PHOTOS
TO SOME 40-YEAR-OLD
PERVERT!
YOU CAN'T MAKE IT UP
WITH A BIBLE QUOTE.
I REPENT, I REPENT,
I REPENT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY NOW?
I SAY MATTHEW 10:42.
LOOK IT UP AND BE HERE
TOMORROW MORNING AT 7:00.
ON A SATURDAY?
BUSES DON'T EVEN RUN
THAT EARLY.
WHATEVER.
IT'S UP TO YOU.
I CANNOT BELIEVE
MOM AND DAD ARE RENOVATING
THIS WEEKEND.
AND HELLO TO YOU,
TOO.
MOM AND DAD ARE RENOVATING
EVERY WEEKEND.
MARCO:
HEY!
I MISSED YOU!
HERE, HOMEMADE GENETTIS.
BRAIN FOOD.
MMM!
I AM STARVING.
WHOA...
ARE YOU SURE THAT ELLIE
DIDN'T MAKE THESE?
ELLIE TOOK HER LAUNDRY HOME
FOR THE WEEKEND.
OH, AND JOKES!
KEIKO AND SUKI
ARE OFF
DISCOVERING OUR COUNTRY'S
NATURAL WONDERS -
NIAGARA FALLS.
SO YOU ARE MAKING
THE MICHALCHUK FAMILY DINNER?
HEY, I'M UNDER ENOUGH
PRESSURE AS IT IS
WITH MY PARENTS COMING TOO,
OKAY?
ALEX:
YOU GUYS ARE HAVING
A DOUBLE DATE WITH YOUR FOLKS?
A DATE?
GOSH, NO.
MARCO AND I
ARE JUST ROOMMATES.
RIGHT, DARLING?
EXACTLY, DARLING.
COME ON, LET'S GET YOU
SOME NON-HOMEMADE SNACKS.
YOU LIKE?
I MADE IT MYSELF.
FEELING HOSTILE,
ARE WE?
IT'S NOT HOSTILITY,
IT'S AFFECTION.
THE MESSAGE YOU LEFT
SOUNDED LIKE
THE FABULOUS BANTING GIRL
NEEDED A LITTLE BIT
OF A CHEER-UP.
YEAH, BECAUSE THE FABULOUS
BANTING GIRL
HAS TWELVE TONS
OF WORK TO DO.
WELL, NOW I'M HERE.
AND WE HAVE SOME SERIOUS
CATCHING UP TO DO.
GREAT.
OKAY, I'M BAKED.
GOOD NIGHT, LADIES.
NIGHT.
MMH!
I GOT TO BE UP
BY COCK-A-DOODLE-DAWN
TO HIT THE BOOKS.
GREAT.
I SHOULD GO.
NO. WAIT.
LET'S HAVE A SLEEPOVER,
RIGHT HERE.
JUST FRIENDS.
YEAH, I KNOW DOOFUS.
I HAVE A GIRLFRIEND.
YOU ARE SO LYING.
YOU MIGHT HAVE ONE FRIEND
AT BANTING NEXT YEAR.
WHO?
YOU? SERIOUSLY?
DESPITE YOUR DOUBTS,
I'M KICKING BUTT
AT SCHOOL -
MARKS, NOT PEOPLE.
WELL, THAT IS FANTASTIC,
HON.
I AM VERY GLAD
THAT YOU'VE PROVED ME WRONG.
WHATEVER.
LET'S GET OUR DEGREES
AND THEN ROAD TRIP.
IMAGINE A COUPLE OF BANTING
BABES GONE WILD.
THANKS, ALEX.
YOU'RE SO COMFY.
GOOD NIGHT.
HEY!
HEY, I BROUGHT
THESE FOR YOU-
GREAT IDEA!
THE HOMELESS DESERVE BEAUTY
WITH THEIR MEALS TOO, RIGHT?
HOMELESS WHAT?
DARCY:
OUR CHURCH GROUP'S DOING
A SPECIAL DINNER FOR THEM -
FOR TOMORROW.
AND I'M HERE THIS EARLY
BECAUSE...?
DID YOU READ MATTHEW 10?
UH, YEAH,
SOMETHING ABOUT
A GUY NEEDS WATER,
GIVES IT TO A DISCIPLE
OR SOMETHING...?
"I TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
HE WILL CERTAINLY
NOT LOSE HIS REWARD."
AKA THE FORGIVENESS YOU WANT -
A REWARD.
RIGHT.
SO WHY ARE YOU HERE?
WE ALL NEED FORGIVENESS
FOR SOMETHING.
AND YOU...
CAN START BY PEELING APPLES.
OH, AND UH, PETER?
(MUSIC BLARES)
(SIGHS)
MARCO:
I'M PRETTY SURE
THAT YOU SCREAMED
"I LOVE TURKEY"
OR SOMETHING
IN THE MIDDLE
OF YOUR SLEEP LAST NIGHT.
I WAS HAVING
A NIGHTMARE, OKAY?
I WAS IN LINE
FOR TURKEY.
OH, GOOD MORNING.
ALEX:
GOOD MORNING.
MARCO:
I'M SORRY,
DID YOU JUST SLEEP HERE...
DYLAN:
(LAUGHS) SHE SLEPT HERE?
MARCO:
WHERE'S PAIGE?
ALEX:
SHE'S OUT ON THE COUCH.
MARCO:
ON THE COUCH?
WHAT, LIKE WHY DID YOU
SLEEPOVER?
HOW LATE WERE YOU
HERE TILL?
DID YOU PASS OUT?
PAIGE:
(FRUSTRATED SIGH)
MARCO: (TEASING)
I DON'T KNOW, ALEX,
IT'S MY HOUSE!
I THINK I WANT THE INFO!
ALEX:
(LAUGHING)
MARCO:
THIS KID WAS JUST TELLING ME-
HEY! DO YOU GUYS THINK
YOU COULD BE A LITTLE LOUDER
FOR ME?
(MUSIC STOPS BRIEFLY)
UM,
HOW ABOUT YOU CHILL?
MARCO:
LIKE DON'T YOU USE,
LIKE, FLOUR TO MAKE GRAVY?
DYLAN:
WELL, YOU DO.
YEAH, YOU USE FLOUR
AND YOU USE
LIKE CHICKEN BROTH,
WHICH IS THE JUICE
FROM THE CHICKEN DRIPPINGS-
YEAH, I KNOW BUT MAKE SURE
YOU GET SALT.
YEAH, OKAY.
LIKE STAR THAT.
OKAY,
IT'S STARRED.
YOU GUYS,
YOU'RE RIDICULOUS.
PLEASE, TAKE THIS.
THIS WAS GRAN'S,
SO CAREFUL.
DON'T PUT IT
IN THE MICRO.
HERE'S THE WALNUT STUFFING
RECIPE FOR DYLAN.
REMIND HIM,
JUST A TOUCH OF SAGE.
OH, MOM.
CAN YOU COME IN FOR A SEC?
I'D LOVE TO,
BUT THE CONTRACTORS...
BUT YOUR DAUGHTER
WANTS TO TELL YOU SOMETHING.
MRS. MICHALCHUK:
OH, CAN'T IT WAIT?
SORRY.
WHAT IS IT, SWEETHEART?
NEVER MIND.
COMPARED TO RENOVATION HELL,
IT'S NOTHING.
UNLIKE THE CONTRACTORS,
YOU'VE NEVER
LET ME DOWN.
(LAUGHS)
DOES SHE BREATHE
LIKE THE REST OF US,
OR DOES SHE PRODUCE
HER OWN AIR INTERNALLY
LIKE A BLOWFISH?
(GASPING FOR BREATH)
(GIGGLES)
EXACTLY.
PAIGE?
YOU ALL RIGHT?
DON'T MAKE ME BE NICE.
(HYPERVENTILATING)
OKAY, YOU MADE ME.
PAIGE MICHALCHUK,
YOU ARE THE PRETTIEST,
SMARTEST, BESTEST -
WHY ARE YOU PUTTING MORE
PRESSURE ON ME, ALEX?!
WHY?
PRESSURE?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
FORGET IT, OKAY?
LEAVE ME ALONE! GO!
FORGET WHAT?
WHAT'S WRONG?
PAIGE:
YOU DON'T GET IT, ALEX,
AND YOU NEVER WILL!
SO JUST GO BACK TO YOUR STUPID,
PATHETIC,
LITTLE STAIGHT 'A'
HIGH SCHOOL LIFE,
WITH YOUR PATHETIC,
IMAGINARY GIRLFRIEND, OKAY?
JUST GO AWAY!
(CRYING)
DYLAN, JUST MOVE,
OKAY?
I'M MUCH BETTER
AT FRIDGE TETRIS.
JUST LEAVE THE TURKEY OUT.
NO, MY ARM'S FREEZING.
JUST GET OUTTA HERE.
SALMONELLA
IS SO NOT FESTIVE.
EVERYTHING OKAY?
ALEX BOLTED
LIKE SHE WAS ON FIRE.
YEAH, THAT'S ALEX
BEING ALEX.
YOU CAN'T JUST LEAVE
POULTRY SITTING OUT.
SEE?
I TOLD YOU, DYLAN.
EXCUSE ME,
BUT I'M THE ONE...
YOU KNOW WHAT?
JUST I'LL- I'LL COOK,
TAKE SOME PARENT PRESSURE
OFF YOU.
DON'T YOU HAVE AN ESSAY
TO COOK UP?
YEAH, I CAN HANDLE MY OWN
COURSE LOAD, THANKS.
BOTH OF YOU, OUT!
FINE, I'M DONE.
FINE.
HERE.
(SIGHS)
DYLAN:
TRY TO RELAX.
EVERYTHING WILL BE FINE.
WHEN I'M NERVOUS,
I FIDGIT.
NO, NO, NO...
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
IS IT TOO LATE
TO CANCEL?
HEY, MOM, DAD,
HERE, COME IN.
HI.
(LAUGHS) HEY...
PLACE LOOKS GREAT,
MARCO.
YEAH, YEAH,
IT'S GOOD.
FOR YOUR HOUSE.
OH, THANK YOU,
MRS. DEL ROSSI.
THANK YOU.
(KNOCK AT THE DOOR)
OH, I'LL GET THAT.
HERE.
I'LL GET THAT.
SORRY.
DYLAN:
MOM, HEY!
HI, SPORTO.
HEY, DAD.
HOW'RE YOU DOING?
STILL NO HAIRCUT?
STILL NO HAIR.
PAIGE:
BUTTERNUT SQUASH SOUP
WITH FRIZZLED LEEKS
AND CREME FRAICHE.
SO GOURMET!
MRS. MICHALCHUK:
SHE'S SUCH A TALENT.
SHE WON THE BROWNIES'
BEST BROWNIE AWARD
WHEN SHE WAS SIX.
I ALWAYS WISH
I'D HAD A DAUGHTER.
I'M GLAD YOU DIDN'T.
(NOT SO GENTLE THUD)
THIS LOOKS DELICIOUS.
(DOOR OPENING)
ARE WE LATE?
WE BROUGHT BUNS.
I MADE BUNS.
DON'T BE RUDE.
HELLO, ALEX.
DYLAN?
OH YEAH,
I'VE GOT SOME EXTRA CHAIRS
IN OUR ROOM-
MY ROOM.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
WELL, YOU INVITED ME.
AND I WANTED TO MAKE SURE
YOU WERE OKAY
AFTER YOUR LITTLE BREAKDOWN.
BREAKDOWN?
ALEX IS A PATHOLOGICAL LIAR.
ALEX, MAYBE WE SHOULD
JUST-
MR. DEL ROSSI:
HEY!
NO ARGUING OVER DINNER.
SIT.
NOW, WHO'S YOUR FRIEND?
THIS IS CARLA,
MY IMAGINARY GIRLFRIEND.
(SHOCKED SNORT)
HELLO.
OKAY.
THELO FA-GEE-TO -
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
PEE-NAO,
THELO DIO FROUTA GLIKA.
SLOW DOWN!
IS THERE A PROBLEM?
MY GREEK'S
A LITTLE ROUGH.
I THINK HE WANTS
AN EXTRA PIECE OF PIE,
IS THAT ALL RIGHT?
YOU SPEAK GREEK?
YEAH, I LEARNED SOME
FROM MY BABU-
GRAMPA.
HE USED TO EAT
A LOT OF DESSERT TOO.
TELL HIM YOU PEELED
THE APPLES YOURSELF.
YEAH, I'LL TRY.
UH... ORMORA...
PEELED THEM MYSELF.
(LAUGHTER)
MRS. MICHALCHUK:
THE POMEGRANATE DRESSING,
JUST EXQUISITE!
PAIGE, YOU COULD HAVE
GOT A SCHOLARSHIP
FOR CHEF SCHOOL TOO!
MOM...
MR. MICHALCHUK:
OH, AND DYLAN HAS
HAD OFFERS RECENTLY
TO PLAY PRO HOCKEY
IN SWITZERLAND.
ONCE MY VISA
COMES THROUGH.
YEAH,
DON'T REMIND ME.
DID YOU KNOW CARLA'S
AN HONOURS GRAD STUDENT?
AND SHE'S CAPTAIN
OF THE TORONTO U.
DISTANCE RUNNING TEAM.
I'LL CLEAR THE SALAD PLATES.
MRS. MICHALCHUK:
BANTING WANTED PAIGE
FOR THEIR POWER SQUAD -
THEY CALLED IT CHEERLEADING
WHEN I WAS CAPTAIN -
BUT SHE CHOSE TO FOCUS
ON ACADEMICS.
MOM, PLEASE.
MRS. MICHALCHUK:
ONCE PAIGE GETS
HER HONOURS DEGREE,
THE BANTING MBA PROGRAM-
MOM?!
MRS. MICHALCHUK:
SWEETIE, TELL EVERYONE
HOW BANTING HAS
THE MOST PRESTIGIOUS PROGRAM.
WHY DON'T WE TALK ABOUT
SOMETHING ELSE?
FINE.
OH, DON'T YOU HAVE
SOME SORT OF ANNOUNCEMENT?
YES.
THE TURKEY'S READY.
SHE'S SO MODEST.
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
OKAY.
PETER:
HEY DARCY,
DO YOU WANT A RIDE HOME?
DARCY:
SURE. BUT I THOUGHT
SINCE THE STREET RACING THING,
YOU CAN'T...
NO, I CAN DRIVE.
THEY GAVE YOU
YOUR LICENCE BACK?
YEAH.
I DIDN'T HIT THE GUY.
I'M IN THE CLEAR.
BUT IT'LL COST YOU.
WILL HALF A PIE DO IT?
HEY, I TAKE AFTER MY BABU.
HERE IT IS,
COMPLETE WITH TRADITIONAL
MICHALCHUK FAMILY
WALNUT STUFFING.
OH!
LOOKS DELICIOUS!
MRS. MICHALCHUK:
COME ON, PAIGE,
LET'S HERE YOUR NEWS.
REALLY, IT'S MORE OF A DESSERT
AND COFFEE KINDA THING.
MRS. MICHALCHUK:
DEAN'S LIST?
A BURSARY?
NEW BOYFRIEND,
HMM?
WHO WANTS WHITE
AND WHO WANTS DARK?
MR. DEL ROSSI:
I'LL TAKE WHITE.
ALL:
OHHH!
ALEX AND CARLA:
(BURST OUT LAUGHING)
DYLAN:
I TOLD YOU NOT
TO OVERSTUFF THE BIRD.
TRADITIONAL MICHALCHUK
FAMILY WALNUT STUFFING.
ALEX:
WE STILL HAVE
BRUSSEL SPROUTS.
AND CARROTS.
(SHAKY BREATHING)
(GASPING FOR BREATH)
UGH...
HEY!
EVERYBODY'S SO WORRIED
ABOUT YOU.
EXCEPT MY POPS,
WHO'S STILL, YOU KNOW,
EATING,
BUT TAKE THAT
AS A COMPLIMENT.
I BLEW UP
A 20 POUND TURKEY.
YEAH.
COME ON, PAIGE,
THAT'S NOT ALL
THAT'S BOTHERING YOU.
WHAT IS IT?
WHAT COULD POSSIBLY
HAVE MY SMART, BEAUTIFUL,
TALENTED FRIEND
SO DOWN?
DON'T... CALL ME THAT.
I AM AN IDIOT.
I'VE FOOLED ALL OF YOU.
YOU ARE TOO STRESSED.
IS IT SCHOOL,
WITH ALL THAT WORK
YOU BROUGHT HOME?
PAIGE, YOU'RE NOT
THE ONLY ONE.
I'LL LET YOU IN
ON A LITTLE SECRET.
LAST WEEK,
I GOT A C-MINUS
ON MY PSYCH PAPER.
I SHOULD DRIVE BACK
TONIGHT.
WHAT? TONIGHT?
IT'S THREE HOURS AWAY!
IT'S FINE, MARCO.
UM...
I'LL TELL MY PARENTS
AND THEN GO.
ARE YOU SURE?
HEY, YOU CALL ME
IF YOU NEED TO TALK,
ALL RIGHT?
YEAH.
YEAH, 250K AN HOUR,
BEFORE MODS.
YOU'VE NEVER GONE
THAT FAST!
(REVS CAR)
DARCY:
PETER!
THERE ARE NOT ENOUGH AIRBAGS
IN THIS WORLD...
(REVS CAR)
LICENCE
AND REGISTRATION.
WHAT DO WE DO?
JUST RELAX.
THEY HASSLE YOU
IF YOU GO FASTER THAN THEM.
BUT THEY'RE ON BIKES.
YEAH, ESPECIALLY THE ONES
ON BIKES.
WE'VE GOT
A PETER STONE HERE,
N31 PENOT AVENUE,
PLEASE.
OUT OF THE CAR,
WHY?
WE'RE STOPPED.
WELL, YOUR FRIEND
PETER HERE,
HAS BEEN DRIVING WITH
A SUSPENDED LICENCE.
IT'S TRUE?
I CANNOT BELIEVE I ACTUALLY
STARTED TO LIKE YOU!
YOU'LL NEVER CHANGE.
(SLAMS DOOR)
(SIGHS)
(SLIGHTLY PANICKED BREATHING)