(RACING CAR WHIRS)
PAIGE:
THANKS, EMILY.
YOU ARE THE HOSTESS
WITH THE MOSTEST.
EMILY:
YOU COME OVER
ANYTIME YOU LIKE, PAIGE.
OH, PUT ME DOWN
FOR OSCAR NIGHT.
SO LONG AS
CHAD LETS US WATCH
ON HIS 6000 INCH
PLASMA THINGY.
(KNOCK AT THE DOOR)
PIZZA MONEY'S
ON THE SIDE TABLE, HON.
COP:
GOOD EVENING,
WE'RE LOOKING
FOR CHAD KENT.
ARE YOU HIM?
DEPENDS. UH...
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
WE HAVE A WARRANT
FOR YOUR ARREST
FOR THE CRIME
OF CREDIT CARD FRAUD.
CREDIT CARD FRAUD?
WHAT? NO.
THERE MUST BE SOME...
SOME... MISTAKE.
SORRY, EMILY.
EMILY:
NO, WAIT.
ALEX:
SHOULD I COME?
EMILY:
NO.
NO, YOU STAY.
I'M SURE WE'LL
GET THIS ALL UH...
SORTED OUT.
WOW.
HOW "COPS" WAS THAT?
ARE YOU OKAY?
PAIGE, YOU SHOULD GO.
ARE YOU SURE?
THE...
TV'S ALL OURS.
IT'S LATE
AND I HAVE EXAMS.
COULD YOU JUST GO
PLEASE.
AS YOU WISH, HON.
UM...
THANKS FOR YOUR HELP.
♪♪♪
NOTHING LIKE AN ALL-NIGHTER
AT THE POLICE STATION.
WHERE'S CHAD?
IN JAIL.
YOU KNOW THAT BIG RAISE
HE TOLD US ABOUT?
IT WAS A LIE, LEXI.
HE WAS FIRED.
MOM, THAT WAS
SIX WEEKS AGO.
WHAT'S HE BEEN DOING
ALL THIS TIME?
OH, BESIDES BUYING
NEW PLASMA TVS
WITH STOLEN
CREDIT CARDS?
MOM, IT'S OKAY.
WE'LL SEND IT BACK.
AND THEN WE'RE FINE,
RIGHT?
TV'S GONE.
LOSER'S IN JAIL.
GOOD RIDDANCE.
WHAT?
I UH...
I GAVE HIM A CARD
WITH HIS NAME ON IT.
HE TOOK ADVANTAGE
OF ME, LEXI.
NOW I'M IN THE HOLE
FOR SIX GRAND.
THAT'S NOT A HOLE, MOM.
THAT'S THE GRAND CANYON.
EMILY:
I KNOW.
ARGH. HOW DID HE PUT
$6000 ON YOUR CARD?!
HE TOLD ME HE WAS
MAKING THE PAYMENTS.
LIE NUMBER TWO.
YOU'RE NOT PAYING
THOSE CHARGES.
BANK SAYS MY CREDIT CARD;
MY PROBLEM.
WE NEED THAT CREDIT CARD
TO PAY THE BILLS.
I MEAN,
I'LL WORK DOUBLE SHIFTS,
BUT UH...
I'M NOT SURE IT'S GONNA
BE ENOUGH, YOU KNOW.
IT'S OUR PROBLEM,
OKAY?
AND WE'RE GONNA
GET THROUGH IT.
I PROMISE.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
MANNY:
I'M DOOMED
ON MY FUNCTIONS EXAM.
DOOMED!
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO BE
YOUR FAB UNIVERSITY ROOMMATE
IF I FAIL?
ASSUMING I DON'T ALREADY
HAVE A ROOMIE LINED UP
OF THE BLUE-COLLAR,
SEXY-MECHANIC TYPE?
YEAH RIGHT.
SEAN'S LIKE,
"HEY, LET'S SHACK UP.
I'M REAL SERIOUS
ABOUT OUR FUTURE, YO."
IS THAT SO COMPLETELY
UNBELIEVABLE?
I THINK IT'D BE GREAT
TO HAVE SOMETHING
THAT'S JUST OURS.
LIKE...
A LITTLE HOME TOGETHER.
EM, YOU'RE 17.
YOU HAVE THE WHOLE LIFE
TO SETTLE DOWN
BEHIND THE WHITE
PICKET FENCE.
WELL, EXCUSE ME
FOR WANTING TO MOVE IN
WITH MY BOYFRIEND.
AND YOU'RE SURE
HE WANTS TO MOVE IN?
WHY WOULDN'T HE?
BECAUSE, THERE'S ONLY ONE
FOUR LETTER WORD
IN THE YOUNG MALE
DICTIONARY:
COMMITMENT.
I USED TO LOVE
DISPENSING ARTIFICIAL
NACHO CHEESE PRODUCT.
THAT OOEY-GLUEY TEXTURE.
GREAT! FIRST THE COPS
RAID MY HOUSE.
AND NOW YOU SEE ME
WRAPPED IN POLYESTER.
REAL ATTRACTIVE.
HON, IF YOU NEEDED
A JOB SO BAD
YOU COULD HAVE ASKED ME.
'COURSE, I CAN ONLY PAY YOU
IN T-SHIRTS.
MY MOM NEEDS CASH,
FAST.
BIG, FACELESS CORPORATIONS
WEREN'T THE ONLY ONES
CHAD STOLE FROM.
HE RACKED UP MY MOM'S
CREDIT CARD, SO...
UM...
I WISH I COULD
DO SOMETHING.
I MEAN, MAYBE I COULD
LEND YOU A LITTLE BIT.
(HALF LAUGH)
NO. I'LL BE FINE.
SO, UM...
HOW IS THE LOVELY
AND TALENTED MS. CARLA
THESE DAYS?
I THINK MS. P.H.D. WAS
SLUMMING IT WITH ME.
BESIDES, WE HAD
ZERO IN COMMON.
IT JUST WASN'T
WORTH MY TIME.
WELL,
IF MS. SNOOTYPANTS
THINKS SHE'S
TOO GOOD FOR YOU,
SHE ISN'T INVITED TO
MY HOUSEWARMING PARTY.
MARCO:
MAN, THESE APPETIZERS
ARE LIKE TINY LITTLE
FLAVOUR-BOMBS.
HOW DOES PAIGE DO IT?
SHE'S JUST A CULINARY
WIZARD, I GUESS.
EVEN THE DEVIL
HAS HER FINE POINTS.
ELLIE, DON'T START,
OKAY?
YOU TOLD HER IT WAS
OKAY TO DATE JESSE.
IT BUGS.
I CAN'T HELP IT.
SO, THERE'S PLENTY MORE
FISH IN THE SEA, OKAY?
WE'LL HIT A CLUB,
PUT YOU OUT THERE.
GREAT. MEETING GUYS
AT A CLUB.
YAY.
YOU MADE IT!
WITH GUESTS.
PAIGE, THIS IS
MY NEW GIRLFRIEND, MEL.
YOU SAID INVITE PEOPLE.
THEIR MOVIE ENDED,
SO I DID.
NOW WHERE CAN I CHANGE
OUT OF THIS LOSER-SUIT.
MEL'S BEEN TELLING ME
SHE MIGHT BE ABLE
TO GET YOU OUT OF THAT
SEXY UNIFORM.
YEAH. THEY'RE LOOKING
FOR CUTE SERVERS
WHERE I WORK.
WHERE'S THAT,
A STRIP BAR?
CLUB ZANZIBAR.
PERFECTLY RESPECTABLE
COCKTAIL BAR -
ON ONE SIDE -
CRAZY-HOT PEELERS
ON THE OTHER.
OR SO I'VE BEEN TOLD.
MEL:
YEAH. THEY PREFER TO BE CALLED
"EXOTIC DANCERS".
BESIDES,
I WORK IN THE BAR.
FULLY CLOTHED
AT ALL TIMES.
IT'S GOOD TIPS;
ABOUT 150 A NIGHT.
AND THEY'RE HIRING?!
COME BY.
I'LL GET YOU
AN INTERVIEW.
JAY'S GIRLFRIEND WORKS
AT ZANZIBAR,
QUELLE SURPRISE.
GUESS NASA
WASN'T HIRING?
SPIKE:
HOW ARE THINGS
AT THE GARAGE?
SEAN:
OKAY.
ACTUALLY, NOT SO GOOD.
IT'S KINDA DEAD-END.
NEED TO UPGRADE MY SKILLS
IF I WANNA RUN MY OWN SHOP.
HAVE CONSIDERED
A TECHNICAL HIGH SCHOOL?
I NEED HANDS-ON EXPERIENCE
AND A PAYCHECK.
SO YOU'RE JUST GONNA
SKIP HIGH SCHOOL?
FORGET YOUR DIPLOMA?
I CAN GET ALL
THE TRAINING I WANT
AND GET PAID FOR IT.
WHERE?
NOWHERE. JUST...
FORGET IT.
FORGET WHAT?
WHERE IS THIS WONDERFUL,
MERRY,
MAGIC MECHANIC LAND?
THIS ISN'T EXACTLY HOW
I WANTED TO TELL YOU THIS.
IT'S THE ARMED SERVICES.
(INCREDULOUS LAUGH)
YOU'RE NOT SERIOUS.
YEAH.
I AM.
I SIGNED UP ALREADY.
PASSED MY PHYSICAL.
I'M PRETTY PSYCHED ACTUALLY.
YOU KNOW,
WITH YOUR SKILLS?
YOU MIGHT BE A PERFECT FIT.
I'M SORRY,
I'VE LOST MY APPETITE.
KETCHUP?
STEPHANIE:
THE GIRLS ARE ALL
FRIENDS HERE.
YOU'LL LIKE IT.
(SMIRKS)
THANKS, STEPHANIE.
I'LL...
I'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT
FOR MY FIRST SHIFT!
HEY, WORK BUDDY!
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
YOU GOT IT.
THAT'S AMAZING!
STEPH'S COOL,
BUT THEN THERE'S...
(SMIRKS AND CLEARS THROAT)
ALEX, THIS IS VLAD.
HI.
THE OWNER.
UM, ALEX IS
OUR NEW SERVER.
WELCOME, ALEX.
YOU ARE PRETTIER
THAN MANY OF MY DANCERS.
(LAUGHS)
WELL, THANK YOU -
I THINK.
IN A CLOTHES-ON
SORT OF WAY.
MY GIRLS ARE PAID WELL
AND THEY ARE VERY HAPPY.
MAYBE SOMETIME YOU WANT
TO AUDITION?
OH... DEFINITELY NOT.
I UNDERSTAND.
I'M SURE YOU WILL MAKE
A GREAT WAITRESS.
LIKE THIS ONE.
(DISGUSTED GAG)
(BAR MUSIC PLAYS)
YOU WEREN'T LYING, EH?
I THINK I'VE CLEARED
A HUNDRED ALREADY.
(MIMICKING VLAD)
THAT IS NOTHING.
GIRLS ON THE OTHER SIDE
ARE RICH AND HAPPY
LIKE MOVIE STAR.
ALEX:
(LAUGHS)
OOH. SHE DOESN'T LOOK
SO HAPPY TO ME.
OH, MAYBE NOT.
BUT... SHE IS PAID WELL.
YEAH.
SMALL PRICE TO PAY
FOR YOUR SOUL.
MEL:
LEXI,
IF YOU WERE
SO AGAINST STRIPPING
THEN WHY ARE YOU
WORKING HERE?
(SMIRKS)
WHY ELSE?
I NEED THE MONEY.
MEL:
SO DOES SHE.
THE ONLY DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN HER AND US
IS THAT SHE NEEDS IT
MORE.
HEY.
BEEN SWEEPING UP POPCORN
'TIL 2:00 AM?
ALEX:
I QUIT.
I GOT A JOB
AS A WAITRESS
AT THIS SHMANCY BISTRO.
GOODBYE MINIMUM WAGE,
HELLO CRAZY TIPS!
THAT'S GREAT.
I'M REALLY HAPPY
FOR YOU.
YOUR HAPPINESS
IS OVERWHELMING.
WE'RE GETTING EVICTED?
YUP.
WE HAVE TEN DAYS TO COME UP
WITH THE MONEY.
YOU KNOW ANYONE
WITH A SPARE TWO GRAND
KICKIN' AROUND?
JUST HOW?
HOW DID THIS HAPPEN?
WELL, WE'VE BEEN
BOUNCING RENT CHEQUES
FOR THE LAST TWO MONTHS.
AND I HAD NO IDEA.
MOM, HOW COULD YOU
NOT KNOW THAT?
EMILY:
CHAD HIDING THE LETTERS
FROM THE BUILDING MANAGER,
THAT'S HOW.
AND NO, I'M NOT PROUD
I TRUSTED THAT SCUMBAG.
OKAY?
SO WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
WELL, I ASKED
FOR A RAISE AGAIN.
THEY TURNED ME DOWN
AGAIN.
I NEVER WANTED IT
TO BE LIKE THIS, LEXI.
(SNIFFLES)
I LET YOU DOWN.
CHAD DID THIS, MOM,
NOT YOU!
♪ WE PULL
WE PUSH ♪
AND WE PUSH PUSH ♪
(KNOCK AT THE DOOR)
OKAY.
TELL ME I DON'T LOOK
COMPLETELY IDIOTIC.
WELL...
NOT IF YOU'RE ON YOUR WAY
TO A RAP VIDEO SHOOT.
OR, SAY,
THE STAGE AT ZANZIBAR?
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
THIS IS WHY
YOU CALLED ME HERE
AT 9:00 IN THE MORNING?
ALEX:
KIND OF.
WHATEVER HAPPENED
TO "SMALL PRICE TO PAY
FOR YOUR SOUL?"
WELL, MY SOUL JUST GOT
A WHOLE LOT CHEAPER.
TRY NOT TO LAUGH, OKAY?
(VIDEO TAPE BEGINS)
INSTRUCTOR:
ROLL IT IN.
NICE AND SLOW.
ALEX:
I NEED YOUR HELP.
INSTRUCTOR:
ANOTHER HIP CIRCLE.
AND THEN WE JUST
TAKE ONE STEP.
♪ GO BANGIN'
GIMME SOME ♪
♪ DO IT, DO IT
DON'T ♪
♪ DO IT,
DON'T BLUSH BLUSH ♪
♪ DO, RE, MI ON THE FLOOR ♪
♪ LA TI ON ME AT THE DOOR ♪
(LAUGHS)
NICE VOTE OF CONFIDENCE,
JERK!
I'M SORRY.
I'M ON THREE
HOURS SLEEP.
MAYBE IT'S...
JUST TOO EARLY
FOR ME TO PICTURE YOU
AS AN EXOTIC DANCER.
WHO AM I KIDDING?
I CAN'T DO THIS.
MEL:
AND THAT'S BAD?
THERE'S GOTTA BE
ANOTHER WAY.
ALEX:
SURE. UH, ARMED ROBBERY,
PROSTITUTION, DRUG MULE,
TIGER POACHING.
WHAT ABOUT PAIGE?
PAIGE LOOKS A LOT
BETTER OFF THAN SHE IS.
NOT THAT I'D EVER ASK.
EMMA.
SEAN, ARE YOU CRAZY?
IF PRINCIPAL HATZILAKOS
SEES YOU OUT HERE SHE'LL-
SHE'LL WHAT?
SHE'LL GIVE ME DETENTION?
I'M OUTSIDE!
JUST TALK TO ME,
ALL RIGHT.
I'VE BEEN CALLING YOU
AROUND THE CLOCK.
I KNOW.
SO THEN WHY HAVEN'T YOU
ANSWERED?!
BECAUSE I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'D MAKE
SUCH A STUPID DECISION
WITHOUT EVEN TALKING
TO ME!
EM, I THOUGHT
YOU'D BE HAPPY FOR ME.
YOU KNOW,
SPREADING DEMOCRACY,
PEACEKEEPING,
PROTECTING OUR COUNTRY.
THESE ARE ALL
GOOD THINGS.
SEAN,
YOU WOULD HATE IT.
THE ARMY IS ALL ABOUT
TAKING ORDERS
AND BEING TOLD
WHAT TO DO
AND WHAT TO THINK.
SO BEING TOLD WHAT
TO THINK IS WRONG?
ISN'T THAT
WHAT YOU'RE DOING?
THIS IS DIFFERENT.
HOW?
BECAUSE I'M YOUR
GIRLFRIEND, SEAN!
IF YOU JOIN THE ARMY,
YOU COULD GET HURT.
AND I NEED YOU
RIGHT NOW!
WHY? TELL ME.
I CAN TAKE IT.
HONESTLY,
I'M NOT SURE YOU CAN.
(SIGHS)
PAIGE:
DESCRIBE THE FUNCTION
OF ENZYMES
IN METABOLIC REACTIONS
IN MITOCHONDRIA.
HOW ABOUT NOT.
BREAK TIME.
MM. I THOUGHT
YOU'D NEVER ASK.
SO, UH...
I HAVE SOME NEWS.
YOU ARE LOOKING AT
A NEWLY SINGLE GIRL.
YOU BROKE IT OFF
WITH JESSE?
WE HAD ZERO IN COMMON,
HON.
HE WASN'T WORTH
MY TIME.
WELL, IT SOUNDS LIKE
YOU'VE GOT IT ALL
FIGURED OUT, PAIGEY.
(SMIRKS) HARDLY.
I WAS SUPPOSED
TO BE AT BANTING.
FAST TRACKING TO AN MBA.
I WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
A SORORITY GIRL
SIPPING COSMOS
WITH BRITTANY AND AMBER.
(GIGGLES)
BUT... HERE I AM
CHILLING WITH YOU
AND...
IT FEELS RIGHT.
WHY IS THAT?
WHY DO YOU KEEP
DOING THIS TO ME?
SORRY, I...
I THOUGHT THE DOOR
WAS KIND OF OPEN.
YEAH.
IT'S BEEN OPEN FOR WEEKS.
THE PROBLEM IS
YOU KEEP OPENING IT
AND THEN CLOSING IT
AND OPENING IT
AND CLOSING IT.
JUST MAKE UP YOUR MIND!
LOOK! YOU'RE COOL
WITH BEING A LESBIAN, BUT...
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I AM.
THE WORD IS BISEXUAL,
PAIGE,
AND IT'S JUST A LABEL.
WHO CARES?
MY PARENTS ALREADY
HAVE ONE GAY KID.
(SCOFFS) SO?!
SO, I JUST DROPPED OUT
OF UNIVERSITY
LET THEM DEAL WITH ONE
MAJOR PARENTAL CRISIS
AT A TIME!
GREAT. EVERYTHING'S ALWAYS
ON YOUR SCHEDULE,
ISN'T IT?
I AM SUPPOSED TO GIVE THEM
GRANDKIDS ONE DAY.
YOU DO NOT GET THE PRESSURE
I AM UNDER.
PRESSURE?!
EXCUSE ME FOR FINDING
YOUR IDEA OF PRESSURE
PRETTY... PRETTY DAMN PATHETIC
RIGHT NOW.
HON, DON'T CRY.
STOP.
YOU DON'T GET
TO BREAK MY HEART
AND THEN COMFORT ME TOO.
THIS IS MY WORST NIGHTMARE,
MANNY.
MY BOYFRIEND'S IS JOINING
THE WAR MACHINE.
HE COULD GET HIMSELF KILLED
PROTECTING BIG CORPORATIONS
FROM THE POOR.
WELL, AT LEAST YOU'RE
KEEPING AN OPEN MIND, CHE.
LOOK, I'M SURE
SEAN'S DOING IT
FOR THE RIGHT REASONS.
AND I BET ONE OF THEM
IS YOU.
(SIGHS)
I KNOW.
I JUST...
I HAD THESE PLANS
FOR ME AND SEAN
AND HIM JOINING THE ARMY
WASN'T AMONG THEM.
MANNY:
AND YOU DON'T LIKE IT
WHEN THINGS DON'T GO
ACCORDING TO PLAN.
NO.
I REALLY, REALLY DON'T.
EM, WE'RE GETTING INTO
CONTROL ISSUES ZONE.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE OKAY?
YES! I'M FINE!
THIS IS JUST SEAN,
OKAY.
(PHONE RINGS)
(JACK SPEAKS UNCLEARLY)
(SMIRKS)
JACK.
(PHONE RINGS)
HEL-HELLO?
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER
OF BAR PATRONS)
(SNAPS)
ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
TWO.
(HARD SMACK)
THANK YOU.
(DOG BARKS IN THE DISTANCE)
SEAN:
EMMA.
WHAT WAS SO IMPORTANT
THAT YOU COULDN'T TELL ME
ON THE PHONE?
I'M WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO SIT
'CAUSE THIS IS GONNA
FREAK YOU OUT.
I DON'T NEED TO SIT.
I KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON.
YOU'RE EMOTIONAL.
YOU'RE SCATTERED.
YOU HAVE TROUBLE
CONCENTRATING. IT...
IT ADDS UP.
YOU'RE ANOREXIC AGAIN,
AREN'T YOU?
NO.
SEAN,
YOU'RE NOT EVEN CLOSE.
(SIGHS)
I'M PREGNANT.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I AM GONNA FREAK OUT.
UH...
ARE YOU SURE?
YOU DO A TEST?
WE'LL DO IT TOGETHER,
OKAY?
TELL ME SOMETHING
GOOD, MOM. PLEASE.
HOW DID IT GO WITH
THE UH, BUILDING MANAGER?
GET THAT EXTENSION?
I TRIED.
YOU TRIED WHAT?
WHAT DID YOU DO?
WELL, TURNS OUT
HE DOESN'T HAVE A THING
FOR ME AFTER ALL.
(CHUCKLES)
SO WE'RE STILL
BEING EVICTED?
YOU THINK THEY'LL
REMEMBER US
AT THE WOMEN'S
SHELTER?
WE'RE NOT GOING
BACK THERE, MOM,
EVER.
I KNOW WHAT TO DO.
I THOUGHT WE HAD
ALL THE BASES COVERED.
AND SOMETIMES
YOU HIT A HOME RUN.
ACCIDENTS CAN HAPPEN.
MAYBE THE PILL
DIDN'T KICK IN.
TIME'S UP.
IT'S NEGATIVE.
YES!
DON'T GET TOO EXCITED.
FALSE NEGATIVES
ARE COMMON.
I HAVE ALL THE SYMPTOMS,
I'M DAYS LATE!
SO NOW WHAT DO WE DO?
WE TALK.
WE... WE MAKE DECISIONS.
I NEVER THOUGHT
I'D ABORT,
AND THERE'S ALWAYS
ADOPTION, BUT...
WHOA, EMMA. EMMA.
THE TEST WAS NEGATIVE!
ALL RIGHT.
JUST TAKE A BREATH
BEFORE YOU START GETTING
ALL WORKED UP ABOUT THIS!
OKAY. (INHALES)
I'LL BREATHE.
(CALMING INHALE AND EXHALE)
(SIGHS)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
OH, MY GOD.
YOU'RE ACTUALLY
GOING TO DO THIS?
THAT WOULD EXPLAIN
THE OUTFIT. YEAH.
VLAD LET YOU AND...
NO AUDITION?
APPARENTLY I HAVE
NATURAL TALENTS.
MIGHT AS WELL USE 'EM.
SO YOU JUST
CHANGED YOUR MIND.
LIFE CHANGED IT
FOR ME, MEL.
(SYMPATHETIC SIGH)
LEXI,
I'VE SEEN SO MANY
GIRLS DO THIS.
IF YOU GO OUT THERE?
IT CHANGES YOU.
ANNOUNCER:
AND NOW LET'S WELCOME
A NEWCOMER TO OUR STAGE...
THE BEAUTIFUL LEXTACY!
CLUB GOERS:
(WHISTLING AND CHEERING)
I'M NOT GOING OUT THERE, MEL.
(DEEP BREATH)
LEXTACY IS.
(WHISTLING AND CHEERING)
(CLUB MUSIC PLAYS LOUDLY)
♪♪♪