♪♪♪
WAY TO STICK IT,
GUYS!
I LOVE YOU, MANNY.
YOU ARE A MIRACLE WORKER.
WELL, SO TO SPEAK.
MIRACLE, SHMIRACLE.
HARD WORK,
PLUS DEGRASSI SPIRIT
EQUALS FIRST-TIME-EVER
METRO FINALS!
CHANTAY:
WITH ONLY ONE TEAM
IN OUR WAY.
SUCKS TO BE THEM!
GO DEGRASSI!
(APPLAUDING AND CHEERING)
HEY GUYS.
WOW, ARE ALL NON-CHEERLEADERS
INVISIBLE?
THEY'RE JUST EXCITED.
GOING TO THE FINALS
IS LIKE SCALING EVEREST
WITH POM-POMS.
JUST IMAGINE
IF WE ACTUALLY WIN?
IT'LL BE A DEGRASSI FIRST.
IF YOU WIN,
IT'LL BE WITHOUT JT.
IF WE WIN,
WE'LL MAKE DEGRASSI
FEEL BETTER.
IT'S OUR JOB.
YEAH.
YOU'RE RIGHT, I GUESS.
I'M JUST NO MYSELF
SINCE... YOU KNOW.
LET'S GET LATTES
AND HANG OUT.
I'M KINDA MEETING
SOMEONE, EM.
LET ME GUESS...
DAMIAN, YOUR NEW FANCY BOY
FROM THE ENEMY SCHOOL?
MRS. SANTOS:
MANUELLA?
MOM, CAN YOU
GIVE ME A SEC?
WHAT'S SHE DOING HERE?
SHE'S JUST HERE TO TALK.
DON'T BE MAD, EM,
BUT I THINK IT'S TIME
FOR ME TO GO HOME.
♪♪♪
HEY! THAT'S MINE!
REALLY?
I WORE IT ALL SUMMER.
WITH MY STRAPPY SANDALS,
I KNOW!
AND I THOUGHT
YOU WANTED ME TO STAY.
I DO!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE LEAVING,
ESPECIALLY NOW.
MY PARENTS ARE FREAKED,
OUR HOUSE IS THE CENTER
OF A MURDER INVESTIGATION.
MAYBE THAT'S WHY MY PARENTS
WANT ME BACK HOME.
DO YOU MISS
YOUR DAD'S TIRADES?
MOM SAYS HE'S WILLING TO HANG UP
THE DICTATOR CAP.
TO TRY, ANYWAY.
WHAT ABOUT THE CURFEWS
AND THE DRESS CODE?
EM,
THEY'RE MY PARENTS.
YOUR MOM AND ARCHIE
ARE GREAT,
BUT THEY'RE NOT MY FAMILY,
AND THIS ISN'T MY HOME.
I LOVE YOU FOREVER
FOR LETTING ME STAY.
IT'S TIME.
I'M GOING TO MISS YOU,
MANNY.
YOU'RE LIKE THE SISTER
I NEVER HAD.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT,
CUCKOO-BANANAS?
I'LL BE HERE CONSTANTLY!
IT'LL BE LIKE
I NEVER LEFT.
PROMISE!
YOU KNOW,
JUST WHEN YOU THINK
YOU'RE GONNA GET
TO BED EARLY,
YOU LOOK OVER YOUR ESSAY
AND HELLO,
ALL-NIGHTER.
IT DOESN'T GET ANY EASIER,
TRUST ME.
(GROANS)
MMM...
WANT SOME COFFEE?
THE LAST OF ELLIE'S
PERSONAL STASH.
ACTUALLY,
I GOT TO JET.
MEETING SOME GUYS
FROM THE TEAM.
AW, YOU AND YOUR
HOCKEY BUDDIES.
HOW CUTE!
OKAY, SO WE'LL ORDER IN
LATER THEN?
IT'S WING NIGHT!
DYLAN, YOU'VE BEEN OUT
EVERY NIGHT THIS WEEK!
WHEN DO I SEE YOU?
WE LIVE TOGETHER.
WE SEE EACH OTHER PLENTY.
BYE!
HEY MIA!
YOU'VE BEEN M-I-A
FROM THE SQUAD LONG ENOUGH.
OKAY.
WHAT DO YOU GUYS WANT?
DARCY:
RECIPE FOR SPIRIT SQUAD
SUCCESS?
TAKE ONE MIA JONES,
SHAKE AND WIN.
DID YOU GUYS LIKE
FORGET MY BOYFRIEND -
YOUR MASCOT,
JT YORK -
WAS KILLED TWO WEEKS AGO?
THANKS,
BUT I'LL PASS.
OF COURSE, MIA,
WE UNDERSTAND.
SORRY FOR ASKING.
HEY.
THEY WERE TRYING TO HELP
IN THEIR OWN BIZARRELY
DYSFUNCTIONAL WAY.
WHATEVER.
LIKE I'M GONNA TAKE PART
IN ANYTHING
LAKEHURST IS INVITED TO.
WAIT.
LAKEHURST IS COMING HERE?
WHY CAN'T THEY DO IT
SOMEWHERE ELSE?
NO KIDDING.
THEY SAY IT WAS SET UP
MONTHS AGO
AND IT'S LIKE,
TOO LATE TO CANCEL.
BUT I DON'T CARE.
I THINK WE SHOULD
DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
I THINK WE NEED TO PROTEST
OR WHATEVER.
I CAN'T.
MANNY'S MY BEST FRIEND.
BESIDES,
MAYBE IT'S A GOOD THING
IF LAKEHURST COMES HERE.
MAYBE IT'LL HELP
MEND FENCES?
A STUDENT FROM LAKEHURST
KILLED JT.
I'M NOT ABOUT MENDING FENCES
RIGHT NOW.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
MANNY:
DAMIAN AND I ARE GOING
TO THE MALL.
HE'S SO CUTE!
SEAN:
ISN'T HE FRIENDS
WITH THAT FREAK THAT KILLED JT?
MANNY:
DRAKE?
UH, NO. HE'S NEVER
EVEN TALKED TO DRAKE.
OKAY. WHATEVER.
LATER, EMMA.
SO IF MY PARENTS CALL,
YOU'LL COVER FOR ME,
RIGHT?
OF COURSE.
OR YOU COULD JUST
COME OVER TONIGHT
WHEN YOU'RE DONE
WITH DAMIAN.
JUST YOU, ME, THE COUCH
AND DR. MCDREAMY?
AND A BOWL OF POPCORN
WITH EXTRA KETCHUP POWDER?
YOU'RE ON!
HAVE FUN.
SPINNER:
OH, I GOT THIS!
I GOT IT AND... YES!
DUDE,
THAT WAS WAY TOO EASY.
COME ON.
SORRY. I'M NOT GOOD
AT THESE DRIVING GAMES.
I'M DONE.
JIMMY:
WHAT?!
AND YOU HAVEN'T EVEN TRIED
TO GET US
TO PLAY KARAOKE REVOLUTION YET,
MAN?
WHO ARE YOU?
MARCO:
WHAT'RE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I'M FINE.
I COULDN'T BE BETTER.
SERIOUSLY, MAN,
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
MARCO:
MY PROBLEM...
MY PROBLEM IS TALL,
BROAD SHOULDERED,
AND EMOTIONALLY ABSENT.
AH, MONSIEUR DYLAN.
SPINNER:
HEY.
DOES HE HAVE A MYROOMPAGE?
MARCO:
I DON'T KNOW.
HE'S JUST NEVER HERE.
AND WHEN HE IS HERE...
IT STILL FEELS LIKE
HE ISN'T, YOU KNOW?
IT HAPPENS, MY MAN.
THE HEAT COOLS.
YOU JUST GOTTA CHASE
THE ROMANCE A LITTLE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
(COUGHS)
MYROOMPAGE.
SPIN, SHUT UP.
LOOK, IT'S ALL ABOUT
THE FOUR C'S:
CANDLES, COOKING, COLOGNE
AND CHILL.
NOBODY'S IMMUNE.
DON'T WORRY.
NICE.
WHO KNEW HANGING OUT
WITH YOU AT THE MALL
MEANT P.J. SHOPPING?
WELL, I CAN'T MOOCH OFF EM
ANYMORE.
BUT DON'T GET TOO EXCITED.
YOU WON'T BE SEEING ME
IN THESE ANYTIME SOON.
HM, THAT'S COOL.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
YIKES!
I-I GOTTA GO.
I THOUGHT WE WERE GONNA
CHILL TONIGHT.
I'M SORRY,
BUT I TOTALLY PROMISED EMMA.
I KNOW, BUT...
BETWEEN YOUR SPIRIT SQUAD
AND MY STUDENT COUNCIL,
I NEVER GET TO SEE YOU.
I JUST REALLY WANT TO TALK
TO YOU, YOU KNOW?
WOW. MOST GUYS AREN'T AFTER ME
FOR CONVERSATION.
WELL,
I'M NOT MOST GUYS.
COME ON, MANNY.
HANG OUT WITH ME
TONIGHT.
(PHONE RINGS)
WHERE ARE YOU?
MANNY:
HEY, EM.
I CAME HOME AFTER
SEEING DAMIAN?
AND MY DAD'S TOTALLY BACK
IN TYRANT MODE.
EMMA:
OH, YOU POOR THING!
I'M OKAY. I JUST...
I THINK NEED TO STAY HOME
AND LET IT BLOW OVER?
EMMA:
OKAY.
WELL, I MISS YOU.
MANNY:
I MISS YOU, TOO.
BYE.
DYLAN:
SORRY, MY SEMINAR WENT LONG.
YOU COULD'VE CALLED.
DYLAN:
PHONE'S DEAD.
OH, SMELLS GREAT,
MARCO.
DID YOU MAKE STEAK?
YEAH.
IT'S MY NONA'S
BISTECCA.
YOU KNOW, SUPPOSEDLY,
IT'S THE FASTEST WAY
TO ANY MAN'S HEART.
SO LUCKILY, I CONVINCED
ELLIE TO GO TO THE MOVIES
WITH KEIKO AND SUKI.
A NIGHT ALONE.
THANK YOU.
CAUSE...
MAYBE NEXT YEAR
WE'LL HAVE A PLACE
OF OUR OWN,
YOU KNOW? JUST...
JUST ME AND YOU.
WELL, WHO KNOWS
WHAT COULD HAPPEN
BETWEEN NOW AND THEN?
MEANING WHAT?
MEANING NOTHING.
I WAS JUST TALKING.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
I GOTTA TAKE THIS.
I THOUGHT YOUR PHONE
WAS DEAD.
I GUESS IT RECOVERED POWER
OR SOMETHING.
FUNNY, HUH?
HELLO.
YEAH.
IT'S FUNNY.
EMMA:
SO HOW'D IT GO
WITH YOUR PARENTS?
MANNY:
FINE.
THAT'S FUNNY,
YOUR DAD DIDN'T SEEM FINE
WHEN HE CALLED MY HOUSE
LOOKING FOR YOU.
EM, DID YOU-
COVER FOR YOU?
OF COURSE.
I'M NOT SURE WHY,
SINCE YOU TOTALLY
BLEW ME OFF.
I'M SORRY.
I JUST REALLY, REALLY,
REALLY LIKE DAMIAN.
THINGS ARE JUST
SO GOOD BETWEEN US.
CLASS, TODAY WE'RE GOING
TO START ON "KING LEAR".
A TRAGIC TALE ABOUT SISTERS
FIGHTING FOR WHAT THEY THINK
THEY DESERVE.
HOW GOOD CAN IT BE?
YOU'VE KNOWN HIM
FOR TWO WEEKS?
COME FIND OUT.
I'M MEETING HIM
AT THE DOT AFTER SCHOOL.
BRING SEAN, TOO.
I WANT US ALL TO BE FRIENDS.
I'M NOT SURE
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE,
PLEASE, PLEASE?!
CLEARLY RESISTANCE
IS FUTILE.
THANK YOU!
YOU WON'T REGRET IT.
KWAN:
CORDELIA MIGHT HAVE THOUGHT
DIFFERENTLY.
(COMPUTER BEEPING)
MANNY:
EMMA, YOU KNOW DAMIAN.
DAMIAN, THIS IS EMMA'S
WONDERFUL BEAU, SEAN.
DAMIAN:
HEY, HOW IS IT GOING?
SEAN:
HEY...
SO, HOW ARE THINGS
AT LAKEHURST?
AH, FINE.
SEAN:
SERIOUSLY?
'CAUSE LAST I HEARD
ONE OF YOUR STUDENTS
WAS IN JAIL.
SEAN.
DAMIAN:
LOOK, MAN.
I'M REALLY SORRY
ABOUT YOUR FRIEND JT.
I MEAN,
IT'S A TOTAL TRAGEDY.
DAMIAN.
SO UH, TELL ME,
HOW'S DRAKE DOING?
I HAVE NO IDEA, MIA.
BUT HE'S YOUR FRIEND,
ISN'T HE?
NO. THAT'S NOT TRUE.
EXCUSE ME,
BUT I WENT TO LAKEHURST?
SO HOW ABOUT
YOU SAVE YOUR LIES
FOR SOMEONE WHO'LL
BUY THEM?
SO, MANNY,
WHO ARE YOU LOYAL TO?
YOUR DEAD FRIEND
OR YOUR NEW LAKEHURST CRUSH?
LET'S GO, MANNY.
NO, WAIT.
EM, A LITTLE HELP
HERE PLEASE?
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME
TO SAY?
YOU'RE SLEEPING
WITH THE ENEMY.
YOU KNOW WHAT, EMMA?
I'M SO GLAD
I'VE MOVED HOME.
BECAUSE NOW I DON'T
HAVE TO SEE YOUR MEAN,
JUDGMENTAL, STUCK-UP
LITTLE FACE ANYMORE.
FOR THE FIRST TIME EVER,
DEGRASSI HAS MADE CHEERLEADING
CITY FINALS!
COME OUT TOMORROW
AND SUPPORT THE SQUAD.
GO DEGRASSI!
I SENSE HISTORY
IN THE MAKING.
GOOD LUCK TOMORROW,
MANNY.
MANNY:
THANKS, MR. S.
IT'S ALL ABOUT
PANTHER PRIDE.
WHICH IS SO MUCH MORE
IMPORTANT THAN ACADEMICS
OR EVEN ACTUAL SPORTS.
YEAH, IF THE SCHOOL
PRINTED MONEY,
YOUR FACE WOULD BE ON IT.
AND I'D USE IT
TO BUY YOU
A BIG BOX OF SHUT UP.
UH, GIRLS?
CLASS HAS BEGUN.
OKAY. I'D LIKE TO BRING UP
A DISCUSSION TOPIC,
IF I MAY?
FINE.
WHAT IS IT, EM?
IN THE AFTERMATH OF THE DEATH
OF ONE OF OUR CLASSMATES,
WHAT DOES DEFEATING
LAKEHURST PROVE, EXACTLY?
THAT WE'RE BETTER
THAN THEM?
MANNY, OUR ENTIRE SCHOOL
IS IN MOURNING.
AND NOT ONLY THAT,
THERE'S ANGER.
THEY WANT REVENGE.
WHAT DOES THAT
HAVE TO DO
WITH THE SPIRIT SQUAD
COMPETITION?
I THINK WE SHOULD
CANCEL IT.
IT PREVENTS LAKEHURST
FROM SHOWING UP HERE,
FROM REMINDING US
OF OUR LOSS,
AND RUBBING OUR NOSES
IN IT.
AFTER ALL THE HARD WORK
THAT WE'VE PUT INTO IT?
I THINK NOT.
WE CAN MISS CHEERLEADING
ONE YEAR.
YOU GUYS ARE RIDICULOUS!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
WHAT I'M HEARING.
AND I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE TURNING YOUR BACK
ON YOUR FRIENDS.
SIMPSON:
OKAY, THAT'S ENOUGH.
THIS IS NOT THE TIME OR PLACE
FOR THIS DEBATE.
LET'S TALK ABOUT OUR NEXT UNIT:
VIDEO PODCASTING.
HEY, SO YOU GUYS GOT
A SINGLE BOY DISCOUNT?
I FOUND SOMETHING
ON HIS LAPTOP, GUYS.
HE HAS A MYROOMPAGE!
MAN, I KNEW IT!
MARCO, I TOLD YOU,
THAT THING IS
AN ONLINE ABYSS, MAN.
MARCO:
SPIN, NO.
IT WAS AN EMAIL.
AN EMAIL FROM SOME CREEP
NAMED JULIEN,
WHO HE'S MEETING TOMORROW
FOR SOME SECRET LUNCH
OR SOMETHING.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
MARCO:
YEAH.
HE'S CHEATING ON ME,
GUYS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE'S CHEATING
ON ME AGAIN!
OKAY. YOU DON'T KNOW
THAT FOR A FACT.
MARCO:
OH...
BY THIS TIME TOMORROW
I WILL.
THEY BETTER GET A TABLE
FOR THREE.
(CHEERING)
MANNY:
LET'S DO THIS FOR JT.
♪♪♪
(APPLAUDING AND CHEERING)
JUDGE:
ALL RIGHT, LET'S HEAR IT
FOR THE DEGRASSI PANTHERS!
(CHEERING)
THE FINAL SCORE
IS 9.0.
(LOUD CHEERING)
PUTTING DEGRASSI
CLEARLY IN THE LEAD.
MARCO:
HEY DYLAN.
(STAMMERING) MARCO,
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
MARCO:
WHATEVER.
WHO IS THIS?
JULIEN...THIS IS JULIEN.
JULIEN, MARCO.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
MARCO:
SORRY I CAN'T SAY THE SAME,
JULIEN.
DID DYLAN HERE
EVEN BOTHER TO TELL YOU
THAT HE'S IN A COMMITTED
RELATIONSHIP OR...?
MARCO, WHOA!
MARCO:
SHUT UP, CURLY.
BECAUSE YOU KNOW HE IS.
OR AT LEAST HE WAS.
BEFORE HE STARTED CHEATING...
AGAIN.
DYLAN:
MARCO, STOP!
JULIEN IS FROM ZURICH HC,
A HOCKEY TEAM
IN SWITZERLAND.
HE'S BEEN SCOUTING ME.
THEY WANT ME TO PLAY
FOR THEM.
YEAH.
JUDGE:
LET'S SEE IF LAKEHURST
CAN COME UP WITH AN ANSWER
TO THAT FLAWLESS ROUTINE!
♪♪♪
DANNY:
LAKEHURST SUCKS!
NOBODY WANTS YOU HERE!
LEAVE!
GO HOME, LAKEHURST!
WE CAN DO THIS.
EVERYONE: (CHANTING)
GO HOME, LAKEHURST!
JUDGE:
(INDISTINCT COMMENT)
IS THIS WHAT
YOU WANTED?
FINALLY FEELING
SELF-RIGHTEOUS ENOUGH?
EMMA:
MANNY, YOU WON.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
I SO FEEL MUCH BETTER.
I THINK I CAN ACTUALLY FEEL
THE SCHOOL SPIRIT
COURSING THROUGH MY VEINS.
YEAH,
CALL THE MEDIA.
MANNY SANTOS HAS HEALED
THE ENTIRE SCHOOL!
NOW I KNOW WHY MANNY
WAS YOUR ONLY FRIEND.
SHE'S A SAINT TO PUT UP
WITH YOUR CRAP.
TAKE A BIG STEP BACK,
LAKEHURST GUY.
DAMIAN!
HATZILAKOS:
OKAY, THAT'S ENOUGH!
THAT'S ENOUGH!
BREAK IT UP!
I SAID BREAK IT UP!
THAT'S ENOUGH!
BREAK IT UP,
I SAID!
BREAK IT UP!
ALL RIGHT,
THIS COMPETITION'S OVER!
I WANT EVERYONE TO LEAVE
AND GO HOME RIGHT NOW!
EXCEPT FOR
THE DEGRASSI STUDENTS,
WHO'RE GONNA WAIT IN THE GYM
UNTIL EVERYONE IS GONE!
MOVE IT!
NOW!
SIMPSON:
YOU BOUGHT YOURSELF DETENTION
FOR A MONTH,
AND I'M NOT SURE
THAT'S ALL!
SO?
SO, I WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT I'M NOT EXACTLY
PROUD OF YOU RIGHT NOW.
I'M SORRY.
EMMA,
YOU RUINED A COMPETITION
THAT MEANT A LOT
TO A LOT OF PEOPLE.
AND I CARE?
LAKEHURST KILLED JT!
SIMPSON:
WRONG.
ONE KID KILLED JT.
YOU CAN'T BLAME
THE ENTIRE SCHOOL FOR THAT;
IT DOESN'T MAKE
ANY SENSE!
I'M JUST MAD, OKAY?
JT IS GONE,
AND PEOPLE LIKE MANNY
WANNA PRETEND
LIKE IT DIDN'T HAPPEN.
BUT IT DID HAPPEN,
AND I'M PISSED!
WE ALL ARE,
OKAY?
INCLUDING MANNY.
BUT YOU CAN'T BLAME,
MANNY.
SHE'S NOT THE ENEMY.
EMMA,
SHE'S YOUR BEST FRIEND,
AND MAYBE IT'S TIME
THAT YOU REMEMBER THAT.
AS FAR AS SMELLS GO,
THAT'S UH...
THAT'S JUST ABOVE ROADKILL.
BUT I'M GOING
TO MISS IT.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE,
OKAY?
NOT YET.
I'M JUST...
I WAS JUST THINKING ABOUT IT.
WELL, AS LONG AS YOU'RE
THINKING ABOUT IT,
YOU JUST LET ME KNOW
WHEN YOU'VE DECIDED.
SEE? THAT'S EXACLTY WHY
I DIDN'T TELL YOU.
BECAUSE I KNEW
YOU'D FREAK OUT!
HOW COULD I NOT,
DYLAN?!
WHAT IS IT THAT YOU WANT ME
TO SAY RIGHT NOW?!
MAYBE THAT YOU'RE
PROUD OF ME?!
I AM PROUD OF YOU.
YOU KNOW THAT.
NO, I DON'T.
YOU'VE NEVER TOLD ME.
TO YOU,
HOCKEY'S MY DUMB HOBBY;
TO ME, IT'S LIFE.
DYLAN...
IF THIS IS WHAT
YOU WANT TO DO THEN...
YOU GOTTA DO IT.
BUT I WANT TO BE WITH YOU.
THIS IS AN OPPORTUNITY
KNOCKING.
FORGET KNOCKING,
IT'S BREAKING
THE DOOR DOWN.
YOU GOTTA DO IT,
OKAY?
SO THEN UM...
HOW LONG...
TILL YOU GO?
THERE'S WORK VISAS
AND STUFF TO FIGURE OUT.
MAYBE A FEW WEEKS.
WELL, THEN...
WE BETTER MAKE
THE MOST OF IT, HUH?
SO, GOT YOUR TEXT.
WHAT DO YOU WANNA
SHOW ME?
THIS.
THIS CURB RIGHT HERE.
THIS IS WHERE
IT HAPPENED.
JT DIED HERE.
EM, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO SHOW ME THIS.
NO, I THINK I DO.
BECAUSE THIS WHOLE THING
BETWEEN US,
IT ISN'T ABOUT LAKEHURST
OR DAMIAN.
IT'S ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED
RIGHT HERE TWO WEEKS AGO.
I KNOW.
MANNY...
I'M REALLY, REALLY SORRY,
FOR EVERYTHING.
I KNOW YOU ARE.
BUT EMMA YOU TURNED ME
INTO THE BAD GUY.
YOU TRIED TO HATE ME.
WELL, IT DIDN'T WORK.
ANYTHING WE'VE EVER GOTTEN
THROUGH HAS BEEN TOGETHER.
DON'T GO AND CHANGE
THE FORMULA, OKAY?
THANKS FOR THE REMINDER.