HEY,
SIGHT FOR SORE EYES.
OH, YEAH.
MMM...
I'M FREE...
ALL THANKS TO YOU.
ALL I DID WAS HELP YOU
GET A LAWYER.
YOU GOT ME A HEARING,
YOU GOT MY SENTENCE
REDUCED-
AND TWO YEARS
OF PROBATION.
WHATEVER. I'M OUT.
NOW WE CAN BE TOGETHER:
THE PERFECT GIRL
AND THE GUY
WHO DOESN'T DESERVE HER.
MAN, I MISSED YOU.
I MISSED YOU, TOO.
A LOT.
YEAH?
I ALSO MISSED BACON
DOUBLE CHEESEBURGERS,
WITH THE WORKS!
I SEE JAIL HASN'T
TURNED YOU VEGETARIAN.
SORRY.
BEEN DREAMING ABOUT IT
FOR MONTHS.
I GUESS I COULD PUT
MY CARNIVOROUS
OBJECTIONS ASIDE,
JUST THIS ONCE.
BUT FIRST,
IT'S PRESENT TIME.
IS THAT REALLY US?
EMMA:
SIX UBER LONG YEARS AGO.
SOMETIMES I WISH I COULD
STOP TIME.
GO BACK.
TO BAD HAIR,
BRACES,
AND GENERAL PUBESCENT
AWKWARDNESS?
NO THANKS.
BACK TO A TIME
WHEN YOU WERE PROUD OF ME.
♪♪♪
SIMPSON:
HOW WAS THE SOFA?
NOT TOO LUMPY?
MMMM.
NO, IT WAS GREAT.
THANKS.
I REALLY APPRECIATE
YOU GUYS
LETTING ME CRASH HERE
UNTIL I GET BACK
ON MY FEET.
SPIKE:
WHAT'RE YOUR PLANS
NOW THAT YOU'RE OUT?
ALREADY WITH
THE GRILLING?
I KNOW YOU TWO ARE MORE
THAN JUST FRIENDS, EM.
A MOTHER GETS TO ASK.
IT'S COOL.
WELL, JAY IS HOOKING ME UP
WITH HIS BOSS.
APPARENTLY THEY NEED
A NEW MECHANIC.
SIMPSON:
WHAT ABOUT SCHOOL?
HAVE YOU GIVEN ANY THOUGHT ABOUT
TO COMING BACK TO DEGRASSI?
I GOT EXPELLED.
WELL, MAYBE I COULD
TALK TO HER.
NO.
I MEAN,
NO THANK YOU.
I REALLY DON'T WANNA SET FOOT
IN THAT PLACE AGAIN.
TELL THEM ABOUT
CAMERON'S CUSTOM CARS.
SOME DAY I WANT TO OPEN UP
MY OWN SHOP.
SIMPSON:
WELL THAT SOUNDS LIKE
A FINE PLAN,
IF YOU CAN FIND
A BANK MANAGER
WHO'S WILLING TO LEND MONEY
TO A HIGH SCHOOL DROPOUT.
COUPLE THAT
WITH YOUR RECORD...
EMMA:
MOM?
IT'S HIS FIRST DAY OUT OF JAIL.
CAN YOU GO EASY, PLEASE?
SPIKE:
SORRY.
WE'RE REALLY GLAD
YOU'RE HERE, SEAN.
SIMPSON:
AND WE'RE SURE YOU'RE GOING
TO FIGURE IT ALL OUT -
YOUR LIFE, I MEAN.
YOU'VE GOT LOTS OF TIME
FOR THAT.
HEY!
HOW MANY TIMES
HAVE I TOLD YOU GUYS?
NO RUNNING IN THE HALLS!
BOTH:
SORRY, MR. PERINO.
PERINO:
SORRY?
LOOK AT ME,
LOOK AT MY SHOES!
THEY'RE RUINED!
(UNDER HIS BREATH)
SO BUY SOME NEW ONES.
ARE YOU SURE YOU WANT
TO USE THAT TONE
WITH YOUR TEACHER?
BELIEVE ME, YOU DON'T WANT ME
TO MAKE YOUR LIVES DIFFICULT.
GUYS, GO GET THE MOP
FROM THE JANITOR
AND CLEAN THIS MESS UP.
CAPICHE?
GO!
PERINO:
SMART-ASSES,
YOU KNOW?
DRIVE ME CRAZY.
JUST TRY TO REMEMBER,
THEY'RE JUST KIDS.
RIGHT, DOM?
DOM?
ENGINE RUNS ON?
IT'S A LOOSE TIMING CHAIN.
SHIMMY IN
THE STEERING...
YOU KNOW HOW TO FIX IT?
YEAH. YOU MACHINE
THE FRONT ROTORS.
JAY WAS RIGHT,
YOU KNOW CARS.
SEAN:
CARS ARE MY LIFE.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU KNOW
HOW THEY WORK,
THEY NEVER LET YOU DOWN.
SPOKEN LIKE
A TRUE MECHANIC.
TELL YOU WHAT,
WE'VE GOT A LEXUS
WITH A FAULTY AC.
GO TO WORK!
YOU, YOU MEAN I GOT IT?
I GOT THE JOB?
AND NOT FOR LONG,
IF YOU DON'T GET TO WORK.
YES SIR!
WOO!
I GOT IT, MAN!
WHAT DID I TELL YA?
AFTER YEARS OF FIGHTING,
THE SECOND WORLD WAR
CAME TO AN END
WITH THE BOMBING OF HIROSHIMA.
ONCE THE THIRD RAKE
FINALLY SURRENDERED,
THE IRON CURTAIN
DIVIDED EUROPE-
I THINK IT'S TIME THIS
PRESENTATION SURRENDERED.
AND BY THE WAY,
IT'S REICH NOT RAKE.
YOU'RE DONE.
BUT YOU CUT ME OFF.
THE ASSIGNMENT WAS
TO SUMMARIZE AN EVENT
IN YOUR OWN WORDS;
NOT BORE EVERYONE
BY COPYING THE DAMN THING
FROM YOUR TEXT BOOK.
IT'S NOT MY FAULT
HISTORY'S SO BORING.
PERINO:
WELL, IT MIGHT BE TO YOU,
BUT I'LL ASSURE YOU,
HISTORY'S A FASCINATING
DISCIPLINE.
MAYBE IT'S THE TEACHER.
WHO SAID-
WHO SAID THAT?!
MR. HAIG?
YOU GOT SOMETHING TO SAY?
DON'T BE A CLOWN:
BE A MAN AND SAY IT.
OKAY, I WILL.
CAN'T YOU CUT DANNY
A BREAK?
I MEAN,
HE'S TRYING HIS BEST.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT?
INSTEAD OF GIVING DANIEL
A ZERO FOR PLAGIARISM,
DETENTION - BOTH OF YOU.
AND TOMORROW?
I'LL LET YOU HELP HIM
REDO HIS PRESENTATION.
HEY GORGEOUS.
HOW DID YOU DO THAT?
YOU'RE A LOUSY SNEAKER.
AND EVERY CAR HAS
AT LEAST THREE MIRRORS.
MWAH!
BASED ON THE FACT
THAT YOUR FRESHLY PRESSED
WHITE SHIRT
IS NOW FORGOTTEN
ON THE TOOL BENCH,
YOU GOT THE JOB?
YOUR LITTLE PEP TALK
HELPED.
THANKS.
AND A BIG SHOUT OUT TO JAY,
WHO TOTALLY WENT TO THE MAT
FOR HIS BUD, HUH?
MY BEST FRIEND
AND MY GIRLFRIEND:
THE ONLY TWO PEOPLE
I CAN COUNT ON.
GIRLFRIEND?
OH, I GUESS NOT EVEN
JAIL TIME
CAN KEEP YOU TWO LOVEBIRDS
APART, HUH?
SEAN:
WE SHOULD ALL HANG OUT,
HUH?
CATCH UP ON OLD TIMES?
YEAH, SEAN'S NOT CAUGHT UP
ON OLD TIMES.
OLD TIMES ARE OVERRATED.
SEAN:
ALL RIGHT, WELL UM..
WELL, I'M ALL DONE HERE.
WHY DON'T I TAKE MY GIRL
OUT FOR DINNER?
GO, HAVE FUN.
I'LL LOCK UP.
DETENTION ROCKS!
I'D TAKE IT OVER
HISTORY CLASS ANY DAY.
PLUS WE GOT PERINO OFF
OUR BACKS FOR NOW.
HEY, LATER.
LATER...
HEY, MR. PERINO.
DEREK.
SOMETHING WRONG
WITH YOUR CAR?
WHY? DID YOU DO
SOMETHING TO IT?
NO. I JUST THOUGHT...
BUS STOP.
WHAT, NO FUNNY JOKES?
NOT MUCH OF A COMEDIAN
OUTSIDE OF CLASS, ARE YOU?
I'M SORRY.
DON'T PULL THAT
INNOCENT ACT WITH ME.
UH, UH... I THINK
I'M GONNA WALK HOME.
LET ME MAKE MYSELF CLEAR:
SHOW ME SOME RESPECT
OR WE'VE GOT
A SERIOUS PROBLEM.
UNDERSTOOD?
WHERE IS MY LUCKY BRA?
THE ONE THAT GIVES ME
MANNY BOOBS.
MANNY:
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
YOU'RE JUST GOING ON A DATE
WITH SEAN.
EMMA:
IT'S NOT A DATE.
IT'S THE DATE.
THE HE'S-FINALLY-BACK-
IN-MY-LIFE-
AND-EVERYTHING-
HAS-TO-BE-PERFECT DATE.
AND YOU'RE JUST TRYING
TO LIVE UP TO THE PEDESTAL
THAT HE'S PUTTING YOU ON.
THERE IS NOTHING WRONG
WITH HAVING A BOYFRIEND
WHO THINKS YOU'RE AMAZING.
MANNY:
UNLIKE THOSE SHOES,
NOBODY'S PERFECT.
LEAST OF ALL ME.
I WENT BY THE GARAGE TODAY
AND JAY WAS THERE.
THREE'S DEFINITELY NOT COMPANY.
EMMA:
JAY IS SEAN'S BEST FRIEND.
HOW DO I EVEN BEGIN
TO TELL HIM...
WHAT I DID WITH...JAY
IN THE RAVINE.
MANNY:
YOU WERE SINGLE.
IT WAS A CRAZY TIME.
WHAT WERE YOU SUPPOSED TO DO?
SIT HOME AND KNIT?
I'M NOT SURE THAT SEAN'S
GONNA SEE IT THAT WAY.
IF HE REALLY LOVES YOU,
THEN HE SHOULD.
SPINNER:
OKAY, I WILL BE BACK
IN AN HOUR TO LOCK-UP.
DON'T BREAK ANYTHING.
WE WON'T.
THANKS, MAN.
IT'S NOT MUCH,
BUT JAIL DOES A NUMBER
ON A GUY'S SAVINGS.
THE PLACE,
THE CANDLES,
THE TOFURKEY -
EVERYTHING IS PERFECT.
IT IS PERFECT.
YOU'RE PERFECT.
I'VE STILL MADE MISTAKES.
YOU'RE TALKING
TO THE MASTER OF MISTAKES.
SO YOU WON'T HOLD THEM
AGAINST ME?
OF COURSE NOT.
WHY?
IS THERE SOMETHING YOU NEED
TO TELL ME ABOUT?
NO. IT'S JUST...
STUPID.
NOTHING YOU SAY IS STUPID,
EM.
YOU'RE THE SMARTEST PERSON
I KNOW.
HEY, LAST NIGHT,
I THOUGHT EMMA
WAS DROPPING HINTS.
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
NAH.
IT'S PROBABLY NOTHING.
IF THERE WAS SOMETHING,
YOU'D TELL ME, RIGHT?
NO. FORGET IT.
YOU'RE NOT HEARING IT
FROM ME.
JAY, COME ON.
AFTER EVERYTHING
I'VE BEEN THROUGH?
I CAN HANDLE IT.
FINE,
BUT I WARNED YOU.
ALL RIGHT,
WHILE YOU WERE GONE,
EM AND I KIND OF...
FOOLED AROUND.
YOU HAD SEX?
NO! NO, NO, NO.
I MEAN,
NOT REALLY.
IT DEPENDS HOW
YOU LOOK AT IT.
I HAD MORE
THAN SHE DID.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS!
YOU AND EMMA?
DUDE, DON'T OVERREACT.
LOOK, YOU'D JUST BROKEN UP
WITH ELLIE...
YOU AND EMMA HADN'T BEEN
A THING FOR LIKE YEARS.
IT JUST KIND OF HAPPENED.
ONCE.
YOU SAID YOU COULD TAKE IT.
JUST SHUT UP, OKAY?
SHUT UP!
MAN, I'M SORRY.
I SAID SHUT UP!
SEAN...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
SHOULDN'T YOU BE AT WORK?
NEVER MIND.
DID...
DID YOU AND JAY
HAVE A THING LAST YEAR?
WHO TOLD YOU THAT?
WRONG ANSWER.
SEAN,
IT WAS TWO YEARS AGO,
RIGHT AFTER I HAD A GUN
POINTED AT MY FACE.
TO SAY THAT I WAS
SUPER-DUPER MESSED UP
WOULD BE AN UNDERSTATEMENT.
HOW COULD YOU DO THAT?
AND WITH JAY?
THE THOUGHT OF YOU TWO TOGETHER
MAKES ME WANT TO-
WHAT HAPPENED TO "I WON'T
HOLD IT AGAINST YOU"?
LOVER'S QUARREL?
I TAKE IT
WE'RE NOT COOL.
DON'T TALK TO ME.
HEY, GET ON THE LEXUS.
MR. LEYTON
IS MY BEST CUSTOMER.
UH, YOU WANT TO HAND ME
THAT RATCHET?
GET IT YOURSELF.
LOOK, IT WAS OVER
A YEAR AGO, MAN.
JUST LET IT GO.
LET IT GO?
I'M NOT GONNA LET IT GO,
ALL RIGHT?
YOU TOOK SOMETHING
THAT WAS GOOD
AND YOU RUINED IT.
JUST LIKE YOU ALWAYS DO.
RIGHT, RIGHT,
MAKE ME THE BAD GUY.
ALL RIGHT, WHATEVER HELPS
YOU SLEEP AT NIGHT.
YOU DIDN'T CARE ABOUT EMMA.
YOU USED HER.
YOU TOOK ADVANTAGE
OF HER.
I DIDN'T TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF ANYBODY.
THE TRUTH IS,
SHE CHASED ME, DUDE.
SHE DAMN NEAR BEGGED ME
TO LET HER DO IT.
(FIGHTING GRUNTS)
(LOUD THUD,
TOOLS CLATTER)
SO EACH GROUP IS NOW HOLDING
A DIFFERENT PART
OF THE HUMAN BODY.
I WANT YOU TO EXPLAIN
IN ESSAY FORM,
THE FUNCTION OF YOUR PART.
WELL,
THIS SHOULD BE EASY.
EM!
YOU'RE KILLING
JOHNNY CARCASS MAN.
HIS HEART'S NOT GONNA WORK
WITH A PENCIL IN IT!
I'M SORRY.
I WAS IMAGINING
IT BELONGS TO SEAN,
WHO FOUND OUT ABOUT
ME AND JAY,
FROM JAY.
OUCH.
HOPE YOU HAD
A SOFT LANDING
WHEN YOU FELL OFF
THAT PEDESTAL.
EASY, CUCKOO-BANANAS!
THIS IS ONE
OF THE FEW CLASSES
THAT I'M NOT FAILING.
WHAT IS IT WITH GUYS
AND THEIR RIDICULOUS
DOUBLE STANDARDS?
THEY CAN DO WHATEVER
THEY WANT,
BUT A GIRL MAKES
ONE MISTAKE
AND HER REP
IS TARNISHED FOR LIFE!
LOOK, I KNOW YOUR
LITTLE VISIT
WITH JAY IN THE RAVINE
MAY NOT HAVE BEEN ON
THE EMMA NELSON HIGHLIGHT REEL,
BUT NO GUY HAS THE RIGHT
TO JUDGE YOU,
ESPECIALLY SEAN.
DEREK, CAN I TALK TO YOU
A MINUTE?
LOOK, I JUST WANT
TO MAKE SURE
THERE'S NO MISUNDERSTANDING
ABOUT LAST NIGHT.
WELL, WHAT YOU SAID,
MR. PERINO,
IT WAS KINDA THREATENING.
DEREK,
YOU'RE A SMART KID.
I HATE SEEING YOU
WASTE YOUR POTENTIAL.
I WAS JUST TRYING
TO MOTIVATE YOU.
MORE LIKE YOU
FREAKED ME OUT.
LOOK, WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE JUST FORGET
IT EVEN HAPPENED?
YEAH, I GUESS.
OKAY.
LOOK, GO IN THERE,
AND KNOCK THAT PRESENTATION
OUTTA THE PARK, OKAY?
YOU REMEMBERED
TO CHANGE THE OIL?
THERE'S AN OIL CHANGE
CHARGE ON THE BILL,
ISN'T THERE?
I'VE NOTICED A BIT
OF PULLING LATELY.
HOW IS THE TIRE PRESSURE?
SEEMS FINE TO ME.
MAYBE I SHOULD TALK
TO YOUR BOSS.
IF YOU HAVE A PROBLEM
WITH MY WORK,
THEN YOU TAKE IT UP
WITH ME.
SO, DO WE HAVE
A PROBLEM?
I HAVE A MECHANIC
WITH AN ATTITUDE.
HEY, SEAN,
BACK OFF!
LOOK, I'M SORRY,
SIR.
HIS PROBLEM,
IT'S WITH ME.
TELL TONY I QUIT.
AND IN LATE OCTOBER,
1945,
THE UNITED NATIONS
WAS FORMED.
TO PROMOTE HUMAN RIGHTS
AND PREVENT FUTURE
WORLD WARS.
NICE JOB, YOU TWO.
OKAY, WHO'S MY NEXT VICTIM?
JACKSON, YOU READY?
BLANK STARE.
FIGURES.
DID ANYBODY NOT STAY UP
ALL NIGHT PLAYING VIDEO GAMES
AND LOOKING AT NUDIE PICTURES
ON THE INTERNET?
TAKE THE ZERO.
WHY DO YOU HAVE
TO BE LIKE THAT, SIR?
DO YOU HAVE A PROBLEM,
MR. HAIG?
I DIDN'T THINK SO.
ALL RIGHT, WHO'S GOING TO
BUTCHER ANOTHER PRESENTATION?
OR DO I HAVE TO KEEP
HANDING OUT ZEROES?
HMMM?
HEY!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
CLASSIC SEAN.
WHEN THE GOING
GETS TOUGH,
THE SEAN GETS GOING.
NOT MUCH TO STICK
AROUND FOR.
SO THE MINUTE YOU FIND OUT
I'M NOT PERFECT,
YOU RUN AWAY?
NOT PERFECT?
I'D SAY.
WELL, WHAT DO YOU EXPECT,
SEAN?
I'M A REAL PERSON.
IN THREE MONTHS,
I'LL BE OLD ENOUGH TO VOTE,
TO LEGALLY DRINK
IN QUEBEC!
I'M NOT THE GIRL
YOU KNEW
IN GRADE SEVEN
ANY MORE.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
EMMA:
I GREW UP.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD TRY IT.
MY PARENTS KICKED ME OUT
WHEN I WAS TWELVE.
ALL RIGHT?
I GREW UP IN A HURRY.
I NEEDED TO,
TO SURVIVE.
ALL YOU DID
WAS BUILD A WALL
BETWEEN YOURSELF
AND THE WORLD
TO HIDE BEHIND.
YOU LET ME DOWN.
MY PARENTS LET ME DOWN.
SCHOOL SYSTEM LET ME DOWN.
I'M JUST SAVING MYSELF
FROM MORE.
SO ALL YOUR PROBLEMS
ARE SOMEONE ELSE'S FAULT,
RIGHT?
IT'S NOT MY FAULT
YOU DID THAT TO JAY.
AND YOU'LL NEVER LET ME
FORGET IT, WILL YOU?
OKAY, LITTLE BOY,
I GIVE UP.
(UNINTELLIGIBLE ANNOUNCEMENTS
OVER BUS STATION P.A. SYSTEM)
DID HE GET FIRED?
NO, BUT UH...
MS. HATZILAKOS IS LAUNCHING
AN INVESTIGATION.
I SHOULD'VE KEPT
MY MOUTH SHUT.
NO. YOU DID THE RIGHT THING,
DEREK.
READY TO GIVE YOUR SIDE
OF THE STORY?
IS IT OKAY
IF I'M A LITTLE SCARED?
DON'T BE, OKAY?
I'LL BE IN THERE
WITH YOU.
COME ON.
THIS ISN'T SUPPOSED
TO HAPPEN.
IT DIDN'T HAVE TO.
BUT YOU MADE IT.
WHEN I CAME BACK HERE
FROM WASAGA, EMMA,
IT WASN'T FOR SCHOOL
OR TO OPEN A GARAGE.
IT WAS NONE OF THAT.
THE FUNNY THING IS,
YOU GOT WHAT YOU CAME FOR.
THEN YOU BLEW IT.
DON'T GIVE UP ON ME.
PLEASE.
I CAN'T BE PERFECT,
SEAN.
I CAN'T BE EVERYTHING
YOU NEED ALL THE TIME.
GOOD.
I WANT YOU TO CHALLENGE ME.
I WANT YOU TO CALL ME
ON MY CRAP.
SURE.
BUT IF WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
A REAL RELATIONSHIP,
YOU NEED TO SAVE YOURSELF
FROM YOURSELF SOMETIMES.
I'LL ASK TONY
FOR MY JOB BACK.
OKAY, I'LL GET
MY HIGH SCHOOL EQUIVALENCY.
I'LL START LOOKING
FOR MY OWN PLACE.
AND WHAT ABOUT US?
I WANT TO GET TO KNOW
YOU AGAIN, EM.