GUESS WHO?
UH...HEATHER SINCLAIR?
HMM, VERY FUNNY.
CLOSE YOUR EYES.
I HAVE A SURPRISE.
OKAY.
NOW OPEN YOUR MOUTH.
OH, MAN.
HERE WE GO.
NOW BLOW.
THAT'S VERY COOL!
YOU GOT ME A NEW ONE.
THANK YOU.
WELL, COACH CAN'T KEEP
THE JUNIOR GIRLS BASKETBALL TEAM
IN LINE
WITH A BROKEN WHISTLE.
THAT'S TRUE.
THAT'S THE LOGO
ON YOUR SHIRT.
YEAH.
YEAH, MARCO SAW IT
AND THOUGHT IT WOULD BE
A GOOD DESIGN SO...
ASHLEY:
AND AN OLD PICTURE OF HAZEL.
HOW CUTE.
IT WAS JUST
A CLASS ASSIGNMENT.
SO UM...
WHERE'S THE SKETCH
OF YOUR CURRENT GIRLFRIEND?
THAT'S ALL UP HERE,
BABY GIRL.
I JUST GOTTA CAPTURE IT
ON PAPER.
BELIEVE ME, ASH,
WHEN I DRAW YOU,
IT'LL BE MY MASTERPIECE.
SO UM...
WHEN CAN I SCHEDULE A SITTING
FOR MY MASTER PAINTER?
WELL, GOOD THINGS COME
TO THOSE WHO WAIT.
IT'S JUST THAT YOUR MODEL
IS STARTING TO WONDER
IF MAYBE SHE'S DOING
SOMETHING WRONG.
ASH,
WHEN THE TIME IS RIGHT,
MY CANVAS WILL BE READY.
OKAY.
BUT UH...
JUST SO YOU KNOW?
MODEL IS READY
AND WILLING.
(SIGHS) GREAT.
♪♪♪
SO DARC AND I ARE
AT THE MOVIES LAST NIGHT...
"CLOWN ACADEMY FOUR"
OUT ALREADY?
SPINNER:
HA HA.
DUDE, HOW WOULD I KNOW?
DARC AND I ROCKED
THE BACK ROW,
IF YOU CATCH MY FLOW.
YOU AND DARCY.
FOR REAL?
NO.
UM, ONLY IN MY DREAMS,
WHICH IS WHY
I'M A LITTLE BIT
JEALOUS OF YOU
AND ASH.
JEALOUS?
COME ON, DUDE.
I DON'T SEE
AN ABSTINENCE RING
ON YOUR FINGER.
ME AND YOU ARE FRIENDS,
BUT WE'RE ALSO GUYS.
ERGO, WE DO NOT TALK
ABOUT OUR SEX LIVES, OKAY?
HAIRGROW, AT LEAST
YOU HAVE SOMETHING
TO NOT TALK ABOUT.
LOOK...
THIS STAYS HERE,
ALL RIGHT?
(SIGHS)
THE MIND IS WILLING,
BUT THE BODY...
DUDE...?
SINCE THE SHOOTING,
IT JUST HASN'T BEEN THE SAME.
PHYSIO HELPS.
DOC SAYS IT MIGHT HAPPEN
ONE DAY, BUT....
THE QUESTION IS WHEN.
DUDE...
CAN YOU THINK OF ANYTHING ELSE
TO SAY RIGHT NOW?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT ELSE
TO SAY, MAN.
IT'S HARD.
NOT FOR YOU.
I DIDN'T-
SORRY. SORRY.
LOOK, MAYBE YOU'RE JUST
TOO WOUND UP.
I MEAN YOU ARE TENSE 24/7.
TAKE IT FROM
COACH SPINNER,
JUST RELAX,
LET THE GAME COME TO YOU.
DON'T FORCE ANYTHING.
MANNY!
THE BRILLIANT FUTURE SPIRIT
SQUAD CHOREOGRAPHER.
JUST THE GIRL
I'M LOOKING FOR.
KEEP LOOKING.
I ALREADY SAID NO.
BUT YOU NEVER GAVE ME
A REASON.
YOU KNOW EXACTLY WHY,
DARCY.
"IF YOUR SISTER SINS,
REBUKE HER.
IF SHE REPENTS,
FORGIVE HER."
LUKE, CHAPTER 7.
THANK YOU,
SISTER CUCKOO BANANA.
I'M TRYING TO SAY
I KNOW WE DIDN'T SEE
EYE-TO-EYE LAST YEAR-
THIS YEAR HAS BEEN
A REGULAR STARING CONTEST.
I'M TRYING TO APOLOGIZE,
OKAY, FOR LAST YEAR.
I WAS A JERK TO YOU.
I MAY BE THE CAPTAIN,
BUT THE SQUAD IS NOTHING
WITHOUT YOU.
FORGIVE ME?
PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE!
MANNY:
OKAY, OKAY.
EVERYONE MAKES MISTAKES,
I GUESS.
OH! THE TEAM IS GOING TO BE
SO BRILLIANT THIS YEAR!
MANNY:
YEAH,
AND WE SHOULD PUT A LOT MORE
FOCUS ON OUR AERIALS.
REALLY?
'CAUSE I WAS THINKING
WE SHOULD FOCUS MORE
ON OUR CHEERS.
(EXHALE)
SVETLANA:
WHOA! IMPRESSIVE TRANSFER.
YOU'VE BEEN WORKING OUT
WITHOUT ME.
AH, HONESTLY,
NOT SO MUCH.
JUST BEEN ON THE COURT
A LOT.
PLAYING PICK-UP,
COACHING.
BUSY GUY.
YEAH.
SVETLANA:
WELL, IT SURE HAS HELPED
YOUR CORE STRENGTH.
OKAY,
LET'S STRETCH
THOSE HIP FLEXORS.
THAT'S GOOD.
OKAY, JIMMY.
OTHER LEG.
UH, I'M GONNA KEEP
STRETCHING THIS ONE.
I'M JUST FEELING A LITTLE...
STIFF.
(ROCKY-ESQUE MUSIC BEGINS)
♪♪♪
I OWE YOU
A HUGE SOLID.
OKAY.
WHAT'S UP?
SOMETHING'S UP
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT, THE TEAM'S FREE THROW
PERCENTAGE?
I HAD MY LUNCHTIME
PHYSIO.
I TOOK YOUR ADVICE.
WHAT ADVICE?
IT WAS VERY RELAXING.
UH HUH...
DUDE!
WHAT...?
WOW!
OH!
NO. NO WAY!
(CHUCKLES)
AH, AND HERE COMES
JUST THE PERSON
YOU CAN SHARE IT WITH.
CATCH YOU LATER.
YEAH.
HEY.
SOMEONE'S HAPPY.
MORE THAN YOU KNOW.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE GET
OUR SUSHI ON TONIGHT?
JUST US.
A DATE?
YEAH. SURE.
SO WHAT'S THE OCCASION?
I JUST HAVE A GOOD FEELING
ABOUT TONIGHT, THAT'S ALL.
♪♪♪
IF I SEE ANOTHER
MANGLED HERKIE...
JUST ONE MORE CORPSE.
YOU KNOW, A FINAL "THANKS
BUT NO THANKS."
WHO'S MIA JONES?
MIA:
MEE-A.
I JUST TRANSFERRED HERE.
OKAY, MEE-A.
BREAK A LEG.
(MUSIC BEGINS)
WE'RE MAD!
WE'RE BAD!
WE'RE GONNA KICK YOUR ASS!
WE'LL BEAT YOU!
DEFEAT YOU!
MIGHT EVEN TRY
AND EAT YOU!
WE'RE NASTY,
WE'RE SASSY,
'CAUSE BABY WE'RE DEGRASSI!
GOOOOOOO DEGRASSI!
(HAPPY CHUCKLES)
SO, HOW ABOUT THAT
CALLBACK?
WELL, OBVIOUSLY.
THE REST OF YOU?
SHOW'S OVER.
ME AND MANNY ARE TALKING
SPIRIT SQUAD TONIGHT.
MANNY:
NOW THAT WE'VE MET YOU,
WE HAVE SERIOUS WORLD
DOMINATION TO PLAN.
GET YOUR BUTT
TO "THE DOT" AT 8:00.
MY BUTT'LL BE THERE.
ASHLEY:
IT'S BEAUTIFUL, JIMMY!
YOUR EYES AND YOUR LIPS,
AND THE WAY THE LIGHT
HITS YOUR CHEEK...
IT'S ALL BURNED
INTO MY MEMORY.
THANK YOU.
NO ASH,
YOU'RE MY NUMBER ONE.
BEFORE EVERYTHING,
IT'S ALL YOU.
YOU KNOW, I WAS HOPING
TO POSE FOR YOU SOMEDAY.
BUT LIKE YOU SAID,
GOOD THINGS COME
TO THOSE WHO WAIT.
I THINK THAT WAIT
IS ABOUT TO END.
MY PARENTS ARE
GOING OUT LATER
AND I WAS THINKING
YOU COULD COME OVER
TONIGHT.
ARE YOU SURE?
I MEAN...
WHY NOW?
LET'S JUST SAY I THINK
I'M FINALLY READY...
AND ABLE.
DARCY:
WHAT IS THE ONE TROPHY MISSING
FROM THE DEGRASSI
WALL OF GLORY?
MANNY:
METRO CHEERLEADING
COMPETITION!
AND WITH YOU, ME,
AND OUR NEW
SECRET WEAPON,
I THINK WE'RE READY
TO TAKE THIS SQUAD
TO A WHOLE NEW LEVEL.
HEY GUYS, THIS IS MY DAUGHTER,
ISABELLA.
ISABELLA,
MEET MANNY AND DARCY.
MANNY:
OH MY GOD! SHE'S ADORABLE!
THAT'S YOUR BABY?
MANNY:
SIT. SIT. SIT. SIT. SIT.
SPIRIT SQUAD,
SHMIRIT SQUAD.
I HAVE TO HEAR ALL ABOUT
THIS LITTLE ANGEL.
HI.
MY NAME'S MANNY.
AND YOU ARE JUST SO CUTE.
WHAT?
WOW!
YOU LOOK...
WOW.
EVERYTHING OKAY?
YEAH, YEAH.
I'M FINE.
DON'T STOP.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THERE'S NOTHING
YOU CAN DO.
YOU SHOULD PROBABLY
JUST GO.
JIMMY:
ASHLEY...
ASH, I'M SORRY ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED LAST NIGHT.
OR IN MY CASE,
WHAT DIDN'T HAPPEN.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU SHOULD APOLOGIZE.
BUT NOT FOR THAT.
JIMMY, WHEN A GIRL THROWS
HERSELF AT YOU?
YOU DON'T KICK HER OUT.
I'M SORRY.
I JUST...
I COULDN'T DEAL.
LOOK, SO IT WAS
A BAD IDEA.
JIMMY,
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
WE CAN TOTALLY LIVE
WITHOUT EVER...
YOU KNOW.
OKAY.
WE CANNOT LIVE
WITHOUT "YOU KNOW."
I'M GOING TO MAKE
THIS WORK.
THERE ARE METHODS.
I'VE DONE RESEARCH.
THERE'RE MEDICAL OPTIONS.
I KNOW.
THAT'S WHY I'VE MADE
A DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENT.
5, 6, 7, 8!
HEY! ARE YOU READY?!
ARE YOU READY
TO SHOUT IT OUT!
BLUE AND GOLD!
WE ARE DEGRASSI!
THAT WAS GREAT.
YOU'RE NOT MAKING
THIS DECISION EASY.
UH, MIA? UP FRONT.
DROP THE POMS.
LET'S SEE
A HEAL STRETCH.
SURE.
HOW ABOUT
A BACK WALK OVER?
DARCY:
TOE TOUCH?
NEEDS WORK.
AND WOULD IT
KILL YOU TO SMILE?
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
SHE'S OUR GIRL,
DARCY.
FINE.
GO BACK TO YOUR CHEERS.
MANNY:
OKAY! WE'RE GOING TO TRY
SOMETHING A LITTLE DIFFERENT...
JIMMY:
I WAS INTO IT.
SHE WAS INTO IT.
WE WERE IN THE MOMENT
AND UH...NOTHING.
ANY OTHER TIME
YOU HAD AN ERECTION?
WERE YOU IN
THE MOMENT THEN?
I'M NOT ATTRACTED
TO MY PHYSIOTHERAPIST.
IT JUST...
JUST HAPPENED.
I UNDERSTAND.
JIMMY, IT'S GOOD THAT
YOU HAD SOME ACTIVITY.
IT JUST SEEMS
A LITTLE INVOLUNTARY.
YOU KNOW, NOT THERE
WHEN YOU NEED IT,
THERE WHEN YOU DON'T.
LIKE WAITING FOR A BUS.
YEAH. YEAH.
LOOK, THERE ARE OPTIONS
FOR ERECTILE DYSFUNCTION:
IMPLANTS, PUMPS.
JIMMY:
IS THAT-
IS THAT ALL THERE IS
THOUGH?
I HAVE TO TURN INTO
SOME SEX ROBOT,
WIND ME UP
AND WATCH ME GO?
WELL, IMPLANTS AND PUMPS,
THOSE ARE DOWN THE ROAD.
FIRST THINGS FIRST,
WE'RE GONNA GET YOU
ON SOME MEDICATION.
AS IN THE PILL THAT GETS
THE MIDDLE-AGED PEOPLE
DANCING IN THE STREETS?
WELL, IT CAN BE EFFECTIVE
IN SOME CASES, YEAH.
WHAT IF IT'S NOT,
THOUGH?
I MEAN, I...
I JUST DON'T WANT TO BE
A VIRGIN
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
DON'T BROADCAST IT.
LOOK,
IF THIS DOESN'T WORK?
WE EXPLORE THE OTHER OPTIONS.
YOU TAKE ONE,
GIVE IT AN HOUR.
AND REMEMBER TO RELAX,
OKAY?
SHOULD I PUT
SOME MUSIC ON?
NO, I LIKE THE QUIET.
LET'S SEE HERE.
SAYS SIDE EFFECTS MAY INCLUDE
INCREASED TENSION,
MUSCLE SPASMS,
UPSET STOMACH,
DIARRHEA.
GREAT.
NOW I'M IN THE MOOD.
(THEY CHUCKLE)
WELL, IT SAYS IT COULD TAKE
OVER AN HOUR.
IT'S BEEN ALMOST TWO.
WELL, DID YOU HAVE
A BIG LUNCH OR ANYTHING?
NO, I'M STARVING MYSELF.
I JUST WANTED TO MAKE SURE
THIS'D WORK.
MAYBE YOU JUST NEED TO RELAX.
SEE, ISN'T THAT NICE?
JIMMY:
YEAH.
(TURNS TV ON)
ASHLEY:
WHAT'S WRONG?
JIMMY:
JUST FORGET IT.
STRIKE TWO.
MS. HATZILAKOS: (OVER P.A.)
LISTEN UP, DEGRASSI.
TONIGHT, THE JUNIOR GIRLS
BASKETBALL TEAM
PLAYS THEIR FIRST GAME...
I SAY FORGET
ABOUT CHEERS.
IF WE WANNA WIN
THE METRO COMPETITION,
IT NEEDS TO BE MORE
ABOUT DANCE,
GYMNASTICS, STUNTS,
PYRAMIDS...
YEAH, THAT'S ASSUMING
I'M EVEN ON THE SQUAD.
CAPTAIN DARCY'S BEEN GIVING ME
THE FREEZIE-CHILLS.
SHE'S A BIT UPTIGHT,
BUT SHE WANTS TO WIN
AS BAD AS I DO.
(EXCITED CHATTER)
NO. NO!
DARCY!
SOMEONE'S MISSING
FROM THIS LIST!
EVERYONE WHO DESERVES
TO BE ON THE TEAM
IS THERE.
YEAH, RIGHT.
NOBODY DESERVES
TO BE ON THE SQUAD
MORE THAN MIA DOES.
SORRY, MANNY.
MY DECISION'S FINAL.
♪♪♪
YOU'RE GOING DOWN,
DEGRASSI!
WHOA! THEY'RE BIG.
SIZE ISN'T EVERYTHING,
JT.
DARCY:
WHAT IS THIS?
MANNY:
YOU CAN'T KEEP HER
OFF THE TEAM.
YOU KNOW
I DESERVE THIS.
OR IS THERE SOME SORT OF
NO-SINGLE-MOMS POLICY?
MIA, YOUR BABY IS
A HUGE RESPONSIBILITY,
AND, WELL,
SO IS SPIRIT SQUAD.
I'M SORRY.
MANNY:
WHEN MY NEW MANICURE
MEETS YOUR FACE?
THEN YOU'LL BE SORRY.
MIA:
DARCY, ISABELLA HAS DAYCARE.
SHE CAN BE TAKEN CARE OF
WHENEVER I'M AT PRACTICE.
I CAN DO BOTH.
HOW CAN I BELIEVE SOMEONE
WHO'S MADE SUCH ENORMOUS
LIFE MISTAKES?
MISTAKES?!
UNLESS YOU GOT KNOCKED UP
ON PURPOSE.
IN WHICH CASE,
YOU'VE GOT EVEN BIGGER ISSUES.
NIC:
WHOA!
DEGRASSI CHICKS CAN'T STOP
THROWING THEMSELVES AT ME.
MIA JONES?
SO DEGRASSI'S PICKING UP
ALL THE OTHER SCHOOL'S
TRASH NOW?
HEY!
DID YOU EVER FIGURE OUT
WHO THE FATHER IS?
♪♪♪
TOBY:
WHOA! WHOA! STOP!
♪♪♪
STAY RIGHT HERE.
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?!
JT:
MAN, TWO WEEKS DETENTION!
TOBY:
I KNOW.
NOW I GOT TO FIND
A NEW PANTHER MASCOT.
JT:
WHAT CAN I SAY?
WHEN MY SCHOOL NEEDED ME,
I POUNCED.
TOBY:
YEAH, WELL, THAT'S GREAT.
BUT NOW WHO'S GOING
TO ENTERTAIN THE FANS?
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT IT.
NIC:
HEY, DEGRASSI NERDS!
IF I WERE YOU,
I'D SLEEP WITH ONE EYE OPEN.
THIS ISN'T OVER.
DETENTION NEVER
SOUNDED SO GOOD.
FORFEITING -
NOT THE SAME AS LOSING.
SURE.
WHATEVER.
YOU GOING HOME?
BECAUSE WE STILL HAVE THAT
MEDIA EMERSION ASSIGNMENT.
WE COULD JUST HANG OUT,
DO SOME HOMEWORK.
NO LINGERIE.
NO PILLS.
NO PRESSURE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
COME OVER TONIGHT
AND GET YOUR STUFF.
I CAN'T DO THIS.
MIA'S IN WITH MS. H.
GETTING LECTURED.
I HOPE YOU'RE HAPPY.
SHE'S A TEENAGE MOTHER,
MANNY,
WITH A VIOLENT STREAK.
AND SOMEHOW YOU HAVE
THE RIGHT TO PUNISH HER?
SHE HAS BETTER THINGS TO DO
THAN WAVE POM-POMS.
AND YOU'RE JUST SO CONCERNED
FOR HER DAUGHTER.
SPARE ME.
I'M OFF THE SQUAD.
PROBLEM SOLVED.
WELL, THEN I QUIT.
AND LET MEAN GIRL
TAKE OVER?
DON'T BE STUPID.
THEY NEED YOU.
THIS IS YOURS.
JIMMY:
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU CAN KEEP IT.
I DON'T WANT IT.
ASHLEY:
I THOUGHT YOU WANTED
TO BREAK UP.
JIMMY:
I DON'T.
WE JUST MAY AS WELL
DO IT NOW.
IT'S GONNA HAPPEN
EVENTUALLY.
WHY WOULD YOU SAY THAT?
WHAT?
DID YOU GET YOUR PALM READ?
TAROT CARDS?
LOOK...
IF I CAN'T DO THIS,
HOW LONG ARE YOU REALLY
GONNA STICK AROUND?
SIX MONTHS?
A YEAR?
WHY DO GUYS ONLY THINK
ABOUT ONE THING?
I'M THINKING ABOUT
A LOT OF THINGS.
WHAT IF I CAN'T,
EVER?
THEN WE DEAL WITH IT.
WHO CARES?
I CARE, ASHLEY!
I'M A VIRGIN.
DO YOU GET IT?
DO YOU KNOW WHAT
IT FEELS LIKE
TO KNOW THAT YOUR EPITAPH
IS GONNA READ
"JIMMY BROOKS:
CRIPPLED VIRGIN."
I MEAN...
I CAN'T WALK.
I CAN'T RUN.
I CAN'T DANCE.
I CAN'T PLAY BASKETBALL.
I CAN'T EVEN...
I CAN'T EVEN
MAKE LOVE TO YOU.
BUT YOU CAN, JIMMY.
YOU CAN.
NO, I CAN'T.
SAYS WHO?
WHO SAYS SEX HAS TO BE
JUST ONE THING.
JIMMY...
THERE'RE A LOT OF WAYS
TO MAKE LOVE.
I KNOW, ASH.
I KNOW.
BUT...
THIS ISN'T JUST
ABOUT SEX.
THIS IS ABOUT WHETHER
I CAN DO
ALL THE THINGS
THAT I WANNA DO.
THIS IS ABOUT WHETHER
I CAN BE
THE MAN THAT I WANNA BE.
YOU'RE THE MAN THAT
I WANT YOU TO BE, JIMMY.
ISN'T THAT ENOUGH?
YEAH.