JESSE: (READING)
"A DAY IN THE LIFE
OF CRAIG MANNING."
OUCH.
THAT'S YOUR TITLE?
ENCOURAGING AS ALWAYS,
BOSSMAN.
WOULD'VE THOUGHT
WRITING ABOUT CRAIG
WOULD'VE CAME
EASY TO YOU.
NOT THIS MORNING.
NOT AFTER I FOUND
A BAGGIE OF COKE
ON HIS BEDROOM FLOOR.
COLOUR ME NOT SURPRISED.
HAD A FEELING
HE WAS DOING SOME RAILS.
WHAT?!
HOLD ON,
THOSE DRUGS WEREN'T CRAIG'S.
THEY BELONGED TO HIS GIRLFRIEND,
TWEEDLEDUM.
AH, WELL METHINKS TWEEDLEDUM
HAS BEEN SHARING HER STASH
WITH TWEEDLEDEE,
I.E. CRAIG.
I.E. SHUT UP.
CRAIG DOES NOT DO COKE.
YOU KNOW THIS
FOR A FACT?
NO, I DON'T,
BUT WHAT I DO KNOW
IS THAT I HAVE TO KEEP HIM
AWAY FROM MANNY.
LONG ENOUGH TO
MAKE HIM REALIZE
THAT SHE'S A TOXIC
INFLUENCE.
I HAVE A NEW JOB FOR YOU.
AND FOR THIS ONE,
YOU OWE ME.
"TAKING BACK SUNDAY"
ARE IN TOWN
AND GUESS WHO'S
INTERVIEWING THEM TODAY?
ELLIE:
JESSE, YOU'RE THE BEST!
HEY, MR. MANNING.
UM, YOU'RE RIGHT
ON TIME.
READY FOR YOUR
BIG INTERVIEW?
ACTUALLY, I DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN RIGHT NOW.
I GOTTA GO CLEAN OUT
JOEY'S GARAGE.
OH, I'LL COME WITH.
I CAN HELP.
UH FROSH,
YOU DO HAVE
THE "TAKING BACK SUNDAY"
INTERVIEW TODAY AND...
(QUIETER)
IT'S WAY MORE IMPORTANT
THAN THIS CRAIG THING.
ELLIE:
BOTH ARE IMPORTANT,
BOTH WILL GET DONE.
WILL NOT DISAPPOINT,
PROMISE.
♪♪♪
ELLIE:
SO I'VE BEEN LISTENING
TO YOUR DEMO.
THERE'S A RECURRING THEME
OF HOME.
SOMETHING YOU'RE
PREOCCUPIED WITH?
AH, WHEN YOU'RE
A MUSICIAN,
HOME IS WHEREVER
YOUR GUITAR IS.
(STIFLES A LAUGH)
OKAY,
BUT THAT'S FUNNY,
'CAUSE YOU LEFT
YOUR GUITAR HERE.
I LEFT A LOT
OF THINGS HERE...
AND A LOT OF PEOPLE.
(SIGHS)
I ALWAYS THOUGHT
WHEN I COME BACK
THEY'LL ALL BE WAITING,
YOU KNOW, WITH...
BIG OPEN ARMS
AND A SMILE.
AND ARE THEY?
NOPE.
JOEY'S SELLING THIS PLACE
AND MOVING TO CALGARY.
ALL MY OLD FRIENDS
HAVE MOVED ON AND YOU?
OH, I'M HERE.
YEAH, NO, NOT REALLY.
YOU'RE BUSY.
YOU'VE GOT UH...
YOU KNOW,
UNIVERSITY,
JOURNALISM,
JESSE.
YEAH, BUT I'M STILL HERE,
CRAIG.
AND I ALWAYS WILL BE.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
OH, I HAVE TO GO.
CRAIG:
INTERVIEW'S OVER?
NO, UM...
COME WITH ME.
YOU CAN MEET THE BAND.
IT'LL BE FUN.
DANNY:
SO I'M THINKING
OF CHANGING MY NAME.
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF
"LL COOL D"?
STANDS FOR LADIES
LOVE COOL DANNY.
DEREK:
(SNORTS)
IF ANYONE DESERVES THAT NAME
IT'S ME.
BASED ON WHAT,
YOUR FANTASY LIFE?
(BOYS TALKING QUIETLY
AS THEY APPROACH)
DEREK:
DUDE, THAT WAS A BLIND DATE.
NIC:
WHAT'S THAT STENCH?
DE-LOSERS FROM
DEGRASSI.
LISTEN UP, DORKS.
LAKEHURST HAS DECLARED WAR
ON YOUR SCHOOL.
WHY?
NIC:
ASK YOUR FRIEND
THE MASCOT -
JT YORKE.
YOU KNOW HIS NAME?
FRIEND OF YOURS?
WELL, YOU TELL JT
WE'RE GONNA STOMP HIS ASS.
MAN:
HEY! WHAT'S GOING ON?
LET'S GO!
SO SORRY I'M LATE!
HI, HI!
HI, ELLIE NASH,
FRIENDLY NEIGHBOURHOOD
MUSIC CRITIC.
OH HI, I'M ADAM,
YOUR FRIENDLY
NEIGHBOURHOOD SINGER.
AND I DON'T KNOW,
THE BAND WE GOT, LET'S SEE,
FRED, MARK, ED
AND MATT.
HEY GUYS,
NICE TO MEET YOU.
ADAM:
SO YOUR EDITOR'S BEEN
RAVING ABOUT YOU.
HE SAID YOU'RE
HIS BEST WRITER.
I SAID YOU WEREN'T
MY WORST WRITER.
SAY, CRAIG,
WHY DON'T YOU GO GET A COFFEE,
LET ELLIE DO HER INTERVIEW,
OKAY?
SURE.
I'M GONNA GET GOING, EL.
I'LL GO SEE WHAT
MANNY'S UP TO.
UM, WAIT!
CRAIG, I WANT YOU
TO MEET THE BAND.
GUYS, THIS IS CRAIG MANNING,
LOCAL SINGER/SONGWRITER
EXTRAORDINAIRE!
HEY, ADAM.
HEY, IT'S GREAT
TO MEET YOU GUYS.
"MAKE DAMN SURE"
IS ONE OF MY FAVES.
ACTUALLY, I EVEN
DO IT IN MY SET.
REAL DIFFERENT VERSION,
STRIPPED-DOWN, ACOUSTIC.
OH, I WOULDN'T MIND
HEARING THAT.
RIGHT NOW?
ADAM:
YEAH, UM YOU WANT
TO GRAB A GUITAR.
JESSE:
SORRY TO INTERRUPT, GUYS,
BUT UH...
ELLIE, WE DO HAVE
A DEADLINE, SO...
YEAH, THERE'S ALWAYS TIME
FOR A SONG THOUGH, RIGHT?
GO ON.
(PLAYFUL CHATTER)
YES, YOU ARE!
NO, I'M NOT!
OH YEAH,
YOU WANT TO GO?
(PLAYFUL GIGGLES)
TOBY:
HOPE YOU'RE ENJOYING
THAT BURRITO, JT.
IT'S GOING TO BE
YOUR LAST.
JT:
WHAT? ARE THEY'RE TAKING
THESE BAD BOYS OFF THE MENU?
NO, BUT LAKEHURST IS GOING
TO TAKE YOU OFF THE MENU -
THE MENU OF LIFE.
DANNY:
WE KINDA GOT BEAT UP
THIS MORNING
BY NIC AND THE LAKEHURST CREW.
DEREK:
NIC'S DECLARED WAR ON DEGRASSI.
BUT SPECIFICALLY,
ON YOU.
JT:
WHY?
WHY ME?
WAS IT BECAUSE OF THAT STUPID
BASKETBALL BRAWL?
THAT WAS NOTHING.
IT'S NOT BECAUSE
OF THE BRAWL.
IT'S BECAUSE
YOU'RE DATING ME.
LET'S JUST SAY
NIC'S THE JEALOUS TYPE.
THAT PSYCHO WAS YOUR EX?
OH, SO NOW IT MAKES SENSE.
THIS IS ABOUT YOU, MIA.
YOU'RE GONNA GET US ALL KILLED!
OH YEAH, TOBY,
WAY TO MAKE HER FEEL GOOD.
(SARCASTIC LAUGH)
OH, I'M SORRY.
I JUST HAVE THIS NEUROTIC
AVERSION TO BEING MURDERED.
LAKEHURST IS NOT GOING
TO HURT ANYBODY.
I'M GONNA HANDLE IT.
OH, YEAH,
WHAT'RE YOU GONNA DO?
TICKLE THEM TO DEATH?
DEREK AND DANNY:
(SNICKER)
ELLIE:
SO HOW'S THE TOUR GOING?
MATT:
GREAT, GREAT.
EXCEPT FOR WHEN ADAM
HIT ME IN THE HEAD
WITH A MICROPHONE,
BUT THAT'S ANOTHER STORY.
ANGEL:
ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
WE'VE GOT TO GO RECORD
STATION I.D.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA,
SHE HASN'T INTERVIEWED
ADAM YET.
ANGEL:
AH, SORRY,
WE'RE OUT OF TIME.
SEE YOU BACK AT THE OFFICE,
FROSH.
SO GET THIS...
THE BAND HAS A BREAK
IN THEIR SET TOMORROW NIGHT.
GUESS WHO ADAM INVITED
TO SING FOR THE CROWD?
CRAIG, THAT'S AMAZING!
THIS COULD BE HUGE
FOR MY CAREER, ELLIE,
AND IT'S ALL
THANKS TO YOU.
YOU'RE...
YOU'RE AWESOME.
I GOTTA GO.
ELLIE:
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA,
WHOA, WHOA, WAIT.
WHAT ABOUT OUR INTERVIEW?
COME ON,
I GOTTA GO SEE MANNY.
I GOTTA TELL HER
THE GOOD NEWS.
(SIGHS)
BOY:
ABOUT TIME.
NIC:
LET'S GO.
YOU GOT A LOT OF NERVE
SHOWING UP AT OUR SCHOOL.
WHATEVER.
IS THIS STUPID WAR
ABOUT ME DATING YOUR EX?
I DON'T CARE ABOUT MIA.
SHE'S JUST A DUMB SLUT.
EASY, MASCOT BOY.
YOU WANT A WAR?
YOU GOT IT.
MEET ME IN THE TUNNEL,
TOMORROW AT 5:00.
MIND IF I BRING
MY FRIENDS?
NO.
'CAUSE I'LL BRING MINE.
OOH...
THE CHESS CLUB?
I'M SCARED.
SORRY...
ABOUT BRINGING CRAIG
TO THE INTERVIEW.
IT WAS UNPROFESSIONAL.
THAT'S OKAY.
WHERE IS CRAIG
ANYWAY?
THOUGHT YOU'D BE
INTERVIEWING HIM.
HE BAILED ON ME.
WENT OFF TO PARTY
WITH LITTLE MISS MANNY.
PROBABLY JONESING
FOR COKE.
NICE.
LOOK, MY BEST FRIEND USED
TO BE AN ADDICT, OKAY?
I CAN SEE THE SIGNS
PRETTY CLEARLY.
YOU CAN'T SEE
ANYTHING CLEARLY,
NOT WHEN IT COMES
TO CRAIG.
JEALOUS MUCH?
I AM NOT JEALOUS
OF SOME FAILED
SINGER/SONGWRITER LOSER
THAT YOU'RE STILL
CRUSHING ON.
IT'S PATHETIC.
THAT IS WRONG
ON SO MANY LEVELS.
JESSE:
NO, YOU KNOW WHAT'S
REALLY WRONG?
THE FACT THAT CRAIG
KEEPS CRAPPING ON YOU,
AND YOU KEEP GOING
BACK FOR MORE!
HEY.
WHY DON'T WE GO
OUT TONIGHT?
SEE A MOVIE,
GRAB A BITE?
CRAIG:
OR WE COULD STAY IN,
'CAUSE I HAPPEN TO HAVE
SOME PARTY FAVOURS.
YOU KNOW, AFTER WE DID
THAT LAST NIGHT
I FELT SICK,
HORRIBLE.
I NEVER WANT
TO DO IT AGAIN.
CRAIG:
COOL. THAT'S YOUR CHOICE.
MANNY:
BABY-
LOOK, THIS HAS BEEN
ONE OF THE BEST
ONE OR TWO DAYS
OF MY LIFE.
DON'T RUIN IT.
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
I'M ABOUT TO RUIN ONE
OF THE BEST
"ONE OR TWO DAYS
OF YOUR LIFE".
I'M DUMPING YOUR ASS,
CRAIG.
BYE.
(DOOR SLAMS)
ELLIE, JUST THE GIRL
I WANTED TO SEE.
I HAVE A PRESENT
FOR YOU.
ME AND CRAIG
JUST BROKE UP.
WHAT?
YEAH, HE HAS A LITTLE BIT
OF A DRUG PROBLEM
IF YOU HAVEN'T NOTICED.
(SARCASTIC LAUGH)
I THINK YOU HAVE THAT
THE WRONG WAY AROUND.
I FOUND YOUR "LOOT BAG"
AND I KNOW THE COKE
WAS YOURS.
CRAIG TOLD ME.
CRAIG LIED.
THAT'S WHAT DRUG ADDICTS DO,
ELLIE.
GOOD LUCK WITH HIM.
(DOOR SLAMS)
QUESTION OF THE EVENING:
WHO'S MORE PATHETIC?
YOU FOR LYING TO ME
ABOUT THE DRUGS?
OR ME FOR BELIEVING YOU?
IS THAT A TRICK
QUESTION?
THIS IS FUNNY?
WAIT, JU-
DON'T BE MAD.
PLEASE.
JUST TELL ME THE TRUTH,
FOR ONCE.
OKAY, I...
I STARTED IN VANCOUVER,
BUT I'M NOT AN ADDICT.
DRUG CLICHE NUMBER ONE.
I CAN STOP, ELLIE,
ANYTIME I WANT.
DRUG CLICHE NUMBER TWO.
LOOK, WHAT DO YOU
WANT ME TO SAY?
THAT I'VE GOT A PROBLEM?
YEAH, I HAVE A PROBLEM.
GREAT, I SAID IT.
WHAT NOW?
YOU USED TO COME TO GROUP
THERAPY WITH ME, REMEMBER?
DR. KENDRICK IS GREAT.
HE CAN HELP YOU.
SO JUST COME,
TOMORROW, OKAY?
IF YOU PROMISE TO STOP
BEING MAD AT ME.
(MUSIC PLAYS ON STEREO)
DANNY:
RUMBLE TODAY AT FIVE.
DON'T MISS OUT ON THE LAKEHURST
ASS KICKING ACTION!
WHAT, ARE YOU
GUYS CRAZY?
DON'T ADVERTISE IT.
YOU SAID WE HAD
TO FORM A POSSE.
YEAH, I GOT A COUPLE GUYS
ON THE BASKETBALL TEAM.
THEY'LL PROBABLY
BACK US UP.
OH GOOD.
JIMMY:
HEY.
I HEARD YOU'RE ORGANIZING
SOME BATTLE AGAINST LAKEHURST.
JT:
UH, YEAH.
YOU IN?
JIMMY:
SURE.
I'LL ROLL OVER THEIR FEET
WITH MY CHAIR.
NO, I'M NOT IN.
YEAH, ME NEITHER,
'CAUSE THIS IS
A SERIOUSLY BAD IDEA.
LOOK VIOLENCE
IS A VICIOUS CYCLE.
YOU GUYS ARE GOING
MAKE A SITUATION GO
FROM BAD TO WORSE.
DANNY:
WHATEVER, BUDDHALICIOUS.
GO PICK A FLOWER.
WE'RE GONNA KICK SOME ASS.
THIS ISN'T LIKE YOU,
JT.
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE
SMARTER THAN THIS.
WELL, I THOUGHT YOU'D
OFFER TO JOIN ME.
I'M NOT GONNA FIGHT
LAKEHURST.
YOU'RE BEING AN IDIOT.
YOU'RE BEING A COWARD!
SOME BEST FRIEND.
CAN'T WE WAIT JUST...
JUST A LITTLE LONGER?
I'M SORRY, ELLIE.
LET'S GET STARTED.
GET THE DOOR,
PLEASE.
FIRST OF ALL,
I WANT TO THANK...
(WORDS BECOME MUFFLED)
MIA:
JT.
MIA.
WHAT'RE YOU DOING
HERE?
NOT ONLY IS THIS
REALLY STUPID,
IT'S INCREDIBLY
IMMATURE.
NO, IT'S NOT.
I'M BEING A MAN,
MIA.
THIS IS-THIS IS HOW MEN
HANDLE THINGS.
I BROKE UP WITH NIC
FOR A REASON, JT.
IF YOU DO THIS,
MAKES NO DIFFERENT
THAN HIM.
OKAY.
EVERYBODY...
LET'S GO HOME.
BOY:
LET'S GO, GUYS.
HEY, DEGRASSI NERD.
TOBY:
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
DOING HERE?
YOUR FRIENDS
DIDN'T SHOW.
WHERE YOU GOING?!
(STRUGGLES)
(GRUNTS)
(VIOLENT PUNCH)
(VIOLENT KICK)
(ANOTHER KICK)
♪ A long night spent with your
most obvious weakness ♪
♪ You start shaking
at the thought ♪
♪ You are everything
I want ♪
♪ 'Cause you are everything
I'm not ♪
♪ We lay, we lay together ♪
♪ Just not too close,
too close ♪
♪ How close is close enough? ♪
♪ We lay, we lay together ♪
♪ Just not too close,
too close ♪
♪ I just wanna bring you down
so badly ♪
♪ Well, I trip over everything
you say ♪
♪ I just wanna bring you down
so badly ♪
♪ In the worst way ♪
♪ My inarticulate store bought
hangover hobby kit ♪
♪ It's all shook up ♪
♪ And it says,
"You are, you are so cool..." ♪
ELLIE, HI.
ABOUT GROUP THERAPY,
LISTEN UH...
SOMETHING CAME UP.
HEY!
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
EITHER YOU STOP NOW
OR I CALL JOEY
AND TELL HIM ABOUT THIS.
AND THIS,
THIS WILL ALL END.
THE TOURING,
THE MUSIC CAREER -
FINISHED.
COME ON, WHY WOULD YOU
DO THAT TO ME?
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE,
ALL RIGHT?
I CAN'T.
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE.
BECAUSE WHY?
YOU KNOW WHY, CRAIG.
UM...
YOU KNOW,
SO DON'T MAKE ME SAY IT.
I LOVE YOU, ELLIE.
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
SO DON'T MAKE ME STOP.
PLEASE.
I NEED IT.
DON'T CALL JOEY.
YOU BASTARD!
HOW COULD-
HOW COULD YOU PLAY
WITH ME LIKE THAT?
ELLIE,
I'M-I'M SORRY.
WHAT DO YOU WANT
ME TO SAY?
NOTHING!
IT'S ALL GOING
TO BE LIES!
YOU'LL SAY WHATEVER
IT TAKES
TO GET YOUR HANDS ON THIS,
WON'T YOU?
GOD!
♪ In the worst way ♪
♪ Worst way! ♪
(CROWD CHEERS WILDLY)
ADAM:
ALL RIGHT, WE'LL BE BACK UP
IN A SECOND TO FINISH,
BUT BEFORE THAT,
STICK AROUND
BECAUSE WE HAVE SOMEBODY
SPECIAL HERE
TO PLAY A SONG FOR YOU
AND I THINK YOU'RE GOING
TO LIKE IT.
SO LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
PLEASE WELCOME TO THE STAGE
MR. CRAIG MANNING.
(CROWD CHEERS)
(ROCK STAR YELP)
HEY!
UH, HERE'S A SONG I WROTE
A WHILE BACK
WHEN I FIRST LEFT TORONTO
FOR VANCOUVER.
IT'S CALLED "DROWNING".
(STRUMS GUITAR)
♪ I fly too close
to the sun ♪
♪ I chase the whale
on the run ♪
♪ but I'm,
I'm jumpin" from mountains ♪
♪ and I'm jumpin' from skies ♪
♪ I try realize my size ♪
♪ What you say
when you're me? ♪
♪ What you feel
when you see? ♪
(TAPERS OFF SINGING)
HOW COULD THEY
DO THIS TO YOU?
IF THERE'S ANYTHING
YOU NEED,
LET US KNOW.
OKAY,
TOBEY-TOBES?
OH, I THINK YOU GIRLS
HAVE DONE ENOUGH.
THANKS.
HEY, TOBES, HERE.
LOOK, I'M SO SORRY.
IT'S OKAY, JT.
NO, IT'S NOT.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
LOOK AT THE BRIGHT SIDE.
MAYBE,
MAYBE IT'S OVER.
MAYBE BEATING SOMEONE UP
IS ALL THEY EVER WANTED.
WELL, MAYBE,
BUT, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DON'T CARE.
THEY'RE GONNA PAY
FOR WHAT THEY DID TO YOU.
TOBY:
LOOK, VIOLENCE FOR VIOLENCE
ONLY LEADS
TO THE DEEPENING
OF THE DARKNESS
IN DEEPEST DARK-
WAIT, THAT DIDN'T
COME OUT RIGHT.
LOOK, JUST PROMISE ME
YOU'LL LET THIS GO.
PROMISE ME, JT.
OKAY, I PROMISE.
(GRUNTS IN PAIN)
OH, SORRY.
ELLIE:
YOU'RE ON THE 11:00 AM
TO CALGARY.
JOEY'S WAITING FOR YOU
AT THE AIRPORT.
I GUESS YOU'RE HERE
TO MAKE SURE
I GET ON THE PLANE,
RIGHT?
NO, UM...
MR. SIMPSON IS.
I'M LEAVING.
CRAIG:
ELLIE, I KNOW I MESSED UP.
BADLY.
BUT I AM GLAD
FOR ONE THING.
I WAS FINALLY ABLE
TO BE HONEST WITH YOU.
I MEANT WHAT I SAID.
AND I'VE FELT THAT WAY
FOR A LONG, LONG...
NO, JUST DON'T,
DON'T, JUST...
IT'S BESIDE THE POINT.
YOU NEED HELP.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
I'M GOING INTO REHAB
OR WHATEVER,
BUT WHEN I GET OUT,
MAYBE WE COULD...
(TEARFUL)
GOODBYE, CRAIG.
(CRYING)