EMMA:
I JUST LOVE IT HERE
AND THE VIEW IS AMAZING.
MR. STONE:
MY PLEASURE.
I'M GLAD YOU COULD
HELP US CELEBRATE
PETE'S SEVENTEENTH.
IT'S AN IMPORTANT DAY
TO HAVE PROPER
FRIENDS AROUND.
OH DAD,
THE GUY MADE A MISTAKE.
THAT'S NOT YOUR CAR.
YOU'RE RIGHT, SON,
IT'S NOT.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
YOU'RE KIDDING.
NOPE. NOW I KNOW YOUR BIRTHDAY'S
NOT FOR TWO DAYS...
HERE, HERE, HERE.
BUT I WANTED YOU TO HAVE IT
FOR THE FIRST DAY OF SCHOOL.
YOUR WELCOME.
HERE, WHY DON'T YOU
TAKE IT FOR A SPIN?
♪♪♪
I CAN NOT BELIEVE
THIS CAR'S MINE.
I'M THE LUCKIEST GUY
IN THE WORLD.
MAN:
EMMA?
SEAN?
ONE SEC.
HEY, COME ON.
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
I MOVED BACK.
I'M WITH JAY NOW.
EASY BROKEBACK MOUNTAIN.
HE MEANS HE'S SLEEPING
ON MY COUCH.
(CLEARS THROAT)
OH PETER,
THIS IS SEAN.
SEAN, THIS IS PETER.
MY BOYFRIEND.
OH.
HOW'S IT GOING, MAN?
SO YOU'RE "THE" SEAN.
GUESS SO.
(CLEARS THROAT)
WELL...
SEE YA GUYS
AT SCHOOL TOMORROW.
YOU'RE BACK AT DEGRASSI?
♪♪♪
JT:
WELL, HERE WE ARE.
THE FIRST DAY OF OUR LAST YEAR.
THANK JEHOVAH.
LIBERTY:
A YEAR THAT'LL BE
THE CROWNING ACHIEVEMENT
OF MY ACADEMIC CAREER.
THINK I HEAR SOMEONE'S
VALEDICTORIAN SPEECH
COMING ON.
CHECK OUT OUR NEW CLASSMATES.
SERIOUS MATHLETES.
EH, GOOD THING THOUGH,
'CAUSE WITH MARCO GONE,
I GOTTA COPY MY TESTS
OFF SOMEONE.
LOOKING FINE,
MS. KERWIN.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
SOMEBODY'S GOTTA
MAKE UP FOR SPINNER.
HI, QUEEN BEE.
SPARE SOME HONEY?
FOR MY KING?
ANY TIME.
AFTER BEING AWAY AT BIBLE CAMP
THE WHOLE SUMMER,
I AM SO OVER IT.
READY TO TAKE
THIS PLACE OVER, SPIN?
READY AS I'LL NEVER BE.
(LAUGHS)
YO, DUDES,
CHECK OUT MY WHIP!
STUDENT:
YEAH, WHATEVER, MAN.
I MEAN, MY CAR.
PRETTY FLY, HUH?
OH,
I THOUGHT A NEW RIDE
WOULD GET ME SOME PROPS
AROUND HERE.
MAYBE IF YOU DIDN'T
SAY PROPS?
KIDDING.
I'M GONNA GO SAY HI
TO SEAN'S BICEPS.
CHECK OUT MR. STUD.
DEGRASSI'S BIG TIME
HEARTTHROB.
PLEASE.
SEAN'S GOT A TIRE IRON
FOR A BRAIN.
PETER:
YEAH, WELL,
THE GIRLS LIKE BICEPS,
NOT BRAINS.
YOU SHOULD KNOW,
YOU DATED HIM FOR YEARS.
WELL, I COULDN'T
CARE LESS NOW.
NOT WHEN I'VE GOT BRAINS,
BICEPS, BEAUTY,
AND A HOT CAR
ALL ROLLED UP IN ONE.
I MADE YOU AN EARLY
BIRTHDAY PRESENT.
YOU MADE THIS FOR ME?
UH HUH.
THANKS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
OH, THAT I'M GORGEOUS,
PERFECT,
AND YOU'LL LOVE ME FOREVER?
YES, YES, AND YES.
MR. SIMPSON:
WELL AS I LIVE AND BREATHE,
SEAN CAMERON.
MR. SIMPSON.
IT'S REALLY GOOD
TO SEE YOU, MAN.
MR. SIMPSON:
HEY, WELCOME BACK, STEPHANIE.
HEY, DID YOU HAVE
A GOOD SUMMER?
JOHN, JOHN,
NICE TO SEE YOU.
SOCIAL EVENT PLANER?
WHAT HAPPENED TO THE REAL
EMMA NELSON?
SHE'S THINKING OF
THE REAL PETER STONE.
YOU KNOW HOW HARD IT IS
FOR PETER TO MAKE FRIENDS,
SO I FIGURED
IF HE GOT MORE INVOLVED,
IT'D BE EASIER.
SEAN:
JUST LAST YEAR, YOU KNOW.
FINISHING UP,
THAT KIND OF THING.
YOU'RE SO NOT
LISTENING TO ME.
SEAN CAMERON...
THE BENCH PRESS HAS BEEN
SO, SO GOOD TO YOU.
I'M GONNA TELL CRAIG
YOU SAID THAT.
FEEL FREE
IF YOU CAN EVER
GET HIM ON THE PHONE.
SIMPSON:
ALL RIGHT.
LET ME START OFF BY SAYING
WELCOME TO TWELFTH GRADE.
THIS IS THE START
OF THE MOST IMPORTANT YEAR
FOR YOU GUYS
IN YOUR HIGH SCHOOL LIVES.
YOU'RE YOUNG ADULTS NOW
AND IT'S ALL ABOUT
RESPONSIBILITIES
AND CHOICES,
BUT MOSTLY...
MARCO:
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT
"MEDIEVAL LIT:
MONSTERS IN THE MIST"?
MMM, NO.
LET'S NOT TAKE
ANY COURSES
WHERE THEY MAKE US READ
"BEOWULF".
OOH! HOCKEY ART.
DYLAN'S I PRESUME.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW,
IF YOU MOVED IN
WE COULD OUT-VOTE HIM
ON MATTERS OF DECOR.
DYLAN:
I HEARD THAT.
(CHUCKLES)
ELLIE:
AND WHEN IT COMES TO MATTERS
OF LEAVING
THE TOILET SEAT UP?
THANK YOU, NO.
THE RESIDENCE WAITING LIST
SHALL REMAIN MY FRIEND.
PAIGE:
OKAY, I KNOW MARCO
LIKES FOUR SUGARS,
AND ELLIE TAKES
HER COFFEE BLACK,
LIKE HER SOUL.
OH, HOW I'LL MISS
YOUR CUTTING JIBES
WHEN YOU LEAVE
FOR BANTING, PAIGE.
NOT THAT I'M COUNTING
THE DAYS,
BUT WHEN?
CAN YOU COUNT TO TWO?
AND TO THINK
THAT NO ONE HAS THOUGHT
OF THROWING ME
A GOING AWAY PARTY.
HINT, DOUBLE HINT.
DYLAN:
UH, MARCO?
SOMEONE'S SUPPOSED
TO BE MOVING IN HERE
IN TWO DAYS.
HINT, DOUBLE HINT.
FUNNY 'CAUSE SOMEONE'S
ALSO SUPPOSED TO BE
DECIDING ON UNIVERSITY
COURSES WITH ME.
OKAY, MOM, DAD?
RELAX.
I'M ALL OVER IT,
OKAY?
MMM. AW.
SWEET MOTHER MARY.
THIS IS MUD!
YEAH, YOUR NEW ROOMIE
IS JAVALY-CHALLENGED.
HAVE A COOKIE.
MANNY:
SHE'S PRETTY GORGEOUS, HUH?
YEAH, SHE IS.
(LIGHT PUNCH)
OW!
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT IT.
EMMA'S FINALLY
IN A GOOD PLACE
AND SHE DOESN'T NEED YOU
RUINING IT.
SEAN:
(LAUGHING)
I WASN'T PLANNING ON IT.
I'M SERIOUS.
LAST YEAR WAS NON-STOP
EMMA DRAMA-RAMA.
THIS YEAR SHE NEEDS TO BE
100% STRESS FREE.
GOT IT?
EMMA:
PETER, IT DOESN'T FIT.
YEAH, I GOT IT.
PETER:
YEAH, BUT IT HAS TO.
WHOA! HEY, PETER!
HOLD ON A SECOND!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU CAN'T FORCE
THE FILTER IN
LIKE THAT.
YOU'LL NEVER GET
A PROPER SEAL.
JUST TRUST ME.
THIS IS WHAT I DO.
I WAS JUST TRYING
TO MAKE IT GO FASTER.
IT'S ALREADY PRETTY FAST.
HOW MUCH FASTER
DO YOU WANT?
AS FAST AS
HUMANLY POSSIBLE.
YOU KNOW,
IF YOU WANT,
I CAN HOOK YOU UP
WITH REAL MODS.
YEAH, THAT'D BE ALL RIGHT.
YEAH? SWEET.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, IT ALL STARTS
WITH MORE FUEL.
ONCE WE DO THAT,
WE CAN UP YOUR BOOST.
THIS IS WHAT YOU NEED.
NOW I HAVE TO HEAD
TO WOODBRIDGE,
SO MEET ME LATER.
WHERE THE STREET RACES ARE.
EMMA:
THE ILLEGAL STREET RACES.
EMPHASIS ON ILLEGAL.
COME ON,
IT'S JUST A LITTLE FUN.
WHATCHA GOT AGAINST THAT?
EMMA:
NOTHING.
I'M ALL ABOUT FUN.
I LOVE FUN.
IN FACT,
IF FUN WERE PEOPLE,
I WOULD BE CHINA.
OKAY.
(HARD ROCK TUNE PLAYING)
♪♪♪
JAY:
POINDEXTER'S IN
HIS DADDY'S CAR
AND HE'S WAVING
AT US.
EXPLAIN.
THAT'S PETER,
EMMA'S BOYFRIEND.
THAT'S NOT HIS DAD'S CAR,
THAT'S HIS.
WE'RE GONNA MOD IT.
WHY?
WHY WOULD WE DO THAT?
WHAT'S THAT PHRASE?
"KEEP YOUR FRIEND'S CLOSE,
YOUR ENEMIES CLOSER?"
WHATEVER, ALEX.
(LIGHT WHAP)
JAY:
OH LORD
FORGIVE MY SINFUL THOUGHTS.
HEY.
EMMA'S MY FRIEND,
ALL RIGHT?
AND YOU'RE GOING
TO STAY CLEAR OF HER.
GOT IT?
YO, I GOT THE PART.
HOPE IT FITS.
SEAN:
LOOKS GOOD.
LET'S TRY IT OUT.
PETER:
YEAH, I ASKED THE GUY
AT THE STORE
IF IT WOULD WORK
WITH THE TURBO CHARGER.
HE SAID YEAH,
BUT I THINK HE WAS TALKING
ABOUT THE TURBO CHARGER
FROM THE '05.
THAT'S TOTALLY DIFFERENT,
RIGHT?
SEAN:
IT MIGHT BE.
SPINNER:
AH, PICKING UNIVERSITY COURSES.
MUST BE NICE.
ELLIE:
DON'T GET TOO EXCITED.
"FOUCAULT..."
MARCO:
"FOO-CO."
ELLIE:
"FOO-CO" AND POST-MODERNIST
MARXIST THEORY."
WHAT DOES THAT EVEN MEAN?
DO NOT ASK ME.
(BELL RINGS OVER DOOR)
PAIGE:
MARCO.
PARTY IDEAS POUR...
VOUS!
UH, PAIGE?
I DO HAVE A FEW THINGS
I'M TRYING
TO JUGGLE HERE.
I KNOW, SILLY,
WHICH IS WHY I DID
SOME PRE-SELECTING
POUR VOUS.
HENCE THE PANOPLY
OF PRETTY STICKY FLAGS.
YOU'RE GOING TO BANTING,
NOT TO WAR.
SUE ME FOR WANTING
TO GET EVERYONE TOGETHER
ONE LAST TIME.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
ONE LAST TIME?
UM, YOU, ME, ELLIE -
WE'RE ALL STARTING NEW LIVES.
WHO KNOWS?
WE NEED ONE LAST
GOODBYE HURRAH.
OKAY, OKAY, SO ALL THEN
PREPARE THYSELF
FOR THE MOST ROCKINGEST
BON VOYAGE PARTY IN HISTORY!
YAY! AND DID I MENTION
HOW MUCH I LOVE PINATAS?
(MOTORCYCLE VROOMS BY)
SEAN:
SO WITH THE LARGER INJECTORS
YOU'LL HAVE MORE FUEL
AND WE'LL ABLE
TO RUN MORE BOOST.
SHOULD GIVE YOU ABOUT
20 PERCENT.
SOUND GOOD?
VERY. THANKS.
(WRENCH CLANKS ON ENGINE)
WHOA, DUDE,
DO YOU KNOW HOW MUCH
THIS CAR COSTS?
I KNOW WHAT I'M DOING,
POINDEXTER.
YEAH, WELL,
YOU COULD'VE FOOLED ME.
WHAT IS THIS CALLED?
JAY:
WHY DON'T YOU DO IT YOURSELF
THEN?
WEIRD PLACE
FOR KNITTING.
EMMA:
IT'S MY NEW OBSESSION.
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY
ABOUT IDLE HANDS...
THE DEVIL'S PLAYTHINGS.
THAT'S WHY I LIKE
FIXING CARS.
KEEPS ME BUSY.
SEAN AND CARS.
THERE'S NOTHING NEW THERE.
GUESS SOME THINGS
NEVER CHANGE, HUH?
SOME THINGS DO.
TAKE FOR EXAMPLE YOU.
IF SOMEONE TOLD ME
I WOULD EVER SEE
SEAN CAMERON
BACK AT DEGRASSI...
I JUST WANT MY DIPLOMA.
THERE ARE HIGH SCHOOLS
IN WASAGA.
THERE ARE A LOT OF THINGS
THINGS YOU'RE RUNNING FROM?
I'M RUNNING TO SOMETHING.
A YEAR FROM NOW,
I'M GOING TO OPEN
MY OWN SHOP IN T.O.
"CAMERON'S CUSTOM CARS."
LET ME LOOK.
I THINK IT COULD BE
REALLY AMAZING.
IF YOU'VE HEARD PEOPLE SAYING
THEY'RE TERRIFIED
OF ADVANCED CALCULUS,
VECTORS ARE THE REASON WHY.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
HAVING SAID THAT,
WE'RE GOING TO GET
THROUGH THEM.
(LIGHT COLLISION)
(CHUCKLES)
LATER, EMMA.
LATER, SEAN.
WHAT?
DYLAN:
WITH THESE LIGHTS COMING DOWN
IT'LL FEEL MORE AUTHENTIC
AND EVERYTHING.
IT KIND OF A LIVENS UP
THE SPACE, YOU KNOW?
SO, WE'LL LET YOU KNOW.
GIRLS:
(CHINESE ACCENTS)
THANK YOU.
(GIGGLE)
WOW, UH...
DID I JUST WALK INTO
A GWEN STEFANI VIDEO?
HERE.
I NEED COFFEE, BAD.
I'VE BEEN UP ALL NIGHT PACKING.
GREAT.
WHEN ARE THE MOVERS
COMING?
UH... TOMORROW.
AND THEY'RE NOT MOVERS.
IT'S ME, MY DAD
AND UNCLE LOUIE.
YOUR DAD?
MARCO:
YEAH, MY DAD.
PAYING MOVERS?
THAT'S DEL ROSSI FAMILY
SACRILEGE.
SO IS LETTING
HIS PRIZED SON
MOVE AWAY FROM HOME,
BUT YOU CONVINCED HIM
TO DO THAT.
YEAH, AFTER I CONVINCED HIM
YOU'RE JUST A FRIEND.
BARELY A FRIEND.
A DISTANT ACQUAINTANCE
I BARELY TALK TO.
SO I SHOULDN'T
ASK YOUR DAD
FOR HIS PERMISSION
TO MARRY YOU.
SERIOUSLY, DYLAN.
THIS HAS TO LOOK LEGIT,
OKAY?
WE WENT OVER THIS.
I GOT IT.
OKAY.
T-MINUS EIGHT HOURS
TILL PAIGE'S SEND-OFF.
(CLAPS HANDS)
WHERE DO WE KEEP
THE PINATA STRING?
HEY, ALMOST FORGOT.
WHEN I HAD LUNCH
WITH SEAN YESTERDAY,
WE TALKED A LOT
ABOUT YOU.
MMM HMM.
OH YEAH.
HE WENT ON AND ON
ABOUT HOW GORGEOUS
YOU LOOK.
REALLY?
WHAT DID HE SAY?
(LIGHT SLAP)
OW!
MANNY,
WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
(INCREDULOUS EXHALE)
(SIMPERING)
"LATER SEAN.
I SURE LOVE YOU."
THAT IS SO NOT FAIR.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S
NOT FAIR?
ME AND PETER GOING THROUGH HELL
LAST YEAR WITH YOU
AND YOU FINALLY
BEING BETTER
AND THEN WHAMMO,
YOU STEP RIGHT INTO
THE SEAN CAMERON
MAN-TRAP.
I AM NOT IN A MAN-TRAP.
EM, IT'S OKAY,
I GET IT.
THE BICEPS,
THEY WORK THEIR MAGIC.
THEY'RE NOT MAGIC
AND THEY'RE NOT WORKING.
BESIDES, WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
SEAN'S INTERESTED ANYWAY?
PETER, WOW,
JUST CREEPING UP ON ME
EVER SO SILENTLY.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
OH THANKS.
SEAN SAID HE'D TAKE US
TO THE RACES TODAY.
YOU DOWN?
UH, NO.
BECAUSE WE NEED
TO HAVE
A TRES ROMANTIC
BIRTHDAY DATE.
JUST YOU AND ME,
DINNER, A MOVIE,
AND NO CAR TALK.
PETER:
SO I ASKED HIM IF I SHOULD PUT
AN ADDITIVE IN THE FUEL
TO MAKE THE CAR
GO FASTER,
AND HE SAID I HAVE
A HIGH COMPRESSION ENGINE.
YEAH, I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANT EITHER
UNTIL HE EXPLAINED IT.
UM, BASICALLY,
A HIGH COMPRESSION ENGINE
PUTS OUT MORE POWER.
YOU WITH ME?
NOT EVEN THE TEENIEST BIT,
BUT I'M GLAD YOU AND SEAN
HIT IT OFF.
YEAH, ME TOO.
HE'S A REALLY COOL GUY, EH?
HE'S BEEN SCHOOLING ME ON CARS,
YOU KNOW.
HE KNOWS EVERYTHING.
YOU LIKE HANGING OUT
WITH HIM, HUH?
YEAH, KINDA.
BUT WHATEVER.
WHAT MOVIE ARE WE GONNA SEE?
HOW ABOUT...
"PETER TAKES HIS GIRLFRIEND
TO THE RACES: PART DEUX."
SERIOUSLY?
YOU'RE THE BEST!
(REGGAE MUSIC PLAYS)
♪♪♪
ASHLEY:
♪ COME ON AND JOIN ME ♪
♪ COME PARTY TIME ♪
♪ JUST STEP
INTO MY SOUL SHINE ♪
OH! THANK YOU
FOR COMING!
I'LL SEE YOU SOON,
OKAY?
BYE.
HEY, PAIGE.
I GUESS I'M THE ONLY ONE
NOT SORRY TO SEE YOU GO.
I KNOW YOU HAD SEX
WITH SPINNER LAST YEAR.
THOUGHT YOU WERE ABOVE
BEING A LOW-GRADE HO.
GUESS I WAS WRONG.
SWEETIE?
I WOULD LOVE TO INDULGE
YOUR NEED TO RUIN MY PARTY
WITH A FULL ON CATFIGHT,
BUT I'LL PASS.
SAVE THE DRAMA
FOR HIGH SCHOOL, HON.
I'M MOVING ON.
ASHLEY:
♪ CAN YOU FEEL IT ♪
UH, MARCO?
(MUSIC ENDS AWKWARDLY)
POP, WHAT'RE YOU
DOING HERE?
WE'RE NOT MOVING
TILL TOMORROW.
WELL, LOUIE COULD ONLY
GET THE VAN TODAY.
BUT I'M IN THE MIDDLE
OF A PARTY!
I KNOW.
HEY EVERYONE!
HEY, THIS IS MARCO'S
UNCLE LOUIE.
LOU, EVERYONE.
HI EVERYBODY!
ALL:
HI UNCLE LOUIE.
HEY, MR. DEL ROSSI,
LET ME GIVE YOU A HAND
WITH THAT.
MR. DEL ROSSI:
NO, IT'S OKAY. I GOT IT.
DYLAN:
REALLY, I CAN.
NO, NO, REALLY.
HONEST, I REALLY-
(FURNITURE FALLS)
AH! AH!
POP!
MR. DEL ROSSI:
OH MY BACK.
(GROANS)
IT'S THROWN.
(GROANS IN PAIN)
JUST LEAVE ME, MARCO.
PRETEND I'M NOT HERE.
PRETEND THERE'S NOT A 200 POUND
ITALIAN MAN
LYING ON MY FLOOR?
UM, EVERYBODY, JUST HELP ME
GET HIM TO THE COUCH.
(CARS ZOOM AROUND)
(HIP HOP MUSIC BLARES)
IT'S "THANK YOU" WATER
FOR BEING NICE TO PETER.
YEAH,
HE'S ALL RIGHT.
THAT CHILLS YOU OUT,
HUH?
'CAUSE I TALKED TO MANNY
AND UH...
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN
LAST YEAR?
I HAD SOME ISSUES,
BODY ISSUES.
YOU MEAN LIKE...
YOU CAN SAY IT:
ANOREXIA.
BUT I'M BETTER NOW.
I MEAN...
I'M WORKING ON IT.
IT'S DAY-BY-DAY,
BUT THIS HELPS.
AND IF YOU'RE NICE
I'LL KNIT YOU A SOCK,
BUT JUST ONE.
OKAY, EVERYBODY!
JAY AND PETER
TO THE START LINE!
EMMA:
EXCUSE ME, JAY,
IF YOU PUT HIM UP
TO THIS...
JAY:
HEY, THIS WAS JOHNNY
HARDTOP'S IDEA.
IT'S A RAG-TOP,
IDIOT.
(LAUGHS)
WHATEVER, DORK.
LOOK, DO YOU WANT
TO RACE OR NOT?
PETER:
JUST FROM ONE END OF THE LOT
TO THE OTHER.
DON'T MAKE ME PLAY
THE BIRTHDAY CARD,
'CAUSE I WILL!
CROWD:
(WHISTLING AND CHEERING)
(BLUE CAR REVS)
(ORANGE CAR SKIDS TO HALT)
ALEX:
OKAY!
AROUND THE LAMPPOST
AND DOWN TO THE FENCE.
READY?
GO!
(JAY'S CAR SQUEALS AWAY)
(PETER'S CAR ROARS AFTER)
(CAR SKIDS)
HOLY-!
(PETER'S CAR SKIDS TO HALT)
(JAY'S CAR SCREECHES)
(POLICE SIRENS WAIL)
HE'LL BE FINE.
C'MON, LET'S GO.
LET'S GO.
COME ON!
(SIRENS CONTINUE TO WAIL)
(CARS SCREECH AWAY)
PAIGE:
FRESHLY BREWED,
BY MOI,
MICHALCHUK FAMILY BARISTA.
NICE PARTY, HUH?
GOD, LASTED ALL OF WHAT?
45 MINUTES?
HON, IT WAS SUPPOSED
TO BE FUN.
IF YOU TURN EVERYTHING
INTO A STRESS FEST,
YOU'RE NOT GONNA
MAKE IT.
I KNOW.
IT'S JUST...
HIGH SCHOOL WAS A CAKEWALK
COMPARED TO WHAT'S NEXT.
HOW AM I GONNA
POSSIBLY DEAL?
HON, YOU HAVE DYLAN,
AND THE REST OF US.
IT'S NOT LIKE
WE'RE DISAPPEARING.
OH REALLY?
YOU'RE MOVING FIVE ZILLION
MILES AWAY.
ELLIE'S VANISHING INTO REZ.
SPINNER AND JIM ARE STILL
STUCK AT DEGRASSI.
CRAIG'S IN VANCOUVER!
AND...
I'M MOVING IN WITH DYLAN.
MY FIRST LIVE IN BOYFRIEND.
IT'S...
IT'S NOT EXACTLY
FAMILIAR TERRITORY.
(AMUSED CHUCKLE)
NOT FOR ANY OF US, HON.
WE ARE ALL LOOKING
INTO THE BIG VOID
OF THE UNKNOWN
AND IT'S A LITTLE BIT SCARY.
A LOT A BIT
FOR ALL OF US.
GET A GOOD LONG DISTANCE PLAN,
OKAY?
I'LL MISS YOU TOO,
HON.
(CAR RUMBLES BY)
(CAR SQUEAKS TO HALT)
EMMA:
(LAUGHS)
AND JUST WHEN I THOUGHT
LIFE MIGHT GET BORING.
SORRY ABOUT THE COPS.
A LITTLE DRAMA
KEEPS LIFE INTERESTING.
NOT TOO MUCH DRAMA
I HOPE?
I'M MESSING THINGS UP
FOR YOU, EM.
RIGHT? I MEAN COPS,
STREET RACES...
IT'S BAD NEWS.
OKAY,
I'M BAD NEWS.
I JUST...
I GOTTA STOP HANGING OUT
WITH YOU.
I DON'T WANT YOU TO STOP.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
(CLICKS PHONE CLOSED)