DYLAN:
OH YEAH!
WOW, THAT'S AWESOME!
THANKS, BUDDY.
IS THAT BAKED BRIE?
PHENOMS!
ONLY THE BEST
FOR MY DARLING BRO
ON THE OCCASION
OF HIS MOVING TO SWEDEN.
YOUR BRAIN'S CLEARLY ALREADY
REDECORATING MY BEDROOM.
IT'S SWITZERLAND, PAIGE.
AS IN ZURICH?
MARCO:
YEAH,
AS IN 6497
KILOMETERS AWAY.
JAMES, I HEAR YOU'RE LOOKING
FOR A NEW MANAGER.
SOMEONE TO WHIP
SQUATCH DESIGNS INTO SHAPE?
JIMMY:
YES, MARCO TOLD YOU?
OKAY, GOOD.
SO WE CAN GET TOGETHER AND TALK
ABOUT IT TOMORROW MORNING?
RESUME'S PRINTED
AND AT THE READY!
ELLIE:
THANK YOU FOR IMPLYING
THAT I'M BORING.
I WASN'T IMPLYING
THAT YOU'RE BORING
JUST BECAUSE YOU DON'T
LIKE DANCING, OKAY?
CAN WE NOT FIGHT
ABOUT THIS NOW?
IT'S EMBARRASSING.
SO YOU'RE MOVING IN,
EH?
A FUNKY DOWNTOWN ADDRESS
TO GO WITH MY,
HOPEFULLY, NEW JOB.
CHING-CHING.
SO WHERE IS THE LOVELY
CARLA TONIGHT?
POTTERY CLASS.
YEAH, MY GIRLFRIEND DITCHED ME
TO MAKE A BOWL.
WELL, AT LEAST YOU HAVE
SOMEBODY.
I, HOWEVER, HAVE BEEN WALKING
THROUGH A ROMANTIC DESERT.
AND MY FEET ARE TIRED.
WELL, DON'T LOOK AT ME
TO RUB 'EM.
BUT I'M SURE WE COULD FIND
A HOT GUY OR TWO
TO WARM UP
YOUR COOL AUTUMN NIGHTS.
WELL, CHEERS TO THAT,
DEAR CUPID.
(GLASSES CLINK)
♪♪♪
PAIGE MICHALCHUK.
JESSE... STEFANOVICH.
YOU'RE THE ONE
I SPEAK TO
ABOUT PUTTING AN AD
IN THE CORE?
FOR JIMMY AND SPINNER'S STORE?
YEAH, YOU'RE LOOKING
AT THEIR NEW MANAGER.
CONGRATS.
UM, THESE ARE OUR RATES.
YES. UH... RATES.
FUNNY THING -
THERE IS A MINOR ISSUE
OF CASH AT PRESENT.
NAMELY THAT WE ARE
LACKING IT.
AS ISSUES GO?
FAR FROM MINOR.
WELL, WHAT IF I TOLD YOU
THAT IN LIEU OF CASH,
OUR DESIGNER JIMMY BROOKS
WILL DESIGN T-SHITS
FOR THE CORE?
I'M SURE YOU COULD USE THEM
FOR PROMOTIONS.
AND ONCE WE FIX
OUR CASH-FLOW ISSUE,
WE'RE GOING TO PRESENT
CONCERTS BY LOCAL BANDS,
UNDER THE SQUATCH BANNER.
CORE COULD CO-SPONSOR.
GOOD IDEAS.
GREAT IDEAS.
THANK YOU.
SO, DO WE HAVE A DEAL?
COUNT ON IT.
SIMPSON:
THANK YOU FOR THAT INCISIVE
TREATISE
ON CELEBRITY FACELIFTS.
NEXT CLASS;
LIBERTY AND EMMA.
OUCH.
I HAVEN'T EVEN STARTED.
DIDN'T KNOW LAZY
WAS IN YOUR VOCAB.
NOT LAZY.
JUST DISTRACTED.
DON'T TELL ME:
TOO MANY LATE NIGHT SESSIONS
AT CASA CAMERON?
KEEP A SECRET?
SEAN AND I SEAN ARE...
TAKING THINGS
TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
MAYBE YOU DON'T
REALIZE?
BUT YOU'VE TOLD ME
THIS BEFORE.
MAYBE YOU DON'T
REALIZE
THAT THIS TIME
I MEAN IT.
WOW!
YOU'RE NOT MESSING AROUND,
SISTER.
SO,
I HOPE YOU'RE READY?
TODAY'S THE FIRST EPISODE
OF "PROJECT PAIGE".
MY LIFE IS A REALITY
TV SHOW?
IN YOUR CASE IT'S
THE BACHELORETTE.
AND WE ARE LOOKING
FOR GUYS, HEY?
NOT THE OTHER FLAVOUR?
GUYS WILL DO,
THANK YOU.
I LIKE THEM CUTE,
FUNNY, WORLDLY,
OH, AND TO FILL OUT
A VINTAGE ROCK TEE JUST SO.
SOUNDS DELISH,
IN A HETERO KINDA WAY.
THING IS, PAIGEY,
YOU GOTTA KEEP IT CAJ.
DON'T GET ATTACHED.
TO ANYONE.
PLAY THE FIELD.
BE A PIMP.
OH, I'M THE MADDEST
OF PIMPS.
AND HERE COMES MY DATE.
SPINNER?
CUTE? FUNNY?
WORLDLY?
LOSE THE LESBIAN
FILTER, HON.
HE IS CUTE
AND FUNNY.
IT'S TWO OUT OF THREE.
GIVE MY BEST
TO DEAR CARLA!
AND WHY IS IT EVERY TIME
I BRING SOMETHING UP -
A-A JOKE, A STORY IDEA,
ANYTHING -
YOU JUST SHOOT IT DOWN?
YOU CAN BE SO NEGATIVE,
ELLIE.
GUESS SO.
YOU GUESS SO?
TAURUS MUCH?
WHATEVER.
I DON'T WANT TO ARGUE
ANYMORE!
IT'S ALL WE'VE DONE
FOR WEEKS.
(SIGHING HEAVILY)
ARGUING WAS BETTER
THAN THIS.
NOT TO MENTION ALL
THE MOVIES AND DINNERS,
AND LAUGHS
WE USED TO HAVE.
THAT'S WHY WE NEED
TO END THIS.
BEFORE IT RUINS
WHAT'S LEFT OF US.
SEE YOU
AT THE STAFF MEETING?
PHARMACIST:
HERE YOU GO.
THESE HAVE "SENSUAL"
IN THE NAME.
IS THAT A GOOD THING?
UH, ARE WE REALLY
GONNA DO THIS?
SEX IS AN EXPRESSION OF OUR
INTIMACY AND CLOSENESS.
YOUR NOSE IS SO GROWING
RIGHT NOW.
EM? SEAN?
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
WELL,
I'M-I'M LATE FOR WORK.
LATER, SEAN!
EM, ARE YOU,
ARE YOU SICK?
NO.
IT'S JUST THAT...
WELL, SEAN AND I ARE...
SNAKE?!
OH! OH. OH GOD!
I'M AN IDIOT.
SORRY.
UM, DOES YOUR MOM
KNOW ABOUT THIS?
YEAH.
WE HAD THE TALK.
COOL.
I JUST, YOU KNOW...
I, I DIDN'T KNOW.
WELL, I WILL SEE YOU
AT HOME FOR DINNER?
SURE THING.
LATER SKATER.
THANK YOU.
ENTREPRENEUR'S FAIR,
BOOTH 112 -
YOU PLAYED THE MALL LADY
LIKE A DRUM!
THANKS, HON.
YOU HELPED TOO.
NAH, I DON'T HAVE THE PAIGE
POWER OF PERSUASION.
BUT WE'RE A GOOD TEAM,
HUH?
NOT LOOKING A GIFT PORSCHE
IN THE MOUTH HERE,
BUT WHAT'S GOING ON?
BANTING WAS LESS THAN FUN
FOR ME.
SO TO PARAPHRASE
SHERYL CROW,
"I JUST WANNA HAVE
SOME FUN".
FUN'S GOOD.
IT'S JUST, THE LAST TIME
WE DID THIS LAST YEAR?
IT ENDED WEIRD.
BECAUSE WE HAD
NO GROUND RULES.
THIS TIME WE DO.
WE ARE JUST FRIENDS.
FRIENDS WITH
A BENEFITS PACKAGE.
THOSE ARE BENEFITS
I CAN LIVE WITH.
IT'S THE BEST
OF BOTH WORLDS.
CAJ IS THE WAY
WE ROCK IT.
ALEX:
(LAUGHING)
YOU SAID THAT
WITHOUT LAUGHING?
PAIGE:
THE MOMENT OVERTOOK.
IT JUST FELT SO GOOD
TO MACK ON SPINNER
WITH IMPUNITY.
WELL, GREAT.
I HAVE CLASS WITH HIM
IN 20 MINUTES.
I'LL TRY TO IGNORE
HIS BIG DUMB GRINNING FACE.
JESSE, HEY.
HEY.
UH, LATEST EDITION.
AD'S ON PAGE THREE.
AND I ASKED NINA TO WRITE
A PIECE ON YOU GUYS
FOR HER FASHION COLUMN.
THIS IS - WOW.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THE CORE AND SQUATCH DESIGNS
COULD HAVE A FUTURE TOGETHER.
IN BUSINESS.
(CLACKING AGAINST PAPER)
ALEX, UMM...
YOU KNOW JESSE, RIGHT?
YEAH.
YOU'RE ELLIE'S BOYFRIEND.
WAS.
ELLIE DIDN'T TELL YOU
WE BROKE UP?
SHE KEEPS TO HERSELF
A LOT.
YEAH, SHE'S LIKE THAT.
WELL, I GOTTA RUN.
INTERVIEWING
A FRIEND'S BAND.
HOW JOURNALIST OF YOU!
WHAT ARE THEY LIKE?
KIND OF AN ALT-COUNTRY VIBE?
YEAH, THEY'RE PLAYING TONIGHT.
CAMPUS CLUB.
IF YOU'RE INTO IT,
YOU SHOULD COME.
SO, I RAN INTO EM
AT THE PHARMACY TODAY.
WITH SEAN.
PICKING UP...
BIRTH CONTROL.
YOU KNOW, THE PILL.
REALLY.
WAIT.
SHE TOLD ME
SHE'D ASKED YOU.
WELL, WE HAD THE "TALK"
A WHILE AGO.
I TOLD HER TO GO ON THE PILL
WHENEVER SHE WAS READY.
AND I WAS LEFT OUT OF THIS
CONVERSATION, WHY?
DON'T WE TALK ABOUT THESE TYPES
OF THINGS AS A FAMILY?
I WASN'T SURE YOU COULD HANDLE
THIS "TYPE" OF THING.
OR IF YOU'D EVEN WANT TO.
IT'S A WOMAN THING.
IT'S A PARENT THING.
AND I WANT TO CONTRIBUTE.
YOU CONTRIBUTE DELICIOUS,
NUTRITIOUS DINNERS NIGHTLY.
KIDDING.
UM, EMMA, YOU UH,
YOU LIED TO ME
THIS AFTERNOON.
I DIDN'T LIE.
THERE'S JUST SOME THINGS YOU
DON'T NEED TO KNOW, OKAY?
WELL, PARDON ME
FOR BEING CONCERNED
ABOUT MY TEENAGE DAUGHTER,
WHO'S MADE MISTAKES,
AND FEELS THE NEED
TO HIDE THINGS FROM ME.
STEP-DAUGHTER.
WHATEVER!
I DESERVE TO BE
A PART OF YOUR LIFE!
HEY!
SPIKE:
SNAKE,
THIS IS EXACTLY WHY
SOMETIMES YOU AREN'T!
EMMA, WAIT...
I'M MEETING SEAN.
DON'T WAIT UP.
♪♪♪
THEY'RE REALLY
IN THE POCKET.
LIKE, IN A GROOVE.
I LIKE, LIKE HOW RELAXED
THEY ARE.
TOTALLY VIBING
OFF EACH OTHER.
IN THE MOMENT, YES.
IT IS THE ONLY WAY TO BE.
HEY, LET'S DANCE!
SURE.
JESSE:
THIS IS GOOD.
I ALMOST FORGOT
WHAT IT FEELS LIKE.
ELLIE HATED DANCING.
PAIGE:
WELL, IT'S TOO BAD.
'CAUSE YOU ARE A NATURAL!
MOVE OVER
ANTONIO BANDERAS!
AIN'T SEEN NOTHING,
MICHALCHUK!
THANK YOU.
TELL ME AGAIN
WHY YOU NEED ME TO MODEL
AT THE DUMB FAIR?
BECAUSE MARCO LOOKS
LOUSY IN PINK.
SO, UH,
YOU AND JESSE DANCING UP
A STORM LAST NIGHT.
DID IT END THERE?
THERE WAS COFFEE.
AT HIS PLACE.
HAD AN AMAZING CONVO.
AND THEN SOME OTHER STUFF.
AND BACHELOR NUMBER ONE
KNOWS ABOUT
BACHELOR NUMBER TWO.
I.E. SPINNER?
BACHELORS ONE AND TWO
BOTH KNOW THE SCORE.
AS MATTER OF FACT,
I'M SEEING THEM BOTH TONIGHT.
ALEX:
OOH, MENAGE A PAIGE?
PAIGE:
NOT QUITE.
SPINNER IS MY SEVEN O'CLOCK
AND JESSE'S MY NINE.
HEY, YOU UH...
YOU WANNA COME TO MY PLACE
WHEN YOU'RE DONE?
FOR A POST-GAME WRAP-UP?
I GOT THE GOOD ICE CREAM.
SURE, HON.
LOVE TO.
PRETTY IN PINK.
JUST LIKE THE MOVIE.
HEY.
THOUGHT WE COULD
MAYBE TALK.
THE M.I. SERVER
BLEW A HARD DRIVE.
LOOK, I'M SORRY
ABOUT LAST NIGHT, BUT...
I'M OLD ENOUGH
TO MAKE MY OWN DECISIONS.
HELLO?
I'M TRYING TO HAVE
A CONVERSATION HERE.
SIMPSON:
EMMA,
NO HARD DRIVE
MEANS NO SERVER
MEANS NO MORE CLASSES
FOR TODAY.
I NEED TO HANDLE THIS
RIGHT NOW.
CAUSE YOU OBVIOUSLY
CAN'T HANDLE THE FACT
THAT I'M A SEXUAL BEING.
AND YOU CAN'T
KEEP AVOIDING IT FOREVER.
♪♪♪
OOH!
NOT THAT THIS ISN'T FUN,
BUT I REALLY NEED
TO GET GOING.
GOTTA GO SEE THE OTHER GUY.
JESSE STUPID-FACE?
SPINNER,
YOU KNOW THE DEAL.
YEAH, I KNOW.
IT'S JUST...
BEING WITH YOU FEELS...
SO RIGHT.
AND I ALWAYS
GO BY MY FEELINGS.
SPIN?
DON'T TRUST YOUR
FEELINGS, OKAY?
FEELINGS ARE THE ENEMY.
(EXASPERATED SIGH)
HONEY, SWEETIE?
YOU'RE CLEARLY NEW TO THE WAYS
OF FRIENDS-WITH-BENEFITS.
MAYBE IT'S BETTER
IF WE JUST STOP.
NO.
NO, IT'S COOL.
I'LL GET USED TO IT.
SEE YOU AT THE FAIR
TOMORROW?
JESSE:
LIKE WHAT I'M SEEING HERE.
LOTS OF ADVENTURES.
OF THE FRESHMAN
FLAMEOUT KIND?
I'M KIND OF ON
"ADULTHOOD, TAKE TWO".
REALLY?
I DID THAT
TWO YEARS AGO.
I THOUGHT EVERYTHING
WAS RUINED,
BUT IT KINDA OPENS UP A ROAD,
YOU KNOW?
THAT IS EXACTLY
HOW I FEEL.
JUST HIT THE GAS AND GO...
TOTALLY.
BUT I'M A CAUTIOUS DRIVER.
LET'S DANCE, OKAY?
SHOW ME SOME MORE
OF THOSE MOVES?
OKAY.
(LAUGHS)
MALE VOCALIST:
♪ BUT I KNOW
IF I DON'T COME DOWN ♪
♪ YOU WON'T BE HERE ♪
♪ LIFE'S SO UP
IN THE AIR WITH ME ♪
OH AFTERNOON,
MS. NUNEZ.
READY TO ROCK THE CATWALK
WITH INSOUCIANT SMILE?
YEAH, WHATEVER.
LET'S GET IT OVER WITH.
UM, IS IT "EVERYONE
HATES PAIGE" DAY?
MAYBE.
SEEING AS IT WAS
DITCH ALEX
AND DON'T EVEN CALL HER
LAST NIGHT.
HON, I FORGOT.
I'M SORRY.
BABE, COULD YOU JUST
STRAIGHTEN OUR SIGN A BIT?
DON'T TELL ME,
YOUR NINE O'CLOCK
WITH JESSE BECAME A TEN,
THEN AN ELEVEN,
TWELVE, ONE...
I SAID I'M SORRY.
IT'S JUST...
I THINK THINGS
ARE BECOMING
A BIT MORE THAN CAJ
WITH JESSE.
HE'S KINDA SPECIAL.
RUSH INTO STUFF, MUCH?
PATHETIC, PAIGE.
PATHETIC.
HENCE THE INEVITABILITY
OF ENVIRONMENTAL COLLAPSE.
THANK YOU.
SIMPSON:
OKAY.
THANKS, LIBERTY.
AH, EMMA?
YOU'RE UP.
YOUR THEME?
EMMA:
WOMEN... AND SEX.
MORE SPECIFICALLY?
IT'S ABOUT HOW MEN
HAVE STIFLED
WOMEN'S SEXUAL EXPRESSION
THROUGHOUT HISTORY.
RIGHT ON, SISTER!
WHEN MEN THINK OF GIRLS,
THIS IS WHAT THEY SEE.
BUT, WHEN CONFRONTED
WITH SOMETHING LIKE...
THIS?
A HEALTHY, NATURAL EXPRESSION
OF PHYSICAL INTIMACY,
MEN CAN'T HANDLE IT.
AT ALL.
THEY FEEL FREE
TO RIDE THEIR INSTINCTS.
BUT WHEN WOMEN STAND UP
AND DECLARE THEIR RIGHT
TO BE SEXUAL?
IT'S THIS -
A TYPICAL DOUBLE-STANDARD.
MEN DON'T WANT TO HEAR IT.
(TECHNO MUSIC)
PAIGE:
ARE YOU SURE YOU WANT TO MODEL
JIMMY'S FAB DESIGNS
WITH THAT UNFAB POUT?
I'M NOT POUTING.
OKAY, I AM.
LOOK, PAIGE,
HERE'S THE DEAL:
I NEED ALL OF YOU,
OR NONE AT ALL.
BABE, I'M SORRY.
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN
THIS WOULD HAPPEN.
IT'S JUST -
ULTIMATUMS MAKE ME ITCHY.
IT'S NOT AN ULTIMATUM,
PAIGE.
BUT IF YOU DON'T BREAK IT OFF
WITH JESSE RIGHT NOW,
WE'RE THROUGH!
AND NOW I'M ITCHY.
DON'T MAKE ME CHOOSE.
YOU WON'T LIKE MY CHOICE.
SO YOU'D PICK
STUPID JESSE!?
WITH HIS STUPID HAIR
AND HIS STUPID SHIRTS
AND HIS STUPID FACE?!
FIVE MINUTE WARNING.
AND YOU'VE GOT A VISITOR,
PAIGE.
JESSE! UM...
WHAT A CRAZY SURPRISE!
WANTED TO WISH YOU LUCK,
AND GET A QUOTE
FOR THE CORE
NOW IS NOT
SUCH A GREAT TIME, HON?
SPINNER:
YEAH,
GO DRINK A LATTE,
EMO-BOY.
SPINNER, CAN WE PLEASE
BE GROWNUP ABOUT THIS?
YEAH.
NO.
GET OUTTA HERE,
LOSER!
OH, I'M A LOSER?
OKAY... "SPINNER".
SPINNER:
YOU'LL BE CURSING THAT NAME
AFTER IT KICKS YOUR ASS!
(HYPERVENTILATING)
COME ON, PAIGE,
IN FOR TEN.
ONE, TWO, THREE,
THAT'S IT.
I MEAN...
WHATEVER!
YOU SUCK!
WILL YOU BOTH SHUT UP?
YOU. GO STAND OUT FRONT.
YOU, GO PUT ON THE REST
OF YOUR OUTFIT AND A SMILE
BECAUSE WE HAVE TO GO MODEL
THESE FREAKING CLOTHES.
CLEAR?
ALEX, I...
SAVE IT.
(DOOR OPENING AND CLOSING)
GOT A MINUTE FOR SOMEONE
WHO'S MEAN,
CRUEL AND HURTFUL?
I HAVE ALL THE TIME
IN THE WORLD,
BECAUSE YOU'RE NONE
OF THOSE THINGS.
I'M SORRY FOR WHAT I DID
IN CLASS.
I KNOW IT KINDA HURT.
SIMPSON:
IT'S FINE.
BECAUSE YOU WERE RIGHT.
AND YOUR PRESENTATION,
BY THE WAY, IT WAS GOOD.
NOT VERY SUBTLE.
BUT GOOD.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
EMMA,
I'VE KNOWN YOU SINCE
YOU WERE IN A STROLLER,
AND THE IDEA
OF YOU GROWING UP?
IT'S... IT'S A TRIP.
FOR ME TOO.
I MEAN,
I'LL BE MOVING AWAY.
GOING TO UNIVERSITY.
I'M NOT A LITTLE KID
ANYMORE.
I JUST THOUGHT THIS
WAS GOING TO BE EASIER.
I GUESS I'D BETTER
GET USED TO IT.
SO... DAD,
DO YOU WANT TO HAVE
"THE TALK"?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK I'M GOOD.
JIMMY:
WELL, HERE'S TO OUR FIRST
FIREWORKS-FILLED FASHION SHOW.
BUT HEY, THREE NEW BUYERS
CAN'T BE WRONG, RIGHT?
CHEERS.
SO, SPIN SPOKE TO ME
AFTER THE SHOW.
ALL APOLOGIES
FOR FREAKING OUT.
BUT, WE BOTH KNOW
THAT IT JUST...
IT WASN'T MEANT TO BE.
BUT JESSE IS STILL
INTO THE CAJ THING.
SO, WHAT SAY YOU,
WISE COUNSEL?
I SAY THEY BOTH SUCK.
AND FOR THAT MATTER?
SO DO YOU.
(SCOFFS)
YOU KNOW WHAT, ALEX?
YOU SUCK TOO.
SORRY!
OH, YOUR APOLOGY IS KILLING ME
WITH ITS PLAINTIVE SINCERITY.
GOD,
I HATE YOUR THESAURUS.
AND I HATE HOW YOU'RE
ACTING RIGHT NOW.
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?!
BECAUSE I LOVE YOU,
YOU IDIOT.
SO MUCH IT SCARES
THE CRAP OUT OF ME.
WHY?
JUST -
WHY DID YOU TELL ME
TO GO ON ALL THOSE DATES?
BECAUSE I THOUGHT
YOU BEING CAJ WITH GUYS
WAS NOTHING SERIOUS.
AND A LOT BETTER THAN YOU
WITH SOME OTHER GIRL.
I JUST...
CAN'T WITH YOU RIGHT NOW.
I REALLY DO...
I REALLY HAVE
TO GO BACK INSIDE.