MR. STONE:
I REALLY APPRECIATE YOUR TIME,
CHUCK.
I'M GLAD WE SEE EYE TO EYE
ON THIS.
CROWN ATTORNEY:
WELL LOOK, I'VE KNOWN PETER
SINCE HE WAS A BOY.
HE'S A GOOD KID.
HE JUST GOT MIXED UP
WITH THE WRONG ELEMENT.
MAN, DID I EVER.
I TRULY REGRET THE DAY
THAT I MET SEAN CAMERON.
WELL, THANKFULLY,
WE WON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT SEEING SEAN AGAIN.
PETER:
OH, MOM? DAD?
DO YOU MIND IF I GO TALK
TO EMMA FOR A MINUTE?
GO AHEAD.
EMMA:
WHAT HAPPENED?
I'M DYING!
WELL, THE CROWN ATTORNEY'S
BEEN GOING
TO MY DAD'S CHRISTMAS PARTY
FOR YEARS,
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
I'M FREE, EMMA.
I'M FREE.
MY DAD JUST PULLED
SOME STRINGS
WITH HIS BUDDY CHUCK.
SO YOU GOT OFF
WITH NOTHING?
HARDLY.
NO, I LOST MY LICENSE,
I'VE GOT TONS
OF COMMUNITY SERVICE,
AND I'M UNDER STRICT HOUSE
ARREST AT MY MOM'S.
OUCH.
THAT'LL BE NO PICNIC.
YEAH,
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
THERE'S GOOD NEWS.
SOUNDS LIKE SEAN IS GONNA BE
NAILED TO THE WALL FOR THIS.
I HAVE A NEW ZERO
TOLERANCE POLICY
WHEN IT COMES TO
TALKING ABOUT SEAN.
SO YOU HAVEN'T HEARD
FROM HIM?
NOPE.
WITH HIS HIT
AND RUN CHARGES,
I DON'T THINK EITHER OF US WILL
FOR A LONG, LONG TIME.
♪♪♪
PETER:
ILLEGAL STREET RACING
IS LIKE PLAYING
WITH A LOADED GUN.
IT'S A SERIOUS CRIME.
SO MY ACTIONS
HAVE HAD REPROCATIONS
BEYOND MY PERSONAL PUNISHMENTS.
AND I HOPE I CAN EXPLAIN
TO EVERYONE
JUST HOW SORRY AND ASHAMED
I FEEL.
MY BEHAVIOUR, AS WELL AS
THE OTHER PEOPLE INVOLVED,
HAD TERRIBLE CONSEQUENCES.
I ALSO NEED TO SAY
THAT I'M SORRY
FOR TARNISHING DEGRASSI'S REP
IN OUR COMMUNITY,
AND HOPE THAT I CAN
GAIN YOUR TRUST BACK.
THANK YOU.
WE'VE SEEN IT FROM C.E.O.'S,
ATHLETES AND PRESIDENTS.
IT'S A CLASSIC EXAMPLE
OF THE ON-AIR "MEA CULPA".
BUT IN THIS CASE,
I'M SURE IT'S COMING FROM
A VERY GENUINE PLACE.
MANNY:
SO PETER GOT OUT OF JAIL
BECAUSE HE SAID
HE WAS SORRY?
AND BECAUSE HE AGREED
TO A ZILLION CONDITIONS.
PETER'S TAKING THIS
SERIOUSLY, MANNY.
IT'S NO JOKE.
YOU'RE RIGHT,
NO ONE'S LAUGHING,
LEAST OF ALL SEAN.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
NOTHING.
I JUST...
FEEL A LITTLE BAD.
I MEAN, I KNOW THIS
WAS SEAN'S FAULT.
BUT STILL,
HE'S IN JAIL.
SEAN WILL TAKE CARE
OF HIMSELF.
HE ALWAYS DOES.
PETER'S THE ONE
I'M WORRIED ABOUT.
HEARD MY NAME.
HOPE YOU'RE SAYING
GOOD THINGS.
EMMA:
ONLY.
DON'T WANT TO DISTURB
VISITING HOUR.
SO, HOW'S LIFE
UNDER HOUSE ARREST?
THE WARDEN IS NOT
CUTTING ME ANY SLACK.
SHE'S NOT EVEN GONNA LET ME
TAKE YOU TO THE DANCE.
WHAT? YOU'RE KIDDING!
THAT IS SO UNFAIR!
YEAH, I'M COMING!
I'LL TALK TO YOU
LATER?
LIBERTY:
SO WE'LL HIRE A MARIACHI BAND.
WHAT?
YOU SAID WE NEEDED A THEME
FOR THE DANCE.
A GOOD THEME.
LOOK,
AS THE NEW TREASURER,
I'VE DONE THE MATH.
NO BAND.
THE MOST WE CAN AFFORD
RIGHT NOW
IS JIMMY AND SPINNER
JAMMING IN SOMBREROS.
EVEN IN DISGUISES
THAT WOULD BE LAME.
WAIT! THAT'S IT!
THAT'LL BE OUR THEME -
A MASQUERADE.
LIKE EVERYONE WILL COME
IN COSTUME,
ALL INCOGNITO.
CUCARACHA!
SPEAKING OF COCKROACHES,
WHAT'S HE DOING HERE?
IF HE'S BACK AT DEGRASSI,
I'M DROPPING OUT.
IT'S NOT HERE.
JESSE:
OKAY, NINA,
YOU'RE ON THE ESSAY
PLAGIARISM RING.
ERIC, YOU'RE ON THE CHANCELLOR'S
RECKLESS SPENDING.
AND YOU'RE IN MY WAY,
FROSH.
WHAT HAPPENED TO MY ARTICLE
ON THE TUITION RALLY?
OH, YOU MEAN THE ONE FILLED
WITH ROOKIE REPORTER MISTAKES?
HMM. GUESS I FORGOT
TO PUBLISH IT.
WONDER WHY?
WELL, DON'T I EVEN GET
A CHANCE TO FIX IT?
JESSE:
NO.
AND IF YOU NEED TALKING DOWN,
FROSH?
THERE'S A COUNSELLOR
IN THE CLINIC.
(DISBELIEVING)
UGH!
I GAVE UP FOOD AND SLEEP.
I DID RESEARCH
IN A BEER BONG PUDDLE!
NINA:
WELCOME TO THE CORE.
(SIGHS)
THANKS, MR. S.
I APPRECIATE YOUR CONCERN.
I'LL PASS IT ON
TO SEAN.
WHATEVER YOU'RE HERE FOR?
WE'RE NOT INTERESTED.
I WAS JUST TALKING
TO YOUR STEP-DAD ABOUT SEAN.
REMEMBER HIM?
I'M TRYING TO FORGET.
WELL, SOMEONE'S CHANGED
THEIR TUNE.
SEEMS TO ME SOMEONE WAS
PRETTY DAMN INTERESTED IN SEAN
FOR A WHILE.
EXCUSE ME?
WHAT DID HE TELL YOU?
NOTHING.
HE DIDN'T HAVE TO.
LOOK, IT WAS OBVIOUS
THERE WAS SOMETHING GOING ON.
SOMETHING THAT YOU DIDN'T WANT
YOUR BOYFRIEND TO KNOW ABOUT.
THIS CONVERSATION IS OVER,
JAY.
SPEAKING ABOUT
YOUR BOYFRIEND,
I HEARD HE GOT OFF
WITH A SLAP ON THE WRIST.
PLEASE! HE'S UNDER MAJOR
HATZILAKOS LOCKDOWN,
PLUS COMMUNITY SERVICE.
POOR BABY.
I REALLY HOPE THE LEAF-BLOWER
DOESN'T STRAIN HIS BACK.
I'M REALLY BEGINNING
TO REMEMBER WHY
I DON'T LIKE YOU.
THIS ISN'T ABOUT ME.
IT'S ABOUT SEAN,
OKAY?
HE IS IN HELL.
YESTERDAY, HE WAS SENT
TO THE INFIRMARY
SOME DUDE JUMPED HIM
IN THE CHOW LINE.
JUMPED HIM? WHY?
'CAUSE...
HE DIDN'T LIKE SEAN'S FACE.
IT'S JAIL, EMMA.
IT AIN'T YOUR BOYFRIEND'S
COUNTRY CLUB.
JUST MAYBE YOU COULD GO
TO SEAN'S COURT HEARING
TOMORROW?
I HAVE TO WORK,
BUT HE COULD USE
A FRIEND.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
LOOK,
I'M SORRY I BLEW IT,
BUT BEING A JOURNALIST
IS MY LIFE.
IF YOU GIVE ME
ANOTHER CHANCE
I PROMISE I WILL NOT
SCREW IT UP.
SEE? THAT'S WHAT YOUR
LAST ARTICLE NEEDED -
PASSION,
CONVICTION.
ELLIE:
MY ARTICLE WAS GOOD.
GOOD ENOUGH TO GET ME AN "A"
IN JOURNALISM CLASS.
WELL, THE CORE'S THE FIFTH
LARGEST PAPER IN TORONTO.
WE DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR SCHOOL PROJECTS, FROSH.
MAYBE YOU'D BE FOURTH
IF YOU PRINTED STUFF
PEOPLE CARED ABOUT.
OH, SO YOU KNOW MY JOB
BETTER THAN I DO, HUH?
MAKES YOU PRETTY
DAMN ARROGANT.
ELLIE:
I'M ARROGANT?
I'VE NEVER MET SUCH A POMPOUS,
FULL-OF-HIMSELF JERK.
KINDA MAKES YOU
HATE MY GUTS, HUH?
NO. I'D HAVE TO CARE
TO HATE YOU.
HEY, FROSH,
CARE ENOUGH
TO GET A BEER?
TALK IT OVER?
YOU DROVE?
CAN'T YOU GET IN
TROUBLE FOR THIS?
IT'S CALLED
TAKING A RISK.
BESIDES, YOU'RE MORE
THAN WORTH IT.
UGH! YOU'RE WEARING
THAT VANILLA STUFF?
HONEY-VANILLA SHAMPOO.
SORRY, I FORGOT
YOU DON'T LIKE IT.
PROMISE NOT TO USE IT
BEFORE FRIDAY'S DANCE.
WHAT? SUDDENLY YOU'VE
BECOME GOVERNOR
AND ISSUE ME A STAY?
BETTER.
I SUGGESTED
A COSTUME PARTY -
A MASQUERADE -
SO YOU CAN BE
MY INCOGNITO DATE.
SNEAKY AND GORGEOUS.
NICE!
OKAY.
TIME'S UP, ROMEO.
YOU NEED TO GO HOME.
I DON'T WANT YOU
TO GET INTO
ANY MORE TROUBLE.
I WON'T.
MY MOM'S AT A PTA MEETING.
SO HOW DID YOU
GET THE CAR?
FOUND OUT WHERE
SHE HID THE KEYS.
WHAT CAN I SAY?
I'M GOOD.
(CHUCKLES)
THIS IS WEIRD.
BEING IN THIS CAR
AND EVERYTHING.
WHAT?
I DIDN'T HIT THAT GUY.
SEAN DID.
THAT'S WHY HE'S IN JAIL.
BUT YOU DON'T FEEL BADLY?
OH, OF COURSE I DO!
IT'S TERRIBLE.
AN INNOCENT GUY
GETTING HURT.
IT'S A GOOD THING
HE'S OKAY, HUH?
YEAH,
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
IMAGINE IF HE'D DIED?
NO WAY I WOULD'VE
GOTTEN OFF
WITH THAT LITTLE SLAP
ON THE WRIST.
THE TIME.
I SHOULD GO.
ELLIE:
YOU LECTURE ME
ABOUT MY WRITING,
AND THEN YOU GO GA-GA
OVER A BAND
THAT SCREAMS GIBBERISH
INSTEAD OF TAKING THE TIME
TO CRAFT ACTUAL LYRICS.
GIBBERISH?
YOU GOTTA BE
KIDDING ME.
WELL, YOU'RE LUCKY THE MUSIC
WAS A WICKED BLEND
OF ZEPPELIN AND SABBATH.
I'M SO WRITING
THAT REVIEW.
WELL, THIS TIME IT GOES IN.
NO QUESTIONS ASKED.
SO...
UH... GUESS I...
BETTER GET TO WORK.
YEAH.
NIGHT.
(SIGHS)
MARCO:
GUESS THIS MEANS
YOU'RE OFFICIALLY OVER CRAIG?
WHO DIED?
I'M TRYING TO LOOK
RESPECTABLE,
NOT FUNEREAL.
YOU'RE GOING TO SEAN'S
COURT HEARING?
WHAT HAPPENED TO THE "ZERO
TOLERANCE O' SEAN" POLICY?
JAY GAVE ME
HIS COURT NOTICE.
I JUST THOUGHT...
I DON'T KNOW.
I THOUGHT I SHOULD CHECK ON
HOW HIS CASE IS GOING.
AND FOR THAT YOU NEED A TOP
THAT BRINGS OUT YOUR
GLOWY, GLOWY SKIN?
YOU WERE WORRIED
ABOUT HIM TOO.
STILL AM.
BUT I'M ALSO WORRIED
ABOUT MY BEST FRIEND,
WHO'S BEING AN EMOTIONAL
PING-PONG BALL.
SEAN, PETER,
PETER, SEAN...
I'M NOT!
I'M WITH PETER
100 PERCENT.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
SEAN'S OKAY, OKAY?
MANNY:
OKAY.
FORGET I ASKED.
(CHURCH BELL RINGS)
EXCUSE ME, I'M LOOKING FOR
SEAN CAMERON'S HEARING,
COURTROOM H?
SEAN:
EMMA!
SEAN.
YOU LOOK TERRIBLE.
UH...I UH... TRIPPED.
FELL.
IT...IT DOESN'T MATTER.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
OH, VANILLA.
I MISS THAT SMELL.
JAY SAID
YOU WEREN'T COMING.
I WASN'T GOING TO.
UH, BUT I THOUGHT
YOU COULD USE A FRIEND.
THAT WAS FAST.
SEAN:
MY PUBLIC DEFENDER DIDN'T SHOW!
HE'S GOT A BACKLOAD
OF CHARITY CASES
JUST LIKE MINE.
UNLESS I CAN GET SOME MONEY
FOR A REAL LAWYER,
I'M SCREWED.
WHAT CAN I DO?
NOTHING.
JUST TELL ME ONE THING.
TELL ME YOU'RE NOT
STILL WITH PETER.
OF COURSE!
HE'S MY BOYFRIEND.
THAT GUY IS SLIME.
HE PLANTED THOSE DRUGS
IN MY LOCKER.
I ASKED HIM,
AND HE SAID
HE DIDN'T DO THAT.
OH, WHATEVER.
IF YOU DON'T
BELIEVE ME,
THEN WHY ARE YOU
EVEN HERE?
BECAUSE RIGHT OR WRONG,
YOU NEED HELP.
AND I'M GONNA HELP YOU,
SEAN.
(KNOCKS ON DOOR)
EMMA, WHERE WERE YOU?
YOU MISSED HOMEROOM.
YES, AND I CAN
EXPLAIN THAT,
BUT LISTEN TO THIS FIRST.
WHAT IF JACK MOVED IN
WITH YOU AND MOM,
AND MANNY AND I
TAKE JACK'S ROOM?
THAT WAY WE COULD RENT
OUT THE BASEMENT.
OH WELL...
AS MUCH AS I RELISH
THE IDEA
OF SHARING MY ROOM
WITH A THREE-YEAR-OLD,
WHAT'S THIS ALL ABOUT?
I SAW SEAN TODAY,
AT THE COURTHOUSE.
HENCE WHY I MISSED
HOMEROOM.
SNAKE, IT'S BAD.
HE REALLY NEEDS HELP
AND HE'S GOT NO ONE.
SIMPSON:
JAY TOLD ME.
LOOK, I'M GLAD YOU'RE
TAKING UP HIS CAUSE,
BUT WHAT SEAN REALLY NEEDS
RIGHT NOW IS A GOOD LAWYER,
AND THEY COST BIG MONEY.
MORE THEN THE PEANUTS
WE'LL EARN
RENTING OUT
A LEAKY BASEMENT.
OKAY, IDEA NUMBER TWO:
FUNDRAISER.
THERE'S LOTS OF COMPETITION
OUT THERE
FOR THE CHARITY DOLLAR.
BUT UH...
YOU'LL FIGURE OUT
SOMETHING.
YOU ALWAYS DO.
TORONTO MUSIC WEEK
SHOWCASE?
HOW DID I GET THAT?
AH, IT'S FALL AGAIN...
SCHOOL STARTS,
THE LEAVES CHANGE COLOURS,
AND JESSE GETS IT ON
WITH A NUBILE, EAGER FROSH.
YOU SHOULD TALK,
MS. 2005.
PETER:
SURPRISE!
A MASK BEFITTING
A TRUE QUEEN.
I WAS GOING TO GO
WITH PAPER MACHE,
BUT THIS IS REALLY WOW.
WHEN YOU GONNA REALIZE
YOU DESERVE BETTER
THAN PAPER MACHE?
THAT'S SWEET.
THANK YOU.
WHAT'RE THE TICKETS FOR?
OH, JUST A LITTLE RAFFLE
TO MAKE THE DANCE
MORE INTERESTING.
COUNT ME IN.
I GOT GAMBLING
IN MY BLOOD!
WOW! I CAN FEEL MY OVERPRICED
DESIGNER JEANS
NOT FITTING AS WE SPEAK.
DON'T GET USED TO IT.
I ONLY COOK WHEN
I'M MAJORLY STRESSED.
MARCO:
WELL, WE SHOULD STRESS YOU OUT
MORE OFTEN.
I THINK YOUR DESIGNER
JEANS ARE SAFE.
MARCO:
OKAY, LAY IT ON ME.
I CAN HANDLE IT.
JESSE CUT MY ARTICLE.
THEN HE ASKED ME OUT
ON A DATE
AND KISSED ME.
WELL, HE TRIED TO.
OKAY, THOSE ARE SOME TALL,
DARK, HANDSOME PROBLEMS
THAT YOU GOT THERE.
YEAH, AND THEN HE GAVE ME
THIS PLUM MUSIC ASSIGNMENT
AND SUDDENLY,
I'M LIKE THE NEW CORE TRAMP.
SO, YOU GOTTA CHOOSE.
ELLIE, SELF-RESPECT
OR JESSE?
IT SOUNDS LIKE
A PRETTY EASY CALL.
MARCO, YOU SAW HIM,
RIGHT?
IT IS NOT AN EASY CALL.
YEAH, I KNOW.
BUT, YOU KNOW,
JUST REMEMBER
THAT THE DEVIL'S
NOT UGLY.
OKAY?
I MEAN THE DEVIL
IS CUTE.
WAY CUTE.
I'M TALKING
BRAD PITT CUTE.
DON'T SELL OUT
FOR JUST SOME
PRETTY FACE.
THANK YOU...
FATHER MARCO.
YO, FROSH!
WE'RE GONNA BE LATE.
WHAT?
SORRY, UM...
I CAN'T.
YEAH, I KNOW HOW TRYING
FREE ROCK CONCERTS CAN BE.
ACTUALLY,
I'M MORE INTERESTED IN...
INTERMURAL WATER POLO
FINALS.
ERIC:
SWAPSIES?
(HAPPY LAUGH)
YES!
THAT'S SO RAD!
SO YOU'RE...TURNING DOWN
THE ASSIGNMENT?
WELL LOOK HOW HAPPY
IT'S MADE ERIC.
HMM.
GOODY.
EMMA:
TOBY!
TWO DOLLARS EACH,
THREE FOR FIVE DOLLARS.
IT'S FIFTY-FIFTY.
AND THE OTHER FIFTY
GOES TO...?
A FRIEND OF OURS
IS IN JAIL.
I'M TRYING TO HELP
GET HIM OUT.
YOU'RE TAKING UP MONEY
FOR SEAN
WITHOUT COUNCIL'S
APPROVAL?
AND WHAT DOES MS. H. SAY?
EMMA:
SHHHHH!
MS. H DOESN'T KNOW.
MANNY:
WHAT ARE THOSE FOR?
NOTHING.
SEAN'S DEFENSE FUND.
THANKS, DR. DORKWAD.
YOU'RE WANTED
IN THE O.R.
DOES GORILLA MAN,
A.K.A. PETER
IN A LAME COSTUME,
KNOW YOU'RE SELLING TICKETS
AND COLLECTING MONEY
FOR HIS ARCH-NEMESIS?
NO.
AND HE'S NOT GOING TO.
LOOK, I KNOW MY ADVICE
ISN'T ALWAYS DR. PHIL SOLID,
AND WHAT'S HAPPENING
TO SEAN ISN'T FAIR,
BUT BABE?
YOU GOTTA LET HIM GO.
MANNY, I CAN'T HELP IT.
SEAN IS IN HERE.
BUT I CAN'T.
I CAN'T FEEL THIS WAY.
WHEN I WAS IN
THE HOSPITAL,
WHO WAS THERE HOLDING
MY HAND? PETER.
AND JUST LOOK AT
THIS GORGEOUS MASK.
PETER BOUGHT IT FOR ME.
IT WAS A SURPRISE.
HE LEFT IT
IN MY LOCKER.
YOUR LOCKER?
HE HAS YOUR COMBO?
NO...
THEN HOW'D HE GET IN?
(BANG)
OW! OW!
SOMEONE SPIKE THE PUNCH
OR SOMETHING?
OPEN MY LOCKER,
OR I TELL YOUR MOM
YOU'RE HERE.
OKAY, FINE.
GIVE ME THE COMBINATION.
I THOUGHT YOU KNEW IT.
I WROTE IT DOWN.
FROM WHERE?
MY MOM HAS THEM,
IN HER OFFICE.
PETER...
DID YOU BREAK
INTO SEAN'S LOCKER
AND PLANT THE POT
THE SAME WAY
YOU BROKE INTO MINE?
OKAY, SEAN IS A LOSER.
HE ALWAYS HAS BEEN,
AND HE ALWAYS WILL BE.
ANSWER THE QUESTION!
WELL, WHAT DO YOU
WANT ME TO SAY?
THE TRUTH!
EVERYTHING I DID,
I DID TO KEEP US
TOGETHER.
ALL RIGHT,
SEAN IS SCUM!
HE DESERVED
WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM!
WHEN YOU SEE ME IN CLASS,
DON'T LOOK AT ME.
WHEN YOU PASS ME IN THE HALL,
DON'T TALK TO ME.
BECAUSE YOU AND ME
ARE DONE!
PETER MICHAEL.
DO THE WORDS HOUSE ARREST
MEAN NOTHING TO YOU?
A WHOLE PIECE
ON WATER POLO
WITHOUT AT LEAST
ONE REFERENCE TO SPEEDOS?
AND YOU CALL YOURSELF
A JOURNALIST.
ELLIE:
ROOKIE REPORTER MISTAKE.
JESSE:
LOOK...
I DIDN'T GIVE YOU
THE MUSIC PIECE
TO GET INTO YOUR PANTS.
I GAVE IT TO YOU
BECAUSE YOU LOVE MUSIC,
AND EVERYONE ELSE
IS BUSY.
GREAT.
YOU'RE A GOOD WRITER,
FROSH.
NOT MY FAULT
YOU ALSO HAPPEN TO BE CUTE.
I'M NOT GONNA APOLOGIZE
FOR LIKING YOU.
AND...YOU?
GUESS YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
BUT ONE QUESTION?
WHAT ARE WE GONNA TELL
EVERYONE?
AND DON'T CALL ME FROSH.
IT'LL BE OUR
LITTLE SECRET...
ELLIE.
SO THE BAD NEWS IS
THAT I ONLY RAISED
$243.00.
I'M GONNA BE
IN JAIL FOREVER.
HMPH!
I'M SORRY ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED.
WITH PETER, I MEAN.
SOUNDS BRUTAL.
NO, I'M SORRY,
FOR BEING SO BLIND.
SHOULD NEVER HAVE
BELIEVED HIM.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
SO WHAT'S THE GOOD NEWS?
BESIDES YOU BEING HERE?
SNAKE IS FINDING YOU
A PUBLIC DEFENDANT,
A GOOD ONE.
ONE WHO HAS TIME
TO WORK ON YOUR CASE.
(KNOCKING)
UM, VISITING HOURS
ARE ALMOST OVER.
I GOT YOU SOMETHING.
VANILLA-HONEY SHAMPOO.
I THOUGHT IT WAS
THE NEXT BEST THING
TO ACTUALLY BEING
WITH ME.
NOTHING COULD REPLACE
THE REAL THING.