SPINNER?
HEY. DARCE.
YOU KNOW, WHAT HAPPENED
BETWEEN ME AND YOU -
THE BREAKUP?
I'M REALLY SORRY.
ME TOO.
MORE THAN ANYTHING
IN THE WORLD.
BUT IT WAS THE RIGHT
THING TO DO.
THERE WAS SOMETHING...
MISSING.
I'M SORRY.
I HOPE WE CAN
BE FRIENDS.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
SIMPSON: (FRENCH ACCENT)
OH, SPINNER MASON,
JUST UNDER THE WIRE.
OH, AND HERE IS OUR VERY SPECIAL
GUIDANCE COUNSELOR,
MS. SAUVE.
WHY DON'T YOU ALL OPEN UP
YOUR CAREER APTITUDE TESTS.
SAUVE:
IF NOTHING ELSE,
THE RESULTS MAY HELP
TO INFORM
WHAT UNIVERSITIES
YOU APPLY TO
AND WHAT MAJORS
YOU CHOOSE.
JIMMY:
CRIMINAL LAWYER!
ALL RIGHT!
ASHLEY:
FAMILY LAW FOR ME!
NYU, HERE WE COME!
I KNOW.
I THINK WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO OPEN
A PRACTICE TOGETHER,
DOWNTOWN MANHATTAN.
FAMILY AND CRIMINAL LAW.
(CHUCKLES)
SPINNER:
CLOWN?
I'M SUPPOSED TO BE
A CLOWN?
WELL REMEMBER,
THIS IS JUST A GUIDE.
OKAY?
IT'S IMPORTANT THAT
YOU FIND SOMETHING
THAT YOU'RE PASSIONATE ABOUT.
SPINNER:
LIKE BEING A COP?
OH YEAH!
GET RIGHT ON THAT.
♪♪♪
(SIGHS)
PULL IT TOGETHER, MAN.
I CAN'T HAVE BASKET CASE
SPORTING MY GEAR.
(HEAVY SIGH)
"SHE SAID THERE WOULD
ALWAYS BE AN US
THEN SHE CRUSHED MY HEART
WITH A BUS.
I PLEDGED ABSTINENCE
IN FAITH
'CAUSE SHE SAID
'TWAS FOREVER,
BUT NOW IT'S JUST ME.
"TWAS?!"
ARE YOU SURE POET
WASN'T IN YOUR TEST RESULTS?
DIDN'T SEE ARTIST
IN YOURS.
WHAT HAPPENED TO
THE WHOLE ART DREAM?
I WOKE UP.
ART ISN'T A CAREER;
LAW IS.
YEAH, SO IS BEING A CLOWN,
I GUESS.
YOU KNOW, SPIN,
PAIGE IS IN TOWN.
MARCO AND ELLIE ARE
HAVING SOME PEOPLE OVER.
YOU SHOULD COME.
I DON'T KNOW.
WRONG.
YOU ARE NOT SITTING HOME
ANOTHER NIGHT
WRITING THESE SAD-ASS,
MWAH MWAH,
I'M GONNA KILL MYSELF POEMS.
I FORBID YOU.
TIME TO GET ON
THE POSITIVE TIP.
ALL RIGHT?
ALL RIGHT.
HEY...
THANK YOU.
(GIRLS LAUGHING LOUDLY)
AND THE FACE
THAT HE WAS MAKING?
(LAUGHING)
ZIP IT.
I'M TRYING TO STUDY.
TRYING TO GRADUATE
BEFORE YOU TURN 30?
GOOD LUCK.
A, I ALREADY GRADUATED.
AND B,
DO I EVEN KNOW YOU?
UNLESS YOU WANT THESE CARROTS
TO BECOME PART OF YOUR ANATOMY,
I SUGGEST YOU STOP.
OOOH.
(LAUGHING)
I'M OFFICIALLY
TOO OLD FOR THIS.
(ROCK MUSIC BLARES)
MARCO:
OKAY. ALL WE HAVE LEFT HERE
IS KEIKO AND SUKI'S
RICE CRACKERS.
I SPENT ALL MY SNACK MONEY
ON TEXTBOOKS,
AND I'M THINKING THOSE
ARE KIND OF DRY. SO HERE...
PAIGE:
WELL, ONE OF THE MANY
PERKS AT BANTING,
AMAZING MEAL PLAN.
HEY! THAT IS A SPIFFY TOP,
SPIN.
SINCE WHEN ARE YOU
SO AU COURANT?
IT'S A JIMMY BROOKS ORIGINAL.
ELLIE:
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW MANY PEOPLE
HAVE ASKED ME
WHERE THEY CAN GET ONE
OF THESE DESIGNS.
NAH. REALLY?
REALLY.
EVER THINK ABOUT
SELLING THEM?
A LOT OF MONEY IN IT.
YEAH, JESSE,
DON'T EVEN BOTHER.
I KEEP TELLING JIM TO START
HIS OWN LINE OF T-SHIRTS,
BUT HE NEVER LISTENS.
IT'S 'CAUSE IT'S CRAZY,
MARCO.
I'M NOT GONNA START
SELLING T-SHIRTS.
WHY NOT?
THERE'S NOTHING
STOPPING YOU.
THERE'S A LOT STOPPING ME,
ACTUALLY.
WHAT?
LIKE YOUR DAD?
LIKE REALITY.
DIDN'T SOMEBODY SAY SOMETHING
ABOUT PLAYING POKER?
PAIGE:
OH, I'M IN!
THANKS TO TOO MANY
ALL NIGHT POKER SESSIONS,
I AM A TEXAS HOLD 'EM WHIZ.
ALL RIGHT,
WHAT'S THE BUY IN?
SPINNER:
CHECK IT OUT.
"SPIMMY DESIGNS,"
HUH?
OR "THE JIMMNNER
CLOTHING COMPANY."
"SQUATCH WEAR."
I LIKE THAT ONE.
OKAY, STOP.
REWIND.
LOSING THE PLOT.
WHAT IS THIS?
THIS IS THE FUTURE,
BABY.
I'M TURNING YOU INTO
THE NEXT JOHN-JOHN.
IT'S SEAN-JOHN.
SPINNER:
POT-AY-TO, POT-AW-TO.
OKAY, LOOK...
JIMMY, PEOPLE LOVE
YOUR T-SHIRTS, MAN.
LET'S START A BUSINESS.
WITH WHAT MONEY?
I GOT SOME SAVED.
PLUS, MARCO'S DAD CAN GIVE US
SOME SHIRTS ON SPEC.
WE MAKE A BUNCH,
GO TO CAMPUS,
BRAD'S YOUR UNCLE.
DO YOU KNOW HOW MUCH WORK
THAT WOULD TAKE?
OH, WE COULD DO IT -
YOU AND ME -
TOGETHER?
PLUS,
WHEN IT TAKES OFF,
BECOMES A HUGE
MONEY-MAKER,
I CAN FORGET ALL ABOUT
CLOWN ACADEMY.
(EXHALES)
JIMMY,
YOU'RE GONNA NEED MONEY
FOR YOUR FANCY NEW YORK
UNIVERSITY, RIGHT?
LET'S MAKE SOME.
I'VE GOT
AN ACADEMIC FUND.
I'M TOTALLY
TAKEN CARE OF.
ALL RIGHT.
JIMMY...
THEN AGAIN...
I GUESS IT WOULD
BE COOL
TO SEE MORE PEOPLE
WEARING MY STUFF.
YEAH?
YEAH.
LET'S GIVE IT A SHOT.
ALEX NUNEZ
SMILING AFTER A TEST?
(CHUCKLES)
JUST HAPPY.
KINDA ACED IT.
CONGRATULATIONS.
I'M PROUD OF YOU.
IT SHOWS REAL MATURITY
THAT YOU CAME BACK
TO UPGRADE YOUR MARKS,
ESPECIALLY AFTER YOUR
FRIENDS MOVED ON.
YOU CAN'T BECOME
A PHYSIOTHERAPIST
WITHOUT A DEGREE.
WHICH MEANS I GOTTA UP
MY MARKS
IF I WANNA GET ACCEPTED
ANYWHERE.
SO, GOTTA RUN...
YOU KNOW WHAT
WOULD REALLY HELP
WITH YOUR UNIVERSITY
APPLICATION?
EXTRA-CURRICULARS?
WHICH YOU DON'T HAVE.
I KNEW THIS WAS
GOING SOMEWHERE.
LOOK, I REALLY NEED GIRLS
FOR LACROSSE.
I MEAN...
I'M SO LOW ON PLAYERS
I MIGHT EVEN HAVE
TO CANCEL THE TEAM.
A TRAGEDY OF GLOBAL
PROPORTIONS.
ALEX, YOU LOVE LACROSSE.
I REMEMBER FROM GYM CLASS.
YOU'RE A NATURAL.
I AM FOND OF BASHING PEOPLE
WITH A LARGE STICK.
SO YOU'LL THINK
ABOUT IT?
ME AND TEAM SPORTS?
SORRY.
NOT A WHOLE LOT
TO THINK ABOUT, MS. H.
♪♪♪
I'M SORRY,
WE'RE ALL OUT.
SPINNER:
WE CAN'T RUN THIS OPERATION
OUT OF A CARDBOARD BOX, EH?
I'M THINKING MAIL ORDER
PYRAMID SCHEME?
OR WE COULD SET UP SHOP
OUTSIDE LIKE RAPTORS GAMES
AND CONCERTS.
OR...OR...?
WE LET THE MARKET
COME TO US.
WHAT ABOUT RENT?
DUDE, I'VE SAVED A COOL GRAND
WORKING AT THE DOT.
AND IT'S NOT LIKE I'M GONNA
NEED IT FOR CLOWN ACADEMY.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
I'VE NEVER BEEN SERIOUSER.
WHAT ABOUT YOUR
ACADEMIC FUND?
SAY YOU SKIM A LITTLE
OFF THE TOP.
NO.
MY DAD HAS BEEN PUTTING
MONEY INTO THAT FUND
SINCE I WAS 2-YEARS-OLD.
IF I EVEN THINK ABOUT
TOUCHING IT, I'M DEAD.
COME ON, GIVE YOUR DAD
A LITTLE CREDIT.
HE MIGHT JUST GO FOR IT.
ESPECIALLY WHEN HE HEARS ABOUT
HOW GOOD WE'RE DOING.
ALEX:
SO, HERE YOU ARE
BACK FROM THE MAGICAL
UNIVERSITY LAND OF BANTING,
WHICH I ASSUME IS GOING...
HM, BETTER THAN PERF.
BUT WHAT ABOUT YOU?
ARE YOU SEEING ANYONE?
IS SHE CUTE?
DO I KNOW HER?
I WANT ALL THE JUICY
DETAILS.
SORRY.
CAN'T HELP YOU.
I'M THE QUEEN OF BORING
SINGLE LAMELAND.
DEGRASSI IS ALL
I GOT GOING ON.
WELL, I BET YOU MUST BE
RUNNING THAT PLACE.
ARE ALL THE KIDDIES
RUNNING SCARED?
ACTUALLY,
THEY'RE SHAKING
AT MY TERRIFYINGLY
GOOD STUDY HABITS.
APPARENTLY I'M ALSO
A NATURAL LACROSSE PLAYER.
MS. H. WANTS ME
TO JOIN THE TEAM.
(GIGGLES)
MY OH MY.
YOU?
ON A SPORTS TEAM?
AIN'T GONNA HAPPEN.
LACROSSE IS FOR LOSERS.
YEAH, THERE'S THE BITTER GIRL
THAT I KNOW.
THE BITTER LONER
YOU USED TO KNOW
IS TRYING TO BE A LITTLE
SWEETER THESE DAYS.
WELL, SWEETIE,
A TIGER CAN'T CHANGE
ITS STRIPES OVERNIGHT.
SPINNER, I HAVE TO READ
AN ENTIRE NOVEL -
A RUSSIAN ONE.
YEAH, CAN YOU GUYS
FIND ANOTHER PLACE
TO SET UP SHOP?
GOOD IDEA, MARCO!
THAT'S FUNNY,
WE JUST PASSED ONE
ON THE STREET.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
ALL SET, JIM?
YEAH.
DUDE, ASK HIM.
DAD...
WE HAVE THIS LITTLE
BUSINESS.
IT'S UH...THESE T-SHIRTS
WITH MY DESIGNS,
AND PEOPLE ARE REALLY
DIGGING THE ART.
OH, GOOD FOR YOU,
SON.
I'M NOT CRAZY
ABOUT THE COLOUR,
BUT UH...
PUT ME DOWN FOR ONE.
WE ALSO THOUGHT WE COULD
TAKE IT TO THE NEXT LEVEL
AND OPEN UP A SHOP.
MAKE IT LEGIT,
YOU KNOW?
SO I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU'D MIND
IF I DIPPED INTO
MY ACADEMIC FUND?
SON, YOU CAN'T AFFORD TO CHASE
THESE LITTLE DREAMS.
THE ANSWER IS NO.
I'LL BE IN THE CAR.
I DON'T EVEN NEED
MY DAD'S PERMISSION
TO ACCESS MY FUND.
WE'RE GONNA DO THIS, SPIN.
WE'RE GONNA OPEN THIS SHOP.
DOES THAT SOUND GOOD?
DUDE, THAT'S LIKE...
THAT'S LIKE MY TEN
FAVOURITE SONGS
PLAYING AT THE SAME TIME,
TURNED UP TO ELEVEN.
SPINNER:
HI.
YO, CHECK OUT THAT STORE!
HEY!
JIMMY, MAN,
THIS IS INCREDIBLE.
WELL, IT AIN'T PRETTY,
BUT THE CUSTOMERS
DON'T SEEM TO MIND.
I JUST CANNOT BELIEVE
WE'RE MAKING THE MONEY.
I MEAN,
IF THIS THING TAKES OFF?
I COULD PAY MY OWN WAY
TO ART SCHOOL.
ART SCHOOL?
WHAT HAPPENED TO PRE-LAW?
NYU?
I DON'T KNOW.
I-I JUST THINK MAYBE
THIS ART THING
COULD WORK OUT,
YOU KNOW?
HOW COOL WOULD THAT BE?
VERY COOL.
AS LONG AS WE'RE
TOGETHER
AND YOU'RE HAPPY,
IT'S ALL GOOD.
MAN, WE'RE GONNA BE FAMOUS
FASHION DESIGNERS.
JUST LIKE DUTCHIE
AND GABBANA.
MARCO:
YEAH, THAT'S UH...
DOLCE AND GABBANA, SPIN.
YOU KNOW, THE GAY
FASHION DESIGNERS?
YEAH,
EXCEPT... NOT SO GAY.
YOU GUYS TAKE DEBIT?
CASH ONLY,
MY FRIEND.
THEY'LL BE BACK.
MS. HATZILAKOS:
OKAY GUYS,
THAT WAS GOOD FOCUS
AND GOOD PASSING.
AH...HERE'S OUR RINGER!
SO YOU READY TO HELP
WITH THE TEAM?
NOTHING I LOVE MORE
THAN GIVING UP MY WEEKEND...
FOR THE TEAM.
MOST OF YOU PROBABLY
KNOW ALEX.
SHE GRADUATED LAST YEAR,
SO WE ARE VERY LUCKY
TO HAVE HER BACK.
I CAN'T GET ENOUGH
OF THIS PLACE.
OKAY, LET'S CONTINUE
LOOSENING UP A LITTLE BIT.
LET'S DO SOME
PASSING DRILLS, OKAY?
STAY FOCUSED, GUYS!
HEY, BABY CARROTS.
LOOKS LIKE
WE'RE TEAMMATES.
YEAH. DOESN'T MEAN
I HAVE TO TALK TO YOU.
MARCO:
(UNINTELLGIBLE COMMENT)
WE SOLD A TRUCKLOAD.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS DAY.
ASHLEY:
WHEN THESE GUYS ARE FAMOUS?
THEY'D BETTER REMEMBER
THEIR FRIENDS.
OKAY. THIS SHOULD IMPROVE
THE SNACKS AROUND HERE.
MM, YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO,
JIMMY.
SPEAK FOR YOURSELF.
AFTER MARCO'S DAD'S CUT
FOR THE T-SHIRTS?
THE REST IS PURE GRAVY.
DYLAN:
AH, NOT TO BE A KILLJOY,
BUT I'VE TAKEN
SOME BUSINESS CLASSES.
YOU'VE GOT TAXES,
BOOKKEEPING,
INSURANCE,
OVERHEAD,
AND HYDRO.
DUDE, OUR GRAVY!
I GUESS WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
♪♪♪
SIRINA, I'M OPEN!
OVER HERE!
COME ON!
♪♪♪
(BUZZER GOES)
(CHEERING)
SPINNER:
RIIIING!
SQUATCH DESIGNS.
WHAT CAN I PUT YOU DOWN FOR?
A HUNDRED?
SUPER!
YOU'VE BEEN BUSY.
AH, YOU KNOW,
JUST SAVING THE STORE!
YOU DOUBLED
THE PRICES?
YEAH, TO RECOUP
OUR COSTS TWICE AS FAST.
JIMMY:
SPIN, LOOK AROUND.
YOU'RE DRIVING
BUSINESS AWAY.
AT LEAST I'M TRYING.
YEAH, TOO HARD!
SPIN...
LOOK, I'VE BEEN THINKING.
MAYBE THIS IS A BAD IDEA.
MAYBE MY DAD WAS RIGHT?
NO, HE WAS WRONG.
AND WE'LL SEE JUST HOW WRONG
AND LAUGH
IN 10 YEARS,
WHEN WE'RE SIPPING COGNAC
ON OUR FLY COMPANY YACHT.
SPINNER, WAKE UP!
THERE'S NO YACHT,
OKAY?
IN TEN YEARS, I WILL BE
PRACTICING LAW IN NEW YORK
AND YOU WILL BE TWISTING
BALLOON ANIMALS
IN NORTH YORK!
LOOK, LET'S JUST FIX
THESE TAGS, PLEASE,
AND SELL EVERYTHING WE HAVE
ON THE SHELVES,
AND WE'LL BE DONE.
YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU DO IT.
I'M ON BREAK.
SIRINA!
SO YOU FINALLY
REMEMBERED MY NAME.
MS. HATZILAKOS TOLD ME.
SHE ALSO TOLD ME
THAT YOU AND I HAVE
TO GET ALONG.
SO...?
GO TEAM GO!
I'M TRYING TO BE NICE HERE.
PLEASE!
YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE NOT FOOLING ANYONE.
YOU'RE A HATEFUL BITCH,
ALEX.
IT'S ALL YOU'RE EVER
GONNA BE.
MS. HATZILAKOS:
ALEX!
MY OFFICE.
NOW!
HEY, WHAT'S UP?
FEEL FREE TO LOOK AROUND.
WE'VE GOT SOME COOL TEES HERE.
SO JUST IGNORE THE PRICES,
I'M STILL FIXING THEM.
IT'S NOT THE TEES
THAT I'M INTERESTED IN.
JIMMY:
HEY!
(GRUNTS OF EFFORT)
JIMMY:
SPINNER! HELP!
(PAINED GROANS)
MOVE AND I BREAK IT
IN HALF.
I OWE YOU ONE.
THEY'RE NOT POISONED.
AND THEY MAKE GREAT
PROJECTILES.
(SIGHS)
I GOT A WEEK'S
WORTH DETENTION.
THAT SHOULD
MAKE YOU HAPPY.
YOU REALLY DON'T REMEMBER,
DO YOU?
AM I IN
THE TWILIGHT ZONE?
NO.
I DON'T KNOW YOU, SIRINA.
TWO YEARS AGO
YOU ALMOST BLINDED ME
WITH A LASER POINTER
DURING MY FIRST
AND LAST DEBATE.
OR HOW ABOUT
WHEN YOU TRIPPED ME
ON THE WAY TO THE CAF.
I SPRAINED MY ANKLE,
AND I HAD TO QUIT
THE TEAM.
IT WASN'T PERSONAL.
YOU COULD HAVE
BEEN ANYBODY.
BUT IT WAS ME.
A REAL PERSON.
YOU MADE MY LIFE HELL.
AND THE WORST PART?
YOU DON'T EVEN
REMEMBER DOING IT.
COP:
HECK OF A TAKEDOWN THERE,
CHIEF.
YOU GUYS'LL GET
THAT VENDOR'S LICENCE
BEFORE YOU OPEN UP
AGAIN?
JIMMY:
ACTUALLY, WE UH...
WE WON'T NEED IT.
WE'RE GONNA CLOSE SHOP
PERMANENTLY.
COP:
WE'LL BE IN TOUCH.
YOU KNOW, YOU HAVE NO IDEA
HOW LUCKY YOU ARE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT GUY COULD
HAVE KILLED ME.
I'M NOT I'M TALKING
ABOUT THAT.
I'M TALKING ABOUT THIS!
LOOK AT THAT DESIGN.
IT'S AWESOME.
PEOPLE LOVE IT.
I WOULD GIVE ANYTHING TO
HAVE WHAT YOU HAVE, JIMMY -
TALENT.
WHO SAYS YOU DON'T?
I JUST WATCHED YOU
TAKE DOWN SOME DUDE
LIKE JACK BAUER IN THERE,
MAN.
THAT WAS SICK.
IF THAT AIN'T TALENT...
DUDE.
YEAH, I GUESS I AM
A CRIME-FIGHTING SUPER STUD.
YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
MR. BROOKS:
OFFICER, WHAT'S-
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
WELL, IT SEEMS TO ME
THERE WAS A ROBBERY
IN THIS LOCATION.
HE LOOKS PISSED.
JUST WAIT TILL I TELL HIM
WHERE I GOT THE MONEY
FOR THIS PLACE.
MAN,
I AM A DEAD MAN ROLLING.
DUDE, I JUST FACED DOWN
A ROBBER.
I THINK YOU CAN
FACE DOWN YOUR DAD.
THANKS.
I APPRECIATE IT.
JIM, I'M SO RELIEVED
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET YOU HOME NOW, OKAY?
OKAY.
DAD, UH... JUST WAIT.
WE GOTTA TALK.