(FIRE ALARM RINGS)
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED.
I WAS STUDYING
AND THEN SUDDENLY,
I'M STARING INTO
DANTE'S INFERNO.
THIS COULD'VE BEEN
A LOT WORSE.
(SIGHS) KEVIN,
YOU ARE MY FIREFIGHTING
RESIDENCE ASSISTANT HERO.
I'M NOT GOING TO FIND
MELTED WAX
IN THE BOTTOM OF THIS
TRASH CAN, AM I?
UM... VERBOTEN CANDLE?
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
MY COMPUTER, IT MUST'VE
SPONTANEOUSLY COMBUSTED.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
YOU CAN CRASH IN
THE COMMON ROOM TONIGHT.
YOU MAY HAVE TO LIVE THERE
A WHILE.
I HAVE GOT TO DO A,
A 20 PAGE ESSAY AND...
AND ACE
A TAKE-HOME EXAM
AND DO A MILLION
CHAPTER SUMMARIES
BEFORE 5:00,
OR I'M A BIG, FAT,
FLUNKING-OUT FAILURE!
WELL, THEY ALWAYS SAY
EVERYTHING LOOKS BETTER
IN THE MORNING.
WELL, THAT'S ONLY TRUE
IF YOUR ENTIRE WORLD
HASN'T ALREADY GONE SUPERNOVA!
(CHOKING BREATHS)
♪♪♪
I JUST NEED A FEW MORE DAYS.
THERE WAS A TEENSY WEENSY FIRE
AND A BIG FAMILY EMERGENCY.
(PHONE RINGS)
ALEX?
GUESS WHO JUST GOT HER THIRD
BIO A-PLUS IN A ROW?
HEATHER SINCLAIR?
ALEX:
OUCH. DESERVED.
ANY CHANCE A MARKETING GURU
CAN FORGIVE A SCIENCE GEEK
FOR BEING AN OBNOXIOUS TURKEY?
ARE YOU ACTUALLY
APOLOGIZING?
I'M FULL OF SURPRISES.
I'M STILL KINDA WORRIED
ABOUT YOUR WHOLE FAMILY DINNER
FLAME OUT.
APOLOGY ACCEPTED.
AND I COULD NOT BE
MORE FINE, HONESTLY.
LAST MINUTE
IS MY MIDDLE NAME.
BUT ENOUGH ABOUT ME -
AH, GO CELEBRATE
YOUR SCHOLAR-NESS.
ANY A-PLUS PLANS?
CARLA'S MEETING ME
AT THE DOT TONIGHT.
NOTHING SPECIAL,
BUT SHE'S PAYING.
WELL, CONGRATS, HON.
AH, SEND HER MY LOVE,
OKAY?
ALEX:
LATER.
PROFESSOR JANES.
MS. MICHALCHUK,
FINISHED ALREADY?
I GAVE YOU UNTIL 5:00 TODAY.
PAIGE:
UM...
ACTUALLY, UH,
YOU KNOW HOW IT IS,
FAMILY WEEKEND,
PARENTAL DRAMA,
AND A MINOR DORM ROOM
FIRE-TYPE INCIDENT.
I WAS HOPING FOR ANOTHER
VERY SMALL EXTENSION.
I JUST WOULDN'T
WANT TO HAND IN
LESS THAN MY BEST.
A FIRE?
DO YOU HAVE
THE FIRE MARSHALL'S REPORT?
NO, BUT I HAVE SOOT-FILLED
EVERYTHING AS PROOF.
BELIEVE ME,
I WOULDN'T MAKE THIS UP.
I JUST THOUGHT THAT MAYBE
UNDER THE CIRCUMSTANCES...?
I CAN'T MAKE LAST MINUTE
EXCEPTIONS, PAIGE.
YOU UNDERSTAND THAT,
I'M SURE.
(SIGHS)
I GUESS I HAVE TO.
HAND IN WHATEVER YOU'VE GOT.
I'LL SEE YOU AT 5:00.
NO EXCUSES.
(PANICKY BREATHS)
MR. STONE:
IMPOUNDED?!
THE $60,000 VEHICLE
YOU SNUCK OUT OF MY GARAGE
HAS BEEN IMPOUNDED!
I WAS ON MY WAY HOME
FROM FEEDING THE HOMELESS;
DOING A GOOD DEED?
MRS. HATZILAKOS:
I DON'T CARE IF YOU WERE
CURING THE BLIND, OKAY?
A SUSPENDED LICENSE MEANS
NO DRIVING PERIOD!
MR. STONE:
THE PROBATION OFFICER SAYS
IF YOU UP
THE COMMUNITY SERVICE,
THEY MIGHT REDUCE
THE FINE.
'KAY, FINE.
I'LL BE AN ANGEL.
WELL, YOU MAKE SURE
THAT YOU ARE!
HERE!
MRS. HATZILAKOS:
AND TROY?
IF YOU CAN'T CONTROL PETER
ON THE WEEKENDS,
THEN I WILL.
MR. STONE:
HEY, DAPHNE,
SAVE THE PRINCIPAL ROUTINE
FOR YOUR DELINQUENT SON,
OKAY?
MRS. HATZILAKOS:
WHO'S DELINQUENT?
HOW ABOUT THE GUY WHO BOUGHT
HIS 16-YEAR-OLD SON
A $60,000 CAR.
PETER:
GUYS, STOP!
MRS. HATZILAKOS:
WHO'RE YOU TRYING TO IMPRESS?
(SIGHS) OKAY,
ONE THING AT A TIME.
(EXHALES)
I SEE YOUR LAPTOP SURVIVED.
ANY CHANCE I COULD
CHECK MY BLOG?
UH, SAVING MY SEMESTER
BY 5:00 P.M.
IS A TAD MORE IMPORTANT
THAN YOUR BLOG.
RIGHT.
STUPID QUESTION.
SO UH...
YOU ALMOST DONE?
(SIGHS)
NOT REMOTELY.
BETTER HURRY UP.
TICK-TOCK.
(INAUDIBLE P.A. ANNOUNCEMENT)
WHAT'S THIS?
BUS PASS.
ONCE I WALKED
ALL THE WAY HOME,
I KINDA COOLED DOWN.
OH, WOW.
AFTER THE COP
PULLED US OVER,
I DIDN'T THINK YOU'D BE
SPEAKING TO ME ANYMORE,
LET ALONE
BUYING ME GIFTS.
SO YOU FORGIVE ME
FOR SMOTHERING YOU
WITH PIE?
IT WAS STUPID TO DRIVE.
BUT I HAD TO GET
TO THE SOUP KITCHEN.
I COULDN'T LET
THE HOMELESS STARVE.
WERE YOUR PARENTS MAD
ABOUT THE CAR?
(SIGHS)
THEY'RE OFF THE CHARTS.
BLAME EACH OTHER
FOR EVERYTHING.
(FAKE TEARING UP)
I TRY TO BE BRAVE
OR WHATEVER,
BUT DEEP DOWN,
THERE'S THIS LITTLE,
SAD... (CHUCKLES)
HEY, HOW ABOUT A NICE
LONG WALK IN THE PARK,
AFTER SCHOOL?
ARE YOU ASKING ME OUT
ON A DATE?
DEPENDS ON YOUR ANSWER.
THAT WAS A "YES", RIGHT?
PAIGE:
PROFESSOR JANES?
HERE IT IS.
5:00 P.M.
RIGHT ON TIME.
SOMETIMES I WORK BEST
UNDER PRESSURE!
(SIGHS)
I HAVE SEEN THIS ESSAY
FOUR TIMES
IN THE LAST TWO YEARS.
MOST STUDENTS TRY TO CHANGE
A SENTENCE OR TWO.
PROFESSOR JANES,
WITH THREE HUNDRED STUDENTS,
THESE ESSAYS MUST ALL
JUST START TO LOOK THE SAME.
DON'T INSULT ME.
YOU'RE GIVING ME A ZERO?
OR I COULD TALK
TO THE DEAN.
WHO, BY THE WAY,
HAS MADE IT HIS MISSION
TO ERADICATE PLAGIARISM.
YOUR CHOICE.
MY CHOICE?
I'M GOING HOME...
TO A REAL SCHOOL,
WITH REAL FRIENDS,
WITH FLAME RETARDANT DORMS!
I DON'T CARE IF I AM
A STUPID BANTING GIRL
BECAUSE I HATE BANTING!
PETER:
FOR YOU.
NOT SOUP KITCHEN DECORATIONS
THIS TIME.
AWW... (SNIFFS)
MY FAVOURITE WEED.
I THOUGHT THEY WERE
FLOWERS?
UH... WHAT'S ALL THIS?
PETER:
BEAUTIFUL DAY FOR A WALK!
(LAUGH OF DISBELIEF)
WAIT,
THIS IS YOUR IDEA
OF A DATE?
PETER:
YEAH! IT'S COMMUNITY SERVICE,
BUT IT'S ALSO DOING GOOD.
ISN'T THAT HOW YOU ROLL?
OH, I MEANT TO ASK,
DO YOU THINK YOU COULD
GET THE REVEREND
TO SIGN SOME FORMS
FOR LAST WEEKEND?
SO THAT'S WHAT THIS IS?
I'M YOUR COMMUNITY SERVICE
HOOKUP?
WHAT? DARCE,
THIS IS MY LIFE.
I THOUGHT YOU GOT
THAT NOBODY'S PERFECT.
MMM.
WHAT'S WRONG, PICKY?
I THOUGHT WE WERE
CELEBRATING.
YEAH, WELL, AREN'T SALADS
SUPPOSED TO BE FRESH?
THIS IS DISGUSTING.
WELL, MAYBE IF YOU
TRIED RED MEAT,
YOU WOULDN'T BE
SO CRANKY.
YOU ARE UNBELIEVABLE.
ISN'T SHE?
HUMAN TRASH COMPACTOR.
EITHER YOU'RE IN TORONTO
MID-WEEK
OR THIS AIN'T ROOT BEER.
DINNER'S ON ME.
UH... OKAY, MY MOM.
TO ALEX, THE NEWEST SCHOLAR
ON DEGRASSI'S BLOCK.
YOU DROVE THREE HOURS
TO POACH MY DRINK?
YEAH, YOU MUST'VE BEEN
THIRSTY.
I DROVE THREE HOURS
FOR A GREAT REASON,
BUT TONIGHT IS ALL ABOUT
MS. A-PLUS,
THE BRIGHTEST NUNEZ EVER.
OH, YOU KNOW SHE TURNED DOWN
PARADISO BISTRO
TO COME HERE.
I'M NOT SAYING
SHE'S PERFECT.
(CHUCKLES)
SHOULD I LEAVE
YOU TWO ALONE?
PAIGE:
YEAH, WELL,
I WANNA HEAR
ALL ABOUT A DAY
IN THE LIFE
OF AN HONOURS GRAD
MARATHON RUNNER
AT TORONTO U.
WELL, IT'S, IT'S NOT
THAT INTERESTING REALLY.
ALEX:
QUESTION OF THE NIGHT:
WHY AREN'T YOU SLEEPING
AT MARCO'S AND DYLAN'S?
WELL, EVERYONE'S BACK
FROM THE WEEKEND;
IT'S A FULL HOUSE.
AND WHY ARE YOU
IN TOWN?
BECAUSE PEOPLE HERE
DON'T ASK A MILLION QUESTIONS?
NICE TRY,
MICHALCHUK.
I DON'T KNOW.
IT WAS SO CHAOTIC
WITH ALL THE FAMILY
AND THE SCHOOLWORK
I WAS JUST
CRAVING SOME HAPPY;
SOME YOU.
HON, WE'RE GONNA STAY
THIS CLOSE FOREVER, RIGHT?
DEPENDS. ARE YOU GONNA
SCREAM AT ME
FROM BEHIND ANY
BATHROOM DOORS?
(CHORTLES)
BUT SEE, I DID THAT,
AND THREE DAYS LATER
YOU'RE MAKING ME A COUCH-BED.
I'M CRAZY,
AND YOU'RE SO STRONG.
EVEN PERFECT BANTING GIRLS
NEED TO LET THEIR HAIR DOWN
ONCE IN A WHILE.
(SIGHS)
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO HAS ANY IDEA.
WELL, IT'S A SCHOOL NIGHT.
I'LL TUCK YOU IN.
WHAT WAS THAT?
UM...
GOOD NIGHT KISS?
PENANCE WAFFLES?
WITH EXTRA
"I'M SORRY" WHIP.
AND "I WOULD
NEVER INTENTIONALLY
PLAY WITH YOUR FEELINGS"
STRAWBERRIES.
MY FOOD USUALLY
ONLY SAYS,
"EAT ME."
WELL YOUR MOM AND CHAD
CALLED THEM
"LITTLE PUFFS OF HEAVEN."
AND THEY WERE MADE
BY SUCH AN ANGEL.
ARE WE GOING TO
TALK ABOUT
WHAT THAT LITTLE
SMOOCHY-SMOOCH
WAS ALL ABOUT
LAST NIGHT?
OH, YOU MEAN THAT THING
THAT NEVER HAPPENED?
OKAY...
YOU'VE DRIVEN HERE
TWICE THIS WEEK.
AND FOR WHAT?
TO COOK A COUPLE OF MEALS?
IT SEEMS KINDA STRANGE,
EVEN FOR YOU.
OKAY, VERONICA MARS,
I MISS HOME.
(SCOFFS) OKAY,
WHAT'S IN THESE WAFFLES?
PAIGE:
NOTHING. I'M JUST...
I'M HAPPY,
AND I HAVE A PLAN.
IS TONIGHT STILL
KARAOKE NIGHT?
UH HUH.
PAIGE:
WELL, THEN ROUND UP
THE TROOPS.
I HAVE A FEELING
I'LL NEED TO CELEBRATE.
I KNEW I WASN'T THE ONLY REASON
YOU CAME BACK.
DO I EVEN GET A HINT?
HERE. THE REVEREND
HOPES TO SEE YOU
AT THE NEXT SOUP KITCHEN.
WAIT, DARCY,
I HATE SOUP.
I HATE DOG TURDS
EVEN MORE,
BUT I LIKE YOU.
I HAVE FUN WITH YOU.
YOU'RE UNDER
HOUSE ARREST.
I'VE GOT SPIRIT SQUAD,
FRIENDSHIP CLUB.
PLUS, I'M STILL GROUNDED
THANKS TO THOSE WEB PHOTOS.
I JUST DON'T
SEE IT WORKING.
SORRY.
PETER:
WAIT, WHO WAS THAT GUY
WHO WORKS IN MYSTERIOUS WAYS?
ADMISSIONS CLERK:
AWESOME HIGH SCHOOL RECORDS.
WELL, TORONTO U
ACCEPTED ME LAST SPRING,
SO, I WAS HOPING
I COULD TRANSFER.
WE'LL NEED YOUR BANTING
TRANSCRIPTS.
EVEN IF I TAKE
A DIFFERENT PROGRAM?
YEAH.
UNLESS YOU WANNA REAPPLY
FOR THE FALL.
NEXT FALL?
MY MOM WILL DIE -
I'M TALKING CARDIAC ARREST -
AND THEN SHE'S GOING TO KILL ME
FROM BEYOND THE GRAVE.
WELL,
FROSH OFTEN FLOUNDER.
FLOUNDER?
NO, NO ,NO.
I CAN'T FLOUNDER.
I CAN'T BE THIS PERSON:
HORRIBLE GRADES,
SOCIAL OUTCAST,
GAINED THE FRESHMAN
FIFTEEN-ZILLION.
IN THREE MONTHS,
BANTING HAS TURNED ME
INTO A...
A CHUNKY, ESSAY-FLUNKING
PYROMANIAC!
I'M GUESSING BANTING
ISN'T THE PROBLEM.
SORRY.
NEXT.
(SOBBING)
PSST! DARCE, IT'S ME.
DARCY:
PETER?
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
I BELIEVE THE WORD IS ROMANCE.
YOU'RE GONNA GET US BOTH
IN SUGAR.
I DON'T CARE.
I'LL RISK ALL THE SUGAR
IN THE WORLD -
MY PROBATION,
MY HOUSE ARREST,
MY PARENTS LOSING THEIR MINDS -
JUST FOR ONE MINUTE
WITH YOU.
HEY, BE CAREFUL,
I WILL SING.
(CHORTLES) NO.
MY DAD HEARS YOU,
I'LL NEVER GET TO SEE YOU.
SO YOU WANNA SEE ME?
GO HOME, PETER.
♪♪♪
MARCO: (SINGING)
♪ I DON'T CHANGE MY MIND
FOR ANYBODY ♪
♪ I WON'T WASTE MY TIME
ON JUST ANYBODY ♪
♪ I WON'T SHARE MY LIFE
WITH ANYONE BUT YOU ♪
♪ WITH ANYONE BUT YOU ♪
PAIGE: (GIGGLING)
SORRY, I'M LATE.
UH, PINCHY BOOTS -
CUTE BUT SLOW.
AW, THAT'S LIKE SPINNER.
WHATEVER. I'LL TAKE THAT
AS A COMPLIMENT.
SO, ALEX SAYS
YOU'RE BACK IN TOWN
TO CELEBRATE.
YEAH. SO WHAT'S
THE AMAZING NEWS?
PAIGE:
UM...
WELL, YOURS TRULY JUST...
GOT A HUGE SCHOLARSHIP
TO TORONTO U!
I'M MOVING HOME.
MARCO:
IN THE MIDDLE
OF A SEMESTER?
PAIGE:
YEAH, THEY MADE AN EXCEPTION.
SO, ARE WE GONNA DO THIS
OR NOT?
MARCO:
YOU BET.
SPINNER:
BUST IT, MAESTRO!
MARCO AND PAIGE: (SINGING)
♪ I DON'T CHANGE MY MIND
FOR ANYBODY ♪
♪ I WON'T WASTE MY TIME
♪ I WON'T SHARE MY LIFE
WITH ANYONE BUT YOU ♪
ALEX:
SO WHEN ARE YOU
GONNA TELL ME
WHY YOU REALLY
LEFT BANTING?
PAIGE:
I ALREADY TOLD YOU.
ALEX:
YEAH.
BIG MID-SEMESTER SCHOLARSHIP.
THING IS,
YOU ALREADY HAD ONE.
BANTING IS NOT
WHAT I EXPECTED.
I MEAN I AM KICKING BUTT,
BUT IT'S SO LAME.
THERE'S NOT FUN TIMES
LIKE TONIGHT
AND DEFINITELY
NO FUN PEOPLE.
THAT'S IT?
PAIGE:
BANTING WAS GREAT FOR MY MOM,
BUT...
I HAVE CONNECTIONS HERE.
CONNECTIONS?
BY THAT YOU MEAN...?
MY FRIENDS,
PEOPLE WHO THINK
I COUNT FOR SOMETHING.
COOL PEOPLE.
OH...
MY PINCHY BOOTS.
UM... THERE SHOULD BE
PAPER TOWELS IN HERE SOMEWHERE.
MY DAD WENT ALL BOY SCOUT
WHEN I GOT THE CAR.
(SIGHS)
DID YOU FIND ANYTHING?
YEAH.
I SURE DID.
UGH! EW!
PETER:
OKAY. BYE, DAD.
HERE.
IT'S A DAY-TIMER.
I WROTE DOWN
ALL MY FREE TIME THIS WEEK.
YOU DO THE SAME
AND THAT'S WHEN I'LL SEE YOU.
COOL! THANKS.
OH, SO YOU'RE FREE TODAY
AFTER SCHOOL?
I HAVE AN HOUR
BEFORE I HAVE TO REPORT
TO MY PROBATION OFFICER.
IT'S A DATE.
MRS. HATZILAKOS:
OH. HERE YOU GO.
WHAT'S THIS?
DIRECTIONS TO A
"CONVICTED STREET RACERS"
PRESS CONFERENCE
AFTER SCHOOL.
I VOLUNTEERED YOU
TO GIVE AN APOLOGY.
TODAY?
YOU'VE GOT TO BE JOKING.
AND IF YOU'RE THINKING
ON SKIPPING, DON'T.
I'LL BE THERE.
TRASHMAN?
FORGET SOMETHING?
PETER:
YEAH, CAN'T LIVE WITHOUT THIS.
AND YOUR UNCLE'S
LOOKING FORWARD
TO SOME SQUEAKY CLEAN DISHES
AT HIS RESTAURANT
THIS WEEKEND.
PETER:
YEAH, AND EVERY OTHER WEEKEND.
I KNOW.
YOU KNOW ANOTHER WAY
TO MAKE THE FIVE GRAND
IT COST ME TO GET THE CAR
OUT OF IMPOUND?
MAYBE YOUR MOTHER'LL
TAKE A CUT
TO HER ALIMONY PAYMENTS.
LOVE YOU TOO!
MY OFFICE,
3:00 SHARP!
YEAH,
YOU WERE RIGHT.
THIS ISN'T GOING TO WORK.
(SIGHS)
PAIGE:
TWO BEDROOM,
ON THE SUBWAY LINE.
TWELVE HUNDRED.
OUCH.
TWO BEDROOM?
ISN'T IT TIME
YOU GAVE YOUR MOM
AND CHAD
THEIR PERSONAL SPACE?
HON, ARE YOU WAITING
FOR SOMEONE?
MAYBE.
WHO, CARLA?
LOOK, IF WE MOVE IN TOGETHER,
IT DOESN'T MEAN...
MOM?
HI.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
WE NEED TO TALK,
PAIGE.
YOU HAVE SOME
EXPLAINING TO DO.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
ALEX FOUND SOME ESSAYS,
SOME TESTS, IN YOUR CAR.
YOU DID THIS?
I'LL LET YOU GUYS TALK.
(PANICKY BREATHS)
(INAUDIBLE ANNOUNCEMENT
ON THE P.A.)
DARCY:
THOUGHT I'D FIND YOU HERE.
YEAH, I'M FORMING
A PERMANENT BUTT-GROOVE.
WHY ARE YOU HERE?
(SIGHS)
JUST SEEING YOUR PARENTS,
THE WAY FIGHT...
IT MUST BE HORRIBLE
TO FEEL LIKE
THEY'RE ALWAYS ANGRY.
JUST NOT A GREAT EXAMPLE
OF LOVE, I GUESS.
I KNOW SOMEONE WHO HAS
A LOT OF LOVE TO GIVE.
OKAY, NO OFFENCE,
BUT YOU BETTER NOT BE
TALKING ABOUT JESUS.
DARCE, I'M GONNA BE LATE
TO PICK YOU UP.
I'M GONNA BAIL ON DATES.
ALL THE DAY PLANNERS
IN THE WORLD
CAN'T CHANGE THAT.
BUT I'LL NEVER STOP
THINKING ABOUT YOU.
I HOPE NOT.
AND IF YOU EVER HURT ME?
I'LL TELL YOUR MOM.
(PLAYFUL HUFF)
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU TOLD MY MOTHER!
WHO ELSE WOULD I TELL?
(STAMMERS)
I DON'T KNOW!
NOBODY?
YOU NEED HELP,
PAIGE.
AND YOU NEEDED TO TELL
THE TRUTH TO SOMEONE.
IT WAS THE ONLY WAY
TO FORCE IT OUT.
WELL, WHY DIDN'T YOU
TALK TO ME FIRST?
PAIGE,
YOU'VE BEEN LYING TO ME
EVER SINCE YOU GOT HERE,
AND I HAVE NO IDEA WHY.
I'VE ALWAYS
KIND OF FELT LIKE...
YOU LOOKED UP TO ME.
AND I WANT YOU
TO BE PROUD OF ME,
BUT THE TRUTH IS
I'M JUST A...
A LOSER.
AND YOU USED ME TO PULL
SOME BIG, CRAZY SCAM?
(SIGHS)
I'M SORRY, ALEX.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHO ELSE
TO TURN TO.
WELL, NEXT TIME
YOU NEED A SAFETY NET,
CALL THE FIRE DEPARTMENT.
ACTUALLY, THEY'LL PROBABLY
BE CALLING ME.
I KINDA BURNED DOWN
MY DORM ROOM.
SERIOUSLY?
WOW.
WHEN YOU FLAME OUT,
YOU REALLY FLAME OUT.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
THAT'S THE THING, MISSY,
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?