SEAN:
WHOO! EMMA PLUS SEAN.
IT'S NEVER BORING.
FIRST THAT CAR RACE,
THEN THAT KISS.
IT JUST FELT SO RIGHT AND-
AND I HAVE A BOYFRIEND,
AND I FEEL TERRIBLE.
I DON'T DO THIS.
I'M NOT THAT KIND OF GIRL.
I KNOW.
THAT'S WHY I LIKE RESPECT YOU
AND WHATEVER.
WELL I'M GLAD I HAVE
YOUR "RESPECT OR WHATEVER".
I HAVE MORE THAN
JUST RESPECT FOR YOU.
YOU KNOW THAT, RIGHT?
PETER'S INSIDE.
I HAVE TO GO.
HELLO?
(DOOR SHUTS)
SO SHE MADE IT HOME
IN ONE PIECE.
WHERE'S SEAN?
IS HE COMING IN?
UH, NOPE.
HE'S JUST LEAVING.
HE HAD TO GO.
AW, MAN.
I WANTED TO SEE
WHAT HE THOUGHT ABOUT
THE BIG RACE.
ME BEATING JAY.
IT WAS AWESOME,
WASN'T IT?
UNTIL THE COPS
CRASHED THE PARTY.
SO YOUR CELL PHONE WAS OFF.
WE'VE BEEN CALLING.
WE WERE WORRIED.
SHE WAS WORRIED,
NOT ME.
♪♪♪
(RAP MUSIC)
SPINNER:
YO EMINEM, WHERE'S D12?
JIMMY:
DEGRASSI'S NEWEST MC:
2 WHITE, 2 FURIOUS.
SPINNER:
(LAUGHS)
PETER:
YO, CAM-SHAFT!
WHAT'S UP, DAWG?
YOU DOWN FOR ANOTHER
RACE TONIGHT?
UH, YOU'RE SURE EMMA
DOESN'T MIND
BEING DRAGGED TO
THE STREET RACES AGAIN?
SHE'D RATHER BLUDGEON
A BABY SEAL.
THAT'S WHY IT'S JUST
ME AND YOU, MY MAN.
I GOT CALCULUS.
I'M SORRY.
I CAN HELP, MAN.
I'M PRETTY SMART.
THANKS...
BUT NO THANKS.
P.A. ANNOUNCER:
ATTENTION STUDENTS!
WELCOME BACK!
HEARD THE WEATHER REPORT
FOR TODAY?
SUNNY WITH PARTIAL CLOUDS?
SLIGHT CHANCE OF CALCULUS
BEFORE LUNCH?
MANNY:
MORE LIKE DARK, STORMY,
CHANCE OF STREET RACING
IN THE AFTERNOON,
FOLLOWED BY MORE SECRET
MAKE OUT SESSIONS WITH SEAN.
STICK TO ACTING,
MANNY,
'CAUSE YOU'RE A LOUSY
WEATHER GIRL.
SO YOU'RE SAYING
NOTHING HAPPENED?
FOR THE GAZILLIONTH TIME,
YES.
I MEAN, NO.
I'M WITH PETER.
SEAN IS TOTALLY
NOT EVEN ANYTHING.
SO WHO'S ACTING NOW?
(CRASH)
HEY.
COME ON.
ARE YOU CRAZY?
WE'RE GONNA BE LATE
FOR HOMEROOM.
JUST GIVE ME A SECOND.
I HAD TO GIVE YOU SOMETHING.
EMMA:
THEY'RE GORGEOUS.
BUT HOW DO I POSSIBLY
EXPLAIN THEM TO PETER?
I HADN'T THOUGHT
ABOUT THAT.
THERE ARE A LOT
OF NICE,
ATTRACTIVE GIRLS
AT DEGRASSI.
THANKS, MOM.
OR WHAT ABOUT ELLIE?
YOU GUYS WERE HOT
AND HEAVY FOR A WHILE.
FORGET ELLIE.
I KNOW WHO I WANT.
I THINK YOU DO TOO.
COUNSELOR:
THREE RESIDENCE SPOTS
HAVE OPENED UP.
HOWDEN, MICHELLE.
ROOM 206.
AGUIAR, COLIN.
ROOM 416.
AND NASH, ELEANOR.
BOTH:
NASH!
MARCO:
YES!
CONGRATS, ELEANOR.
THANK YOU!
HOT GUY:
HEY.
HI.
(EXCITED GASP)
UH...
UM...
WELL, IT'S COSY.
AND HEY,
YOU HAVE A ROOMMATE...
FROM YESTERYEAR.
ELEANOR?!
I'M YOUR NEW ROOMIE,
AMBERLEY!
ELLIE, ACTUALLY.
(SELF-CONSCIOUS LAUGH)
(WORRIED LAUGH)
UM, THIS IS MY FRIEND,
MARCO.
OH CUTE!
YOU'D BETTER TIE YOUR SCARF
AROUND THE DOORKNOB
WHEN HE'S OVER.
HI, I'M GAY.
AMBERLEY:
OH MY GOD, REALLY?
ELEANOR, YOU ARE ALREADY
SO MUCH COOLER
THAN MY LAST ROOMMATE.
SUCH A SOURPUSS.
OH!
IT'S FOR ALL
THE AMAZING MEMORIES
WE'RE GOING TO BE MAKING
THIS YEAR.
(POLITE LAUGH) OH.
AMBERLEY, UH...
ELEANOR HERE IS JUST
SUPER DUPER
AT MAKING MEMORIES.
YOU TWO ARE GONNA BE
SO HAPPY TOGETHER.
HAPPY.
(FAKE LAUGH)
YAY.
(GIGGLES)
WHAT'S WITH THE FROWN,
MISS MOPEY?
EM!
YOU SAID NOTHING HAPPENED.
I SORTA LIED.
JUST DON'T PUNCH ME, OKAY?
MY ARM IS STILL HURTING
FROM YESTERDAY.
WHY, EM? WHY?
IT WAS ALL GOING SO WELL.
YOU AND PETER WERE PERFECT.
MANNY,
YOU NEVER LIKED PETER.
STILL DON'T AT ALL.
BUT HE'S BEEN GOOD TO YOU,
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU WERE SICK.
LIKE I DON'T FEEL
GUILTY ENOUGH.
MANNY:
IT'S NOT ABOUT GUILT.
IT'S ABOUT YOU NOT
MESSING UP YOUR LIFE.
YOU ARE NOT GOING BACK
TO REXIEVILLE EMMA NELSON,
NOT ON MY WATCH.
I WON'T.
I PROMISE.
I JUST...
I HAVE A LITTLE
ROMANTIC DILEMMA,
WHICH I'LL FIGURE OUT,
OKAY?
I GOT DRIPPED ON
BY SOMETHING GREEN AND LIVING
ON THE BATHROOM CEILING.
AMBERLEY:
OOH! FUNGUS-MOLD.
ICKY-WICKY.
IS THIS SUPPOSED TO BE FOOD?
UH...
SOME KIND
OF DELICIOUS CHOWDER?
LOOKS LIKE SOMEBODY
ALREADY ATE IT.
WELL YOU'RE TAKING JOURNALISM,
RIGHT?
SOUNDS LIKE
YOUR FIRST ARTICLE.
YEAH.
WHAT HAPPENED TO MY PRINT?
OOH... PRINT?
I HOPE NO ONE STOLE IT.
MY THINGS.
YOU...YOU UNPACKED THEM?
(SELF-CONSCIOUS EXHALE)
SOMETIMES PEOPLE NEED A PUSH.
THAT'S WHAT MY GRAN-GRAN SAYS,
AND GRAN-GRAN KNOWS EVERYTHING.
(QUIETLY TO HERSELF)
OKAY.
BOO!
HEY, UH, YOU TOOK OFF
AFTER SCHOOL.
I WANTED TO GIVE YOU
A LIFT.
YEAH, SO SEAN TOTALLY
BAILED ON ME.
SO YOU WANNA HANG?
MAYBE GO TO THE RACES?
EMMA:
RAIN CHEQUE. I...
I JUST NEED TO BE
BY MYSELF TONIGHT.
EM.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOU'RE EATING RIGHT?
I DIDN'T SEE YOU AT LUNCH.
YES, I AM EATING.
I WASN'T AT LUNCH BECAUSE...
I JUST NEED MY OWN SPACE
RIGHT NOW.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN SPACE?
FROM ME?
I JUST THINK MAYBE WE SHOULD
TAKE A LITTLE HIATUS.
NOTHING MAJOR.
YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
I'M SORRY.
I JUST NEED A BREAK.
IT'S NOTHING TO DO FREAK OVER.
DON'T TELL ME NOT TO FREAK.
YOU'RE DUMPING ME.
I DIDN'T SAY I WAS!
YOU'RE NOT UNDERSTANDING ME.
NO, I THINK I AM.
IT'S SEAN, ISN'T IT?
GOD, I'M SO STUPID.
HOW COULD I TRUST THAT GUY?
PETER, STOP IT.
IT'S NOT SEAN'S FAULT.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
HOW IT HAPPENED.
WELL DID YOU HAVE
SEX WITH HIM?
NO!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'D EVEN ASK ME THAT!
I'M NOT SOME KIND OF SLUT.
COULD'VE FOOLED ME.
NO, EM,
I DIDN'T MEAN IT.
OKAY, FINE!
GOOD LUCK WITH SEAN!
HE IS NOT WHO
YOU THINK HE IS.
(ANGRY KICK)
JESSE:
IF YOU'RE LOOKING
FOR FREE CONDOMS,
HEALTH CLINIC'S NEXT DOOR.
ELLIE:
NO, I'M GOOD, THANKS.
I WAS WONDERING HOW TO GET
SOMETHING PUBLISHED.
FOUND THE RIGHT PERSON.
I'M JESSE. EDITOR.
WRITTEN BEFORE?
ELLIE:
CO-OP STUFF THAT I DID
IN HIGH SCHOOL.
YOU'RE FROSH?
YEAH, WE DON'T GIVE ASSIGNMENTS
TO FRESHMEN,
NOT UNLESS THEY HAVE SOMETHING
TOTALLY GENIUS.
WELL I DO HAVE
SOMETHING.
UM, IT'S A FIRST PERSON
REPORTAGE ON DORM LIFE.
I THINK IT'S KIND
OF FUNNY.
NOT LAUGHING.
GETS BETTER.
SO I'LL JUST LEAVE IT THERE
AND MAYBE YOU'LL READ IT.
BUT IF YOU DO PRINT IT,
UM, IT'S GOT TO BE ANONYMOUS.
I WAS KINDA
A LITTLE BIT HARSH.
A LOT HARSH.
YOU'RE STILL HERE?
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
SEAN CAMERON?
SEAN:
THERE'S NOTHING IN THERE,
MS. H.
I TOLD YOU,
I'M JUST FOLLOWING UP
ON A TIP.
SO LET'S GET THIS
OVER WITH.
THAT'S NOT MINE.
MS. H, I SWEAR TO YOU,
YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE ME.
I THINK THE EVIDENCE
SPEAKS FOR ITSELF.
EMMA:
SEAN, WAIT!
WAIT!
I'M SUSPENDED INDEFINITELY.
I DON'T GET IT.
WHO WOULD DO THIS?
WHO WOULD PLANT DRUGS
IN MY LOCKER?
WHO HATES ME THAT MUCH?
DID YOU TELL PETER?
ABOUT US?
YES. BUT-
HE DID THIS!
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
YEAH?
HE'S THE PRINCIPAL'S SON.
HE PROBABLY FIGURED SOME WAY
TO GET INTO MY LOCKER.
DO YOU KNOW HOW PARANOID
THAT SOUNDS?
THEN WHO?
WHO ELSE PLANTED IT?
OH.
YOU THINK THEY'RE MINE.
YOU THINK I ACTUALLY
SELL DRUGS?
NO, BUT...
YOU DID BUY ME SOME
VERY EXPENSIVE EARRINGS.
(INCREDULOUS GASP)
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU JUST
CALLED ME A DRUG DEALER.
I DIDN'T.
YOU KNOW WHAT, EMMA?
GO TO HELL!
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
THERE I AM.
THERE I REALLY AM.
JESSE, I SAID THE BYLINE
HAD TO BE ANONYMOUS.
WHY? YOU DON'T STAND
BY WHAT YOU WROTE?
BUT I TRASHED
THE HOUSING DEPARTMENT.
THE ADMINISTRATION?
AND THAT ROOMMATE OF YOURS.
(CHUCKLES)
"GRAN-GRAN."
OH, YOU WERE RIGHT.
IT WAS FUNNY.
WON'T BE TO HER.
HEY, YOU WANT TO BE
A JOURNALIST?
THAT'S THE NAME
OF THE GAME.
IT'S ABOUT TELLING THE TRUTH,
NO MATTER WHAT.
(SIGHS)
FROSH, I'LL MAKE IT
UP TO YOU, OKAY?
YOU CAN COVER
THE TUITION RALLY.
LIKE, AN ACTUAL NEWS STORY?
YOU STILL HERE?
(HAPPY GIGGLE)
HEY.
HEARD THE NEWS.
HOW'S SEAN?
WHERE IS HE?
PROBABLY FAR AWAY
FROM HERE.
WELL, IF YOU SPEAK TO HIM,
TELL HIM I'LL DO
WHATEVER I CAN.
LIKE I'LL TALK TO MY MOM.
I'LL DO ANYTHING.
DID YOU KNOW ABOUT THIS?
I MEAN, THE DRUGS?
I KNEW HE WAS INTO
SOME STUFF, YEAH.
I JUST DIDN'T KNOW
HOW DEEP.
HE THINKS YOU DID IT.
WHAT?
OKAY, SEAN IS MY FRIEND.
YEAH, I WAS HURT,
BUT LIKE...
I WOULD NEVER.
AND I DON'T KNOW WHO MADE
THAT TIP...
MAYBE HE RIPPED SOMEONE OFF
ON A DRUG DEAL OR SOMETHING.
I DON'T KNOW.
EM.
ABOUT YESTERDAY.
I'M SO SORRY.
ME TOO.
(TOOLS CLATTER)
(BANG)
(WHACK)
YEAH, I WAS GOING
TO USE THOSE,
BUT WHATEVER.
WHATEVER'S RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT,
I'M OUT OF HERE, MAN.
I'M GOING BACK TO WASAGA.
JAY:
MAN, THAT IS SO WEAK.
YOU'RE GONNA LET THAT
LITTLE WIENER BEAT YOU?
HE'S ALREADY WON!
ALL RIGHT,
I'VE BEEN KICKED OUT OF SCHOOL,
EMMA THINKS
I'M A DRUG-DEALER.
I'M SCREWED, MAN.
BUMMER TIMES.
LOOK, AT LEAST YOU'LL BE
ABLE TO SLEEP BETTER
KNOWING THAT YOU FIXED
THAT PUNK.
KICKING THE CRAP OUT OF HIM
ISN'T GOING TO HELP.
ALL RIGHT, HIS MOM'LL
PROBABLY HAVE ME
CHARGED WITH ASSAULT
OR SOMETHING.
JAY:
THERE ARE OTHER WAYS
TO BEAT HIM.
I BET HE'S AT
THE RACES AGAIN.
HE WAS THERE LAST NIGHT
LOOKING FOR A RACE.
AND I FINALLY INSTALLED
THE NITROUS OXIDE IN YOUR RIDE.
JUST THE EDGE YOU NEED
TO SMOKE THAT LITTLE PUNK.
LET'S TEACH HIM A LESSON.
YEAH, PAIN 101.
MY FAVOURITE SUBJECT.
(WHACK)
HEY, THAT'S MY STUFF!
(READING)
"AND MY ROOMMATE,
THE STEPFORD OMAROSA,
MINUS THE LOOKS..."
WHY WOULD YOU DO THIS?
LOOK, I WANT TO BE
A JOURNALIST,
AND, AND SOMETIMES THAT MEANS
PEOPLE GET HURT.
AND SOMETIMES BLACK-CLAD
SOURPUSSES GET BOOTED OUT.
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN,
ELEANOR.
GIVE ME YOUR TORCH.
BUT, I...
(SLAM)
(SIGHS)
(CARS RUMBLE BY SLOWLY)
(CAR SKIDS TO HALT)
(SLAMS DOOR)
SEAN:
GET OUT OF THE CAR!
WHAT!
GET OUT OF THE CAR,
MAN!
RELAX, DUDE.
WHAT'S THIS ABOUT?
YOU KNOW WHAT
THIS IS ABOUT.
WE GOT A SCORE TO SETTLE.
DUDE, YOU TRIED TO STEAL
MY GIRLFRIEND.
DON'T THEY TEACH
YOU GUY CODE
IN WAGAWAGA BAY?
DON'T THEY TEACH YOU
TO FIGHT YOUR OWN BATTLES?
NOT TO GET YOUR MOM
TO FIGHT THEM FOR YOU?
OH YEAH, YOU SPENT SOME TIME
IN HER OFFICE TODAY, RIGHT?
YOU KNOW SHE KEEPS A LOT
OF COOL STUFF IN THERE.
LIKE UH, PERMANENT RECORDS,
ANSWER KEYS...
LOCKER COMBINATIONS.
YOU SON OF A-
JAY:
EASY, SEAN, EASY.
REMEMBER WHAT WE CAME
HERE TO DO, OKAY?
YEAH, I DO.
YOU AND ME, ALL RIGHT?
WE'RE GONNA SETTLE THIS
OUT THERE
ON THE STREET.
WHAT?
YOU WANT TO RACE ME?
IN THAT HUNK OF JUNK?
YOU'RE ON, BITCH.
(CARS CRUISE TO STOP)
(ENGINE REVS)
(ENGINE REVS AGAIN)
(SWITCH CLICKS)
(TIRES SQUEAL)
(ENGINES ROAR)
(GEARSHIFT CLICKS)
(CARS ROAR)
(CARS ROAR BY)
(AIR FLOWS)
(CAR SPEEDS FASTER)
(CAR SCREECHES IN FRONT)
(CAR BUMPS ALONG)
(TIRES SKID)
(JOGGER GRUNTS)
(CLATTERS ALONG GROUND)
(CAR WHEELS SPIN)
(PANICKED GASPS)
(CAR DOOR OPENS)
(RUNNING FEET)
(CAR ROLLS UP)
(CAR IDLES AND STOPS)
OH MY GOD!
WHAT DO WE DO?
SEAN:
YOUR PHONE.
GIVE ME YOUR CELL PHONE.
YEAH.
I NEED AN AMBULANCE.
THERE'S A GUY.
HE'S BEEN HIT BY A CAR.
NEAR SARAH SIMCOE PARK,
PAST COUNTRYSIDE DRIVE.
THANKS, OKAY.
(CAR PULLS UP)
IS HE STILL BREATHING?
YEAH.
WHERE'S THAT AMBULANCE?
JAY:
SEAN.
LISTEN TO ME.
YOU HAVE TO GO.
WHAT?
PETER IS A MINOR,
YOU'RE EIGHTEEN.
YOU'RE GONNA DO
HARD TIME FOR THIS.
DUDE,
DON'T LISTEN TO HIM.
AM I TALKING TO YOU?
PETER:
(FRUSTRATED GRUNT)
SEAN!
GET IN YOUR CAR
AND DRIVE.
GO!
(DOOR SLAMS)
(CAR PEELS OUT)
(AMBULANCE SIREN WAILS)
(DOOR CREAKS OPEN)
THAT ANONYMOUS ARTICLE?
NOT SO ANONYMOUS.
STUDENT HOUSING GAVE YOU
THE BOOT, HUH?
LOVELY, INSANE AMBERLEY
SAVED THEM THE TROUBLE.
WELL, COULDN'T YOU ISSUE
A RETRACTION?
ON MY FIRST PIECE?
THAT'D MAKE A GREAT IMPRESSION
ON THE EDITOR.
DYLAN:
QUE PASA?
UH, ELLIE NEEDS SOMEWHERE
TO CRASH.
JUST FOR TONIGHT.
WELL, WAIT,
WE ARE LOOKING FOR A ROOMMATE.
RIGHT, DYLAN?
WELL, SO LONG AS YOU CAN
MAKE RENT,
MI CASA ET SU CASA.
MARCO:
YES! THIS IS GOING BE SO GREAT!
I KNOW JUST HOW TO KICK OFF
OUR FIRST NIGHT AS ROOMIES:
"SAVED BY THE BELL" MARATHON
STARTS IN FIVE,
AND I HAVE THE MICROWAVE POPCORN
WITH THE BUTTERY JALAPENO SAUCE.
COULD YOU AT LEAST
PRETEND YOU'RE UNHAPPY
I GOT KICKED OUT?
GOOD NEWS.
JUST GOT OFF THE PHONE
WITH PETER'S DAD.
THEY POSTED BAIL
AND HE IS SAFE AND SOUND
AT HOME.
WHAT ABOUT THE GUY
WHO GOT HIT?
WELL, HE'S IN HOSPITAL.
HE'S HURT,
BUT HE'S STABLE.
AND SEAN JUST TOTALLY BAILED?
THAT'S A HIT-AND-RUN,
RIGHT?
EM?
I THINK EVERYTHING'S
UNDER CONTROL NOW.
WHY DON'T YOU GO GET
SOME SLEEP.
THIS IS BAD.
(STEPS ON STAIRS)
(LIGHT CLICKS)
SEAN?!
SHHHH!
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
I SCREWED UP, EM.
I SCREWED UP REAL BAD.
EMMA:
UNDERSTATEMENT OF THE CENTURY.
THE POLICE ARE LOOKING FOR YOU.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
THAT'S WHY I NEED
YOUR HELP.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO CARES.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE WHO-
YOU'RE WRONG.
I DON'T CARE, SEAN.
I CAN'T.
NOT ANYMORE.
(SIGHS)
YOU NEED TO TURN
YOURSELF IN.
(DOOR SLAMS)