(PAPER RIPPING)
LOCKER RENOVATION
TIME?
TIMES CHANGE,
THINGS GET OUTDATED.
LIKE HAIRSTYLES,
OUTFITS,
AND STUPID COKEHEAD
BOYFRIENDS.
JT:
HEY.
I HEARD ABOUT YOU
AND CRAIG.
SORRY.
DON'T BE.
I DUMPED HIM
AND I COULDN'T BE HAPPIER.
HAPPY, HAPPY, HAPPY!
THIS IS HAPPY?
MANNY:
(IRRITATED EXHALE)
I GUESS I AM
A LITTLE CUCKOO-BANANAS.
WHICH IS TOTALLY NORMAL
RIGHT NOW.
DR. EM'S PRESCRIPTION
IS TO CHILL.
AND AS OF THIS AFT,
THE HOUSE IS OURS
THE ENTIRE WEEKEND!
WE CAN DO WHATEVER.
WE SHOULD HAVE A PARTY!
OR WE COULD...
RENT A DVD,
JUST YOU, ME AND SEAN,
COZY AND QUIET.
OR WE COULD HAVE
A PARTY!
OKAY, LET'S JUST SAY
WE GO AGAINST MY MOM'S
SPECIFIC ORDERS
NOT TO HAVE A PARTY.
WE DON'T HAVE A REASON
OR AN OCCASION TO CELEBRATE...
AT ALL.
JT:
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT IS LIBERTY'S BIRTHDAY.
SHE COULD REALLY USE
SOME CHEERING UP.
AND AS HER OLDEST FRIENDS,
THAT'S OUR SOLEMN DUTY,
ISN'T IT?
WE JUST HAVE
TO HAVE A PARTY!
THANKS, JT.
YOU ARE SO THOUGHTFUL!
JT:
WELL, THAT'S ME.
MR. THOUGHTFUL.
(EXCITED SQUEAL)
♪♪♪
LIBERTY!
JUST THE PERSON
I WANTED TO TALK TO.
UM, WHAT YOU'RE UP TO?
OH, JUST SENDING
A REMINDER EMAIL
FOR THE "INCREASE THE PEACE"
SUMMIT.
I MEANT TONIGHT.
'CAUSE WE ARE GONNA PARTY
LIKE IT'S YOUR BIRTHDAY...
BECAUSE IT ACTUALLY IS.
PASS.
EXCUSE ME?
I'M HOLDING A BIRTHDAY PARTY
FOR YOU, LIB,
MY OLDEST, DEAREST FRIEND
IN THE ENTIRE SCHOOL.
WE'VE BARELY TALKED
ALL YEAR.
MANNY:
WE'LL FIX THAT TONIGHT.
MUCHO CONVO WHILE WE PARTY
OUR BRAINS OUT!
(GROANS) I DON'T HAVE
A THING TO WEAR,
AND MY HAIR'S A MESS.
WHO ARE YOU
TALKING TO HERE?
COME OVER EARLY,
I'LL HOT YOU UP.
WELL, I SUPPOSE THIS
STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT
COULD USE
A LITTLE ROMANCE.
THAT'S THE SPIRIT!
WE ARE GONNA PARTY TONIGHT,
GIRLFRIEND!
PARTY WE WILL,
GIRLFRIEND.
BUT IT COMES
AT A PRICE.
COME TO MY PEACE SUMMIT
WITH LAKEHURST, AT LUNCH.
ME? WHY ME?
EXPERIENCE SHOWS
THAT MANNY SANTOS
DOUBLES THE MALE
ATTENDANCE.
WHATEVER. I JUST HOPE
SOMEONE CUTE IS COMING
BECAUSE YOU NEED
A DATE FOR TONIGHT.
MM.
LET US PRAY.
DAMIAN:
HI, I'M DAMIAN.
I'M LAKEHURST'S
STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT.
THIS IS OUR VP, NORA.
HEY GUYS,
NICE TO BE HERE.
SOMEONE'S PRAYERS
WERE ANSWERED.
DAMIAN:
SO, WE'RE HERE TODAY
TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO SOLVE THE PROBLEM
OF VIOLENCE
BETWEEN OUR SCHOOLS.
WHAT DO WE DO?
DANNY:
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT
THE PROBLEM IS:
YOUR SCHOOL IS FULL
OF PSYCHOS!
(QUIET CHATTER)
PEOPLE, IF PEACE IS
TO BE ACHIEVED,
WE NEED TO GET
TOGETHER.
ANY IDEAS?
HOW ABOUT A SPIRIT SQUAD RALLY?
TOBY:
UH, HOW DOES CHEERING
PREVENT MY OTHER ARM
FROM GETTING SPRAINED?
OKAY.
WELL, WE CAN FOLLOW IT
WITH AN "INCREASE THE PEACE"
DANCE?
KIND OF LIKE THE U.N.,
EXCEPT WITH HUMAN PYRAMIDS
AND DANCING?
SOLD.
SOUNDS LIKE FUN.
ALL IN FAVOUR?
EXCELLENT!
WE'LL TAKE MANNY'S IDEA
TO OUR PRINCIPALS.
MEETING ADJOURNED.
GREAT IDEA,
KOFI ANNAN.
ACTUALLY LEARNED SOMETHING
IN HISTORY CLASS, I GUESS.
CHEERLEADER
AND A DIPLOMAT;
BRAINS AND BEAUTY.
SPEAKING OF BRAINS
AND BEAUTY,
IT'S LIBERTY'S BIRTHDAY.
BIG BASH TONIGHT!
CLOSE FRIENDS,
FELLOW PEACENIKS.
GOTTA "INCREASE
THE PEACE", RIGHT?
RIGHT.
COUNT ME IN.
UNTIL THEN,
HAVE A GOOD ONE, LIBERTY.
I'LL DO MY DARNEDNEST!
LIBERTY.
HEY!
YOU MISSED
THE PEACE SUMMIT.
I'M STAYING OUT OF IT.
I'VE CAUSED
ENOUGH PROBLEMS.
I JUST WANTED TO
CONGRATULATE YOU.
YOUR B.B.P.E.
IS WELL DESERVED.
TRANSLATION?
BIG BIRTHDAY PARTY
EXTRAVAGANZA.
YEAH, I APPRECIATE
MANNY'S EFFORT,
BUT YOU KNOW HOW I FEEL
ABOUT BIRTHDAYS.
AH, YES.
AS I RECALL,
YOUR EXACT WORDS
LAST YEAR WERE,
"WHY CELEBRATE
THE PASSAGE OF TIME?"
YEAH, WELL, A LOT
HAS CHANGED SINCE THEN.
WE'VE MOVED ON,
GROWN UP.
BOTH MATURED.
EVEN YOU, JT.
(LAUGHS)
HA HA, VERY FUNNY.
MIA'S A LUCKY GIRL.
ALAS, SHE'S GONZO
THIS WEEKEND.
WELL, THERE IS
MY BIRTHDAY PARTY.
YOUR PRESENCE WOULDN'T
BE OBJECTED TO.
(LAUGHS) WOW,
WHAT A WARM INVITATION,
CONSIDERING THAT I'M THE ONE
WHO SUGGESTED IT!
YOU TOLD MANNY
TO HOLD A PARTY?
NO BIG.
YOU'VE JUST BEEN
IN A FUNK.
SO I THOUGHT THAT
A BIRTHDAY PARTY
WOULD GIVE YOU SOMETHING
TO SMILE ABOUT.
SEE YOU LATER.
MANNY:
YOUR LOVE CHARIOT'S HERE
TO WHISK YOU OFF
TO A LAND OF ROMANCE!
SIMPSON:
IT'S A NATURE RETREAT,
MANNY.
REMEMBER THE RULES:
KEEP THE HOUSE CLEAN
AND NO PARTIES!
DON'T WORRY.
IT'LL BE LIKE YOU NEVER LEFT.
SAY HI TO NATURE FOR ME.
TOBY:
♪ PARTY, PARTY, PART-Y! ♪
♪ PARTY, PARTY, PAR... ♪
WHAT'S WITH
THE CORNY SAMBA?
TOBY:
IS IT WRONG TO BE EXCITED
ABOUT A ROCKIN' BASH
AT CASA EMMA-MANNY?
YES!
BECAUSE IT'S NOT
A ROCKING BASH.
IT'S A TEENY-TINY
BIRTHDAY PARTY
ENDING AT 9:00 SHARP.
THAT'S NOT WHAT
MANNY TOLD ME.
EMMA:
MANNY!
COME ON, EM.
I REALLY NEED THIS.
I KNOW, BUT...
SEAN AND I SORT OF
HAD PLANS LATER.
OF A ROMANTIC NATURE?
NO WAY! REALLY?
REALLY.
TONIGHT IS THE NIGHT.
ER... AT LEAST IT WAS.
WELL, ABORT! ABORT!
I'LL SEND BULK EMAILS,
I'LL CARPET BOMB
THE SCHOOL WITH FLYERS.
ANYTHING.
IT'S TOO LATE.
WORD'S OUT.
BUT I GUESS SEAN AND I
COULD STILL...
YOU KNOW.
JUST PROMISE IT WON'T
GET TOO CRAZY?
EEE! I PROMISE.
PARTY'S AT EMMA NELSON'S
HOUSE.
HERE'S THE ADDRESS.
WILL YOU BE THERE?
(NERVOUS CHUCKLE)
PARTY AT EMMA'S?
HEY-OH!
OH, DON'T TELL ANYONE.
PLEASE.
DUDE, WE'D NEVER!
DEREK AND DANNY:
CHECK IT!
PARTY TONIGHT!
EMMA'S HOUSE!
WOO!
♪♪♪
MANNY:
GOLD EYESHADOW WILL REALLY
MAKE YOUR EYES POP,
AND WE'LL FINISH IT OFF
WITH A BRONZE GLOSS.
LIBERTY;
DO GUYS ACTUALLY NOTICE
THESE THINGS?
I BET DAMIAN WILL.
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN
HE MEETS THE PERSON
BEHIND THE LIPSTICK?
HE'LL LOVE YOU.
YOU'RE CUTE, SMART,
AND VERY UNIQUE.
TELL THAT TO JT.
LIBERTY, YOU NEED
TO FORGET ABOUT HIM.
PUT HIM OUT OF YOUR MIND.
EASIER SAID THAN DONE.
I KNOW.
TALK TO ME ABOUT CRAIG.
BUT SISTA,
WE'VE GOTTA MOVE ON!
OUT WITH THE OLD
AND IN WITH THE NEW.
SPEAKING OF NEW?
SAY HELLO TO LIBERTY
VERSION 2.0.
WHY, MS. VAN ZANDT,
I RECKON YOU COULD STEAL
ANY MAN'S HEART.
(SIGHS)
(BLENDER WHIRS)
EMMA:
ARE YOU UP
FOR SOME OF MY TRADEMARK
SWEET BERRY SLUSHY?
I'M UP FOR SOME TRADEMARK
SWEET BERRY YOU.
COUNTING THE MINUTES.
ME TOO.
TICK-TOCK.
EMMA, YOU SURE
ABOUT THIS?
AH, I AM THE VERY
DEFINITION OF SURE!
(MUSIC PLAYS)
(LOW PARTY CHATTER)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
SEAN, JT AND TOBY:
SURPRISE!
MY FAVOURITE KIND:
UNSURPRISING.
WELL...
SPEAKING ABOUT SURPRISES,
YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL,
LIBERTY.
THANKS, JT, I THINK.
WAIT, DON'T MOVE.
(RAPID KNOCKING
ON THE DOOR)
MANNY:
MARCO!
SPINNER AND...
(VOICE TRAILS OFF)
AND ELLIE.
MARCO:
WE BROUGHT SNACKS!
DANNY AND DEREK:
HELLO, LADIES!
JAY:
LOCK UP THE FAMILY JEWELS!
LET'S ROCK THIS JOINT!
JAY, WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
WHO EVEN TOLD YOU
ABOUT THIS PARTY?
WORD'S OUT ON THE STREET,
POLKA DOT.
OH, GREAT.
IT'S THEM.
EMMA:
OKAY. ANYBODY WHO ISN'T
LIBERTY'S CLOSEST
AND PERSONAL FRIEND,
CIAO!
ADIOS! SAYONARA!
SUCH A COLD GREETING
FROM SUCH A HOT-
SHUT IT.
SPINNER:
HEY!
UH, IF YOU IDIOTS ARE HERE
TO START SOMETHING,
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT IT.
MANNY:
OKAY! OKAY!
LET'S TAKE THE TESTOSTERONE
DOWN A NOTCH?
COME IN, HAVE FUN.
BUT PLEASE,
"INCREASE THE PEACE!"
CONSIDER US
LAKEHURST'S AMBASSADORS.
(PARTY CHATTER AND MUSIC)
MANNY:
AH! LOOK WHO'S HERE?
DAMIAN:
HEY.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
IT'S NOT MUCH BUT...
THANKS.
IT'S NICE.
WELL, I'LL LET YOU TWO
GET BETTER ACQUAINTED.
SO...
IT'S YOUR BIRTHDAY.
HAPPENS THIS DAY
EVERY YEAR.
(MUSIC BLARES OVER
EXCITED CHEERING)
BOTH:
(LAUGHING)
THAT'S NOT A TOY,
IT'S A FERTILITY SYMBOL!
EM, CAN I HAVE A LITTLE HELP?
THIS IS YOUR HOUSE.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
MY THERAPIST SAYS
I GOTTA LEARN TO CHILL.
UGH!
DOES MEXICO KNOW YOU'VE TAKEN
ALL THEIR TEQUILA?
DRINK THIS!
♪♪♪
MANNY:
BABY'S ROOM IS OFF LIMITS.
SORRY.
SORRY, I THOUGHT YOU WERE
ONE OF THE CRAZIES DOWNSTAIRS.
OH, WHAT LIKE
JOHNNY AND DRAKE?
MAN, I HAVE NO IDEA
HOW THEY EVEN HEARD
ABOUT THIS PARTY.
THE WHOLE WORLD HEARD
WELL, I THOUGHT IT WAS REAL COOL
THE WAY YOU HANDLED IT.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
I THOUGHT IT WAS BETTER TO HAVE
HAPPY LAKEHURST GUYS INSIDE
THEN PISSED-OFF ONES OUTSIDE.
OH YEAH. TOTALLY.
SMART THINKING.
THANK YOU.
SO, YOU AND LIBERTY?
EHN... SHE'S COOL,
BUT WE'RE NOT RIGHT.
I MEAN,
YOU CAN'T FAKE THIS STUFF.
YOU EITHER FEEL IT
OR YOU DON'T.
AND WHEN YOU DO FEEL IT,
IT'S LIKE TIME STOPS.
AND YOUR SKIN
GETS ALL GOOSEBUMPY.
DAMIAN,
I BARELY KNOW YOU.
AND YOU BARELY KNOW ME.
LET'S FIX THAT.
HOW ABOUT WE GO
FOR A DRIVE SOMETIME?
UH, PEE-WEE,
DO YOU EVEN HAVE A LICENCE?
DEREK:
YEAH... IDIOT LICENCE.
OHHH!
HEY BIRTHDAY GIRL,
WHERE'S YOUR HOT DATE?
HE FOUND SOMEONE ELSE
TO NOT TALK TO.
WELL,
LIKE THE SONG SAYS,
"IT'S YOUR PARTY,
YOU CAN CRY IF YOU WANT TO."
NO NEED.
DAMIAN AND I ARE
NO LOVE MATCH.
DISAPPOINTING,
BUT PAR FOR THE COURSE
ON MY BIRTHDAY.
WELL, LUCKILY THERE ARE
364 NON-BIRTHDAYS.
GOOD DAYS.
DAYS WORTH REMEMBERING.
LIKE WHEN YOU TAUGHT ME
HOW TO DRIVE?
YEAH,
THAT WAS CLASSIC.
OR WHEN WE WENT
TO THE DRIVE-IN
AND YOUR ROOF LEAKED
ON US?
NOT SO CLASSIC.
WELL, IT WAS TO ME.
LIKE EVERY DAY
WITH YOU.
LIBERTY,
ARE YOU DRUNK?
NO.
I JUST WANT TO
TELL THE TRUTH.
I DON'T WANT
TO LIE ANYMORE.
I STILL LOVE YOU.
I UH...
WOW. HEH.
UM...
WOW, I-I DON'T...
(MUSIC PLAYING, LAUGHING,
LOW CHATTERING)
JT:
CAN WE JUST TALK ABOUT THIS,
PLEASE?
WHAT IS THERE
TO TALK ABOUT?
YOU ALREADY GAVE ME
YOUR ANSWER.
LOOK...
I HAVE A GIRLFRIEND,
MIA,
WHO I REALLY,
REALLY LIKE.
DO YOU LOVE HER?
YES!
OF COURSE I DO.
THEN WHY ARE YOU
STANDING HERE
TALKING TO ME?
I-I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK YOU DO.
YOU'RE JUST TOO MUCH
OF A COWARD TO ADMIT IT.
(MUSIC BLARES)
CROWD:
(CHEERING) OOOH!
♪♪♪
I'M SORRY,
I JUST NEED WATER.
SEAN:
YOU LOOK GORGEOUS TONIGHT.
HOW'RE YOU FEELING?
I'VE NEVER BEEN BETTER,
SEXY MAN!
BOTH:
(GIGGLE)
SEAN:
WHOA! OH... (LAUGHS)
EM, ARE YOU WASTED?
THE QUESTION IS,
AM I WASTED ENOUGH?
(VOMITING)
OH, OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL,
MARGARITA MEET WASTEBASKET.
WASTEBASKET MEET MARGARITA.
SOMEBODY'S HUNGRY.
MY BEST FRIEND'S LOADED,
I JUST KISSED A STRANGER,
AND THE HOUSE IS COVERED
IN A BOOZY FILM.
WHEN I'M STRESSED,
I EAT.
GLAD I'M NOT THE SOURCE.
MY WORLD DOESN'T REVOLVE
AROUND YOU, ELLIE.
ELLIE:
GOOD.
BUT THAT...
THAT LITTLE VOICE
INSIDE MY HEAD,
IT, IT WANTS ME TO APOLOGIZE
FOR WHAT HAPPENED
WITH CRAIG.
HE FOOLED BOTH OF US.
AND... THANKFULLY,
HE'S FAR, FAR AWAY NOW.
IT'S FUNNY THOUGH,
I'M-I'M SO INCREDIBLY
PISSED AT CRAIG,
BUT I STILL
THINK ABOUT HIM.
WORRY A LITTLE.
ME, TOO.
HE REALLY MESSED
WITH US.
BOY:
SORRY.
JOHNNY:
HEY. PEACE OFFERING.
(BEER SPRAYS AND FIZZES)
JOHNNY:
(LAUGHING)
JAY:
YOU KNOW WHAT THIS MEANS?
BUH-BYE.
HEY RELAX, SLIM SHADY.
IT'S A PARTY.
AND NOW IT'S TIME TO GO.
JOHNNY:
MAN, GET YOUR HANDS OFF OF ME!
BAD MOVE, DEGRASSI.
PEE BREAK!
KNOW WHAT ROCKS, JT?
MAKING OUT...
WITH A CHICK!
WELL, AT LEAST SOMEONE'S
HAVING A GOOD TIME.
OH! (LAUGHS)
AM I EVER!
DUDE,
I CAN'T FEEL MY LIPS!
TOBES,
I GOT A SITUATION HERE.
ALL RIGHT, SHOOT.
(EXHALES)
OKAY, SO,
I HAVE THIS MEATBALL SUB,
RIGHT?
YOU KNOW, ZESTY SAUCE,
OOEY-GOOEY CHEESE...
AND-AND I LIKE THE SUB -
A LOT.
BUT... (SIGHS)
SOMEHOW I FIND MYSELF
CRAVING OATMEAL.
THIS A MIA-BALL SUB?
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, IT'S VERY TASTY,
BUT YOU GET TIRED OF IT.
OATMEAL...
IT'S ALWAYS BEEN
THERE FOR YOU.
YOU CAN DEPEND ON IT.
I MISS HER, TOBES.
I-I-I KNOW I SHOULDN'T,
BUT I DO.
IT'S SO STUPID.
NO, LOOK,
IT'S NOT STUPID.
YOU CAN'T FIGHT
HOW YOU FEEL.
GO OUT THERE
AND FIND HER.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU'RE ALWAYS RIGHT,
TOBES.
I'M GONNA GO OUT THERE
AND I'M GONNA GET MYSELF
A BIG BOWL OF LIBERTY!
OATMEAL.
LIBERTY!
(CRICKETS CHIRP)
COULDN'T FIND A TOILET?
HE DID!
JT:
OH, I GET IT!
MY CAR SUCKS.
HA HA!
YOU GUYS SLAY ME
WITH YOUR HUMOUR!
YEAH, MASCOT BOY?
LAUGH AT THIS.
MAN, WHAT THE HELL
DID YOU DO?!
(HYSTERICAL SCREAMING)
SOMEBODY HELP!
PLEASE!
(PANICKED WHIMPERS)
SOMEBODY!
(EXHALES) DRAKE LEMBKE
AND JOHNNY DIMARCO -
BOTH LAKEHURST GUYS.
DETECTIVE:
AND YOU DIDN'T SEE WHICH ONE
COMMITTED THE OFFENCE?
MANNY:
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
THIS PARTY WAS MY IDEA.
THIS IS MY FAULT.
MANNY, NO,
IT'S NOT, OKAY?
JT'S HURT.
IT'S SERIOUS.
MOM, I'M SO SORRY.
OKAY.
I'LL SEE YOU SOON.
I NEED TO SPEAK
TO A FAMILY MEMBER.
HIS GRANDMA'S COMING,
BUT SHE'LL BE A FEW HOURS.
TOBY:
WAIT.
YOU CAN TALK TO ME.
I'M HIS BROTHER.
HIS AORTA WAS PUNCTURED.
IT'S A MAIN ARTERY
AND...
WE COULDN'T REPAIR
THE DAMAGE.
HE DIDN'T MAKE IT.
WHA- WHAT?
(LAUGH OF DISBELIEF)
YOU'RE JOKING.
I'M SORRY,
YOUR BROTHER'S GONE.
(GASPS)
HE'S GONE?
(CRYING)
(LOUD PUNCH)
WHAT HAPPENED?
IS HE OKAY?
WHAT DID THE DOCTOR SAY?
TOBY?!
MANNY:
(SOBBING QUIETLY)