(BIRDS CHIRP)
CLARE, WAIT!
CLARE:
I HAVE A SPIRIT WEEK ARTICLE
TO PROOF BEFORE SCHOOL STARTS.
I COME IN PEACE
WITH BREAKFAST SANDWICHES.
PLEASE,
CAN YOU LET ME EXPLAIN?
SPEAK.
I SHOULDN'TVE READ
YOUR JOURNAL, OKAY?
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH
THAT I CAN'T THINK STRAIGHT
SOMETIMES.
BUT I WAS WRONG,
AND I'M SORRY.
CLARE:
APOLOGY ACCEPTED.
ELI:
WE WERE BROKEN UP
WHEN YOU WERE WITH JAKE,
SO IF YOU'VE LOVED HIM...
I DIDN'T.
OKAY, BUT YOU SAID
IN YOUR JOURNAL-
"I THINK I'M IN LOVE
WITH JAKE."
I WASN'T! I...
BACK THEN, I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT LOVE WAS.
DID I MENTION I'M SORRY?
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH,
SOMETIMES I CAN'T THINK
STRAIGHT EITHER.
THAT'S WHY YESTERDAY
WHEN I WAS JOKING ABOUT US
TAKING THE NEXT STEP,
I THINK I WAS ACTUALLY
BEING SERIOUS.
YOU THINK YOU WERE,
OR YOU WERE?
I WAS! I WAS!
I DEFINITELY WAS.
(SIGHS)
OKAY.
THEN LET'S GO EAT BREAKFAST
AND MAKE A PLAN.
NO QUIZ THOUGH,
RIGHT?
ZIP IT.
(BOTH LAUGH)
(COFFEE AND BREAKFAST SPLATTERS)
ELI? WHAT'RE YOU-?
DON'T LOOK!
JUST GO FIND A TEACHER
AND CALL 911, OKAY?
GO!
CLARE, NOW!
(BREATHING SHALLOWLY)
(GASPS)
(HYPERVENTILATING)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
(Ooh-ooh-ooh)
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ I can make it! ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
KATIE:
WOULD YOU HURRY UP?
MAYA:
YOU PARKED SO FAR AWAY!
WELL, DID YOU SEE ANYTHING
CLOSER, GRUMPY PANTS?
KATIE, I'M NOT HAVING
A GOOD DAY, OKAY?
CAM MAYBE TEXT-DUMPED ME
LAST NIGHT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
"MAYBE"?
I DON'T KNOW.
HIS MESSAGE WAS PRETTY VAGUE,
BUT I CALLED HIM
LIKE THIRTY TIMES
AND HE NEVER ANSWERED.
YEESH.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
I MEAN, WE HAD A PERFECT NIGHT
AND NOW HE'S BAILING ON ME?
IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
KATIE:
WELL, CAM'S ACTED WEIRD BEFORE.
I MEAN, CHOP-SOCKYING
ZIG'S FACE IN -
NOT THAT THE SLIMEBALL
DIDN'T DESERVE IT.
MAYA:
COMMENTARY, KATIE.
LOOK, DON'T ASK FOR MY ADVICE
IF YOU DON'T LIKE THE SIDEBARS.
WHAT DO I DO?!
I DON'T KNOW.
FORGET ABOUT CAM FOR NOW.
YOU HAVE YOUR NATIONAL
YOUNG MUSICIANS
ORCHESTRA AUDITION
TODAY!
IT'S SOMETHING
YOU'VE BEEN DREAMING ABOUT
AND WORKING TOWARDS
YOUR WHOLE LIFE!
JUST FOCUS ON THAT.
OKAY, YOU'RE RIGHT.
MUSIC FIRST,
CAM LATER.
EXACTLY.
MAYA, YOU SEEING CAM TODAY?
NOT IF I CAN HELP IT.
HE'S PROBABLY SITTING
AT HIS BILLET HOME,
WORKING OFF HIS WEEK-LONG
SUSPENSION LIKE A CHUMP.
WE'RE IN A FIGHT.
THAT SEEMS TO BE THE THEME.
(SIREN CHIRPS)
(FIRE TRUCK RUMBLES)
MADAME JEAN-AUX:
ALLEZ, ALLEZ, ALLEZ, VITE!
WHAT IS GOING ON?
MADAME JEAN-AUX:
INTO YOUR CLASSROOMS!
VITE! VITE!
OH BONJOUR, MADAME.
UM, I WAS HOPING TO SKIP
FIRST PERIOD THIS MORNING.
MY NYMO AUDITION'S TODAY,
AND IF I COULD SQUEEZE IN
ONE MORE REHEARSAL,
C'EST POSSIBLE?
MAYA, YOU NEED TO GO SEE
PRINCIPAL SIMPSON.
RIGHT AWAY.
WHY?
YOU SHOULD GO WITH HER.
RIGHT AWAY, PLEASE.
OKAY.
WHATEVER IT IS,
I SWEAR I DIDN'T DO IT.
MM-HMM.
GIRLS, COME ON IN.
PLEASE SIT.
THIS IS DR. TARA.
SHE'S BEEN ASSIGNED TO DEGRASSI
AS OF THIS MORNING.
UM...
I'M VERY SORRY TO HAVE
TO TELL YOU THIS, MAYA...
CAMPBELL SAUNDERS IS DEAD.
KATIE:
OH... OH MY GOD!
WHAT...?
MR. SIMPSON:
IT APPEARS THAT
HE COMMITTED SUICIDE
IN THE GREENHOUSE
SOMETIME OVERNIGHT.
UM, A STUDENT FOUND HIM
ABOUT AN HOUR AGO.
WAIT, THERE- NO, THERE'S A-
THERE WAS A MISTAKE.
I... I JUST SAW HIM
THE OTHER DAY.
CAM IS OBVIOUSLY FINE.
DR. TARA:
IF YOU TWO WOULD LIKE
TO TALK PRIVATELY,
YOU CAN USE THE OFFICE
NEXT DOOR,
AND I'M AVAILABLE ANYTIME
JUST TO TALK.
IF YOU'D LIKE TO GO HOME,
YOU HAVE PERMISSION.
BUT, KATIE, I THINK
YOU SHOULD GO AS WELL.
YEAH, UM...
NO, I'M NOT GONNA
LEAVE HER SIDE.
MAYA, WHAT WOULD YOU
LIKE TO DO?
UM...
UH, CAN I PRACTICE
FOR MY AUDITION?
(PIANO PLAYS SAD MELODY)
(CELLO PLAYING)
DR. TARA:
AS THE NEWS SPREADS
ABOUT CAMPBELL,
PLEASE LET YOUR FRIENDS KNOW
THAT THERE'S A TEAM
OF COUNSELORS HERE
TO HELP THE SCHOOL
THROUGH THIS DIFFICULT TIME.
THERE'S NO RIGHT WAY
TO RESPOND TO A SUICIDE.
SOME OF YOU MIGHT
FEEL SADNESS,
GRIEF, ANGER,
GUILT...
WHILE OTHERS MAY BE
LESS AFFECTED.
ALL OF THESE EMOTIONS
ARE COMPLETELY NORMAL.
BUT NO MATTER HOW YOU FEEL,
THE BEST THING THAT YOU CAN DO
IS STAY OPEN.
TALK TO YOUR PARENTS,
AND YOUR TEACHERS,
AND YOUR FRIENDS,
AND MORE IMPORTANTLY,
LISTEN -
LISTEN TO WHAT OTHERS
HAVE TO SAY.
JUST KNOW THAT
YOU'RE NOT ALONE.
♪♪♪
FIONA:
SO ALL THE SPIRIT WEEK'S EVENTS
ARE CANCELLED.
CONNOR:
WHY?
MARISOL:
BECAUSE SOMEONE DIED.
BUT WE WERE HAVING
SO MUCH FUN.
JENNA:
I'M WITH CONNOR.
FIONA:
GUYS, IT'S NOT MY CHOICE.
SIMPSON MADE THE CALL.
BECKY:
SO THE WHOLE STUDENT BODY
HAS TO SUFFER
BECAUSE OF WHAT ONE KID
DECIDED TO DO?!
OUCH.
I'M SORRY,
BUT SUICIDE IS SELFISH!
I MEAN, DIDN'T HE THINK ABOUT
HIS FAMILY AND HIS FRIENDS?
MARISOL:
WELL, FIONA AND I TALKED
TO DR. TARA
ABOUT WHAT WE COULD DO.
SHE MENTIONED MANY SCHOOLS
HAVE CANDLELIGHT VIGILS,
SO WE'RE GONNA ORGANIZE ONE
FOR THIS EVENING.
AS A WAY TO BEGIN THE HEALING
AND OPEN UP DISCUSSION.
MO:
THAT'S A HELL OF A LOT
OF CANDLES!
IT'S LIKE, HELLO,
CANDLE STORE?
WHAT? YOU'RE ALL SOLD OUT?
AW MAN, BUT WE'VE GOT
THIS WHOLE LIKE,
CANDLELIGHT VIGIL THING
HAPPENING
AND IT'S JUST LIKE, OHHH!
YOU KNOW!
(LAUGHS)
YEAAAAAH...
SORRY, GUYS,
I'M NOT GOOD WITH THIS STUFF.
CONNOR:
SO WHY DID HE DO IT?
WHY DID CAMPBELL KILL HIMSELF?
I-I DON'T GET IT.
MARISOL:
HE WAS OBVIOUSLY DEPRESSED.
BECKY:
WHY DIDN'T HE REACH OUT
FOR HELP?
MO:
MAYBE HE FELT LIKE
HE COULDN'T.
I MEAN, HE WAS UNDER
A LOT OF PRESSURE WITH HOCKEY.
ALLI:
SCHOOL TOO.
JENNA:
DOES ANYONE KNOW
IF HE WAS GETTING BULLIED?
FIONA:
I GUESS WE'LL NEVER KNOW.
(CHAIR CRASHES)
ALLI:
DALLAS!
IT'S GONNA BE OKAY!
WHAT?!
IT'S GONNA BE OKAY?!
I DON'T... I...
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY!
SAY IT'S OUR FAULT!
SAY WE FAILED HIM -
YOU AND ME!
ME?
DALLAS:
YOU KNEW HE HAD PROBLEMS.
HE WAS CRYING,
HE WAS UPSET!
WHY DIDN'T YOU DO SOMETHING?
YOU SHOULD'VE DONE SOMETHING!
YOU DID NOTHING!
(SOBS)
HEY, UM...
DAD JUST CALLED.
THEY'RE ON THE NEXT FLIGHT
OUT OF PEI.
WELL, THEY DIDN'T HAVE TO CUT
THEIR TRIP SHORT.
BESIDES, I THINK I'M AS READY
AS I'LL EVER BE
FOR MY AUDITION.
UM...
MAYA, YOU CAN'T
AUDITION TODAY.
THIS IS MY CHANCE.
THEY NEVER AUDITION
14-YEAR-OLDS.
OKAY, WELL, MAYBE WE CAN CALL
ABOUT RESCHEDULING IT.
NO. I'M READY
TO PLAY TODAY.
WHAT WOULD PEOPLE THINK?
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S NOT LIKE I'VE EVER BEEN
THE GIRLFRIEND OF THE GUY
WHO KILLED HIMSELF BEFORE.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
HI, MARE.
I'M SO SORRY.
MM-HMM.
THE STUDENT COUNCIL IS HOLDING
A CANDLELIGHT VIGIL
FOR CAM THIS EVENING.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO SAY
A FEW WORDS?
UM... I DON'T KNOW.
LOOK, MAYBE IT WOULD BE
A GOOD IDEA
FOR YOU TO SPEAK.
THE WAY YOU'RE ACTING
IS KINDA SCARING ME.
MAYBE THIS WILL BE
THE BEST WAY FOR YOU
TO GET THROUGH
THE SHOCK.
WHAT ABOUT MY AUDITION?
LOOK, I'M SORRY,
BUT YOU CAN'T DO BOTH.
WHAT DO PEOPLE EVEN SAY
AT A VIGIL?
I DON'T KNOW, HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO DO THIS, KATIE?
UM...
JUST WRITE WHAT'S IN YOUR HEART,
I GUESS.
YOU WANT ME TO GET YOU
SOME WATER
FROM THE VENDING MACHINE?
OKAY.
CAM: (ON PHONE MESSAGE)
GOOD MORNING, MAYA MATLIN!
I'M SORRY I HAD TO LEAVE -
EARLY MORNING HOCKEY PRACTICE,
AND I DIDN'T WANNA WAKE YOU -
YOU WERE DROOLING SO CUTELY.
SO LAST NIGHT WAS PRETTY MUCH
THE BEST NIGHT EVER.
UM, THANK YOU FOR THAT.
AND ALSO,
I KIDNAPPED HOOT!
IF YOU EVER WANNA SEE
YOUR OWL AGAIN,
MEET ME ON THE STEPS
AT LUNCH
AND WE'LL NEGOTIATE
FOR HIS SAFE RETURN.
MUHAA-HA-HA-HA-HAAA!
TORI:
HEY, I'VE BEEN LOOKING
EVERYWHERE FOR YOU.
I HEARD YOU'RE SPEAKING
AT THE VIGIL.
DO YOU NEED HELP?
SO YOU WANNA BE FRIENDS
ALL OF THE SUDDEN.
I KNOW YOU DON'T MEAN THAT.
YOU'RE IN SHOCK.
DON'T TELL ME
WHAT I AM!
AND DON'T BE NICE TO ME
JUST BECAUSE CAM'S DEAD!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(GROANS)
(CAN CLATTERS)
ARGHHH!
(HISSED BREATH)
WHAT'D IT LOOK LIKE,
CAM'S BODY?
IT LOOKED LIKE
A DEAD KID.
DID IT SMELL?
YEAH, LIKE OREGANO
AND PETUNIAS.
I WASN'T UP CLOSE AND PERSONAL
WITH IT.
YEAH, WELL, MY DAD SEES
DEAD BODIES
ALL THE TIME AT WORK.
IT'S MESSED UP.
I MEAN, HE MUST'VE BEEN
SO SICK
TO DO SOMETHING
LIKE THAT.
LIKE HOW-HOW DO YOU EVEN
GET YOUR HEAD THERE?
SO HOW DOES YOUR DAD DEAL
WITH THE THINGS HE SEES?
I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS HE JUST DOESN'T
TAKE IT HOME WITH HIM,
AND FORGETS.
I WISH MY BRAIN WORKED
LIKE THAT.
ARE YOU GONNA GO
TO THE VIGIL?
UM...
CLARE IS,
BUT I'M PRETTY WIPED.
I'M PROBABLY JUST GONNA
GO HOME.
OKAY.
(PLANE WHISTLES OVERHEAD)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
(CHOKES BACK A SOB)
FIONA:
OH, THANK GOD!
I OVERHEARD SOME STUDENTS SAYING
THERE WAS A GUY ON THE ROOF.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
DALLAS, ARE YOU OKAY?
I'M SO MESSED UP...
I THOUGHT ABOUT JUMPING.
FIONA:
BUT YOU DIDN'T.
DALLAS:
IT'S MY FAULT CAM DID IT.
I KNOW HOW HARD IT IS
TO BE AWAY FROM HOME,
AND HE HATED HOCKEY,
BUT I DIDN'T CARE!
I STILL PUSHED!
OH! I SHOULD'VE BEEN EASIER
ON HIM.
NO ONE WOULD MISS ME.
THAT'S NOT TRUE!
YOUR FAMILY,
ADAM AND DREW,
YOUR TEAM, ALLI.
COME ON, THERE MUST BE SOMEONE
YOU SHOULD STICK AROUND FOR.
(CRYING)
(SNIFFLES)
YEAH, THERE IS.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
GOOD!
BECAUSE I'M GONNA NEED
YOUR HELP
SO THAT THIS NEVER HAPPENS
AGAIN.
I CAN'T HELP ANYBODY,
FIONA!
YES, YOU CAN.
BUT LET'S START
BY HELPING YOU, OKAY?
(CRYING)
I'M SURPRISED YOU DIDN'T GO
TO THE VIGIL.
JAKE:
HUH? OH, I DIDN'T WANNA
COMPLICATE THINGS FOR KATIE.
ELI:
HMM...
HEY, I, UH, DRIZZLED
SOME CARAMEL ON THERE.
ELI: NICE!
JAKE: YEAH.
OHHH!
HEY UH...
YOU KNOW, IF YOU HADN'T
FOUND CAM,
IT PROBABLY WOULD'VE
BEEN ME,
SO THANKS FOR THAT.
YOU ARE WELCOME,
GOOD SIR.
THANKS.
IS MY GARDEN GONNA BE
HAUNTED NOW?
NAH!
JUST ME.
HEY, YOU WANNA PLAY
TURBO MODE?
YEAH, COME ON,
LET'S PLAY TURBO MODE.
YEAH, OKAY.
YEAH.
(SIGHS)
HEY, HOW'RE YOU DOING?
I'M GREAT.
WELL, UM,
THEY FOUND HOOT.
OKAY, I'LL COME GET YOU
WHEN WE'RE READY.
(SIGHS)
FINALLY, SOMEONE WHO WILL
TREAT ME NORMALLY.
COME ON,
NOT YOU TOO!
YOU HATED CAM YESTERDAY!
BUT I'M THE REASON
THAT HE DID IT.
I TOLD HIM TO GET OUT
OF YOUR LIFE,
AND HE DID.
IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
WELL, THAT'S RIDICULOUS!
(LAUGHS) GOD!
HOW ARE YOU LAUGHING
RIGHT NOW?
I DON'T KNOW, PEOPLE KEEP SAYING
DO WHATEVER I FEEL,
BUT I GUESS WHAT I FEEL
IS WRONG, BECAUSE-
KATIE:
WE'RE ALL READY TO START.
ARE YOU READY TO SPEAK?
HEY, UM...
YOU READY?
SURE.
(HUSHED WHISPERS)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
THIS IS SO STUPID.
THIS IS SO... STUPID!
CAM DOESN'T DESERVE
A CANDLELIGHT VIGIL.
HE MADE A CHOICE!
IT WAS THE WRONG ONE,
BUT US STANDING HERE,
FEELING SAD LIKE THIS,
EVERYONE BLAMING THEMSELVES,
FEELING GUILTY,
IT'S NO ONE'S FAULT!
I MEAN, IT'S HIS FAULT!
MAYA, HE WAS SICK.
WELL, HE SHOULD'VE FOUGHT.
HE WAS REALLY SICK.
HE SHOULD'VE FOUGHT HARDER,
OR FOUND SOMEONE TO HELP!
I WOULD'VE HELPED HIM,
BUT HE DIDN'T GIVE ME
THE CHANCE!
CAM HAD SO MANY REASONS
TO STAY,
BUT INSTEAD,
HE JUST CHECKED OUT.
WELL, FINE!
BUT I'M NOT LIGHTING
ANY CANDLES,
AND I WON'T CRY.
I WON'T.
STUDENTS:
(SURPRISED MURMURS)
KATIE:
MAYA! MAYA!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
DALLAS:
I SAID SOME BAD THINGS TO YOU
YESTERDAY.
I'M SORRY,
I DIDN'T MEAN IT,
IT'S JUST...
SOMETIMES I FEEL LIKE ANGER'S
THE ONLY THING I'VE GOT.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I KNOW IT ISN'T.
(SIGHS)
SO YOU'RE GONNA GO SEE
THE COUNSELOR?
DALLAS:
YEAH. I NEED TO.
PLUS I GOT A LITTLE
ENCOURAGEMENT
FROM A FRIEND.
ALLI:
SPIRIT WEEK'S BACK ON?
DALLAS:
FIONA CONVINCED SIMPSON
IT'D BE A GOOD WAY
TO GET THE SCHOOL
BACK ON TRACK.
AND ARE YOU STILL PLANNING
ON WINNING, MIKE?
ALL I CAN DO IS TRY.
DR. TARA:
HI.
WHO'S NEXT?
UM, HE IS.
(SIGHS)
I'M TARA.
MIKE DALLAS.
I'M ON CAM'S HOCKEY TEAM.
I WAS HIS CAPTAIN.
I REMEMBER YOU.
LET'S TALK.
♪♪♪
♪ Know that you can bend
a little ♪
♪ To make it through ♪
♪ There's a star in you ♪
KATIE:
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT BEING HERE
TODAY?
I DON'T WANNA MISS
ANYTHING.
ESPECIALLY ALL THE WEIRD LOOKS
I'M PROBABLY GONNA GET.
YEAH, WELL, YOU SAID
A LOT OF THINGS
AT THE VIGIL YESTERDAY.
YES, AND I MEANT
ALL OF THEM.
OKAY, WELL,
IF YOU NEED ME...
I KNOW WHERE YOU LIVE.
GOT IT.
(SIGHS)
HI.
LISTEN, I'M SORRY
FOR BEING SO MEAN TO YOU
THE OTHER DAY.
THANKS.
I'M SORRY
I WAS SO NICE.
I WAS TRYING TO HELP OUT.
I KNOW.
THING IS, I WANTED TO BE
BEST FRIENDS AGAIN,
EVEN BEFORE CAM.
I JUST DIDN'T KNOW
HOW TO SAY IT.
WELL, GOOD.
'CAUSE...
I REALLY NEED
MY BEST FRIEND RIGHT NOW.
IT'S GONNA BE OKAY, MAYA,
I PROMISE.
(SNIFFLES)
OKAY.
ARE YOU GETTING SNOT ON ME?
UH, SORRY.
IT'S OKAY,
I CAN TAKE IT.
(LAUGHS)
WE SHOULD PROBABLY GET
TO CLASS.
OKAY.
♪ Be the change
you want to see ♪
♪ There is a star
shining on you ♪