♪♪♪
AUDRA:
DREEEEW! DREW!
COME DOWNSTAIRS - NOW!
COMING!
THE PARTY.
THE BASEMENT.
AUDRA:
I'M SO UPSET WITH YOU.
MOM, I CAN EXPLAIN...
THOSE ARE MY COURSES...
NO, DREW.
THEY'RE ALL BIRD COURSES!
THERE IS A REASON I MADE YOU
TAKE GRADE 11 MATH
IN SUMMER SCHOOL
TO CATCH UP WITH THE REST
OF YOUR CLASS.
(ADAM GIGGLES)
ADAM... GO!
AND MISS ALL THE FUN?
I'M SORRY, MOM.
I'LL SWITCH.
IT'S NOT TOO LATE.
I PROMISE.
IT FEELS LIKE A SMALL ANIMAL
IS TRYING TO GET OUT
OF MY SKULL.
WHAT HAPPENED LAST NIGHT?
YOU PASSED OUT!
ME AND ADAM TO CLEAN UP
THE MESS.
WELL, EXCEPT FOR THE ONE
ON YOUR BACK. (LAUHGS)
WHEN DID THIS HAPPEN?
BETWEEN YOU FALLING DOWN
THE STAIRS
AND STREAKING
THROUGH THE YARD?
I STREAKED?
OH YEAH.
NAKED?
(GROANS)
HOW MUCH DID I HAVE TO DRINK
LAST NIGHT?
DALLAS:
I LOST TRACK AFTER
A FEW HOURS.
YOU'RE IN FOR ONE FUN DAY.
(EXHALES)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh... ♪
(Oh-oh-oh)
♪ I can make it through ♪
(I can make it!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(SNORING THROUGH THE PHONE)
ELI?
GOOD MORNING.
I GUESS WE FELL ASLEEP
ON THE PHONE.
CLARE:
I GUESS SO.
YOU HAVE MORNING VOICE.
LOOK WHO'S TALKING.
IS IT WEIRD THAT
I ALREADY MISS YOU?
IT'S BEEN EIGHT HOURS SINCE
WE LAST SAW EACH OTHER.
NO MORE UNIFORMS
MEANS I'M GONNA NEED EXTRA
TIME TO GET READY.
ARE WE STILL SET
FOR OUR FIRST DATE TONIGHT?
LIKE, OUR RE-FIRST DATE?
I SAID I WAS ALL IN,
DIDN'T I?
I'LL SEE YOU AT SCHOOL.
♪♪♪
♪ It's getting harder
and harder to sleep ♪
♪ Can't you see
I wanna keep it going ♪
♪ It's getting harder
and harder to breathe ♪
MAYA:
I STAYED UP ALL NIGHT WRITING
MUSIC FOR A BAND
I'M NOT EVEN IN YET.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH ME?
TORI:
HEY, MO WILL LOVE
YOUR AUDITION.
YOU'LL BE THE NEXT
INDIE ROCK SENSATION.
LIKE, THE BLACK EYED PEAS!
WHAT?
AGH... NEVERMIND.
I JUST HOPE HE THINKS
I'M MATURE ENOUGH.
I USED THOSE BRA-PAD-CHICKEN
CUTLET-THINGIES YOU GAVE ME.
DO THEY LOOK OKAY?
MAYA, YOU HAVE-
YOU HAVE UNI-BOOB.
WHAT?
YOU ONLY HAVE ONE!
YOU HAVE TO KIND OF-
SO THERE ARE TWO.
MAY I?
OKAY.
OKAY, BUT HURRY UP.
DON'T WORRY I GOT THIS.
MAYA:
TORI!
JUST RELAX,
I KNOW WHAT I'M DOING,
I'M A PAGEANT GIRL.
BEAUTY TRICKS ARE MY THING.
WHAT IS HAPPENING?
MAYA:
NOTHING.
I WAS JUST HELPING
HER WITH-
GIRL STUFF!
LOVE THE HAIR TODAY.
ARE YOU EXCITED
FOR YOUR AUDITION?
I'M PUMPED.
(HAPPY EXHALE)
HEY, BED-HEAD.
CALCULUS?
REALLY?
MY MOM FORCED ME
TO TRANSFER.
WELL,
COME SIT WITH ME.
YOU'RE NOT...
STILL MAD AT ME?
LET'S JUST CALL
YOUR COURTNEY LIE...
A MISUNDERSTANDING.
ARMSTRONG:
ALL RIGHT, CLASS.
WE'VE GOT A LOT TO COVER
THIS TERM,
SO WE'RE JUMPING RIGHT IN
WITH TRIGONOMETRIC RATIOS!
TRIGONOMETRY IS THE STUDY
OF RIGHT ANGLE TRIANGLES.
HEY, I-I'M SORRY,
I HAD TO RUSH OUT LAST NIGHT.
BOO! OVER-PROTECTIVE PARENTS
WHO WANT ME HOME BY TWELVE.
I HAD A REALLY SPECIAL TIME
AT THAT PARTY.
YOU DID?
I DON'T WANT TO SOUND
LIKE A CLICHE,
BUT... I'VE NEVER FELT
CLOSER TO YOU.
ARMSTRONG:
ANYBODY?
(VOMITS)
(STUDENTS GROAN WITH DISGUST)
(VOMITING)
YOU ALL RIGHT, MR. TORRES?
WHY DON'T YOU GO
TO THE BATHROOM,
AND TAKE THE GARBAGE
CAN WITH YOU.
MS. OH:
HERE'S A TEMPLATE
YOU CAN USE
TO LOG YOUR CO-OP HOURS.
I'M LOOKING FOR DETAILS:
EVERY TASK, WHAT YOU'VE LEARNED,
WHAT YOU WANT MORE OF...
AND WHEN I WOKE UP,
WE WERE STILL ON THE PHONE.
WE'RE GOING ON A FIRST
DATE RE-DO TONIGHT.
A CHANCE TO ERASE THE DARK
PAST AND START ANEW.
MS. OH:
EVERYONE,
CLARE'S THE FIRST OF YOU
TO START HER CO-OP TODAY
WITH ONE OF MY FAVOURITE
LOCAL JOURNALISTS.
EVERYONE GIVE HER A ROUND
OF APPLAUSE FOR GOOD LUCK.
(APPLAUSE)
MS. OH, ARE YOU SURE
IT STARTS TODAY?
IT SAYS SO HERE
ON YOUR PAPERWORK.
I GUESS YOU HAVE
TO CANCEL YOUR DATE?
IT'S DAY ONE, AND I'M ALREADY
LETTING ELI DOWN.
(RESONATING SOUND)
♪ LA, LA, LA, LA, LA, ♪
♪ LA, LA, LA, ♪
♪ LA, LA, WHOOO! ♪
♪ LA, LA, LA, LA, LA, ♪
♪ LA, LA, WHOOOO! ♪
♪ LA, LA, LA, LA, LA! ♪
THANKS, IMOGEN.
THAT WAS-
THAT WAS PRETTY WEIRD.
BUT GREAT.
ALL RIGHT,
WHO WANTS TO GO NEXT?
MAYA:
I WILL.
MO:
ALL RIGHT!
KNOCK US DEAD.
(STARTS SLOWLY
BUT THEN PLAYS A QUICK TUNE)
HEY, DALLAS.
SORRY.
ONE SEC.
OKAY MAN,
I NEED A PLAY-BY-PLAY
OF WHAT HAPPENED
LAST NIGHT.
DUDE, YOU HAD A TIME!
I KNOW,
BUT I NEED DETAILS.
DID YOU SEE ME
WITH KATIE AT ALL?
YEAH,
SHE SHOWED UP CRYING.
YOU SENT HER TO YOUR
ROOM TO CHILL,
AND YOU WENT TO BREAK UP
WITH HER.
IF WE BROKE UP,
THEN WHY DID SHE SAY
SHE'S NEVER FELT
CLOSER TO ME?
BECAUSE YOU HAD SEX?
THAT'S CRAZY.
I'D REMEMBER MY FIRST TIME.
NOT IF YOU BLACKED OUT.
I ONLY HAD A FEW BEERS.
AND A SERIOUS HIT
TO THE HEAD.
YOU KNOW WHAT? WHY DON'T YOU
JUST GO AND ASK KATIE?
ACTUALLY,
DON'T ASK KATIE.
OH MAN, YOU'RE STARTING
TO FREAK ME OUT HERE.
WHY WOULD I HAVE SEX
WITH KATIE?
IF BIANCA'S THE ONE
I LOVE.
ALL RIGHT, I GAVE YOU A CONDOM
LAST NIGHT, REMEMBER?
YEAH?
YOU PUT IT
IN YOUR WALLET.
IF IT'S THERE,
YOU DIDN'T HAVE SEX.
AND IF IT'S GONE...?
HEY MAN,
AT LEAST YOU WERE SAFE?
OH NO...
(PLAYING THE CELLO)
(STOPS PLAYING)
UH, WHO WANTS TO GO NEXT?
PA:
ANYONE WANTING TO DONATE THEIR
OLD UNIFORMS TO GOODWILL
PLEASE SEE BECKY BAKER
IN HOMEROOM 1202 AT LUNCH.
ADAM:
WHY ARE YOU CREEPING?
I MESSED UP.
DID MOM FIND OUT
ABOUT THE PARTY?
ADAM,
I BLACKED OUT.
THIS MORNING-THIS MORNING
MY CONDOM WAS MISSING.
I HAD SEX WITH KATIE.
YOU HAVE A PROBLEM
THAT MOST GUYS DREAM OF.
TWO GIRLS LIKE YOU.
TWO GREAT GIRLS.
HOW COULD YOU DO THIS?
SHHHH! OKAY.
I DON'T KNOW!
WELL, I CAN'T TELL BIANCA.
AND I CAN'T BREAK UP
WITH KATIE
THE DAY AFTER WE LOST
OUR VIRGINITY TO EACH OTHER.
WHAT DO I DO?
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
HAD SEX LAST NIGHT.
MAN UP.
MRS. COHEN:
TODAY YOU'LL BE CHOOSING YOUR
LAB GROUPS FOR THE TERM.
CHOOSE WISELY AS YOU'LL BE
SPENDING A LOT OF TIME TOGETHER.
KATIE, BIANCA:
PARTNERS?
(NERVOUS EXHALE)
DREW:
HOT PLATE, BEAKERS,
TEST TUBE, GOGGLES.
KATIE:
CHECK, CHECK, AND CHECK!
YOU'RE IN A GOOD MOOD TODAY.
YEAH.
WHY WOULDN'T I BE?
DREW:
I THINK WE'RE MISSING TONGS!
NOPE.
THEY'RE RIGHT HERE.
MRS. COHEN:
GLOVES ARE MANDATORY WHEN WE'RE
SYNTHESIZING ACETAMINOPHEN.
COME GET YOUR CHEMICALS.
KATIE, DO YOU MIND?
MY LEG'S CRAMPED UP.
YEAH, KATIE.
DO YOU MIND?
KATIE:
NOT AT ALL.
EITHER KATIE'S TAKING
THE BREAK UP SUPER WELL,
OR IT DIDN'T HAPPEN.
IT HAPPENED, ALL RIGHT,
BUT IT KINDA REVERSED.
SHE THINKS
WE'RE BACK TOGETHER.
OKAY.
THAT MAKES NO SENSE!
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO BREAK UP
WITH HER JUST TELL ME.
YOU KNOW THAT'S NOT TRUE.
THEN DO I HAVE TO DO IT
FOR YOU? RIGHT NOW?
SHHH. NO! PLEASE.
YOU CAN'T.
ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS A DELICATE MATTER.
FOR NOW, CAN YOU JUST PRETEND
WE'RE NOT TOGETHER?
NEXT TIME I'M NOT GONNA BE
PRETENDING.
KATIE:
ACETIC ANHYDRIDE DELIVERY!
DON'T BURN YOURSELF.
WHOA!
WHAT'S HER PROBLEM?
THE CHEMICALS
MAKE HER LIGHT-HEADED.
SO UM, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING TONIGHT?
HANGING WITH YOU,
I HOPE.
(BELL RINGS)
(EXHALES)
HEY...
I CAN'T FIND
MY MUSIC SHEETS.
I HEARD THAT'S NOT
THE ONLY THING YOU LOST.
EVERYONE'S CALLING YOU
CHICKEN CUTLET.
I THINK I PREFERRED
PANCAKE.
FOR WHAT IT'S WORTH, I'M REALLY
IMPRESSED YOU KEPT ON PLAYING.
I WOULD HAVE RAN OUT
OF THERE, MORTIFIED.
WELL,
FIRST RULE OF BAND:
NEVER STOP PLAYING
IN THE MIDDLE OF A SONG.
I THINK I RATHER
JUST HIDE FROM MO
AND THOSE STUPID HOCKEY GUYS
UNTIL I GROW REAL BOOBS.
YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE PERFECT AS YOU ARE.
IF YOU JUST WAIT A YEAR-
WHY DON'T YOU HAVE
TO WAIT A YEAR?
WELL, BECAUSE...
BECAUSE I FAILED GRADE FOUR.
WHAT?
TELL ANYONE AND YOU DIE.
JUST SO YOU KNOW,
I WOULD TRADE THESE IN
FOR JUST A FRACTION
OF YOUR MUSICAL TALENT...
ANY DAY.
(SIGHS)
CHICKEN CUTLET?
I'LL NEVER LIVE THIS DOWN?
TORI:
AH, GIVE IT 'TIL TOMORROW.
UNTIL THEN, I'LL MAKE SURE
YOU MAKE IT OUT ALIVE.
HEY.
GUESS WHAT?
YOU'RE EXCITED I GOT TICKETS TO
THE ARCADE FIRE SHOW TONIGHT.
YOU DID NOT!
OH, YES, I DID.
IT'S OUR RE-FIRST DATE,
SO WE'RE GONNA NEED
A RE-FIRST SONG.
I'M THINKING TUNNELS.
BUT I HAVE MY INTERNSHIP
PLACEMENT TONIGHT.
OH.
WHAT TIME IS THE SHOW?
EIGHT.
I CAN BE DONE BY THEN.
I WILL BE DONE BY THEN.
(SIGHS)
THAT'S IT.
WE'RE DONE HERE.
DALLAS:
(BUZZER SOUND)
MINOR PENALTY
FOR BEING A SOFTY.
"DONE HERE" SOUNDS LIKE
YOU'RE WRAPPING UP A MEETING.
YOU GUYS WANNA DO IT FOR ME?
ADAM:
MAYBE USE DIFFERENT LANGUAGE,
LIKE:
"WE CAN'T BE TOGETHER ANYMORE."
OR, "THIS ISN'T GONNA
WORK OUT."
DREW:
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I DON'T WANT HER TO HATE ME,
YOU KNOW,
WE USED TO LOVE EACH OTHER.
DALLAS:
(BUZZER SOUND)
STOP SAYING THE L WORD.
IT'S DANGEROUS AND LEADING.
YOU WANNA MAKE SURE
ALL DOORS ARE CLOSED.
TRUE DAT.
DALLAS:
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S TALK GAME PLAN.
WHERE ARE YOU
GONNA DO THIS?
UM...AT THE DOT.
THERE IS LOTS OF PEOPLE THERE.
SO SHE CAN'T MAKE A SCENE.
DALLAS:
GOOD. WHEN?
BEFORE WE ORDER.
SO I CAN ESCAPE.
DALLAS:
ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE ON THE BREAKAWAY,
STAY FOCUSED
AND DON'T HESITATE.
IF YOU DO,
YOUR WHOLE PLAY'LL COLLAPSE.
HOW MANY TIMES
HAVE YOU DONE THIS?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
WHAT IF SHE TRIES
TO HUG YOU?
YOU NEVER HUG OR TOUCH
AFTER A BREAK UP.
IT COULD LEAD TO MORE.
OKAY, BUT WHAT IF SHE'S CRYING?
AND SAYS SHE LOVES YOU?
THEN... MAYBE A LITTLE HUG?
(BUZZER SOUND)
I'M NOT A MONSTER!
ADAM:
IN THIS SITUATION,
YOU KINDA ARE.
DALLAS:
YOU BEING THE GOOD GUY ISN'T
DOING ANYONE ANY FAVOURS.
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE
IN THIS MESS. DROP IT.
I JUST WANNA GET OUR OF HERE.
DON'T WORRY.
NOBODY CARES.
HE'S FOLLOWING US.
WALK FASTER.
MO:
MAYA, YOU DROPPED SOMETHING
AT YOUR AUDITION.
I KNOW.
YOU CAN THROW IT OUT.
WELL, I WOULD.
BUT I TOOK A CLOSER LOOK-
AWESOME.
AT YOUR MUSIC SHEET.
I WAS KINDA BLOWN AWAY.
YOU WROTE ALL THIS?
I THOUGHT IT MIGHT WORK
FOR THE BAND.
WELL,
WHAT ELSE DO YOU PLAY?
BASS, GUITAR, PIANO.
I CAN PICK UP MOST
STRING INSTRUMENTS.
OKAY.
I NEED YOU IN THIS BAND.
REALLY?
YES.
THIS IS MY HAPPY FACE,
I SWEAR.
WHO ELSE MADE IT?
NO ONE YET, BUT CAN I GET
YOUR INPUT TOMORROW?
YOU WILL NOT REGRET THIS.
AWESOME.
(HAPPY SQUEALS)
OWEN:
MAN, I'M HUNGRY.
I COULD REALLY GO FOR
A CHICKEN CUTLET RIGHT NOW.
EAT THIS.
YOU KNOW, I THINK YOU'RE
GONNA WANT THIS BACK.
KEEP IT.
IT'S THE MOST ACTION
YOU'LL GET ALL YEAR.
OH!
(OTHERS LAUGH)
I'M SORRY.
I'LL BUY YOU NEW ONES.
DON'T EVEN BOTHER.
YOU'RE MY NEW HERO.
ASHER:
TELL YOU WHAT, I'LL GIVE YOU
THAT PIECE ON LRT TRANSIT
THAT YOU WANTED.
FIFTEEN MINUTES?
COME ON.
HALF AN HOUR, MY TERMS,
OR NO LRT.
NOW WE'RE TALKING.
OKAY, SEE YOU TOMORROW.
CLARE:
MR. SHOSTAK?
SORRY TO INTERRUPT.
I'M CLARE EDWARDS,
FROM DEGRASSI.
HOW ARE YOU
WITH FACT CHECKING?
GREAT.
GOOD.
YOU CAN GET STARTED
ON THESE.
JUST SO YOU KNOW,
I GET FIVE REQUESTS A DAY
FROM STUDENTS WANTING
A CO-OP.
THIS IS A COVETED SPOT.
I KNOW,
AND I AM VERY GRATEFUL.
I DON'T WANT YOU
TO BE GRATEFUL.
I WANT YOU TO BE SERIOUS
ABOUT JOURNALISM.
I AM MORE SERIOUS
ABOUT THIS THAN ANYTHING.
I REALLY WANT TO LEARN.
WHEN IT COMES TO WRITING,
WHAT'S MOST IMPORTANT TO YOU?
THERE IS NO RIGHT
OR WRONG ANSWER,
JUST GETTING A SENSE
OF WHAT YOU DO.
UH...
I'D SAY... CLARITY.
JUST LIKE YOUR
NAME SUGGESTS.
GET TO WORK, NEWSIE.
YEAH.
GOT IT.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
(SIGHS)
KATIE:
YOU WANNA SHARE FRIES?
DREW:
NO!
OKAY, WEIRDO.
GUESS I'LL EAT A WHOLE
PLATE MYSELF.
YOU READY TO ORDER?
WE NEED TO TALK.
OKAY. WELL, CAN IT WAIT
'TIL AFTER WE ORDER?
I'VE BEEN WAITING WEEKS.
I CAN'T WAIT ANYMORE.
(SIGHS)
WE NEED TO BREAK UP.
FOR GOOD THIS TIME.
THAT'S WHY I ASKED YOU
TO COME HERE.
I DON'T WANT TO BE
WITH YOU ANYMORE.
BUT YESTERDAY,
WE-WE TALKED.
YOU SAID WE WERE
GONNA BE OKAY.
WE HAD SEX.
I WAS DRUNK.
I DON'T EVEN REMEMBER.
YOU SAID YOU WEREN'T.
THIS IS MY WORST NIGHTMARE.
WHY IS THIS HAPPENING TO ME?
DREW:
WHEN YOU WERE ON DRUGS,
I REALIZED I WANTED
TO BE WITH BIANCA.
WE WAITED UNTIL
YOU WERE BETTER.
SO I CAN BREAK UP
WITH YOU.
I LOVED YOU.
YOU'LL FIND SOMEONE NEW.
BIANCA DOESN'T KNOW
THAT WE HAD SEX...
YOU CAN'T TELL ANYONE.
(SOBS)
(DOOR SLAMS)
(SIGHS)
HERE YOU ARE -
ALL DOUBLE CHECKED,
WITH RECOMMENDED ADJUSTMENTS
MARKED ON EVERY PAGE.
RECORD TIME.
THANKS.
SO, I'LL SEE YOU NEXT WEEK?
OR YOU CAN COME WATCH US
COVER THE TENT CITY PROTEST
DOWN AT CITY HALL?
IT'S A BIG OPPORTUNITY
ON YOUR FIRST DAY.
YOU SAID YOU WANTED TO LEARN.
CAN YOU GIVE ME
ONE MINUTE?
(BUTTONS BEEP)
(PHONE RINGS)
HEY, HOW'D IT GO?
WELL.
REALLY WELL.
ELI:
AWESOME!
SHOULD I COME GET YOU?
ACTUALLY...
ASHER ASKED ME TO GO WITH
HIS TEAM TO COVER A PROTEST.
ARE YOU MAD?
NAH, I'M JUST GONNA GO DRIVE
MY HEARSE INTO A WALL.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
I'M KIDDING!
ELI!
ELI:
(CHUCKLE) SORRY!
SERIOUSLY THOUGH, WE CAN GO
ON OUR RE-FIRST DATE ANYTIME.
CLARE:
I KNOW, BUT IT WAS IMPORTANT
TO ME.
ELI:
YEAH. ME TOO.
BUT BEING "ALL IN" DOESN'T
MEAN DROPPING EVERYTHING.
AND JUST BECAUSE YOU CANCEL
A DATE ON ME,
DOESN'T MEAN I'M GONNA LOSE IT.
I KNEW THAT, YOU KNOW?
YOU GONNA GO WITH ADAM?
YEAH. HE'S GONNA HIT
THE CEILING WHEN I TELL HIM.
AND SINCE YOU FOUND YOUR THING,
MAYBE THE SHOW WILL
INSPIRE ME TO FIND MINE.
YOU KNOW, BULK UP MY NYU
PORTFOLIO.
I CAN'T WAIT TO HEAR
WHAT YOU COME UP WITH.
NEWSIE, YOU COMING?
HAVE FUN.
THANKS.
I'M RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
YOU SHOULD HAVE
SEEN HER FACE.
SHE'S NOT THE FIRST GIRL
TO GET DUMPED.
SHE'LL GET OVER IT.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYONE SO SAD.
WELL, AT LEAST THE HARDEST
PART'S OVER.
AND THE BEST PART'S
JUST STARTING.
(BOTH GIGGLE)
BIANCA:
TWELVE O'CLOCK.
MARISOL:
OH, LOOK WHO IT IS.
THE LIAR, THE BITCH,
AND HER SLUTTY WARDROBE.
KATIE:
MARE.
BIANCA:
LOOK, I'M SORRY
HOW THIS WENT DOWN.
DREW:
AT LEAST WE CAN ALL MOVE ON.
NOW THAT EVERYTHING'S OUT
IN THE OPEN.
IS IT?
WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
NO IDEA.
ARE MY CLOTHES THAT SLUTTY?
(CHUCKLES)
DO ME A FAVOUR?
AND DON'T EVER LISTEN TO
ANYTHING THOSE GIRLS SAY.
OKAY.