♪ I feel you let go ♪
♪ Where I end up
I don't know ♪
UGH! WHAT AM I DOING?
I MEAN, ASKING THIS GUY
FOR MONEY?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW HIM.
MARISOL:
WELL, THEN LET'S GO.
I MEAN, WE CAN STILL
GET A SWIM IN
NO, MARE.
I CAN'T GO HOME
AND TELL MY PARENTS
THAT I LOST MY ENTIRE
UNIVERSITY FUND.
DARRIN:
NOTHING SAYS
"GOOD MORNING, LAS VEGAS"
LIKE A MIMOSA.
KATIE:
THANKS.
SO, UH, BLACKJACK
DIDN'T GO SO WELL?
HOW MUCH?
UM, FIVE THOUSAND.
LOOK, I'M NOT HERE
FOR A HANDOUT OR ANYTHING.
UM, MAYBE I COULD...
I COULD WORK FOR YOU
THIS SUMMER.
I CAN TYPE A 150 WORDS
PER MINUTE
AND I MAKE A MEAN LATTE.
I'VE ALREADY GOT PEOPLE
WHO DO THAT FOR ME, KATIE.
RIGHT.
OF COURSE YOU DO.
OF COURSE
YOU CAN'T HIRE ME.
NO, BUT I CAN GIVE YOU
THE MONEY.
YOU WOULD JUST HAND OVER
FIVE GRAND?!
IF YOU SPEND THE AFTERNOON
WITH ME.
MARISOL:
UH, SHE'S NOT HAVING SEX
WITH YOU.
NO, I KNOW.
BUT YOU'RE YOUNG,
YOU'RE AMBITIOUS,
YOU'RE SMART.
I JUST WANNA RUN
SOME FACERANGE IDEAS BY YOU.
(DARRIN'S PHONE CHIMES)
ANYWAYS, YOU TWO THINK IT OVER.
SORRY,
I GOTTA TAKE THIS.
YOU'RE ACTUALLY
CONSIDERING THIS?
WELL, I NEED THE MONEY
AND HE NEEDS IDEAS...
OKAY,
DO YOU REMEMBER JAKE?
TALL, WEARS FLANNEL,
IS YOUR BOYFRIEND.
WELL, I DON'T HAVE
TO TELL HIM.
KATIE,
I CAN'T COVER FOR YOU.
I AM THE WORST LIAR
IN THE WORLD.
WELL, YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO WORK ON IT, OKAY?
CUZ I DON'T KNOW
WHAT ELSE TO DO,
AND I'M IN THE HOLE,
MARE,
AND THIS IS THE ONLY WAY
I'M GONNA BE ABLE
PULL MYSELF OUT.
(SIGHS)
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ I can  make it through ♪
(Ooh-ooh-ooh)
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ I can make it! ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
BECKY:
GIRLS? WHAT DO YOU MEAN
THERE WERE GIRLS THERE?
WELL, THERE MIGHT'VE BEEN
OTHER GIRLS THERE,
BUT I ONLY HAVE EYES
FOR YOU.
AW! THAT'S SO SWEET.
DREW:
ADAM!
CALL MY PHONE!
I GOTTA GO.
BEST MAN TIME.
BEST MAN EVER!
'KAY, WELL,
I'M GOING TO THE POOL.
SHOULDN'T YOU WORK
ON YOUR VOWS OR SOMETHING?
JUST... CALL MY PHONE.
(DREW'S PHONE RINGS)
OKAY, YEAH,
SO IT IS WORKING.
WHY ISN'T SHE
CALLING ME BACK?
I DON'T KNOW.
DIDN'T IMOGEN CONFISCATE
BIANCA'S PHONE?
NOT... NOT BIANCA.
MOM.
YOU CALLED MOM?!
WHY WOULD CALL MOM?
SHE THINKS
WE'RE CAMPING!
ADAM...
IT'S BECAUSE I DON'T THINK
I CAN GET MARRIED
WITHOUT HER HERE!
SO, WHAT,
YOU'RE JUST GONNA CANCEL
THE WEDDING?
YOU'RE A GENIUS.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
TO FIND BIANCA
AND TELL HER.
SHE LOVES ME.
SHE'LL UNDERSTAND.
HAVE YOU MET BIANCA?!
JAKE:
ALL RIGHT! WE ARE SO RIDING
THE ROLLER COASTER
AT NEW YORK, NEW YORK.
YOU GIRLS READY?
UM... ACTUALLY,
I'M REALLY NOT FEELING SO HOT.
I THINK I MIGHT JUST,
YOU KNOW,
WATCH A MOVIE IN THE ROOM
OR SOMETHING.
MARISOL:
WELL, GOOD LUCK.
KATIE:
LOOK, YOU GUYS HAVE FUN, OKAY?
I'LL, UH, SEE YOU
AT THE WEDDING.
'KAY.
GET ME A KEY CHAIN
OR SOMETHING
SO I CAN PRETEND
I WAS THERE.
OKAY.
DREW:
OKAY, SHE'S NOT ANSWERING
HER PHONE,
NOT IN HER ROOM.
HEY, GUYS, HAVE YOU GUYS
SEEN BIANCA TODAY?
NO. WHY?
I NEED TO CALL OFF
THE WEDDING.
MARISOL:
HA! I TOLD YOU!
FIVE BUCKS!
ADAM:
NO, HE DOES NOT NEED
TO CALL OFF THE WEDDING.
DREW,
YOU'RE BEING DUMB!
THE ONLY REASON I WENT ALONG
WITH YOUR CRAZY PLAN
TO GET MARRIED
IN LOS VEGAS
IS BECAUSE I KNOW
HOW MUCH YOU LOVE BIANCA.
YEAH. YEAH.
SHE'S THE ONLY ONE
WHO'S STUCK WITH ME
THROUGH EVERYTHING,
BUT...
ADAM:
DO YOU WANNA LOSE BIANCA
FOREVER?
KATIE:
I KNOW YOU'RE PAYING
FOR THIS, BUT...
YOU HAVE A BOYFRIEND.
YES, I KNOW.
YEAH, AND HE'S A LOT BETTER
THAN THE ONE I HAD LAST YEAR,
SO I JUST DON'T WANNA CROSS
ANY BOUNDARIES, YOU KNOW?
UM, YOU SAID YOU WANTED
TO TALK ABOUT FACERANGE?
EVENTUALLY, BUT RIGHT NOW
I NEED HELP WITH SOMETHING ELSE.
UH, WHAT EXACTLY?
I NEED SOME NEW CLOTHES.
UNGH!
KATIE:
(LAUGHS)
LET ME SEE...
THIS ONE?
YEAH, MONEY CAN BUY
A LOT OF THINGS...
NOT STYLE?
(BOTH LAUGH)
UM, WHAT ABOUT THIS ONE?
ALL RIGHT.
KATIE:
SO, UH, YOU LIVE LIKE THIS
EVERY DAY?
WELL, I LIKE TO TREAT MYSELF
TO THE FINER THINGS.
YEAH. TOO BAD
YOU DON'T HAVE ANYONE
TO SHARE IT WITH.
WELL, TODAY, I HAVE YOU.
YOU UP FOR A CONCERT?
UH... YEAH.
JUST, UM,
IS THIS OKAY TO WEAR?
OR YOU COULD PICK
SOMETHING NEW.
WOW! UM...
WOW! YEAH.
GO TRY IT ON.
WOW!
WOW,
YOU NAILED IT!
YOU LIKE?
YES, I LIKE.
(BOTH LAUGH)
WOW!
UH, YOUR CHECK IS OVER HERE,
JUST TO GET THE BUSINESS
OUTTA THE WAY.
I ALSO THREW IN A BOTTLE
OF CHAMPAGNE
FOR THE NEWLYWEDS.
THANK YOU.
UM, HAVE I MENTIONED
THIS IS NUTS YET?
SO, UM, HOW FAR
IS THIS CONCERT?
IT'S NOT TOO FAR.
(BAND CHATTERS)
KATIE:
(GASPS) OH MY GOD,
IS THAT... HEDLEY?
YEAH, YOU LIKE?
DARRIN: HEY, GUYS! JACOB!
JACOB: HOW ARE YOU?
DARRIN: GOOD TO SEE YOU!
JACOB: GOOD TO SEE YOU!
DARRIN: BOYS.
JACOB: SHALL WE?
(OPENING STRAINS OF
"KISS YOU INSIDE OUT" PLAY)
HOW IS THIS EVEN REAL?
YOU WANNA DANCE?
C'MON. I'VE BEEN
TAKING LESSONS.
(JACOB STARTS SINGING)
DARRIN:
COME ON,
I'M NOT TAKING NO.
YOU'RE PRETTY GOOD.
VERY NICE.
♪ I WILL FEEL
EVERY INCH OF YOUR SKIN ♪
♪ AND YOU KNOW
I CAN ROCK YOUR WORLD ♪
♪ I'M GONNA BE THE CALM
IN THE STORM ♪
♪ YOU'RE LOOKING FOR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THE SHIPWRECK
THAT TAKES YOU DOWN ♪
♪ I DON'T MIND
IF YOU LIE IN MY BED ♪
♪ WE CAN STAY HERE FOREVER NOW ♪
♪ WOO-OOH-OOH!
TURN OFF THE LIGHTS ♪
♪ TAKE OFF YOUR CLOTHES ♪
♪ TURN ON THE STEREO ♪
♪ WOO-OOH-OOH!
GIVE UP THE FIGHT ♪
♪ I'M IN CONTROL ♪
♪ WHY DON'T YOU LET IT GO ♪
♪ YEAH, I WANNA KNOW YOU
INSIDE OUT ♪
KATIE:
SO, WHY'D YOU DO THIS?
I MEAN, THE BAND,
THE DRESS...
WE DIDN'T EVEN TALK
ABOUT FACERANGE.
DARRIN:
HONESTLY?
I WANNA HAVE SEX
WITH YOU.
KATIE:
UH... WOW, THAT IS HONEST.
DARRIN:
AND, IF YOU'RE WILLING,
THROW ON ANOTHER
TWENTY THOUSAND DOLLARS
TO THAT CHECK.
IT SHOULD BE ENOUGH TO COVER
YOUR FIRST YEAR AT STANFORD,
RIGHT?
UM, I'M REALLY SORRY,
BUT I'M JUST...
NOT THAT GIRL.
DARRIN:
OKAY.
WELL, IF YOU FIND THAT GIRL,
TELL HER WHERE TO FIND ME.
(CHURCH BELLS CHIME)
(DREW SIGHS, NERVOUS)
OKAY, SHE SHOULD'VE...
SHE SHOULD'VE BEEN HERE
TEN MINUTES AGO.
THINK SHE GOT DELAYED?
ADAM:
DON'T LOOK SO EXCITED.
(SIGHS) ADAM,
IT COULD BE PERFECT.
WE COULD RESCHEDULE
AND...
DUDE, THIS IS HAPPENING.
FOCUS.
KATIE IS NOT RETURNING
ANY OF MY TEXTS.
HAVE YOU TALKED
TO HER?
MARISOL:
UH... YEAH.
IT'S PROBABLY
JUST BAD RECEPTION
IN THE SHOPPING CENTRE.
YOU SAID SHE'S THERE
BUYING TIGHTS.
YUP,
TO MATCH HER DRESS.
MARISOL:
(SIGHS) I CAN'T LIE TO YOU.
KATIE:
HEY!
HEY.
(SIGHS, HURT)
MARISOL TOLD YOU?
YEAH.
WHY WOULD YOU LIE
TO ME?
I'M SORRY, OKAY?
I...
I NEEDED THE MONEY.
OKAY, JAKE,
PLEASE UNDERSTAND, OKAY?
I COULDN'T GO HOME
WITHOUT MY PARENT'S MONEY.
WHAT IS THE BIG DEAL
ABOUT STANFORD ANYWAY?
IT IS ONE OF THE BEST
SCHOOL'S AROUND
AND I GOT IN.
AND THAT MEANS MORE TO YOU
THAN I DO?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
MAYBE IF YOU WEREN'T STONED
ALL THE TIME, YOU'D GET IT.
WOW. OKAY.
OKAY, I THINK WE'RE
JUST ABOUT DONE HERE.
KATIE:
JAKE...
JAKE! JAKE!
I DIDN'T MEAN IT!
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
FIONA:
ALL CLEAR?
STILL NO DREW IN SIGHT,
BUT WE HAVE TO HURRY!
YOU LOOK SO BEAUTIFUL.
ARE YOU READY
TO GET MARRIED?
I'M SO NERVOUS
I CAN'T FEEL MY LEGS.
DON'T WORRY.
ONCE YOU SEE DREW,
ALL OF THOSE BUTTERFLIES
WILL FLY AWAY.
OH! AND HERE'S
YOUR PHONE BACK
IN CASE YOU WANNA TAKE
SOME WEDDING PICS.
TWENTY MISSED CALLS
FROM DREW?!
I PUT IT ON SILENT.
OKAY, I SHOULD CHECK
MY MESSAGES.
NO! HE WAS PROBABLY
JUST DRUNK-DIALING.
YOUR SOON-TO-BE HUBBY
IS WAITING!
WE HAVE TO RUN!
BIANCA:
OKAY, LET'S DO THIS.
GUYS, I STILL CAN'T FEEL
MY LEGS.
OKAY.
ADAM: DREW?
DREW: YEAH?
ADAM:
THE FRONT DESK SAID SHE LEFT
10 MINUTES AGO.
(BLOWS OUT HIS BREATH)
OKAY, LET'S DO THIS.
(CHEESY ORGAN VERSION
OF "THE WEDDING MARCH" PLAYS)
DREW:
MOM?!
(SUITCASE CRASHES ON FLOOR)
UH-OH.
YEAH, "UH-OH."
I'LL DEAL WITH YOU LATER,
MISTER.
YOU CAME!
YEAH! RIGHT AFTER
I GOT YOUR MESSAGE.
NOW, CAN WE PLEASE
GO HOME
BEFORE YOU GO ON
WITH THIS FOOLISHNESS?
(WEDDING MARCH
STARTS PLAYING AGAIN)
(GASPS)
(RECORDING STOPS PLAYING,
IMOGEN GASPS)
BIANCA:
WHAT'S SHE DOING HERE?
HE CALLED ME...
TO TELL ME HE WAS MAKING
A BIG MISTAKE
GETTING MARRIED.
YOU SAID THAT?!
NO.
I MEAN, UM, YES.
WOULD YOU PLEASE
LET ME EXPLAIN?
NO. SAVE IT, DREW.
I GET IT.
I'LL NEVER BE ENOUGH
FOR YOU.
(DOOR CLICKS SHUT)
(CAR RUMBLES BY
IN THE DISTANCE)
I'M GOING TO FIND BIANCA.
UH, NO,
YOU NEED TO TALK TO ME.
DREW:
STOP TELLING ME
WHAT TO DO!
NOW, I'M GOING TO GET
THE LOVE OF MY LIFE!
MADONNA DRAG QUEEN:
MM-HMM! GO AHEAD, HONEY,
EXPRESS YOURSELF.
UH, EXCUSE ME!
WERE YOU NOT THE ONE
WHO CALLED ME?!
AM I NOT HERE TO TALK
SOME SENSE INTO YOU
BECAUSE YOU WERE MAKING
A "HUGE MISTAKE"?
THE MISTAKE THAT I THOUGHT
I WAS MAKING
WAS GETTING MARRIED
WITHOUT YOU HERE.
I GUESS I WAS WRONG.
DREW,
YOU'RE EIGHTEEN YEARS OLD.
YOU HAVE YOUR WHOLE LIFE
AHEAD OF YOU.
AND THANKS TO YOU,
BIANCA MIGHT NOT BE IN IT.
I KNOW YOU NEVER
APPROVED OF HER,
AND YOU TOLD HER
TO HER FACE
THAT SHE WASN'T GOOD ENOUGH
FOR ME,
BUT I LOVE HER...
AND I NEED HER
IN MY LIFE.
SO, PLEASE...
PLEASE DO NOT MAKE ME
CHOOSE.
I JUST CAN'T SUPPORT
A TEEN WEDDING.
(SHARP INHALE)
OKAY...
BUT, FOR ONCE, WILL YOU
PLEASE JUST SUPPORT ME?
(TRAFFIC RUMBLES
IN THE DISTANCE)
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
SOME SPRING BREAK, HUH?
HEY.
UM... YOU WANT SOME
CHAMPAGNE?
IT WAS A WEDDING GIFT.
THIS MUST'VE COST
A THOUSAND DOLLARS.
YEAH, PROBABLY.
I DON'T KNOW,
SOME RICH GUY GAVE IT TO ME.
WHY? DID YOU HAVE SEX
WITH HIM?
(LAUGHS)
OF COURSE NOT.
UM, BUT IF I DID,
HE WOULD'VE GIVEN ME
A LOT MORE
THAN A BOTTLE OF CHAMPAGNE.
THANKS.
UGH! GROSS.
SO WAS HE LIKE
A MILLION YEARS OLD -
THE RICH DUDE
WHO GAVE YOU THE CHAMPAGNE?
UH, NO, ACTUALLY.
HE WAS LIKE TWENTY-THREE,
TWENTY-FIVE TOPS.
AND CUTE?
REALLY CUTE.
AND HE PLANNED THIS AMAZING,
AMAZING AFTERNOON FOR US.
MY GUY DITCHED ME
AT THE ALTAR.
YOU CAN'T COUNT ON ANYONE,
CAN YOU?
WELL, I UH...
I THOUGHT I COULD.
I... I MESSED UP
SO MUCH THIS YEAR.
I FEEL LIKE I NEED
A FRESH START.
I NEED STANFORD,
YOU KNOW?
WHATEVER IT TAKES,
RIGHT?
YEAH.
LOOK, I'M... I'M SORRY,
I GOTTA GO.
(PHONE CHIMES)
(FOUNTAIN ERUPTS,
WATER SPLASHES GENTLY)
(SIREN WAILS
IN THE DISTANCE)
(DARRIN SIGHS)
KATIE:
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
DARRIN:
YEAH.
YEAH, JUST LIKE YOU.
IS UM...
IS IT GETTING HOT IN HERE?
YEAH, DEFINITELY.
KATIE:
NO. UM, I MEAN...
CAN I, UM, GET A GLASS
OF WATER?
(SIGHS)
YEAH, SURE.
(SIREN WAILS IN THE DISTANCE)
(SLOT MACHINES BEEP AND WHIR,
ROOM BUZZES WITH CHATTER)
GOOD.
YOU'RE STILL HERE.
OH, SO OUR WEDDING'S A BUST
AND YOU GO TO THE GYM
TO WORK OUT?
THAT'S AWESOME, DREW.
LOOK,
I WAS A FOOL TODAY.
THAT'S GENEROUS.
BUT I'M ABOUT TO DO SOMETHING
EVEN MORE FOOLISH.
♪ WISE MEN SAY ♪
♪ ONLY FOOLS RUSH IN... ♪
♪ BUT I CAN'T HELP ♪
♪ FALLING IN LOVE WITH YOU ♪
♪ SHALL I STAY ♪
♪ WOULD IT BE A SIN? ♪
♪ IF I CAN'T HELP ♪
♪ FALLING IN LOVE WITH YOU! ♪
♪ TAKE MY HAND ♪
♪ TAKE MY WHOLE LIFE, TOO ♪
♪ FOR I CAN'T HELP ♪
♪ FALLING IN LOVE WITH YOU ♪
(CLAPPING AND CHEERING)
YOU DID ALL THIS?
NO. I HAD A LOT OF HELP.
I THINK THAT'S THE POINT,
AND THEY SHOULD BE
AT OUR WEDDING.
SO YOU STILL WANNA
GET MARRIED?
YES!
BIANCA DESOUSA,
YOU'RE THE LIGHT
OF MY LIFE -
NOT THE ONLY LIGHT,
BUT DEFINITELY
THE BRIGHTEST.
WILL YOU MARRY ME,
SOMETIME,
IN FRONT OF EVERYONE
WE KNOW AND LOVE?
YES!
YES?
(CROWD MURMURS)
SHE SAID "YES!"
(CLAPPING AND CHEERING)
ANNOUNCEMENT:
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
WELCOME ABOARD YOUR FLIGHT.
PLEASE ENSURE YOUR LUGGAGE
IS SECURELY STOWED
IN THE OVERHEAD COMPARTMENTS
OR TUCKED SAFELY BENEATH
THE SEAT IN FRONT OF YOU.
IF YOU NEED ASSISTANCE,
A FLIGHT ATTENDANT
WILL BE HAPPY TO HELP.
YOU OKAY?
I NEED TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING.
I WENT TO DARRIN'S ROOM
LAST NIGHT.
MARISOL:
OH MY GOD!
THAT IS SO DANGEROUS.
DID YOU...?
HE LEFT ME ALONE AT ONE POINT
TO GET ME A DRINK
AND I SAW MY REFLECTION
IN THE GLASS AND....
I DON'T KNOW, MARE,
IT JUST DIDN'T LOOK LIKE ME.
IT LOOKED LIKE SOME...
DESPERATE GIRL.
I JUST... I COULDN'T SINK
ANY FURTHER,
SO I GRABBED MY BAG
AND I RAN.
(SIGHS WITH RELIEF)
PHEW!
GIRL, YOU HAD ME
SO WORRIED.
YEAH, I KNOW. I KNOW.
I'M... GLAD I GOT OUT.
HEY, UH...
(UNZIPS BAG)
THANKS FOR THE KEY CHAIN.
UH, IT WASN'T ME.
I LOST A REALLY
GREAT GUY, HUH?
MARISOL:
KATIE, YOU'RE NEVER GONNA
BE ALONE, 'KAY?
YOU'RE ALWAYS GONNA
HAVE ME!
AW, THANKS.
(PLANE ENGINE RUMBLES)
OMAR:
NON-ALCOHOLIC BUBBLY FOR ALL.
AUDRA:
WELL, WE'VE ALL BEEN THROUGH
A LOT THIS YEAR,
BUT NO ONE'S BEEN THROUGH MORE
THAN THESE TWO.
AND TO BE HONEST,
PART OF ME BLAMED BIANCA.
MOM...
I KNOW.
IT WASN'T FAIR.
AND BIANCA, I WANNA WELCOME YOU
TO THE FAMILY WITH OPEN ARMS,
WHICH IS WHY
I, UH, HELPED DREW
WITH A LITTLE SOMETHING.
DREW:
I HOPE THIS MAKES IT
A LITTLE BIT MORE OFFICIAL.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
THANK YOU.
AUDRA:
IT WAS MY GRANDMOTHER'S.
OMAR: WOW!
(EVERYONE CLAPS)
AUDRA: CONGRATULATIONS.
DREW: THANKS, MOM.
I REALLY MISSED YOU.
I MISSED YOU, TOO.
(SIGHS HAPPILY)
(DREW CHUCKLES HAPPILY)
SEE? ISN'T LIFE
A LITTLE EASIER
WHEN IT'S NOT JUST
YOU AND ME
AGAINST THE WORLD?
YEAH.
(CLAPPING)