♪ When I lose right now ♪
♪ I'm betting all my chips ♪
♪ When I'm broken down ♪
♪ I'll be brushin' off♪
my kicks ♪
THIS IS IT DALLAS,
THE FAMOUS DEGRASSI.
YOU MEAN INFAMOUS.
MARISOL:
CAN'T TALK HERE.
DALLAS: WHOO!
ADAM: HEY!
I LIKE IT!
AUDRA:
HEY, REMEMBER YOUR FATHER
AND I ARE IN KINGSTON TONIGHT,
BACK IN THE MORNING.
PIZZA MONEY'S ON THE COUNTER.
YOU CAN HAVE ONE OR TWO
FRIENDS OVER.
ADAM: SO, A PARTY!
AUDRA: FUNNY.
SO WHAT'S THE BIG
ASSEMBLY ABOUT?
PROBABLY TO WELCOME YOU.
NEW MAJOR JUNIOR HOCKEY TEAM
TAKING OVER OUR SCHOOL.
I DON'T KNOW DREW,
THEY SENT HOME LETTERS.
I HAVE A TERRIBLE FEELING
THE SCHOOL'S SHUTTING DOWN.
THE SCHOOL IS NOT
SHUTTING DOWN, ADAM!
I HOPE NOT,
I JUST GOT HERE.
THERE'S MY TEAM,
I'LL CHECK YOU GUYS LATER.
WHAT UP, BOYS?
'YO, THE SCHOOL'S DEFINITELY
SHUTTING DOWN.
REALLY?
YOU TOO?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH HIM?
HE WAS SUPPOSED TO DUMP KATIE
LAST NIGHT, AND CHICKENED OUT.
I DID NOT CHICKEN OUT!
I WENT OVER THERE
TO PULL THE TRIGGER,
AND HER PARENTS GAVE ME
A SWEATER.
(ALLI AND JENNA LAUGH)
WELL, I GET IT, OKAY?
BREAKING UP IS HARD.
THE DRAMA, THE CRYING,
CLARE:
HEY, HAVE YOU GUYS SEEN ELI?
THE CAR CRASHES.
DREW:
NOT HELPING.
CLARE:
THAT WAS A LONG TIME AGO!
WHATEVER, I GOTTA DO IT SOON,
OR I'LL LOSE BIANCA FOR GOOD.
BIANCA?
AREN'T YOU WITH KATIE?
LONG STORY, JENNA.
ALI:
WELL, I SURE DODGED A BULLET.
LITERALLY! YOU GUYS WANNA SEE
MY SCAR AGAIN?
ALL:
NO, ADAM!
(BELL RINGS)
BUT IT'S SO COOL!
♪ Better, better ♪
♪ Better ♪
HI.
YOU DIDN'T DO IT.
I TRIED, BUT HER FAMILY
GAVE ME A SWEATER.
OKAY, KATIE JUST FINISHED
REHAB,
AND WE SAID WE'D WAIT UNTIL
SHE WAS IN A GOOD PLACE, DREW!
(SIGHS)
SO HOW UGLY
IS THE SWEATER?
(BOTH LAUGH)
KATIE:
AW, I KNEW
YOU DIDN'T LIKE IT.
IT'S OKAY,
YOU JUST HAVE TO WEAR IT
AT EVERY FAMILY DINNER
AT MY HOUSE.
(LAUGHS)
BIANCA:
WOW, KATIE.
IT SEEMS LIKE YOU'RE
IN A REALLY GOOD PLACE.
THANKS, BIANCA.
I AM.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
(HUSH FALLS OVER STUDENTS)
MR. SIMPSON:
I KNOW YOU'RE WONDERING
WHY I CALLED THIS ASSEMBLY.
I THOUGHT ABOUT INCLUDING
THE NEWS IN MY LETTER HOME,
BUT SOME INFORMATION IS MEANT
TO BE SAID IN PERSON.
(CONFUSED WHISPERS)
MR. SIMPSON:
AFTER MUCH DEBATE,
DEGRASSI IS OFFICIALLY
UNIFORM FREE!
(STUDENTS CHEER LOUDLY)
(JENNA LAUGHS EXCITEDLY)
(TORI SQUEALS)
(STUDENTS CHEER AND HOLLER)
THANK GOD!
THANK SIMPSON!
I HAVE A REALLY GOOD FEELING
ABOUT THIS TERM,
DON'T YOU?
(STUDENTS CHEER AND APPLAUD)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh... ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
JEANS!
WE GET TO WEAR JEANS!
I FEEL LIKE I CAN
BREATHE AGAIN!
MR. SIMPSON:
OKAY GUYS, NOW COME ON,
SETTLE DOWN.
COME ON, TAKE YOUR SEATS.
ALL RIGHT?
IT'S EXCITING, I KNOW.
BUT IN EQUALLY EXCITING NEWS,
I WANT TO GIVE A WARM WELCOME
TO SOME NEW DEGRASSI STUDENTS.
THEY'RE A MAJOR
JUNIOR HOCKEY TEAM,
THE TORONTO ICE-HOUNDS!
GUYS,
WHY DON'T YOU STAND UP?
COME ON, TAKE A BOW.
(STUDENTS CLAP AND CHEER)
JENNA:
NHL HOPEFULS GO HERE?
THE TORRES GOT
THEIR VERY OWN.
SO, ARE YOU SINGLE LADIES
GONNA GIVE THEM A WARM WELCOME
OR, SHOW THEM AROUND?
FINGER QUOTES ALLI,
REALLY?
MR. SIMPSON:
WELCOME BACK TO DEGRASSI,
YOU GUYS.
LET'S MAKE THIS TERM
THE BEST ONE YET!
STUDENTS:
YEAH! (CLAPPING)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
CLARE:
YOU'RE LATE.
HOW WAS NEW YORK?
I HATED IT!
THERE'S ALL THIS INDIE
THEATER,
AND ART, AND ARCHITECTURE,
AND CULTURE, OH!
SO YOU LOVED IT.
I'M ALREADY THINKING ABOUT MY
NYU PORTFOLIO FOR NEXT YEAR.
ELI, THAT'S AMAZING!
SO...
SO, WHAT ELSE?
I DON'T KNOW,
WHAT ELSE WITH YOU?
HI, I'M BECKY BAKER.
MY BROTHER'S AN ICE-HOUND,
AND WE'RE NEW FROM FLORIDA.
THE SUNSHINE STATE,
I MIGHT'VE GUESSED.
I'LL TAKE THAT
AS A COMPLIMENT!
ANY CHANCE YOU CAN
SHOW ME TO MY CLASS?
I GUESS
WE'LL CATCH UP LATER?
YEAH, SURE.
TORI:
WE'RE GOING SHOPPING!
TRISTAN:
I ALREADY AM.
THIS YEAR COULD NOT GET
ANY BETTER!
NO UNIFORMS,
TRIS AND I ARE GONNA LAND
LEADS IN THE PLAY,
AND ZIG'S HAIR
IS AT THAT PERFECT
IN BETWEEN HAIRCUT LENGTH.
AND YOU...
GOD TOR,
WAY TO SHINE A LIGHT.
IT'S FINE,
I'M GONNA BE IN A ROCK BAND!
TRISTAN AND TORI:
YAAAAAY!
AND I WAS WONDERING IF YOU
GUYS WOULD BE IN IT WITH ME?
TRISTAN AND TORI:
OHHH...
YEAH, I THINK MY INSTRUMENT
PLAYING QUOTA
IS MET WITH BAND CLASS.
YEAH, AND I'M WAY
OVER-SCHEDULED, SO.
GOOD THING I HAVE A PLAN B.
ORIGAMI?
I FOUND THIS
ON THE BULLETIN BOARD
BY THE GRADE TWELVE LOCKERS.
TWEET EDMO MASHKOUR.
CUTE NAME.
HE'S DATING MY SISTER'S
BEST FRIEND.
BESIDES, I DON'T NEED
A BOYFRIEND,
I NEED A BAND.
HI, DO YOU KNOW IF THE CAF
IS SERVING PANCAKES TODAY?
OH I WISH, BUT IT'S USUALLY
CEREAL, FRUIT,
BAGELS IF WE'RE LUCKY.
DALLAS:
TOO BAD, I WAS REALLY CRAVING
A NICE, FLAT PANCAKE.
(HOCKEY TEAM GUYS LAUGH)
IS MY FACE FLAT
OR SOMETHING?
I DON'T THINK THEY WERE
TALKING ABOUT YOUR FACE.
TRISTAN!
KATIE:
AND HOW DOES SIMPSON EXPECT ME
TO PUT ON A HOCKEY PEP RALLY
WHEN THERE'S NO MONEY LEFT
IN THE STUDENT COUNCIL
COFFERS?
YOU KNOW, SPEAKING OF UH,
PEP RALLIES...
MM-HMM?
SCRATCH THAT.
HOW DO I SAY THIS...
YOU'RE A GREAT GIRL, KATIE.
WAIT... ARE YOU BREAKING UP
WITH ME?
W-WHAT DID I DO?
NOTHING.
YOU DID NOTHING.
SO THERE'S SOMEONE ELSE?
YES.
BUT YOU DON'T KNOW HER.
COURT... NEY.
COURTNEY.
WE MET AT BLUE MOUNTAIN,
WHEN I WENT SKIING
WITH MY FAMILY.
SO WHILE I WAS IN REHAB,
THINKING OF BEING WITH YOU,
YOU WERE OFF IN A HOT TUB
WITH SOME SLUTTY SKI BUNNY?
I KNOW, I-I'M A PIG.
AND I DON'T DESERVE YOU.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU DON'T!
AND I AM SO GLAD I DIDN'T LOSE
MY VIRGINITY TO YOU AT PROM!
(BELL RINGS)
I JUST...
I HOPE YOU CAN FORGIVE ME
ONE DAY.
YEAH, DREAM ON, DREW.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
HEY!
I SAW YOUR AUDITION POSTER.
WAS IT TOO MUCH?
THE GREEN,
WITH THE CURSIVE?
I WENT FOR SOMETHING.
OH, EXCUSE ME.
NO! NO, NO, NO,
IT WAS GREAT.
SORRY, EXCUSE ME.
UM, I WAS ACTUALLY WONDERING
WHAT YOUR SOUND WAS LIKE?
WHITE STRIPES,
A BIT OF ARCADE FIRE.
I LOVE IT.
AWESOME, DO YOU KNOW SOMEONE
WHO WANTS TO AUDITION?
ME.
OH. REALLY?
UH, YOU'RE KATIE MATLIN'S
LITTLE SISTER, RIGHT?
UH-HUH.
IS THAT OKAY?
YEAH, NO,
IT'S FINE, SURE.
UH, IT'S JUST, I HAD
A DIFFERENT IMAGE IN MIND
FOR THE BAND.
WELL, WHAT KIND OF IMAGE?
UH... MORE MATURE.
♪ Ooh stronger together ♪
♪ Aaah... ♪
♪ I believe in you ♪
♪ Ooh stronger together ♪
♪ Aaah... ♪
♪ I believe it's true ♪
WOW!
THANKS.
OH, NO, REALLY!
WOW!
(LAUGHS)
OKAY, SHUT UP.
SORRY. (WITH A FRENCH ACCENT)
WELCOME TO CHEZ BURGER.
TODAY WE HAVE CHEESEBURGER
UH, SANDWICH,
FRENCH FRY, AND...
ICED TEA.
YOU'RE A DOOF.
WHO CAN'T WAIT TO EAT
A ROMANTIC COMBO MEAL
WITH HIS GIRL.
UM, WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
PREEMPTIVE DAMAGE CONTROL.
YOU DIDN'T TELL HIM?
I THOUGHT YOU DID.
WE'RE HAVING A PARTY TO
WELCOME DALLAS TO OUR HOME.
THANKS, BRO.
BIANCA AND I
ARE ON A DATE.
UH BIANCA,
HELP ME WITH THE COOLER?
WHEN MY MOM FINDS OUT,
SHE WILL KILL US SLOWLY
AND PAINFULLY!
WHO KNEW YOUR SISTER
WAS COOLER THAN YOU?
ADAM'S A GUY. MAKE FUN AGAIN,
I'LL MAKE YOUR LIFE HELL.
ALL RIGHT, RESPECT.
GOOD,
NOW CANCEL THE PARTY.
DALLAS:
THAT'S NOT REALLY POSSIBLE.
IT'S ON FACERANGE?
AND YOUR BRO TWEETED IT.
HE HAS SO MANY FOLLOWERS!
OH, AND UH...
JUST IN CASE YOU PLAN TO SWIPE
YOUR V CARD TONIGHT.
HOW'D YOU KNOW
I WAS A VIRGIN?
I DIDN'T,
BUT I DO NOW.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
OH, THAT MUST BE THE KEG.
DREW:
YOU GUYS GOT A KEG?!
EVERYONE IS GOING
TO THIS PARTY.
CLARE:
EVERYONE EVERYONE?
IS THIS TOP TOO CLINGY?
AND WHO ARE YOU TRYING
TO IMPRESS?
CAN'T A GIRL JUST WANT
TO BE CLING FREE?
(SCOFFS)
I KISSED ELI
BEFORE THE BREAK.
ALLI AND JENNA:
WHAT?!
WHY DIDN'T YOU SAY
ANYTHING?
I DIDN'T WANT TO GET
MY HOPES UP,
AND RIGHTLY SO, HE DIDN'T EVEN
MENTION IT TODAY.
AS IF IT NEVER HAPPENED.
OH, WELL, YOU CAN REMIND HIM
TONIGHT!
BUT WHAT IF HE WANTS
TO FORGET?
I KNOW ELI,
IF HE WAS INTERESTED,
HE WOULD'VE SAID SOMETHING
BY NOW.
OH, JAKE!
WE NEED YOUR PERSPECTIVE.
ALLI AND JENNA:
JAKE...
DO I HAVE TO?
YES.
OKAY, SO IF A GUY
DOESN'T BRING UP A PAST KISS,
DOES IT MEAN HE'S NOT
INTERESTED?
NO, IF HE'S INTERESTED,
HE'LL KISS HER AGAIN.
ALLI AND JENNA:
OOOH! (LAUGHING)
SHOULDN'T SAID PEOPLE
TALK FIRST?
JAKE:
NO, NO, NO, NO TALKING.
HE'LL COME TO YOU.
DOES SAID GUY FAVOUR
THE COLOUR BLACK?
OUT!
(JENNA SIGHS)
AT BLUE MOUNTAIN?
AT BLUE MOUNTAIN.
IN A HOT TUB?
I'M ASSUMING!
UGH! I'M THROWING UP
RIGHT NOW.
I KNOW, RIGHT?
WHAT A MISTAKE.
ARE YOU OKAY?
IT'S JUST THAT...
I HAVEN'T BEEN
THE BEST GIRLFRIEND.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
KATIE:
THAT THIS IS PARTIALLY
MY FAULT.
I MADE MISTAKES TOO,
AND...
DIDN'T YOU SAY HE'S HAVING
A PARTY TONIGHT?
ARE YOU REALLY THINKING
OF CRASHING?
HE'LL BE GLAD I DID,
MARE.
DREW AND I CAN GET
THROUGH THIS.
YEAH.
I KNOW IT.
MAYA:
MO'S BAND SOUNDS AMAZING,
IN FACT, IT'S THE EXACT BAND
I WOULD'VE PUT TOGETHER!
TRISTAN:
WELL, THEN YOU HAVE
TO AUDITION.
MAYA:
HE SAYS I'M NOT RIGHT
FOR THE BAND'S IMAGE.
THAT'S BECAUSE HE HASN'T HEARD
YOU PLAY YET.
AND HE HAS TO GET OVER
THE FACT THAT YOU ARE SO CUTE.
YOU MEAN FLAT.
TRISTAN:
MUSICALLY?
CHEST-ALLY.
ZIG:
SHOULD I BE HEARING THIS?
THAT'S NUTS MAYA,
YOU HAVE SUCH A NICE BODY.
RIGHT? I AM SO JEALOUS
OF YOUR BODY.
I ASKED MY PARENTS
FOR A BREAST REDUCTION.
DON'T WORRY,
THEY SAID NO.
(SIGHS)
THAT'S WHAT I NEED
TO LOOK LIKE FOR TOMORROW.
YOU WANNA AUDITION
IN YOUR BRA?
NO! YOU HEARD
THOSE HOCKEY GUYS,
EVEN MO THINKS I LOOK
LIKE A LITTLE GIRL.
I NEED TO DO SOMETHING DRASTIC
IF I'M GONNA MAKE THAT BAND.
YOU ARE NOT
GETTING IMPLANTS.
TRISTAN,
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
MAYA JUST NEEDS
A LITTLE... SUPPORT.
AND I HAVE GOT
JUST THE THING.
♪♪♪
GUYS: (CHANTING)
GO, GO, GO, GO, GO, GO, GO!
(CHEERING)
(LOUD DANCE MUSIC PLAYS)
DREW:
I'M SORRY OUR DATE'S RUINED.
BIANCA:
IT'S NOT, I'M WITH YOU.
'TIL THE WORLD EXPLODES?
POOF!
(BOTH LAUGH)
ADAM:
I JUST SAW KATIE
OUT AT THE DRIVEWAY.
ONE SEC.
MAN, THIS PARTY
WAS THE BEST IDEA EVER!
UH, YOU KNOW, I'M OKAY.
I-I WANNA BE SOBER
FOR MY FIRST TIME.
IF IT HAPPENS.
THAT'S NOT WHAT IT'S FOR.
ADAM SAW KATIE OUTSIDE
PARKING HER CAR.
WE THOUGHT YOU BROKE UP
WITH HER?
I DID!
SORT OF.
DO ME A FAVOUR AND UH,
AND DISTRACT BIANCA, OKAY?
(PARTYGOERS CHATTER LOUDLY)
ELI:
DO YOU KNOW THAT BAND?
THIS HERE IS ADAM'S HOUSE,
AND WE'VE BEEN FOLLOWING THEM
FOR A LONG TIME,
AND ACTUALLY WHEN I WAS
ON BREAK UH IN NEW YORK,
I ACTUALLY GOT TO SEE
THEM THERE,
AND THEY WERE MUCH
BETTER THERE
THAN THEY WERE IN TORONTO.
YEAH.
HEY, ARE YOU HAVING
A GOOD TIME?
OH YEAH, TOTALLY.
LOVE THE VIBE.
I CAN'T TELL
IF YOU'RE BEING FACETIOUS.
SORRY, WHAT?
CLARE: (LOUDLY)
I CAN'T TELL
IF YOU'RE BEING...
UH, NEVER MIND.
ALLI:
CLARE, I HAVE FUNNIEST STORY
TO TELL YOU,
DO COME HERE A MOMENT.
CAN YOU JUST TRY
AND HAVE FUN?
MINGLE, DANCE!
MM, NO.
JUST DON'T DO THAT, NO.
ADAM:
AND FROM THE UNIFORM'S ASHES,
ROSE STYLE,
AND FREEDOM OF EXPRESSION!
BECKY:
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE,
MISTER!
UGLY KHAKIS TO YOU
ARE PERFECTLY GOOD PANTS
TO A PERSON IN NEED!
I'LL DONATE THEM
ON YOUR BEHALF.
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
(SIGHS)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
GIVING YOU A SECOND CHANCE.
(SIGHS)
OH, UH...
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE HAPPY
TO SEE ME.
(SOBBING)
(SIGHS)
GO TO MY ROOM,
ALL RIGHT?
I'LL MEET YOU THERE IN FIVE,
AND WE CAN TALK, ALL RIGHT?
ME AND YOU.
OKAY.
DO YOU REALLY WANT TO GO
THROUGH THE PARTY CRYING?
NO, UH...
YOU'RE RIGHT,
I'LL USE THE FRONT DOOR.
OKAY.
♪♪♪
(GASPS FOR BREATH)
(SIGHS)
(PLAYS CELLO)
(HAPPY SIGH)
(SIGHS)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(BAGS RUSTLE)
♪♪♪
♪ Katy Perry's on a plane
she's on a plane ♪
BIANCA:
DO YOU WANT ME TO STAY
WITH YOU?
DREW:
UH NO, I MEAN,
YEAH, I WISH,
BUT UM, YOUR CURFEW.
I KNOW,
I ALMOST FORGOT.
WELL, I DON'T WANNA UPSET
AUNTIE AND MY PAROLE OFFICER.
SO, DON'T GET TOO CRAZY.
I WON'T.
OKAY.
♪ I wanna stay up all night ♪
♪ And find a girl ♪
♪ And tell her
she's the one ♪
ISN'T THERE A GIRL WAITING
IN YOUR BEDROOM?
YEAH, WAITING TO BE
BROKEN UP WITH... AGAIN.
DALLAS:
THERE IS AN ANCIENT MYTH.
IT TAKES THREE TIMES
TO BREAK IT WITH A GIRL
BEFORE IT STICKS.
YEAH WELL, THIS TIME,
IT BETTER.
OKAY, OKAY,
BEFORE YOU GO INTO BATTLE,
YOU GOTTA TAKE A DRINK
OUT OF THE UH...
HOCKEY PLAYERS:
TROPHY OF POWER!
NO, NO, NO, STOP,
THAT'S TOO BIG!
HOCKEY PLAYERS:
YOU GOTTA DRINK IT UP!
DRINK! DRINK! DRINK! DRINK!
COME ON, CHUG! CHUG! CHUG!
(DOOR CLATTERS)
(MUTED PARTY CHATTER)
LOOK UH,
IF YOU'RE DRUNK...
DREW:
NO, I JUST AHD A BEER
AND A TROPHY.
I LIED ABOUT COURTNEY,
SO THAT YOU'D BREAK UP
WITH ME.
I WASN'T HAPPY.
YEAH,
I'M-I'M NOT SURPRISED.
I WAS AWFUL TO YOU
BEFORE THE BREAK.
I MEAN, IF I WERE YOU,
I'D END THINGS
WITH ME TOO, SO.
YOU'RE BEING SO COOL
ABOUT THIS.
KATIE:
LOOK, YOU MADE THIS DECISION
TO BREAK UP ON YOUR OWN,
IN YOUR OWN HEAD.
WE NEVER DISCUSSED IT.
AND WE'VE BEEN THROUGH
WAY TOO MUCH
FOR YOU TO MAKE THIS BIG
DECISION ALONE.
(SIGHS)
LAST YEAR WAS PRETTY CRAZY,
HUH?
YEAH, CRAZY
IS AN UNDERSTATEMENT.
YOU KNOW...
I MIGHT BE DEAD RIGHT NOW
IF IT WASN'T FOR YOU.
YOU SAID IT YOURSELF,
WE NEED EACH OTHER.
JUST TALK TO ME, OKAY?
BECAUSE...
THERE IS NO PROBLEM
KATIE MATLIN CAN'T FIX.
♪♪♪
♪ It's about to bust right
boom ♪
♪ And we're gonna
be an us ♪
(MUFFLED DANCE MUSIC PLAYS)
(DOOR SLIDES SHUT)
(SIGHS)
I'M GONNA GO.
UH, O-OKAY.
(SIGHS)
WAIT, THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
I DON'T CARE WHAT
ANYONE ELSE THINKS.
WHY HAVEN'T YOU BROUGHT UP
THE KISS?
BECAUSE, CLARE...
I WROTE A PLAY
TO GET YOU BACK LAST YEAR.
I'VE COME A LONG WAY
FROM THAT,
AND CHASING YOU
AFTER ONE KISS
TAKES ME BACK
ABOUT FIVE STEPS.
THE BALL'S IN YOUR COURT.
UM...
WELL...
I'M HAPPY I KISSED YOU.
NO REGRETS.
ARE YOU... OKAY WITH IT?
UH...YES,
AND...NO.
WHAT'S THE NO PART?
ELI:
YOU KNEW I WAS LEAVING.
THERE WERE TWINKLY LIGHTS.
IT WAS EASY.
I WANNA KNOW IT WASN'T
JUST SOME FLEETING MOMENT,
BECAUSE THERE WON'T ALWAYS BE
TWINKLY LIGHTS.
AND IF WE'RE GONNA DO THIS,
YOU NEED TO BE ALL IN.
ELI, I AM ALL IN.
♪ Don't bring me down
to planet earth ♪
(LOUD DANCE MUSIC PLAYS)
♪ Be careful
what you wish for ♪
HEY, HOW'D IT GO
WITH KATIE?
I DID IT.
(GROANS)
(PARTYGOERS GASP)
OOH. OH MAN.
OKAY, UM...
(HOCKEY PLAYERS GRUNT
WITH EXERTION)
HEY.
I THINK HE'S OKAY.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S GET HIM UP.
HOCKEY PLAYER:
LET'S GO, BIG GUY.
WHOA, WHOA!
(GROANS)
I'M OKAY!
YOU DID IT, MAN!
I DID IT!
WHOO!
(PARTYGOERS CHEER)
DREW:
WHOO!
YEAH!