(BUZZ OF EXCITED CHATTER)
LUKE:
WOO! I LOVE GAME DAY!
YOU READY TO DESTROY
THESE GUYS?
(TEAMMATES YELL AGREEMENT)
FIFTEEN MINUTES
TO WARM-UP,
IF YOU NEED
THOSE SHARPENED, EH?
LUKE:
YEAH, IT'S NOT THE SKATES FAULT
HE'S GONE COLD.
MAYBE HE LOST
HIS LUCKY BOXERS, HUH?
THE ONLY UNDERWEAR
THAT BRINGS ME LUCK
IS SOME GIRL'S THONG
ON MY BEDROOM FLOOR.
LUKE: NICE!
OWEN: BOOM!
DALLAS:
SPECIAL DELIVERY FOR SAUNDERS!
LUKE:
AW! ROOKIE GOT A BALLOON!
HOW CUTE!
OWEN:
MAYBE HE IS GETTIN' SOME.
DALLAS:
SO? WHO IS IT?
WHO'S YOUR PUCK BUNNY?
CAM:
UH, IT'S JUST MY MOM
WISHING ME "GOOD LUCK."
WELL, YOU'RE GONNA NEED IT,
MAMA'S BOY.
NOPE. NOT TONIGHT.
TONIGHT, I'M IN THE ZONE.
DALLAS:
THAT'S WHAT I LIKE TO HEAR!
(TINNY MUSIC PLAYING
THROUGH HEADPHONES)
(CROWD CHEERS)
♪♪♪
CAM!
UNGH!
(CROWD GASPS)
(GOAL BUZZER BUZZES)
TEAM:
AW! COME ON!
(OPPOSING TEAM CHEERS)
(HOUNDS' FANS BOO)
DALLAS:
WHAT THE HELL WAS WITH
THAT LONE RANGER RUSH?
I THOUGHT I HAD A LANE.
LUKE:
HEY, YOU KEEP SKATING
LIKE THAT,
YOU'LL HAVE A LANE,
ALL RIGHT -
ALL THE WAY BACK
TO KAPUSKASING!
(CAM PANTS,
CROWD YELLS AND BOOS)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
(Ooh-ooh-ooh)
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
MAYA: GOTCHA!
CAM: AGH!
MAYA:
OH, SORRY!
CAM:
(GROANS) IT'S FINE.
I'M JUST SORE
FROM LAST NIGHT IS ALL.
WHAT'S THAT?
JUST A STUPID HOCKEY BLOG.
APPARENTLY IT'S MY FAULT
WE'RE LOSING.
MAYA:
I'M SURE THAT'S NOT TRUE.
CAM:
IF YOU COULDN'T DO THE THING
THAT YOU TRAINED YOUR WHOLE LIFE
TO BE GOOD AT,
WHAT WOULD YOU DO?
KEEP MY STICK ON THE ICE?
(LAUGHS)
FORGET I ASKED.
WE JUST DON'T KNOW MUCH
ABOUT HOCKEY.
TORI:
ALL I KNOW IS THAT
HOCKEY GUYS GIVE EACH OTHER
THE MOST RIDICULOUS NICKNAMES.
WHAT'S YOURS?
HMM... CAMELOT?
TORI:
CAMPER VAN? CAMPY?
CAMPS!
GUYS, PLEASE...
CAMEMBERT?
CHEESY! CHEESY!
NOT CHEESY!
TORI:
DEFINITELY CHEESY!
MAYA:
MADE YOU LAUGH,
CHEESY!
OH YEAH,
YOU GUYS ARE REAL FUNNY.
DARN RIGHT!
YOU NEED A BREAK;
MORE US, LESS HOCKEY.
TONIGHT, WE'RE GONNA GO
TO LITTLE MISS STEAKS.
UH...I HAVE PRACTICE.
MAYA:
CAN'T YOU SKIP IT
JUST THIS ONCE?
IT'S KARAOKE NIGHT.
I... I CAN'T SING.
JUST COME WATCH THEN.
YOU DON'T GET IT.
YOU NEED A DAMN GOOD REASON
TO MISS PRACTICE.
TORI:
AND WATCHING TRISTAN AND I
SING OUR DUET
ISN'T GOOD ENOUGH?
GUYS, I'M SORRY.
I JUST... I CAN'T.
(BELL RINGS)
(HALLWAY BUZZES WITH CHATTER)
HAPPY FIONA COYNE DAY!
BUT IT'S NOT
YOUR BIRTHDAY.
AND IT'S UNFAIR THAT PEOPLE
ONLY GET ONE DAY A YEAR
TO CELEBRATE THEMSELVES.
SO I DECIDED THAT TODAY
IS FIONA COYNE DAY,
AN EXTRA SPECIAL DAY,
EVERY YEAR,
JUST FOR ME.
WELL, AS FAR AS
I'M CONCERNED,
EVERY DAY IS
IMOGEN MORENO DAY.
THEN LET'S CELEBRATE BOTH!
OKAY.
MOVIES AT YOUR PLACE.
OR MAYBE, FOR A CHANGE,
YOURS?
UH, NOT TONIGHT.
I'M BEGINNING TO THINK
YOU DON'T WANT ME
TO MEET YOUR DAD!
PROFESSOR MORENO'S
IN THE MIDDLE
OF ONE OF HIS
ACADEMIC OUTBURSTS,
AND YOUR PLACE IS
SO NICE AND QUIET...
NOT SINCE A LARGE, MUSKY,
EATING MACHINE MOVED IN.
BUT DREW IS WORKING
TONIGHT,
SO AT LEAST WE HAVE THE WHOLE
MESSY PLACE TO OURSELVES.
(GASPS) WOW!
A DATE ON MY VERY FIRST
FIONA COYNE DAY.
(LAUGHS)
BIANCA:
QUITO.
ICELAND?
REYKJAVIK.
GIMME A CHALLENGE!
OKAY.
SOUTH SUDAN -
PROPOSED FUTURE CAPITAL?
(SIGHS) YOU GUYS SHOULD DO
YOUR HOMEWORK!
WE'RE GOING TO.
JUST IN TIME FOR ANOTHER
PRACTICE AFTER SCHOOL.
I CAN'T;
I HAVE DINNER
WITH MY DAD.
BIANCA:
I THOUGHT HE WAS BEHIND BARS.
KC:
YEAH, HE GOT EARLY PAROLE.
HE AND MY MOM HAVE BEEN
HANGING OUT.
CONNOR:
YOUR MOM CHANGED.
MAYBE YOUR DAD DID TOO.
KC:
YEAH, THAT'S...
THAT'S WHAT I KEEP
TELLING MYSELF.
BIANCA:
DON'T SWEAT IT.
YOU'LL BE OUTTA HERE
IN A YEAR ANYWAY, COLLEGE-BOY.
(CHUCKLES)
YEAH, BUT...
I CAN'T LEAVE MY MOM BEHIND
WITH SOME JUNKIE LOSER
SO WHAT'S THE ANSWER?
I DON'T KNOW.
NO, TO THE QUESTION -
PROPOSED FUTURE CAPITAL?
GO LOOK IT UP.
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
CAM:
HOLD IT HIGHER, MOM.
NO, NO, NO.
TILT IT.
MRS. SAUNDERS:
BETTER?
CAM:
(SIGHS) WELL,
NOW I CAN'T SEE YOU AT ALL.
RIGHT THERE! THERE! PERFECT!
HOLD IT THERE!
MRS. SAUNDERS:
OH YEAH, THERE I AM!
HELLO, SWEETHEART.
YOU LOOK TIRED.
(SIGHS)
THANKS, MOM.
MRS. SAUNDERS:
YOU'RE CALLING ME
OUT OF THE BLUE.
DON'T YOU HAVE
HOCKEY PRACTICE?
YEAH.
NOT FOR AN HOUR THOUGH.
WHAT'S WRONG?
ARE THE CLARKSONS
TREATING YOU OKAY?
CAM:
YES, THEY'RE FINE.
IT'S NOT LIKE BEING
WITH YOU GUYS THOUGH.
MRS. SAUNDERS:
OH, I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
I SENT MY FIFTEEN-YEAR-OLD
TO LIVE WITH A BILLET FAMILY.
I MUST BE CRAZY.
NO, IT'S FINE.
IT'S JUST... HOCKEY.
MRS. SAUNDERS:
OH HONEY...
I KNOW YOU HAD A ROUGH GAME
LAST NIGHT.
CAM:
(FRUSTRATED) AGAIN!
NO MATTER WHAT I DO!
MRS. SAUNDERS:
ARE YOU EATING WELL?
GETTING ENOUGH SLEEP?
CAM:
(SIGHS) I DON'T KNOW,
SAME AS ALWAYS.
EVERY MINUTE I'M NOT IN SCHOOL
OR ON THE ICE,
I'M LIFTING WEIGHTS, RUNNING,
DOING CORE WORK.
NOTHING'S WORKING.
MRS. SAUNDERS:
YOU'RE THE YOUNGEST KID
IN THE LEAGUE!
THERE'S BOUND TO BE
GROWING PAINS.
YEAH, I GUESS.
MRS. SAUNDERS:
LOOK...
YOU'RE STILL THE SAME
CAM SAUNDERS
WHO SET EVERY RECORD IN TOWN.
I CAN'T WALK TEN STEPS
DOWN MAIN STREET
WITHOUT SOMEONE STOPPING
TO ASK ABOUT YOU.
YEAH, WELL, MAYBE YOU SHOULD
ASK THEM WHAT I SHOULD DO.
OR MAYBE I'LL COME HOME
AND ASK THEM MYSELF.
MRS. SAUNDERS:
OH HONEY,
I KNOW YOU'RE HOMESICK.
BUT IF YOU REALLY THINK
ABOUT WHERE YOU WANNA BE,
IT'S NOT BACK AT HOME,
SEVEN HUNDRED MILES
FROM NOWHERE.
SEE?
KEEP YOUR HEAD UP...
AND STICK ON THE ICE.
I KNOW.
AND I DON'T LET ME HEAR
YOU'RE DROWNING YOUR SORROWS
IN ICE CREAM,
WHAT WITH YOUR DAIRY PROBLEM.
NO ICE CREAM.
PROMISE.
MRS. SAUNDERS:
NOW GO HAVE A GOOD PRACTICE.
(BLOWS KISS)
MUAH!
(COMPUTER BEEPS,
LID SLAPS SHUT)
(TRAFFIC RUMBLES)
(LOUD BUZZ
OF FOOD COURT CHATTER)
KEVIN:
PIZZA'S GETTING COLD.
OR IS PEPPERONI
AND GREEN OLIVE
NO LONGER YOUR FAVOURITE?
NO, IT IS.
YOU REMEMBERED THAT?
KC, I DON'T EXPECT YOU
TO FORGIVE ME.
I'M JUST HAPPY
TO SEE YOU.
HOPED MAYBE WE COULD
START OVER.
THERE'S GOOD IN ME,
SON.
I WANNA PROVE THAT
TO YOU AND YOUR MOM.
HOW?
WELL... I NEED TO START
BY ASKING YOU A FAVOUR.
I'VE BEEN BUSTING MY BUTT
TRYING TO FIND WORK,
AND I NEED A RESUME.
YOUR MOM SAYS YOU'RE PRETTY GOOD
WITH A COMPUTER.
OKAY.
I UH... GUESS I COULD.
MEANS A LOT, KID.
SO I GUESS
I'M A GRANDPA.
UH, TECHNICALLY.
KEVIN:
IT MUST HAVE BEEN TOUGH,
GIVING HIM UP.
LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE ALREADY
A STRONGER MAN
THAN I EVER WAS.
WELL, MAYBE SOMEDAY I'LL GET
MY SECOND CHANCE, TOO.
DALLAS:
YOU CALL THAT A JUMP SHOT?
LUKE:
DUDE, YOU MOVED THE BASKET!
DALLAS:
NO I DIDN'T!
LUKE:
YEAH, I FRIGGIN' SAW YOU.
DALLAS:
YOU KNOW WHAT? I'M GONNA GET
THE TEAM DOCTOR IN HERE,
BECAUSE YOU NEED
YOUR EYES CHECKED.
OWEN:
YO, GUYS, WHERE IS CAM?
LUKE:
PROBABLY BUYING A BS TICKET.
OR HE HIJACKED A RIDE
STRAIGHT FROM SCHOOL
SO HE DIDN'T HAVE
TO WAIT AROUND
AND RISK BEING RECOGNIZED.
LUKE:
MAN, IF I WAS HIM,
I WOULDA WORN A MASK ALL DAY.
(GLUGGING)
(BUZZ OF LOCKER ROOM CHATTER)
DALLAS:
YOU'RE LATE.
CAM:
I KNOW. SORRY.
OWEN:
DUDE, YOU LOOK GREEN.
TEAMMATE:
HEY, SAUNDERS...
HE DOESN'T LOOK SO GOOD.
CAM:
NO, I'M FINE.
I JUST... I'M READY TO GIVE
A HUNDRED AND TEN PER-
TEAMMATE:
OH MAN...
(VOMITING VIOLENTLY)
OWEN: THAR SHE BLOWS!
TEAMMATE: OH MAN.
LUKE:
WE HAVE AN ERUPTION!
OWEN:
AW, COME ON!
THAT'S NASTY!
(VOMITING)
HOW IS THERE SO MUCH BARF
IN SUCH A LITTLE DUDE?
OWEN:
OH, GEEZ, AND THE SMELL?
UGH! GOD! UGH!
(WEAKLY)
I THINK I GOT THE FLU.
DALLAS:
YEAH, WHY DON'T YOU GO HOME
AND GET SOME REST.
I'LL TELL COACH.
(SHAKY EXHALE)
ZIG: (SINGING KARAOKE)
♪ PLEASE TAKE ME HOME... ♪
♪ WON'T YOU PLEASE TAKE ME
HOME... ♪
TRISTAN:
CHEESY!
UH, ROOM FOR ONE MORE?
MAYA:
CAM!
ZIG:
♪ LET'S GO! T-A-K-E... ♪
I THOUGHT-
CAM:
UH, PRACTICE WAS CANCELLED!
EVERYBODY WAS LIKE,
"NIGHT OFF!
LET'S PLAY VIDEO GAMES!"
BUT I BUSTED OVER HERE INSTEAD
TO WATCH YOU GUYS.
ZIG:
♪ WON'T YOU PLEASE
TAKE ME HOME ♪
MAYA:
WELL... IF YOU'RE HERE,
YOU'RE GONNA SING.
NO, NO. IN CLASS,
YOU SAID THAT I COULD
JUST WATCH.
MAYA:
I'M PRETTY SURE
I DIDN'T SAY THAT.
DOESN'T SOUND
LIKE YOU.
TORI:
NOPE.
MAYA:
GREAT! WE'LL GO NEXT.
CAM:
NO. NO, NO, NO. MAYA, MAYA,
SERIOUSLY, I CAN'T-
ENOUGH "I CAN'TS!"
TONIGHT,
YOU CAN DO ANYTHING.
(CROWD CHEERS)
(CROWD APPLAUDS)
OKAY, LOOK, I'LL DO
YOUR HOMEWORK FOR A WEEK.
TWO WEEKS!
OKAY, LOOK, THREE WEEKS -
FINAL OFFER! PLEASE?
JUST LOOK AT ME.
BLOCK EVERYTHING ELSE OUT
AND JUST FOCUS ON ME.
(SINGING)
♪ I CAN'T EXPLAIN
ALL THE FEELINGS ♪
♪ THAT YOU'RE MAKING ME FEEL ♪
♪ MY HEART'S IN OVERDRIVE ♪
♪ AND YOU'RE BEHIND
THE STEERING WHEEL ♪
MAYA:
♪ TOUCHING YOU... ♪
♪ TOUCHING ME ♪
♪ TOUCHING YOU,
GOD, YOU'RE TOUCHING ME ♪
(TOTALLY INTO IT)
♪ I BELIEVE IN A THING
CALLED LOVE ♪
♪ JUST LISTEN TO THE RHYTHM
OF MY HEART ♪
♪ THERE'S A CHANCE
WE COULD MAKE IT NOW... ♪
♪ WE'LL BE ROCKING
'TIL THE SUN GOES DOWN ♪
CAM: (FALSETTO)
♪ I BELIEVE IN A THING
CALLED... ♪
MAYA AND CAM:
♪ LOVE ♪
CAM:
♪ WOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO! ♪
CAM: HUH!
TRISTAN: THAT'S AWESOME!
♪♪♪
IMOGEN:
"TRON," "COWBOYS & ALIENS,"
AND "THE CHANGE UP"?
AND I THOUGHT I HAD
WEIRD TASTE.
WHAT, THEY ALL HAVE
OLIVIA WILDE.
I FEEL LIKE
SOMETHING FUNNY.
FINE.
WE'LL SEE WHAT'S ON
ONE OF MY AMAZING TWENTY-SIX
LOW-DEF CHANNELS!
HOPEFULLY SOMETHING
MONKEY-RELATED.
YOU'RE MONKEY-RELATED.
(MOCK GASP)
YOU TAKE THAT BACK!
OR WHAT?
(SCREAMING AND LAUGHING)
NO, NO, NO!
STOP! STOP TICKLING ME!
SERIOUSLY, STOP.
WELL, GET YOUR TICKLISH PARTS
AWAY FROM MY FINGERS THEN!
IMOGEN:
I'M GONNA PEE MY PANTS! STOP!
(POPCORN BOWL THUMPS)
YOU MADE ME
DO THAT!
NO I DIDN'T!
(MUSIC PLAYS IN THE BACKGROUND)
(DOOR OPENS)
DREW:
BOW-CHICKA-WAH-WAH.
FIONA:
YOU'RE HOME EARLY.
DREW:
YEAH, THE MALL WAS BEYOND DEAD;
THEY DIDN'T NEED ME TO CLOSE.
AND YOU DIDN'T THINK THAT
YOU SHOULD CALL FIRST?
BEFORE I CAME HOME
TO MY APARTMENT?
YOU MEAN MY CONDO.
WHERE I PAY RENT.
YOU KNOW,
LIFE WAS SO MUCH BETTER
BEFORE YOU MOVED IN
WITH YOUR BOY MESS.
MY MESS?
FIONA:
YEAH! YOUR JUNK IS EVERYWHERE!
DISHES IN THE SINK,
PILES OF CLOTHES...
THIS PLACE WAS FILTHY
BEFORE I MOVED IN -
GRIME ON THE GROUND,
DUST BUNNIES EVERYWHERE.
LOOK. IT'S LIKE A POPCORN BOMB
WENT OFF!
YOU KNOW, MAYBE THIS
ROOMMATE EXPERIMENT
ISN'T REALLY GONNA WORK OUT.
WHATEVER.
ALL RIGHT, SINCE YOU NEED
TO KNOW MY SCHEDULE SO BAD,
I'LL BE UP IN MY ROOM
FOR THE NEXT EIGHT TO TEN HOURS.
WELL, YOU BETTER GET CLEANING!
IMOGEN:
HMM...
GUESS NO ONE TOLD HIM
IT WAS FIONA COYNE DAY.
KEVIN:
NEVER NEEDED A RESUME BEFORE.
WHERE DO WE START?
WELL, EXPERIENCE,
I GUESS.
YOU'RE LOOKING
FOR A KITCHEN JOB.
HAVE YOU EVER WORKED
IN A RESTAURANT?
KEVIN:
I WAS A PRISON COOK.
NOT SURE YOU WANNA
SHINE A LIGHT ON THAT.
KEVIN:
UH, WELL THEN, I SLUNG PIZZAS
FOR A FEW YEARS BEFORE THAT.
OKAY, THAT'S GOOD.
KEVIN:
DO YOU REMEMBER THAT PLACE -
THE ITALIAN PLACE
WITH THE TERMITE PROBLEM?
YEAH. DIDN'T THAT PLACE
GET SHUT DOWN
BECAUSE SOMEONE WAS SELLING
CRACK UNDER THE TABLE?
YOU MIGHT WANNA
LEAVE THAT OFF.
WHAT ELSE?
WELL, NORMALLY,
YOU MENTION
YOUR HIGHEST LEVEL
OF EDUCATION.
WELL,
I'M NO COLLEGE GRAD.
THAT'S NOT A PRE-REQ
FOR A KITCHEN JOB.
WHAT ABOUT HIGH SCHOOL?
WHAT YEAR DID YOU GRADUATE?
I NEVER GOT AROUND
TO THAT.
LISA:
YEAH, BUT YOU GOT YOUR GED
IN PRISON.
COOL.
PRETTY SOON WE'LL HAVE
THE SAME LEVEL OF EDUCATION.
AND THEN YOU'LL LEAVE ME
IN THE DUST
WHEN YOU GET TO UNIVERSITY.
WELL, I HAVEN'T BEEN
ACCEPTED YET.
JUST A MATTER OF TIME.
YOUR MOM TELLS ME
YOU'RE A KEENER.
LISA:
ONE OF THE BEST STUDENTS
IN HIS CLASS.
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE
I HAVE SUCH A SMART KID.
LISA:
YEAH, A KID WHO'S GONNA BE
THOUSANDS OF MILES AWAY
IN ANOTHER YEAR.
UBC'S MY DREAM SCHOOL.
KEVIN:
BRITISH COLUMBIA, HUH?
YOU'RE NOT THINKING OF ANYWHERE
A LITTLE CLOSER?
THEY HAVE A GREAT
BIOLOGY PROGRAM THERE,
AND MY GUIDANCE COUNSELOR
THINKS I HAVE A SHOT
AT A SCHOLARSHIP.
OH...
JUST WHEN THE FAMILY'S
GETTING BACK TOGETHER,
WE'LL HAVE TO SAY GOODBYE.
BUT WHAT A REASON, EH?
I'M PROUD OF YOU, SON.
THANKS, DAD.
AND DON'T WORRY,
I'LL BE AROUND
TO MAKE SURE YOUR MOM
STAYS OUT OF TROUBLE.
(LAUGHS) YEAH, I CAN TAKE CARE
OF MYSELF.
LET'S PUT THOSE SMARTS
TO THIS HERE RESUME.
(BELL RINGS)
ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION PROGRAMMERS!
TONIGHT'S COMPUTER CLUB
MEETING IS CANCELLED.
MAYA: HEY!
CAM: (GASPS)
CAN YOU STOP DOING THAT?!
CAN I HELP YOU?
WELL, I THINK,
LAST NIGHT,
WE DISCOVERED YOU HAVE
A HIDDEN TALENT.
TRISTAN GAVE ME THIS.
THE MUSICAL NEEDS
MORE CHORUS MEMBERS.
NOT ON YOUR LIFE.
COME ON! DID YOU NOT HEAR
YOURSELF LAST NIGHT?
THE WAY YOU HIT
THOSE FALSETTO NOTES,
IT WAS AMAZING!
YEAH, THAT'S BECAUSE
THERE WAS NO PRESSURE.
IT DIDN'T MATTER IF I WON
OR IF I LOST.
YOU DON'T REALLY WIN
AT KARAOKE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
LOOK, I HAD A LOT OF FUN
LAST NIGHT,
BUT WE'RE DIFFERENT.
MUSIC'S YOUR THING,
SPORTS IS MINE.
(SIGHS) WELL,
EVERYBODY'S DIFFERENT
FROM EVERYBODY,
AND THAT'S WHAT
I LIKE ABOUT US.
YEAH, ME TOO.
LUKE:
HEY, IT'S THE REGURGITATOR...
WITH HIS LITTLE GIRLFRIEND!
OUR BUDDY LOOKS
PRETTY GOOD TODAY, HUH?
I MEAN, FOR SOMEONE WHO WAS
ON HIS DEATHBED WITH THE FLU.
CAM:
UH, YEAH, MUST HAVE BEEN
A TWELVE-HOUR THING.
DALLAS:
ACTUALLY, MORE LIKE
A TWELVE MINUTE THING.
SOMEONE SENT THIS IN
TO THE GOHOUNDSBLOG.
GUESS THERE WAS SOME SORT
OF KARAOKE JAM LAST NIGHT?
SUCKS WE HAD
TO MISS IT THOUGH;
WE HAD PRACTICE.
COACH BAG-SKATED US
FOR AN HOUR.
HE SAYS WE'VE BEEN LAZY,
'CEPT NONE OF US FAKED SICK
TO GET OUT OF IT.
DALLAS:
NOW IT'S YOUR TURN.
LUKE:
HOPE YOU LIKE PAIN, ROOKIE.
RIGHT THIS WAY,
PLEASE.
BIANCA:
HEY! HOW WAS DIN-DIN
WITH DADDY DEAREST?
(LAUGHS)
SURPRISINGLY GOOD.
HE WANTS TO GET A JOB.
SO HE SAYS.
SO YOU'RE ACTUALLY
GONNA FORGIVE HIM,
AFTER ALL HE DID?
IF HE MAKES
MY MOM HAPPY,
I HAVE TO GIVE HIM
A CHANCE.
MR. TOWNSEND:
ALL RIGHT, BRIGHT SPARKS.
DOWN TO BRASS TACKS.
NATIONALS ARE AFOOT,
SO LET'S JUST DIVE RIGHT IN,
SHALL WE?
GREAT URBAN RIVERS.
I NAME THE CITY,
YOU NAME THE RIVER.
MR. TOWNSEND: ROME:
BIANCA: (DINGS BELL) TIBER.
MR. TOWNSEND:
GOOD. BANGKOK.
(CELL CHIRPS)
(DINGS IN)
CHAO PHRAYA.
MR. TOWNSEND:
VERY NICE. VANCOUVER.
LONGEST RIVER
IN BRITISH COLUMBIA.
KC, YOU SHOULD KNOW THIS.
(DINGS IN)
FRASER.
MR. TOWNSEND:
BOGATA.
(WHISPERING) A 911 CALL?
FROM WHO?
MY MOM.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
YEAH. I'M SURE
IT'S FINE.
MR. TOWNSEND:
ST. PETERSBERG.
FIONA:
I'M POSTING ANOTHER ROOMMATE AD
ONLINE.
IF I LIVED WITH A GIRL,
DO YOU THINK YOU'D BE JEALOUS?
IMOGEN:
DREW'S NOT THAT BAD.
I CAN'T LIVE
LIKE THIS ANYMORE.
THIS IS WORSE
THAN A PIGSTY,
AND TRUST ME,
I OWNED A PIG!
IMOGEN:
WHOA...
FIONA:
WHAT DID YOU DO?
DREW:
SEE, I FELT BAD ABOUT OUR FIGHT
THE OTHER DAY,
SO I TACKLED THE WHOLE MESS
BY MYSELF.
WIPED EVERYTHING DOWN,
MOPPED THE FLOOR,
THE WHOLE DEAL.
YOU LIKE?
BUT IT'S ONLY HALF-CLEAN.
DREW:
YES. MY HALF.
BUT I FOLDED YOUR CLOTHES
THAT WERE ON MY HALF,
AND I VACUUMED UP THE POPCORN
THAT SPILLED ONTO MY HALF.
WELL, ROOMIE,
I GOTTA GO TO WORK.
SO CLEAN YOUR SIDE
WHEN YOU CAN -
NO PRESSURE.
OH, AND UH,
HERE'S YOUR RENT.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
(SKATES RASP ON ICE)
(SHARP STOP)
DALLAS:
STOP!
(PANTING)
LUKE:
DID WE SAY
"DRAG YOUR ASS"?
LET'S MOVE IT,
ICE CUBE!
(PANTING)
(SHARP STOP)
GO!
ALL RIGHT,
THAT'S ENOUGH.
ALL THE WAY
TO THE OTHER SIDE
AND TAKE FIVE.
GET OUTTA HERE.
(PANTING HARD,
STICK CLATTERS ON ICE)
(GASPING FOR BREATH)
MOM! I GOT YOUR TEXT.
I'M GLAD YOU'RE HOME.
WHAT'S WRONG?
IS IT DAD?
LISA:
YEAH, IT'S DAD.
WHAT HAPPENED?
SOMETHING BAD?
SOMETHING GOOD.
ACTUALLY, SOMETHING GREAT.
KEVIN:
I GOT A JOB!
A JOB? WHERE?
A FAMILY RESTAURANT -
ONE OF THOSE BIG CHAINS.
SO YOU'RE WAITING TABLES?
WASHING DISHES,
BUT IT'S A START.
ALL THANKS TO YOU,
BUD;
THAT RESUME REALLY DID
THE TRICK.
IT WAS NO BIG DEAL.
IT WAS A HUGE DEAL,
AFTER EVERYTHING I'VE DONE
TO THIS FAMILY.
LISA:
THAT'S ALL IN THE PAST.
EVERYBODY DESERVES
A SECOND CHANCE.
SHE'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE A GOOD KID,
KC.
KC:
YOU FREAKED ME OUT!
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
AND RUIN THE SURPRISE?
KEVIN:
TIME FOR A TOAST.
THAT'S ALCOHOLIC?
KEVIN:
I KNOW YOU'RE UNDERAGE.
DON'T WORRY, I WON'T SNITCH.
YOU'RE DRINKING AGAIN?
KEVIN:
LOOSEN UP, BUD!
A FEW GLASSES
AREN'T GONNA HURT ANYONE!
A FEW?
KEVIN:
WELL, WE HAD A HEAD START.
LISA:
IT'S OKAY, KC.
NO, IT'S NOT!
YOU PROMISED NO DRUGS,
NO ALCOHOL.
I KNOW, I KNOW,
BUT-
KC:
THIS IS ALL BECAUSE OF HIM.
(LAUGHS)
MY RESPONSIBLE SON!
LIFE'S TOO SHORT
TO SWEAT THE SMALL STUFF.
IT'S TIME TO CELEBRATE.
ALL RIGHT? SIT.
(PADS THUNK
AS CAM SLAPS THEM DOWN)
NOT VERY FUN,
WAS IT?
JUST REMEMBER THIS
NEXT TIME
YOU THINK ABOUT BAILING
ON THE TEAM.
LIKE IT OR NOT,
WE'RE ALL YOU HAVE.
HERE. HYDRATE.
(PAD THUNKS HARD
AGAINST THE WALL)
(SLIGHTLY PANICKED BREATHS)
(CRYING)