MARISOL:
SO, WHO'S READY TO THROW
AN AMAZING PEP RALLY
FOR THE TORONTO ICE-HOUNDS?
YEAH!
(CLAPPING)
GOOD, IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT
TO THE SCHOOL
THAT THE HOCKEY TEAM
FEELS WELCOMED.
SO THIS EVENT
NEEDS TO BE PERFECT.
HEY, SORRY I'M LATE.
UM...ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE UP FOR THIS?
OF COURSE!
I'M STILL SCHOOL PRESIDENT,
RIGHT?
I THINK IT'S TIME
I TAKE BACK THE REINS.
OKAY, WORRY-FACE?
YES, WORRY-FACE.
CAN WE JUST FOCUS
ON THE PEP RALLY?
MARISOL: YEAH.
KATIE: THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT EVERYONE,
RAMP ME UP.
UH, PRINCIPAL SIMPSON APPROVED
EARLY DISMISSAL FOR STUDENTS.
POWER SQUAD IS SET TO GO.
OKAY UM,
WHAT KIND OF AV EQUIPMENT
CAN WE RUN IN THE GYM?
WHATEVER YOU WANT, REALLY.
WHY?
WELL, WE SHOULD CREATE A HOCKEY
TEAM SIZZLE REEL, RIGHT?
UM, I'LL NEED FOOTAGE
OF THE THEM,
AND A LIST OF THE BILLETS.
MO:
EASY. THE TEAM CAPTAIN
IS LIVING AT THE TORRES HOUSE,
SO JUST SNUGGLE UP TO DREW,
KATIE.
(LAUGHS)
YOU KNOW WHAT?
UH, NO FAMILIES, JUST...
JUST STUDENTS.
WHAT DID I DO?
UM, THE BREAK UP!
OH. SORRY, KATIE.
I TOTALLY FORGOT.
NO, IT'S OKAY,
IT'S OKAY.
(TAKES A DEEP BREATH)
(SHARPLY INDRAWN BREATH)
(SOBBING)
OKAY, MEETING ADJOURNED.
I SAID, GET OUT!
(SOBS HYSTERICALLY)
I CAN'T-
I CAN'T STOP!
(SOBS)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
(Swords clank)
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
OH, I FEEL LIKE SUCH A LOSER,
CRYING LIKE THIS!
FORGET ABOUT DREW.
YOU DESERVE SO MUCH BETTER.
WE DID IT.
HAD SEX AT THE PARTY.
OH MY GOD,
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
DREW TOLD ME
NOT TO TELL ANYONE!
UGH, I HATE HIM
SO HARD RIGHT NOW,
I CAN'T EVEN...
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT'S IT!
WHOA,
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
TO FIND DREW, AND INTRODUCE
HIS MAN PARTS TO MY BOOT!
KATIE:
NO MARE, PLEASE?
NO MORE CONFRONTATIONS,
OKAY?
OKAY, WHAT CAN I DO?
KATIE:
MY PARENTS ARE TAKING MAYA
TO THIS CELLO THING TONIGHT,
SO... SLEEPOVER?
YOU BRING THE ICE CREAM,
I'LL BRING THE PIZZA?
THANKS!
YOU'RE THE BEST.
(BELL RINGS)
PARLEZ-VOUS LE FRANCAIS?
(IMITATING A FRENCH ACCENT)
DO YOU-A SPEAK-A FRENCH?
MUST YOU TRANSLATE
THAT WAY?
TRISTAN:
IS A FRENCH ASSIGNMENT, NO?
YOU SPEAK-A DA FRENCH,
AND I TRANSLATE
IN ZEE FRENCH ACCENT.
MADAME JEAN-AUX:
CAMPBELL, YOU NEED A GROUP.
ANY VOLUNTEERS?
(STUDENTS WHISPER)
MAYA: OUCH!
MADAME JEAN-AUX: MERCI.
THERE YOU GO, CAMPBELL.
(WHISPERS)
LOOK AT HIM.
HI, I'M MAYA.
TRIS-TRISTAN.
OH I'M GOOD,
THANKS 1OR ASKING.
YOU'RE ON THE HOCKEY TEAM,
RIGHT?
YEAH, I MISSED MY FRENCH CREDIT
LAST YEAR 'CAUSE OF TRAINING.
MAYA:
WELL, BUCKLE UP, 'CAUSE THIS
CLASS IS A WILD RIDE.
(LAUGHS AWKWARDLY)
YEAH. IT'S CRAAAAZY!
I'M GONNA GRAB
MY TEXTBOOK.
(LAUGHS) DUDE.
I KNOW, HE GOT CLOSER,
AND I LOST ALL ABILITY
TO SPEAK COHERENTLY.
(SIGHS)
WHY CAN'T I TALK TO HIM?
STUDENT (ON PA):
THE ACADEMIC QUIZ TEAM
IS LOOKING TO FILL
SOME OPEN STOPS.
IF INTERESTED PLEASE SEE CONNOR
DESLAURIER, OR KC GUTHRIE.
(KNOCKING)
MR. SIMPSON:
ELI, COME ON IN.
MR. SIMPSON: GOOD HOLIDAY?
ELI: UM, IT WAS GOOD!
MY FAMILY AND I WENT
TO NEW YORK.
TOURED NYU.
TISCH SCHOOL OF THE ARTS?
THAT WOULD BE SO GREAT FOR YOU.
YEAH, THAT'S ACTUALLY
WHY I'M HERE.
I NEED A PROJECT
TO SUPPLEMENT MY APPLICATION,
AND I WANTED TO PRODUCE
ANOTHER SCHOOL PLAY.
I ALREADY APPROVED
ANOTHER PLAY PROPOSAL.
YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
WAIT, WAIT,
I HAVE AN IDEA.
YOU COULD WORK TOGETHER.
THIS PLAY IS GONNA BE HUGE,
AND I WOULD BE MORE CONFIDENT
IF I HAD TWO STUDENTS
RUNNING THE SHOW.
HEY, SHE MIGHT EVEN
LET YOU DIRECT.
SHE?
UH, REBECCA BAKER.
LITTLE MISS SUNSHINE.
(BIKE HUMS)
NICE SOCKS.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
I'M WORKING OUT,
YOU DON'T OWN
THE WEIGHT ROOM.
ONE OF YOUR TEAMMATES
IS IN MY FRENCH CLASS.
CAMPBELL SAUNDERS?
HE'S FAR AWAY FROM HOME,
HUH?
CAMPBELL'S AN ALL-STAR.
HE SAW MORE ICE TIME LAST WEEK
THAN I'LL SEE ALL SEASON.
INTERESTING.
HE'S NOT GAY.
IT'S NOT ABOUT THAT, JEEZ!
I THOUGHT I'D MAKE
A NEW FRIEND.
OWEN:
HE'S A HOCKEY PLAYER.
HE WOULDN'T BE INTERESTED
IN YOU EITHER WAY.
OH, GO SUCK AN EGG!
TRIS,
I'M PROTECTING YOU!
♪♪♪
"THE WAY WILL BECOME CLEAR."
MARISOL:
HELLO?
KATIE:
OH HEY, MARE.
AND MO... AND JAKE.
WHAT-WHAT-WHAT?
SETTLERS OF CATAN!
HEY, WHERE DO YOU WANT THE 'ZA?
KATIE:
OH! UH, YOU CAN PUT IT
ON THE TABLE, I GUESS.
UH-HUH.
I SAID A SLEEP-OVER!
GIRLS ONLY?
YES, LATER!
BUT FIRST, BOYS!
MARE, DOES JAKE EVEN KNOW
THAT YOU ONLY INVITED HIM HERE
TO BE REBOUND BOY?
OH, LIKE HE CARES,
THIS IS WHAT HE DOES.
LOOK, SOON OLD WHAT'S-HIS-FACE
WILL BE A DISTANT MEMORY.
IT IS WORTH A SHOT.
♪♪♪
♪ Pretty little thing ♪
♪ You're pulling
all the strings ♪
♪ We're breaking
all the rules tonight ♪
MAN:
OH, THAT LOOKS REALLY PERFECT.
ELI! OVER HERE!
HI.
THOUGHT I WAS EARLY.
I'M ALWAYS EARLY.
I BELIEVE IT.
SO YOU SURE DIDN'T WASTE
ANY TIME
APPROACHING SIMPSON
ABOUT A SPRING PLAY.
I'M A GO-GETTER!
OKAY LOOK, SO YOU'VE PRODUCED
A PLAY BEFORE, RIGHT?
AT MY OLD SCHOOL,
I RAN THE ENTIRE DRAMA CLUB.
PLAYS ARE MY THING.
WELL, AT DEGRASSI,
I WANT IN.
YAY!
THANK THE LORD!
I WAS SO NERVOUS THAT NO ONE
WOULD WANT TO WORK
UNDER THE NEW GIRL.
W-WELL MAYBE WE COULD SEE IT
MORE AS A PARTNERSHIP.
ABSOLUTELY.
YOU CAN HELP ME HANG THESE
TOMORROW.
NO NEED, NO, I'VE ALREADY
GOT AN ESTABLISHED TEAM.
LET'S MEET TOMORROW,
I'LL TEXT EVERYONE.
WELL, I AM THE PRODUCER.
WHAT CAN I DO?
UH... REFRESHMENTS.
REFRESHMENTS.
OKAY, I JUST WANT
TO BE INVOLVED.
YEAH, NO WORRIES.
I'VE GOT IT ALL UNDER CONTROL,
PARTNER.
(BOTH LAUGH AWKWARDLY)
WHO'S GOT LUMBER?
I NEED LUMBER.
JAKE:
LUMBER'S NO GOOD
IF KATIE'S GOT ALL THE BRICKS.
ESPECIALLY BECAUSE
I'M GOING TO WIN!
(KATIE LAUGHS, OTHERS GROAN)
COME ON!
WELL PLAYED.
WELL, I WAS TWO MOVES
FROM TAKING IT,
BUT, WHATEVER.
YEAH, YOU COULDN'T JUST
LEAVE IT AT A COMPLIMENT,
COULD YOU?
(LAUGHS)
COME ON, MO.
THERE IS A MAKE-OUT SESH
WITH YOUR NAME ON IT!
HEY.
HELLO.
(KATIE SOBS)
OH, UH, THAT'S...
THAT'S NOT GOOD. UM-
I'M SORRY,
THIS JUST KEEPS HAPPENING.
I GUESS THIS ISN'T
GOING TO HELP ME
GET OVER DREW AFTER ALL.
I FEEL USED.
I FEEL LIKE I'M NEVER
GONNA GET PAST THIS.
UH, YOU JUST-
I GUESS YOU JUST NEED
TO GET YOUR FRUSTRATION OUT.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I REALLY NEED
TO DO SOMETHING.
ANY BRILLIANT IDEAS?
YEAH.
YOU UP FOR A FIELD TRIP?
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY,
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
YEAH, JUST TOSS A FEW EGGS
AT DREW'S BEDROOM WINDOW,
GET OUT YOUR ANGER
AND BADA-BOOM,
YOU'RE OVER THE RELATIONSHIP,
TRUST ME.
OKAY, YOU SHOULD WRITE
A BREAK-UP SELF-HELP BOOK.
YEAH, DON'T THINK I HAVEN'T
THOUGHT ABOUT THAT.
COME ON.
OKAY, DREW'S BEDROOM
WINDOW IS...
WAIT,
THAT'S BIANCA'S CAR.
(SIGHS)
THIS IS ALL HER FAULT.
SHE SWOOPED IN THE MINUTE
I WAS OUT OF TOWN.
GIVE THOSE TO ME.
OKAY, THAT HAPPENED.
(EGGS SPLAT)
JAKE:
OKAY, LET IT OUT.
(EGGS SPLAT)
(CHUCKLES)
KATIE, KATIE!
BAD IDEA! BAD IDEA!
COME ON!
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
KATIE, BAD IDEA!
YOU WANNA BUST UP
YOUR KNEE AGAIN, LET'S GO!
AWESOME!
(LAUGHS)
ANY REGRETS
ABOUT LAST NIGHT?
NO, WHEN I LEFT REHAB,
MY THERAPIST TOLD ME
TO START A FRESH, NEW PATH.
SHE SAID,
"THE WAY WILL BECOME CLEAR,"
AND LAST NIGHT,
IT TOTALLY DID.
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL NEW DAY.
UH, FOR YOU, MAYBE.
(GASPS)
KATIE:
AW, LOOKS LIKE SOMEONE DID
A REAL NUMBER ON YOUR CAR, B.
TOO BAD!
BIANCA:
YEAH, SOMEBODY WASTED AN ENTIRE
CARTON OF PERFECTLY GOOD EGGS.
DID YOU KNOW THERE ARE STARVING
CHILDREN IN AFRICA,
YOU DUMB BITCH?
MAYBE YOU'LL THINK TWICE
NEXT TIME BEFORE HOOKING UP
WITH SOME OTHER GIRL'S
BOYFRIEND!
WE WAITED UNTIL AFTER
HE BROKE UP WITH YOU!
YEAH, WHATEVER.
ENJOY YOUR JERK!
SOMEONE'S GONNA PAY
FOR MY CAR!
OH YEAH?
BIANCA:
LET ME GO!
DREW:
BIANCA, SHE'S LIKE
A BLACK BELT.
JUST LET HIM DEAL.
(SIGHS ANGRILY)
CAN YOU LEAVE HER
OUT OF THIS?
HATE ME IF YOU HAVE TO!
OH I DO, AND I STILL HAVE
A LOT OF AMMUNITION
WHEN IT COMES TO YOU!
YOU PROMISED THAT
YOU WOULD KEEP THAT A SECRET.
CAN'T YOU JUST FORGET
IT EVER HAPPENED?
FORGET I LOST MY VIRGINITY
TO A GUY I LOVED?
WHY AM I THE ONLY ONE
IN PAIN, DREW?
WHY DO YOU
GET TO BE HAPPY?
I MEAN, OUR WHOLE RELATIONSHIP
WAS COMPLETELY POINTLESS!
IT WASN'T...
POINTLESS, KATIE.
IT'S JUST OVER.
(SOBS QUIETLY)
OH, THERE HE IS,
MR. SHY AND RESERVED.
I MADE A TERRIBLE
FIRST IMPRESSION!
MAYA:
IT'S NOT THAT BAD,
DIDN'T CAMPBELL FRIEND YOU
ON FACERANGE LAST NIGHT?
NO.
HE FRIENDED YOU,
AND NOT ME?
UGH! THIS IS WORSE
THAN I THOUGHT!
I'M NOT EVEN A BLIP
ON HIS RADAR.
BUCK UP.
MAYBE YOU WILL GET
A SECOND CHANCE.
(SIGHS)
(QUIETLY) MAYA...
YOU FORGOT TO LOG OUT
OF YOUR FACERANGE...
(KEYS CLICK)
(SIGHS HAPPILY)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
(GASPS)
MY SANDWICH?
I'M TAKING YOU
OUT TO LUNCH.
WE'RE GOING TO CELEBRATE
THE AMAZING PLAY
THAT'S GONNA GET ME
INTO NYU.
WITH THE HELP
OF BECKY BAKER?
(GROANS)
COME ON, SHE'S THE ONE
THAT GOT SIMPSON ON BOARD!
ONLY BECAUSE SHE EAGER-BEAVERED
HER WAY IN.
I KNOW THE TEAM,
THE THEATER'S RESOURCES,
IT ONLY MAKES SENSE
THAT I'M THE TOP DOG.
UH, IS THAT WHAT YOU SAID
TO HER?
I'M TOP DOG?
'CAUSE... NO.
SHE GOT THE POINT.
SHE'S NEW HERE.
MAYBE SHE HAS SOMETHING
TO OFFER.
SHE JUST WANTS TO HELP!
(HIGH PITCHED GIGGLE)
WELL, SHE SAID SO HERSELF!
FINE, I'LL BE NICE.
OKAY, WHAT'S THE PLAY?
"A DEATH OF A SALESMAN."
A MODERN RETELLING
FOR THE INTERNET AGE.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
OOH, TRISTAN!
LOOK AT CAMPBELL.
SHUT UP!
HE'S COMING OVER!
OH GOD, SHUT UP!
CAMPBELL:
HEY MAYA, UM...
I CAN LEND YOU MY SEASON ONE
DVDS OF LOST,
IF YOU WANT.
HUH?
UH, MAYA!
YOU KNOW THAT SHOW YOU'VE BEEN
WANTING TO CHECK OUT.
CAMPBELL:
YEAH, YOU SAID THAT
IN OUR FACERANGE CHAT.
AGAIN, HUH?
TRISTAN:
MAYA, YOU HAVE
THE WORST MEMORY!
(NERVOUS LAUGH)
RIGHT, BRAIN FART,
SORRY.
MAYBE WE CAN CHAT LATER TONIGHT
AFTER MY HOCKEY PRACTICE?
(WHISPERS)
YES, YES, YES!
SURE, YEAH.
(CAMPBELL LAUGHS)
I USED YOUR FACERANGE PROFILE
TO CHAT WITH CAMPBELL.
YOU IMPERSONATED ME
ONLINE?!
IT WAS MAGICAL,
WE HAVE SO MUCH IN COMMON!
I COULD REALLY BE MYSELF.
YOU KNOW WHAT,
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
YOU JUST GO OVER THERE,
AND TALK TO HIM.
ARE YOU UN-SANE?!
YOU CAN DO THIS.
VAMOOSE!
GUY:
CAMPBELL, CATCH!
HI, ROOM FOR ONE MORE?
DALLAS:
FRIEND OF YOURS, CAM?
I THINK
YOU HAVE THE WRONG TABLE.
(HOCKEY PLAYERS SNICKER)
(LAUGHING)
(SIGHS)
HEY, KATIE.
UH, I HEARD YOU WANTED
SOME HOCKEY FOOTAGE
FOR THE PEP RALLY.
OH YEAH,
I ALMOST FORGOT.
SOME OF THE YOUNGER PLAYERS
ARE REALLY FAR AWAY FROM HOME,
AND THE HOCKEY TEAM
IS THE ONLY FAMILY THEY HAVE.
IT'S COOL TO KNOW THE SCHOOL
PRESIDENT CARES ENOUGH
TO THROW THEM A PEP RALLY.
(KEYS CLICK)
HOCKEY PLAYER: (ON TAPE)
LET'S GO, JARED!
COME ON, PICK IT UP NOW!
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
KEEP PUSHING ALL THE WAY
THROUGH!
(HOCKEY PLAYERS HOLLER)
(AUDIO FAST FORWARDS
AND REVERSES)
OWEN:
SO WHAT'D YOU...
SO WHAT'D YOU DO, BUDDY?
DREW:
I HAD SEX, WHOO!
OH, I'M A MAN!
OH, I'M A MAN,
I'M A REAL MAN, AND YOU-
(FAST FORWARDING SOUNDS)
OWEN:
YOU ARE OUT OF YOUR MIND,
BUDDY.
WHOO!
JUST ONE BIG JOKE.
STUDENT: (ON PA)
TO THE OWNER
OF A PAIR OF JEANS
FOUND IN THE GIRLS' CHANGE ROOM
THIS MORNING,
THEY'RE DOWN IN THE LOST
AND FOUND.
HEY.
YOU OKAY?
I SPENT THE REST OF LUNCH
UGLY CRYING IN THE BATHROOM.
BUT NOW I KNOW
CAMPBELL SAUNDERS
IS LIKE EVERY OTHER
HOCKEY JERK ON THE PLANET.
OVER IT, MOVING ON.
NEXT STOP BROADWAY,
RIGHT?
OR AT LEAST
THE DEGRASSI STAGE.
(CAMPBELL CLEARS HIS THROAT)
CAMPBELL:
HEY.
LOOK, SORRY ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED AT LUNCH.
I HAD TO PLAY ALONG.
WHATEVER.
I'M HOMESICK LIKE CRAZY,
HOCKEY'S MY WHOLE LIFE,
AND THE TEAM,
THEY'RE MY FAMILY.
UM...
I JUST HOPE YOU GUYS
DON'T THINK I'M A JERK.
I NEED YOUR FACERANGE
PASSWORD.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO "OVER IT?"
OH, YOU SAW HOW
LONELY HE IS!
HE NEEDS ME,
AND IT'S THE ONLY WAY
I CAN TALK TO HIM.
I'LL DO ALL YOUR
FRENCH HOMEWORK.
PLEASE?
(DISGUSTED SIGH)
(STUDENTS CHEER)
HELLO DEGRASSIANS!
NOW, NORMALLY WE'RE CELEBRATING
PANTHER PRIDE,
BUT TODAY WE'RE CHEERING ON
THE TORONTO ICE-HOUNDS!
(STUDENTS CHEER AND APPLAUD)
SINCE THE HOCKEY TEAM
HAS ARRIVED,
THEY SURE HAVE SHAKEN
THINGS UP AT THE SCHOOL.
AND WHO COULD'VE PREDICTED
A WEEK AGO
HOW DIFFERENT OUR LIVES
WOULD BE?
SO LET'S MEET THEM
IN TRUE DEGRASSI SPIRIT!
(STUDENTS CHEER AND APPLAUD)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
(STUDENTS CHEER)
WHOOO!
(STUDENTS CHEER AND HOLLER)
YEAH!
YOU DA MAN!
OWEN: (ON TAPE)
HOW DID IT GO WITH KATIE?
DREW:
I DID IT.
(STUDENTS LAUGH)
DREW: (ON TAPE)
I HAD SEX. WHOO!
OH, I'M A MAN!
WHOO! I DID IT, YEAH!
OH YEAH, I'M THE MAN!
COME ON, LET'S PARTY!
YEAH! (LAUGHS DRUNKENLY)
OWEN:
WHERE'D YOU DO IT,
BUDDY?
DREW:
OH, IN THE BED.
I HAD SEX, YEAH! YEAH!
OH YEAH! WOULD YOU KNOW
I HAD SEX YEAH!
DREW: I'M THE MAN!
OWEN: HE'S THE MAN!
BECKY:
GUYS, THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR BEING A PART OF IT.
I'M REALLY, REALLY EXCITED
FOR THIS YEAR.
IT'S GONNA BE AMAZING.
LIKE, AMAZING!
I CAN'T BELIEVE THEY
KICKED US OUT OF THE GYM
FOR A STUPID PEP RALLY.
THANKS FOR SHOWING UP.
AND MISS THIS SPREAD?
MINI QUICHE?
THEY'RE SO WEE!
OKAY,
LET'S GET STARTED.
I'M VERY EXCITED TO TELL YOU
ABOUT THE PLAY THAT I'VE CHOSEN.
"DEATH OF A SALESMAN."
THE MODERN RETELLING
FOR THE INTERNET AGE.
ELI: I REALLY WANT-
BECKY: ELI!
BECKY:
UM, SO SORRY.
"DEATH OF A SALESMAN"
SOUNDS SUPER FUN AND ALL,
BUT THE PLAY'S ALREADY
BEEN DECIDED.
WHAT?
MR. SIMPSON WOULDN'T HAVE
APPROVED MY PROPOSAL OTHERWISE.
I FILED THE PAPERWORK
FOR THE RIGHTS
EARLIER THIS WEEK,
AND IT'S A DONE DEAL.
WHY DIDN'T YOU SAY THIS
AT OUR MEETING?
OH.
'CAUSE YOU NEVER GAVE ME
A CHANCE.
SO WHAT'S THE PLAY?
EVERYONE,
WE ARE PRODUCING
"ROMEO AND JULIET..."
ELI: OH, OKAY.
BECKY: THE MUSICAL VERSION!
WHAT?!
OOH!
ALL SINGING,
ALL DANCING,
ALL... AWESOME!
"AN ELI GOLDSWORTHY MUSICAL."
IT HAS A NICE RING TO IT,
HUH?
UH NO, NO, IT DOESN'T!
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT MUSICALS.
NO WORRIES,
I'VE GOT IT ALL UNDER CONTROL.
PARTNER.
MR. SIMPSON:
ALL YOUR FACES WERE THERE,
EVERYONE.
DALLAS:
NO, WE-WE WERE THERE,
MR. SIMPSON:
WELL, LISTEN,
SOMEONE WAS FILMING THAT,
I DON'T KNOW HOW THAT MADE IT
UP THERE, BUT LISTEN-
I WAS DRUNK,
I DON'T EVEN REMEMBER!
BUT YOU KNEW IT HAPPENED!
HOW LONG WERE YOU PLANNING
ON LYING TO ME?
I CAN'T DEAL WITH THIS,
DREW!
DON'T CALL ME!
WORST PEP RALLY EVER.
I AM SO SORRY, KATIE.
WE'RE GONNA FIGURE OUT
WHO SABOTAGED THAT VIDEO.
KATIE:
YOU DON'T NEED
TO FIGURE IT OUT.
IT WAS ME.
I DID IT.
MY OFFICE. NOW!
WHY DID YOU DO THIS?
I HAD TO.
SIMPSON IS GOING
TO SUSPEND YOU!
HE'LL TAKE AWAY
YOUR PRESIDENCY!
IT'S OKAY, MARE.
I DON'T HAVE TO PRETEND
ANYMORE.
THE WAY HAS BECOME CLEAR.
I'M FINALLY FREE.