CONNOR:
I DID IT!
KC:
WHAT'D YOU DO?
CONNOR:
I HAD SEX!
KC:
HEY!
(KC AND CONNOR LAUGH)
HOW WAS THAT?
THAT WAS PERFECT.
CONNOR: IT WAS GOOD?
KC: YEAH, DOWN TO A "T."
CONNOR: I'VE BEEN PRACTICING.
KC: NICE!
DREW:
HEY, BIANCA!
I HAVE A BRIGHT SPARKS MEETING.
UH, YOU'RE ON
THE ACADEMIC QUIZ TEAM.
SINCE WHEN?
SINCE I DECIDED
NOT TO BE A SCRUB
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
I'M NOT SURPRISED
YOU DON'T GET IT.
WAIT, UM...
THIS IS FOR YOU.
NOTHING SAYS SORRY
FOR CHEATING
LIKE A BLINGED OUT
CELL PHONE CASE.
PLEASE,
I WANT YOU TO HAVE IT.
AND I WANT YOU NOT
TO BE SO DUMB,
SO I GUESS WE BOTH LOSE.
(DREW SIGHS HEAVILY)
KC: THAT WAS MAD!
CONNOR: IT SOUNDED GOOD?
BIANCA:
HEY, GUYS.
HEY, DREW,
I THINK YOU'VE GOT
THE WRONG CLASSROOM.
NO, NO,
I'M IN THE RIGHT SPOT.
KC:
THIS IS THE ACADEMIC QUIZ TEAM.
AND I WOULD LIKE TO TRY OUT.
YOU NEED TO BE SMART.
ARE YOU SAYING
I'M NOT SMART?
YES.
KC:
UH, LOOK,
IF YOU'RE SERIOUS,
WE HAVE A SPOT OPEN
IN THE GEOGRAPHY CATEGORY.
HERE ARE SOME QUESTIONS,
STUDY THEM AND WE'LL DO
A MOCK ROUND TOMORROW.
GEOGRAPHY.
NO PROBLEMO.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
(Ooh-ooh-ooh)
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
BECKY:
OH! HEY, ELI.
YOU KNOW, CASTING FOR JULIET'S
GONNA BE TRICKY.
SHE'S THE HEART OF THE PLAY,
SHE HAS TO BE PERFECT.
SOMETHING WRONG?
ELI:
LOOK, BECKY,
LIKE I SAID BEFORE,
MUSICALS AREN'T REALLY
MY STYLE.
BUT STILL,
IT'S ROMEO AND JULIET,
SO I'M NOT QUITTING.
OH, I WASN'T WORRIED;
I PRAYED FOR YOU,
AND LOOK,
HERE YOU ARE.
THE LORD HASN'T
LET ME DOWN YET.
OKAY.
AUDITIONS START
RIGHT AFTER SCHOOL.
DON'T BE LATE.
I WOULDN'T DREAM OF IT.
(BELL RINGS)
(MAYA SIGHS)
OOH, MY FRENCH HOMEWORK?
TRISTAN:
YES, PLUS, MY FACERANGE
CHAT LOGS WITH CAMPBELL.
WELL, I DON'T NEED
THE NITTY GRITTY DETAILS,
THANK YOU.
I'M POSING AS YOU,
REMEMBER?
YOU HAVE TO ACT LIKE YOU KNOW
WHAT WE'VE TALKED ABOUT.
NOW, THE YELLOW HIGHLIGHTER
IS CONVERSATION STARTERS,
IN PINK, FUNNY INSIDE JOKES,
AND IN BLUE-
OKAY, WHY CAN'T YOU JUST
TALK TO HIM YOURSELF?
I NEED TO BUILD UP
MY CONFIDENCE.
LIKE ONCE WE'RE BESTIES,
I'LL TELL HIM THE TRUTH.
YEAH,
AND HE'LL BE PISSED!
FRIENDSHIP WILL TRIUMPH!
WE ARE SO MUCH ALIKE,
I FEEL LIKE I CAN TELL HIM
ANYTHING.
THEN TELL HIM
YOU'RE NOT ME!
I CAN'T, NOT YET!
OH, THERE'S ONE MORE THING
WE TALKED ABOUT.
SO, MAYA,
ARE YOU PSYCHED?
UM, YEAH,
TOTALLY...PSYCHED.
SHE TOLD YOU ABOUT THAT TOO,
DID SHE?
WE'RE BOTH AUDITIONING...
FOR THE MUSICAL.
OY, I DON'T THINK SO!
DON'T BE
A NERVOUS NELLY!
HEY, YOU'LL BE FINE.
JUST KEEP YOUR HEAD UP,
STICK ON THE ICE.
YOU'LL DO GREAT.
♪♪♪
♪ YOU ARE THE SUN ♪
♪ THE MOON IN THE NIGHT ♪
♪ YOU ARE MY EVERYTHING ♪
♪ EVERYTHING'S SO RIGHT,
IT WON'T TAKE ANOTHER SUMMER ♪
I'M SUPPOSED TO BE
IN A ROCK BAND, YOU KNOW.
SHUSH! I'M GETTING
INTO CHARACTER.
♪ NOW I HAVE YOU... ♪
♪ DON'T NEED ANYTHING AT ALL ♪
THANK YOU, TORI,
THAT WAS GREAT.
AND FINALLY,
UH, TRISTAN MILLIGAN?
TORI: KILL IT!
TRISTAN: ALREADY KILLED!
(TRISTAN SIGHS)
(TRISTAN SIGHS DEEPLY)
(CLEARS THROAT)
WHENEVER YOU'RE READY,
TRISTAN.
WHAT IS THAT LIGHT
IN THE WINDOW, JULIET?
YOU ARE THE SUN,
THE MOON IN THE NIGHT.
YOU ARE MY EVERYTHING,
EVERYTHING SO RIGHT.
IT WON'T TAKE ANOTHER SUMMER,
ANOTHER SPRING,
ANOTHER FALL.
NOW I HAVE YOU,
I DON'T NEED ANYTHING AT ALL.
ANYTHING AT ALL.
FINALLY AN ORIGINAL TAKE.
WE'LL FIND SOMETHING
FOR YOU, TRISTAN.
REALLY?
WELL, WE STILL HAVE A LOT OF
REALLY HARD DECISIONS TO MAKE.
THANKS! BYE.
THANK YOU, EVERYONE!
YOU SHOULDN'T PROMISE ROLES
LIKE THAT.
WE'D BE DUMB
NOT TO USE TRISTAN.
HE BROUGHT SOMETHING NEW.
TRISTAN IS SWEET,
BUT HE SEEMS...
(SIGHS)
CONFUSED.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
BY THAT?
WE NEED TO PICK
THE BEST PEOPLE,
AND IN MY OPINION,
HE DOESN'T RANK.
I'LL GO OVER THIS LIST
AND MAKE SOME FINAL DECISIONS.
NO WAY!
I'M THE DIRECTOR!
CALM DOWN!
I'M JUST USED TO DOING
EVERYTHING MYSELF,
SORRY!
HERE'S THE SHORTLIST
FOR ALL THE ROLES.
IF YOU WANT TO PICK-
YEAH, I GOT IT.
YOU'LL NEED TO DO CALLBACKS
FOR JULIET ASAP-
I GOT IT!
(SIGHS)
WHICH COUNTRY HAS
THE LONGEST COASTLINE?
ASIA?
COUNTRY!
LOWER ASIA?
THIS STUFF IS REALLY HARD.
YEAH, I KNOW.
MY HEAD IS SWIMMING.
OKAY, NEXT QUESTION.
OKAY, UM...
WHAT COUNTRY DID
THE THIRTEENTH CENTURY
BATTLE OF STIRLING BRIDGE
TAKE PLACE IN?
SCOTLAND.
WHOA!
RANDOM CORRECT GUESS?
HOW'D YOU KNOW?
BRAVEHEART.
ADAM:
OKAY, WELL, THAT'S ONE.
UM...
OKAY, NAME ONE OF TWO COUNTRIES
THAT BEGINS WITH THE LETTER "A"
BUT DOES NOT END WITH "A."
AFGHANISTAN.
YES! HOW?
RUNNING GUNS 3.
ACE SAYS IT TO JACKSON,
AS A JOKE, YOU KNOW?
RIGHT BEFORE THEY KILL
EVERYONE.
BOOYAH!
WOO!
WHOA!
THAT WAS LOUD.
AHHH! JUST...
THE VOLUME, OKAY?
(BUS RUMBLES)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
KC:
HEY, LET'S GET THIS TRYOUT
ON THE ROAD, EH?
CONNOR:
WHY ARE YOU WEARING SUNGLASSES
INSIDE?
UM, I'M A LITTLE
UNDER THE WEATHER.
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
I DON'T WANT YOU
TO THINK I'M STUPID.
KC:
OKAY, SO CONNOR'S GONNA READ
THE QUESTIONS,
YOU HAVE ONE MINUTE TO ANSWER
AS MANY AS YOU CAN CORRECTLY,
AND ANYTHING OVER TEN,
YOU'RE IN, OKAY?
READY, SET, GO.
IN TERMS OF SIZE,
HOW MANY STATES
COULD ALASKA HOLD?
UM...
FOUR?
TWELVE.
WHERE DID THE BATTLE
OF STIRLING BRIDGE TAKE PLACE?
(WHISPERS)
I KNOW THIS.
KC:
YOU CAN PASS TOO.
WAIT.
PASS.
CONNOR:
NAME ONE OF TWO COUNTRIES
THAT BEGINS WITH THE LETTER "A"
BUT DOES NOT END WITH "A."
YOU OKAY?
(DREW SIGHS UNSTEADILY)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
HEY, HOW DID IT GO,
TRIVIA SUPERSTAR?
SCREW OFF.
JEEZ,
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
EVERYTHING, I'M...
I'M-I'M AN IDIOT, OKAY?
YOU LOOK TERRIBLE,
MAYBE YOU SHOULD-
JUST BACK OFF, GRACIE!
WHAT THE HELL DID YOU
JUST CALL ME?
(CLATTERS)
DREW:
ADAM.
I CALLED YOU, ADAM.
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE,
OKAY?
ADAM:
DREW?
DREW, WHAT'S HAPPENING?
I DON'T KNOW.
CALL MOM.
(DREW TAKES LABOURED BREATHS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
HEY.
HOW WERE THE JULIET CALLBACKS?
(GROANS)
THAT GOOD, HUH?
I KNEW I SHOULD'VE
TRIED OUT.
A LITTLE OF THIS?
FUNNY?
IT'S NOT THE ACTORS,
IT'S HER.
YOU AND BECKY STILL
HAVEN'T WORKED OUT
YOUR CLASHING PERSONALITIES YET?
WE'RE STUCK IN A VORTEX
OF CREATIVE DIFFERENCES.
WHEN YOU'RE AT NYU,
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO WORK
WITH A LOT OF PEOPLE
WHO ARE DIFFERENT
FROM YOU.
THIS IS GOOD PRACTICE.
ELI:
CLARE, THIS MUSICAL IS NOT GONNA
GET ME INTO NYU.
WHEN WE WATCHED
"THE DARK KNIGHT" TOGETHER,
YOU TALKED NONSTOP
ABOUT HOW CHRISTOPHER NOLAN
TOOK ALL THESE FAMILIAR,
PLAYED OUT ELEMENTS
AND MADE THEM NEW AGAIN.
YOU CAN DO THAT TOO.
I'M NOT CHRISTOPHER NOLAN.
OR BATMAN.
HELL, I CAN'T EVEN PULL OFF
THE JOKER ANYMORE.
FIND A WAY
TO MAKE IT YOUR OWN.
I BELIEVE IN YOU.
YOUR CT SCAN SHOWS NO EVIDENCE
OF BLEEDING OR ABNORMALITIES,
BUT WE DID A SCAT2 TEST
TO BE SAFE.
IT SEEMS YOUR TUMBLE
DOWN THE STAIRS
HAS RESULTED IN
A SEVERE CONCUSSION.
BUT I FELL A WEEK AGO,
AND I WAS OKAY UNTIL TODAY.
IT'S NOT UNUSUAL FOR SYMPTOMS
TO SHOW UP
A FEW DAYS AFTER THE EVENT.
DREW:
WHAT ABOUT MY MEMORY?
IT'S BEEN HORRIBLE.
DREW, HAVE YOU SUFFERED
ANY OTHER HEAD INJURIES
IN THE PAST TWELVE MONTHS?
WELL...
WHEN I THOUGHT I WAS GONNA GET
JUMPED BY THE GANG AGAIN,
I STARTED DOING MMA FIGHTING.
AND THIS ONE TIME,
I-I GOT HIT SO HARD THAT...
THAT I BLACKED OUT.
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?!
BECAUSE I WAS FINE.
WELL, YOU'RE NOT FINE NOW,
ARE YOU?
I QUIT FIGHTING
A LONG TIME AGO, MOM.
WE NEED TO DISCUSS
A COURSE OF TREATMENT.
YEAH.
DR. YARDLEY:
AS LONG AS YOU REMAIN
SYMPTOM FREE,
YOU CAN GO TO SCHOOL,
BUT OUTSIDE OF SCHOOL HOURS,
YOU NEED TO REST AT HOME.
NO VIDEO GAMES,
NO TV.
(SIGHS)
REDUCED CLASSWORK
WOULDN'T HURT.
WAIT, WAIT.
DOES THAT MEAN I DON'T HAVE
TO DO MY ENGLISH TEST TOMORROW?
DREW!
TAKE THIS SERIOUSLY.
YEAH.
(SIGHS)
(KEYS CLACK)
TRISTAN:
NOT EVEN CHORUS?!
OH!
(KEYS CLICK)
(TRISTAN SIGHS)
TRISTAN: OOPS!
CAMPBELL: OH!
OH, OOPS, SORRY!
NO WORRIES.
UM, HEY,
HAVE YOU SEEN MAYA?
OH, UH, SHE'S SO UPSET
ABOUT THE MUSICAL
SHE CAN'T TALK TO ANYONE.
YEAH, I KNOW,
SHE JUST TEXTED ME.
I'M SO MAD FOR HER.
REALLY?
I'M MAD TOO.
AND THIS WHOLE MUSICAL THING
IS SO STUPID.
SHE SHOULD GO TELL
THE DIRECTOR OFF.
WHAT A JERK.
I SHOULD DO THAT.
SHE SHOULD DO THAT.
GOOD ADVICE.
I'LL PASS THAT ALONG.
OKAY.
(SIGHS)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
TORI: (ON COMPUTER)
♪ YOU ARE THE SUN ♪
♪ THE MOON IN THE NIGHT ♪
TRISTAN: (ON TAPE)
EVERYTHING'S SO RIGHT.
IT WON'T TAKE ANOTHER SUMMER,
ANOTHER SPRING,
ANOTHER FALL.
NOW I HAVE YOU,
I DON'T NEED ANYTHING AT ALL.
ANYTHING AT ALL.
TRISTAN:
AHEM!
HEY.
DON'T YOU "HEY" ME!
YOU SAID AFTER MY AUDITION
THERE WOULD BE A PART FOR ME,
BUT NOTHING,
NOT EVEN CHORUS!
BECKY DIDN'T THINK
YOU WERE RIGHT
FOR ANY OF THE GUY ROLES.
UH, AREN'T YOU THE DIRECTOR?
YES, I AM.
AND SO...
I'D LIKE TO OFFER YOU
THE PART OF JULIET.
YOU WANT ME TO PLAY A GIRL?
NO.
JULIET IS NOW...JULES.
MY VERSION IS A LOVE STORY
BETWEEN TWO GUYS.
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
BECAUSE I USED TO STAND UP
FOR PEOPLE
WHEN NO ONE ELSE WOULD.
AND NOW I'M STANDING UP
FOR YOU,
SO WHAT DO YOU SAY?
I'M GONNA BE THE LEAD
IN THE SCHOOL MUSICAL?
YEAH.
TRISTAN:
I'M GONNA BE THE LEAD
IN THE SCHOOL MUSICAL.
IN THE SCHOOL MUSICAL!
OKAY, OKAY,
YOU NEED TO BREATHE.
YOUR FACE IS GETTING VERY RED!
OH MY GOD!
THIS PLAY IS NOT
GONNA BE EASY.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO WORK
YOUR BUTT OFF.
I WILL TAKE THIS MORE SERIOUSLY
THAN ANYTHING I HAVE
IN MY ENTIRE LIFE.
WE START AFTER SCHOOL.
BUT WHAT ABOUT YOUR PRODUCER?
SHE HATED MY AUDITION.
TRISTAN, YOU NEED TO BE
IN THIS MUSICAL,
AND IF THAT BOTHERS BECKY
IN THE PROCESS,
BONUS.
SO YOU'RE USING ME?
DO YOU MIND?
NOT A BIT,
YOU MAGNIFICENT BASTARD!
(SIGHS EXCITEDLY)
♪♪♪
(BELL RINGS)
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
ARE YOU OKAY?
I'M STILL ON PAGE THREE.
BIANCA:
I'M SURE YOU COULD TAKE
EXTRA TIME.
LOOK, ADAM TOLD ME
ABOUT THE CONCUSSIONS.
(SIGHS)
DO YOU WANT TO TALK?
NO.
YOU KNOW,
YOU MADE THE RIGHT CALL.
I'M STUPID
AND YOU DESERVE BETTER.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
TO THE MALL TO RETURN THE GIFT
YOU DIDN'T WANT.
I'M STUNNED!
THE LEAD GIRL ROLE?
WELL, BOY, NOW.
CAMPBELL:
HEY, THERE'S JULIET!
I WANTED TO COME SAY CONGRATS
IN PERSON,
SO CONGRATS.
MAYA:
(SIGHS)
I'M NOT PLAYING JULIET,
CAMPBELL.
TRISTAN:
I AM. I MEAN, IT'S NOT JULIET,
IT'S A BOY NOW.
NEVER MIND, NOT RELEVANT.
YEAH, BUT MAYA SENT ME
A DIRECT MESSAGE.
OH GOD,
WHAT DID I DO?
I DON'T KNOW,
YOU TELL ME.
TRISTAN:
MAYA DIDN'T SEND YOU
THE DIRECT MESSAGE.
I DID.
I WAS STILL LOGGED INTO HER
FACERANGE ACCOUNT.
OKAY, WHAT DO YOU MEAN
STILL LOGGED IN?
WHEN YOU THOUGHT YOU WERE
ONLINE CHATTING WITH MAYA,
IT WAS ME.
I DIDN'T KNOW HOW
TO TALK TO YOU,
AND IT WAS JUST EASIER ONLINE.
YOU LIED TO ME?
IT WAS MY FAULT TOO;
I LET HIM USE MY ACCOUNT.
WE ARE SO SORRY,
BUT NOW WE CAN START FRESH,
AND ALL BE FRIENDS.
NO...
WE WILL NEVER BE FRIENDS.
EVER!
WE SO MESSED UP.
MAYA:
YEAH. MAYBE HE'LL COME AROUND.
TRISTAN:
I DOUBT IT.
YOU STILL HAVE ROMEO AND JULES,
RIGHT?
(CAR RUMBLES)
(STORE EMPLOYEE TALKS QUIETLY)
HEY,
I NEED TO RETURN THIS.
UH, TOO BLINGY?
NOT BLINGY ENOUGH?
WE CAN FIND AN EXCHANGE.
DREW:
UH, JUST A REFUND.
I MESSED UP BIG TIME.
OH MAN, NOT AGAIN!
THIEF!
(CHAIRS CLATTER)
MAX:
OH! OH MY GOD!
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
DREW:
CAREFUL! OOF!
(THIEF GROANS)
WOMAN:
ARE YOU OKAY?
GOTCHA.
(SPECTATORS APPLAUD)
SPECTATORS:
OH!
♪♪♪
POLICE OFFICER:
LET'S GO!
DUDE, THAT WAS THE COOLEST THING
I'VE EVER SEEN
IN MY LIFE!
AND LIKE, I PLAY A LOT
OF VIDEO GAMES, RIGHT?
YOU TOTALLY TOOK HIM DOWN!
LIKE, IT WAS CRAZY!
BIANCA?
WHAT HAPPENED?
ARE YOU OKAY?
THIS LOWLIFE STOLE
A SEVEN HUNDRED DOLLAR PHONE
FROM OUR KIOSK,
AND DREW TOTALLY TOOK HIM DOWN
CHRIS HEMSWORTH STYLE!
BIANCA:
DID YOU HIT YOUR HEAD?
TELL ME!
MAX:
HEY, WHY ARE YOU YELLING
AT HIM?
HE'S A SUPERHERO!
OKAY, HIPSTER, DISAPPEAR!
NOW!
THANK YOU.
I FOLLOWED YOU HERE
BECAUSE I WAS WORRIED.
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO BE
JUMPING SHOPLIFTERS, DREW.
WHY WOULD YOU DO SOMETHING
SO RISKY?
THEY THOUGHT
IT WAS PRETTY AWESOME.
YEAH,
BUT I LOVE YOU!
YOU DO?
I COULDN'T TAKE IT
IF SOMETHING BAD
HAPPENED TO YOU.
MAX:
(WHISPERS LOUDLY)
KISS!
♪ YOU ARE THE SUN ♪
♪ THE MOON IN THE NIGHT ♪
♪ YOU ARE MY EVERYTHING ♪
♪ EVERYTHING'S SO RIGHT ♪
♪ I DON'T NEED ANOTHER SUMMER ♪
♪ ANOTHER SPRING,
ANOTHER FALL ♪
WHAT'S THIS?
AH, THERE YOU ARE.
I CAST TRISTAN AS "JULES,"
A BOY.
ROMEO IS A BOY.
YEAH.
YOU'RE JOKING!
NO.
THIS IS ABSURD!
DO WE NEED A CONFERENCE WITH
MR. SIMPSON TO CLEAR THIS UP?
I ALREADY TOLD SIMPSON
ABOUT TRISTAN.
HE SAID THE CHOICE
WAS INSPIRED.
DIRECT QUOTE.
BUT HE'S THE PRINCIPAL
OF THE SCHOOL,
HOW CAN HE SUPPORT A PLAY
THAT CONDONES HOMOSEXUALITY?
YOU'RE ONLY DOING THIS
TO SPITE ME.
I'M NOT.
YOU WANT TO PUSH ME OFF
MY OWN PROJECT!
I JUST WANT THE PLAY
TO BE SPECIAL!
IT'LL BE AWESOME,
TRUST ME.
DON'T NEED ANYTHING AT ALL.
I HAVE TO QUIT.
(SIGHS)
I QUIT.
LOOK, THE ONLY THING
THAT HAS CHANGED
IS THAT IT'S TWO GAY GUYS.
BIG WHOOP!
THAT'S NO REASON TO QUIT.
YOU DON'T GET IT.
I CAN'T BE PART OF SOMETHING
THAT DEPICTS AN ALTERNATIVE
LIFESTYLE CHOICE AS NORMAL!
WOW, YOU'RE SERIOUS.
TRISTAN:
♪ YOU ARE THE SUN ♪
♪ THE MOON IN THE NIGHT ♪
♪ YOU ARE MY EVERYTHING ♪
THIS ISN'T RIGHT!
WELCOME TO DEGRASSI.
TRISTAN:
♪ ANOTHER SPRING,
ANOTHER FALL... ♪