(DANCE MUSIC PLAYS NEARBY)
(SOBBING)
(LAUGHING)
ELI:
I'VE MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
CLARE:
ELI...
(HEAVY BREATHING)
OKAY, WE CAN'T HAVE SEX
IN HERE.
YOU KNOW,
WE ARE IN A HOTEL.
I HEAR THEY HAVE ROOMS.
ELI:
DON'T YOU HAVE
A CREDIT CARD?
HELEN GAVE IT TO ME
FOR EMERGENCIES.
I THINK THIS QUALIFIES.
(IMOGEN SOBS)
DID YOU HEAR SOMETHING?
(SOBBING)
NOTHING TO SEE HERE.
JUST LOOKING FOR MY CONTACT.
I'LL... GO TELL ALLI
THAT I'M NOT SLEEPING OVER.
YOU LOOK PRETTY UPSET
OVER A LOST CONTACT.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
(Ooh-ooh-ooh)
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
I DIDN'T LOSE MY CONTACT,
I LOST FIONA.
ELI:
UNLIKELY! IF CLARE AND I
CAN WORK IT OUT,
ANYONE CAN.
ALL SHE CARES ABOUT
IS THAT STUPID JOB!
WELL, THEN HELP HER
GET IT.
SO MY GIRLFRIEND CAN BE
THOUSANDS OF MILES
AWAY FROM ME?
BETTER THAN NO GIRLFRIEND
AT ALL.
(REALIZING SIGH)
("GANGNAM STYLE" BY PSY PLAYS)
MO!
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
YOU MISSED OUR SONG!
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO DANCE!
(DRUNKENLY)
YEAH... WHATEVER.
WHAT IS WRONG
WITH YOU?
YOU TELL ME.
APPARENTLY
I'M SOOOOOOO PATHETIC
YOU GOTTA PAY PEOPLE
TO BE MY FRIEND.
THE ONLY REASON I PAID JAKE
TO COME HERE
IS BECAUSE YOU
DIDN'T WANNA SHARE
YOUR FEELINGS
WITH HIM.
SO I CAME UP
WITH A SCHEME -
I SCHEME!
YOU KNOW I SCHEME! -
AND THEN YOU RUN OFF,
MISS OUR SONG,
AND GET DRUNK?
DALLAS:
GO, MO!
OWEN:
AH! YOU TELL HER, BABY!
YOU TELL HER.
I HOPE YOU HAD FUN
WITH YOUR NEW FRIENDS.
MARISOL, WAIT.
WHAT?!
(VOMITS)
THESE SHOES ARE MERMOZI.
I'M SORRY, BABY.
CAN WE TALK ABOUT THIS?
PLEASE?
NO!
(VOMITS)
CLARE:
GUYS, I NEED SOME ADVICE.
ALLI:
OH, IS THIS ABOUT ELI?
I SAW YOU TWO DANCING.
WE'RE BACK TOGETHER!
AND WE'RE GOING TO...
ON PROM NIGHT?
OH, I KNOW,
IT'S SO CLICHE-
ROMANTIC.
ALLI:
THIS ISN'T BECAUSE WE FOUND
THAT LUMP ON YOUR BACK
AND YOU THINK YOU'RE GONNA DIE,
IS IT?
NO! ACTUALLY,
I TOTALLY FORGOT ABOUT THAT.
WELL, GOOD!
OKAY, SO BACK TO...
ANY LAST MINUTE ADVICE?
BE SAFE.
OF COURSE.
OH, AND DON'T BE CONCERNED
IF IT'S WEIRD.
ELI:
READY?
HAVE FUN, YOU TWO!
(JENNA AND ALLI GIGGLE)
YOU TOLD THEM?
I REALLY WISH I HADN'T.
JAKE:
SO YOU'RE GOING TO STANFORD
IN THE FALL, THAT'S...
KATIE:
YEAH, I'M GONNA BE PAYING OFF
STUDENT LOANS
UNTIL I'M FORTY,
BUT IT'LL BE WORTH IT.
JAKE: YEAH.
KATIE: WHAT ARE YOUR PLANS?
UH, WELL...
I'M MUSHROOM-PICKING IN B.C.
FOR THE SUMMER.
OH.
YEAH, THEN WHO KNOWS?
WHO KNOWS?
GUYS, GUYS, GUYS,
GUYS...
(CHAIR SCRAPES,
CUTLERY CLINKS)
WAIT. ARE YOU BACK-
ARE YOU GUYS BACK TOGETHER?
NO. NO, NO, NO.
WE'RE JUST CATCHING UP.
WHAT'S UP?
MARISOL WON'T TALK TO ME;
I MISSED OUR DANCE.
THE ONE SHE'S BEEN TALKING ABOUT
FOR MONTHS?
YOU GUYS GOTTA HELP ME
MAKE IT BETTER. PLEASE?
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO DO
SOMETHING BIG.
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYS)
IMOGEN:
HEY! UM, CAN WE TALK?
PLEASE!
OKAY, I'M LISTENING.
I'VE BRAINSTORMED
OVER TWO DOZEN IDEAS
TO GET YOU THAT
FASHION JOB BACK.
I ALREADY CALLED
FEDERICO'S HOTEL.
HE'S AT THE AIRPORT.
OKAY,
THEN LET'S GO THERE.
NO.
I SPENT MONTHS
WORKING ON THIS PROM
AND I JUST WANNA ENJOY
MY LAST NIGHT WITH MY FRIENDS.
BUT YOU SAID WE COULD MAKE IT
THROUGH ANYTHING TOGETHER!
MAYBE I WAS WRONG.
MAYBE WE'RE JUST
TOO DIFFERENT.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(GIGGLING)
ELI:
YOUR PALMS ARE SWEATY.
CLARE:
YOU REALLY KNOW
HOW TO ROMANCE A GIRL.
YOU'RE NOT NERVOUS,
ARE YOU?
IT'S JUST WE'VE WAITED
SO LONG...
BUILT UP THIS MOMENT.
WHAT IF
IT'S A DISAPPOINTMENT?
OKAY, STAND STILL.
WAS THAT A DISAPPOINTMENT?
NO.
JUST LET ME KNOW
WHEN IT GOES DOWNHILL.
(DOOR CLICKS OPEN)
IT'S BEAUTIFUL!
SO ARE YOU.
(PLANE ENGINE HISSES)
PLEASE BE HERE!
(BOARDING ANNOUNCEMENT
OVER PA SYSTEM)
(GASPS)
FEDERICO, WAIT!
FEDERICO:
FIONA, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I'M NOT FIONA,
I'M HER GIRLFRIEND.
WELL, EX-GIRLFRIEND.
IT'S COMPLICATED.
SO YOU IMPERSONATED FIONA?
THAT IS CRAZY.
I KNOW.
BUT HAVEN'T YOU DONE
SOMETHING CRAZY
BECAUSE YOU WERE IN LOVE?
I MUST GO.
MY PLANE'S ABOUT TO BOARD.
THIS YEAR'S BEEN A DISASTER.
MY DAD'S LOSING HIS MIND,
LITERALLY,
I COULDN'T KEEP UP
IN SCHOOL,
AND THE ONLY REASON
I MADE IT THROUGH
IS BECAUSE FIONA COYNE
WAS ON MY TEAM,
AND THAT'S WHY
I'M SO SCARED TO LOSE HER.
BECAUSE EVERYONE SHOULD
HAVE A FIONA
AND I DON'T KNOW WHERE
I'LL FIND ANOTHER.
(EMOTIONAL BREATHS)
SHE SOUNDS LIKE
A SPECIAL GIRL.
SHE IS,
SHE REALLY IS,
AND SHE'S A TALENTED DESIGNER.
SHE EVEN DESIGNED THE DRESS
I'M WEARING
AND THE NECKLACE,
AND I HAVE A BUNCH MORE PHOTOS
ON MY PHONE.
I'M SORRY,
I MUST GO.
I UNDERSTAND.
(SIGHS)
TELL REAL FIONA COYNE
TO GIVE ME A CALL.
WE WILL SEE IF SHE'S AS SPECIAL
AS YOU SAY.
OH, MUCHO GRAZIE,
SIGNOR CAVALIERI.
(LAUGHING)
(SIGHS, RELIEVED)
(HOOVES CLOP,
CARRIAGE RATTLES)
CLARE:
SO DO I LOOK DIFFERENT?
ELI:
COMPLETELY.
THEY'RE GONNA KNOW WE HAD SEX
AS SOON AS THEY SEE YOU.
(LAUGHS)
I HAD A GREAT NIGHT.
ME TOO.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU LEAVE
IN TWELVE HOURS.
I GUESS THIS WILL BE
THE LAST DAY
WE HAVE TOGETHER
FOR A WHILE.
WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
YOU HAVE TO GET READY
FOR YOUR GRADUATION
AND SO DO I.
WHAT'S WRONG?
YOUR NOSE,
IT'S BLEEDING.
IT'S UM...
IT'S PROBABLY JUST THE DRY AIR
FROM THE HOTEL.
ARE YOU OKAY?
DO I NEED TO TAKE YOU
TO THE DOCTOR?
NO, BUT I WILL TAKE
YOUR HANKY.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
FIONA'S PRACTICING
FOR HER VALEDICTORIAN SPEECH.
SHE DOESN'T WANT
TO BE DISTURBED.
WELL, CAN YOU DELIVER
A MESSAGE THEN?
I FOUND FEDERICO
AT THE AIRPORT
AND HE AGREED TO GIVE FIONA
A SECOND CHANCE.
SO TELL HER I SAY
GOOD LUCK...
AND GOODBYE.
FIONA:
WAIT.
YOU REALLY CHASED FEDERICO DOWN
AT THE AIRPORT...
LIKE IN A MOVIE?
I HAD TO DO SOMETHING.
DOES THIS MEAN
YOU FORGIVE ME?
JUST DON'T IMPERSONATE ME
AGAIN.
I SOLEMNLY SWEAR!
GOOD.
YOU CAN VISIT LOTS.
WE'LL PUT A SERIOUS DENT
IN MY TRUST FUND.
AND THEN AFTER I GRADUATE
I'LL FIND AN ART SCHOOL
IN ITALY.
YEAH, I'LL PROBABLY BE WORKING
CRAZY HOURS, BUT-
I'LL GET A DOG
FOR COMPANY.
AND YOUR DAD CAN FLY OVER
WHENEVER HE WANTS.
HE'LL BE SO LONELY
WITHOUT ME.
THAT'S WHAT SKYPE'S FOR.
RIGHT!
AND BESIDES,
WE'LL ONLY BE IN ITALY
FOR ONE OR TWO YEARS, RIGHT?
YEAH.
MAYBE, AFTER THAT,
WE'LL GO TO PARIS
OR DUBAI.
WE HAVE THE WHOLE WORLD
TO EXPLORE TOGETHER.
ISN'T THAT EXCITING?
IT'S... SOMETHING.
I'LL CALL FEDERICO.
("POMP AND CIRCUMSTANCE" PLAYS)
SIMPSON:
(SIGHS)
THANK YOU FOR COMING.
THIS YEAR'S GRADUATES
ARE A DIVERSE BUNCH.
I'M PROUD TO BE THEIR PRINCIPAL
AND I'M SAD TO SAY GOODBYE.
(CAMERA SHUTTER SNAPS)
SO BEFORE I GET TOO EMOTIONAL...
THE DIPLOMAS!
FIRST UP,
BIANCA DESOUSA...
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
WOO-HOO!
SHE DID IT!
THAT'S MY GIRL.
WOO-HOO!
SIMPSON:
KATIE MATLIN.
MARISOL LEWIS.
OWEN MILLIGAN.
(APPLAUSE)
MO MASHKOUR.
JAKE MARTIN.
(APPLAUSE)
ALLI:
GOT YOUR EMERGENCY TEXT.
WHAT'S WRONG?
WAS THE SEX BAD?
NO, NO.
IT WAS FINE.
PERFECT, ACTUALLY.
THEN WHY THE 911?
I-I NEED YOU
TO CONVINCE ME
THAT I DON'T HAVE
CANCER.
THE LUMP?
CLARE, I TOLD YOU,
IT'S PROBABLY-
JUST A CYST OR LIPOMA
OR FIBROMA.
SOMEBODY'S BEEN ON
THE INTERNET.
I-I HAD A NOSEBLEED
THIS MORNING
AND IT WOULDN'T STOP,
SO MY MOM TOOK ME
TO THE DOCTOR.
THEY WANT TO DO
A BIOPSY.
A BIOPSY?
YEAH. IT'S WHERE
THEY TAKE A NEEDLE
AND EXTRACT
A PIECE OF TISSUE-
TO TEST FOR CANCER.
YEAH.
APPARENTLY NOSEBLEEDS
AND SWOLLEN LYMPH NODES
ARE...
THE LUMP.
COMMON SYMPTOMS
OF LEUKEMIA.
BUT THEY'RE PROBABLY
JUST BEING CAUTIOUS.
I MEAN...
DO YOU REMEMBER
WHEN I THOUGHT I WAS PREGNANT?
AND EVERYTHING
TURNED OUT FINE.
THAT'S WHAT I KEEP
TELLING MYSELF.
YOU'RE YOUNG,
YOU DON'T SMOKE,
YOU EAT HEALTHY,
YOU VOLUNTEER...
IT'S PROBABLY NOTHING.
AND WHAT IF
IT'S NOT?
DID YOU TELL ELI?
I WILL,
BUT NOT TODAY.
YOU ONLY GRADUATE ONCE.
YEAH. PLEASE.
SIMPSON:
AND FINALLY,
LAST BUT NOT LEAST,
YOUR STUDENT COUNCIL
CO-PRESIDENT
AND YOUR VALEDICTORIAN,
FIONA COYNE.
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
FIONA:
THANK YOU, MR. SIMPSON,
AND THANK YOU, EVERYONE,
FOR COMING.
I NEVER EXPECTED TO BE STANDING
BEFORE YOU AS VALEDICTORIAN.
IN FACT, LAST YEAR,
I NEVER EXPECTED
TO GRADUATE AT ALL.
I WAS AT MY LOWEST POINT.
I SKIPPED GRADUATION
TO GO TO THE LIQUOR STORE.
(SHOCKED MURMURS AND GASPS)
OKAY, THAT MIGHT'VE BEEN
AN OVERSHARE,
BUT MY POINT IS,
I WAS A MESS...
AND SO SCARED OF THE FUTURE.
I HAD TO COME BACK
TO DEGRASSI
EVEN THOUGH ALL OF MY FRIENDS
WERE MOVING ON.
BUT THEN I MADE NEW FRIENDS -
REALLY, REALLY GREAT FRIENDS.
SO DON'T BE AFRAID
OF CHANGE,
NO MATTER HOW SCARY IT SEEMS.
IF I CAN MAKE IT THROUGH,
SO CAN YOU.
SO WHAT MORE IS THERE TO SAY?
THANKS, DEGRASSI.
I'VE HAD THE TIME
OF MY LIFE.
(APPLAUSE,
LIGHT CLICKS OFF)
(GRADUATES MURMUR)
♪ NOW I'VE HAD
THE TIME OF MY LIFE ♪
♪ AND I NEVER FELT
LIKE THIS BEFORE ♪
(BRASS SECTION BEGINS TO PLAY)
♪ YES, I SWEAR ♪
♪ IT'S THE TRUTH ♪
♪ AND I OWE IT ALL TO YOU ♪
KATIE AND JAKE:
♪ 'CAUSE I'VE HAD
THE TIME OF MY LIFE ♪
GRADUATES:
♪ AND I OWE IT ALL TO YOU... ♪
(REST OF BAND BEGINS TO PLAY)
♪ I'VE BEEN WAITING
FOR SO LONG ♪
♪ NOW I FINALLY FOUND SOMEONE
TO STAND BY ME ♪
♪ SO WE TAKE EACH OTHER'S HAND ♪
♪ 'CAUSE WE SEEM TO UNDERSTAND
THE URGENCY ♪
♪ JUST REMEMBER... ♪
♪ YOU'RE THE ONE THING ♪
♪ I CAN'T GET ENOUGH OF ♪
MARISOL LEWIS,
MAY I HAVE THIS DANCE?
♪ THIS COULD BE LOVE
BECAUSE... ♪
♪ I'VE HAD THE TIME OF MY LIFE ♪
♪ NO, I NEVER FELT THIS WAY
BEFORE... ♪
SO AM I FORGIVEN?
NOT UNTIL YOU TELL JAKE
HOW YOU REALLY FEEL,
AND THAT YOU STILL
WANNA BE FRIENDS
NOW THAT WE'RE GRADUATES.
TALK TO HIM.
IT'S YOUR LAST CHANCE.
GRADUATES:
♪ AND I'VE SEARCHED
THROUGH EVERY OPEN DOOR ♪
♪ 'TIL I FOUND THE TRUTH ♪
HEY, MAN.
I JUST WANTED TO SAY...
HAVE A GOOD SUMMER.
YEAH!
COOL, MAN.
ALL RIGHT, DUDE.
YEAH, YOU TOO.
AND I KNOW THIS IS THE END
OF SCHOOL, ALL RIGHT,
BUT I DON'T WANT THIS TO BE
THE END OF OUR FRIENDSHIP.
I WANT YOU IN MY LIFE
FOR THE LONG RUN, DUDE.
ALL RIGHT?
YOU THINK I'M SO LAME.
I WAS GONNA SAY THAT
MAYBE OUR KIDS COULD
PLAY TOGETHER.
YOU KNOW...
MARISOL AND KATIE:
AWWWWWWWWWWWWWW!
(LAUGHING)
GRADUATES:
♪ I'VE HAD THE TIME OF MY LIFE ♪
HEY!
HAVE YOU SEEN CLARE?
I CAN'T FIND HER
AND IT'S TIME TO SAY GOODBYE.
I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT,
ELI GOLDSWORTHY.
GRADUATES:
♪ AND I OWE IT ALL TO YOU ♪
♪ BECAUSE I... HAD... ♪
IMMY!
YOUR SPEECH WAS
SO INSPIRATIONAL.
ALSO, I THINK
WE SHOULD BREAK UP.
IS THIS BECAUSE OF ITALY?
YOU WANT TO EXPLORE
THE WORLD
AND...I JUST WANNA
READ ABOUT IT
FROM MY COMFY CHAIR.
I LIKE THAT
WE'RE DIFFERENT.
ME TOO,
BUT I DON'T WANNA
HOLD YOU BACK.
I KNOW IT'S SCARY...
IT'S TERRIFYING.
BUT IT'S THE RIGHT THING
TO DO.
MARISOL:
COME ON, COYNE!
WE'RE ABOUT TO TOSS OUR CAPS!
ARE YOU COMING?
MAYBE JUST ONE
LAST KISS?
FAREWELL, FIONA.
(BREATH CATCHES)
(SNIFFLES)
(CHEERING)
DALLAS:
GOOD RIDDANCE.
DREW:
SO I GUESS IT'S UP TO US
TO KEEP THE DRAMA GOING.
ALLI:
OR MAYBE NEXT YEAR
DEGRASSI CAN BE DRAMA-FREE.
ALL:
(LAUGHING)
WHY SO GLUM, EDWARDS?
I MIGHT HAVE CANCER.
(LAUGHS)
GOOD ONE.
UM... ARE YOU OKAY?
I'LL SURVIVE.
ELI:
AND WHAT ARE YOU TWO GIRLS
GOSSIPING ABOUT?
CLARE:
ONLY HOW MUCH
I WILL MISS YOU TOMORROW.
SAFE TRAVELS, ELI.
COME HERE.
DON'T YOU HAVE A CAP
TO TOSS?
YES. BUT THEN I'D HAVE
TO LET GO OF YOU.
NO. I DON'T WANT YOU
MISSING OUT ON ANYTHING
BECAUSE OF ME.
PROMISE?
ALL RIGHT,
MISS SERIOUS.
BUT IF I'M GOING...
YOU'RE COMING WITH ME.
♪ There's something
kinda wrong ♪
MARISOL:
EVERYONE READY TO SAY GOODBYE?!
ALL:
YEAH! WOO!
DON'T WORRY.
THIS YEAR WILL FLY BY
AND WE'LL BE IN NEW YORK
TOGETHER.
THAT'S THE PLAN.
WE'LL MAKE IT THROUGH,
TOGETHER.
GRADUATES:
THREE! TWO! ONE!
WOO!
(CHEERING)
♪ Keep your distance ♪
♪ But be careful
how far you stray ♪
♪ And don't forget
where you were born ♪
♪ Don't forget this moment ♪
♪ And the closest thing to God ♪
♪ Is being next to you
in this rusted car ♪
♪ And I'm never going back ♪
♪ And I won't forget
this moment ♪
♪ Remain close
but stay away ♪