FIONA:
OKAY, SO WHISPERHUG IS GETTING
THEIR EQUIPMENT READY.
BECKY AND JENNA ARE SETTING UP
THE SILENT AUCTION...
OH HEY, MO,
CAN YOU HELP ME SET UP
THAT FUNDRAISING THERMOMETER?
WE'RE HOPING TO HIT
TWELVE BIG ONES!
SHOULDN'T BE ANY TROUBLE
WITH THAT KILLER VEGAS TRIP!
SHOWGIRLS, GAMBLING,
SHOTGUN WEDDINGS
TO SHOWGIRLS.
OKAY.
JENNA:
HEY THERE, PRETTY LADY.
(LAUGHS)
GOOD GRIEF, JENNA.
SORRY! IT'S FROM
THE VEGAS DISPLAY.
FUNNY, RIGHT?
I GUESS SO.
HAVE YOU SEEN
MY FRIEND BECKY?
SHE'S ABOUT 5'9",
BLONDE, PERKY.
I KNOW,
I'M NOT MYSELF.
I FEEL SO GUILTY LYING
TO MY PARENTS ABOUT ADAM.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE KEEPING
ADAM A SECRET?
I'M TERRIBLE AT SECRETS.
MY PARENTS NOT ONLY FOUND OUT
I HAVE A BOYFRIEND,
THEY ASKED HIM TO DINNER.
AND?
THEY LOVED HIM!
THAT'S GOOD,
ISN'T IT?
BUT NOW MY PARENTS
WANNA MEET HIS PARENTS
AND WHEN THEY DO,
THEY'LL FIND OUT
HE'S DIFFERENT.
HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT TELLING
YOUR PARENTS THE TRUTH?
THEY'LL NEVER UNDERSTAND.
I TOLD OUR ENTIRE CHURCH
CONGREGATION
THAT I GOT BAPTIZED
BECAUSE OF A BOY,
AND DID YOUR PARENTS MAKE YOU
STOP HANGING OUT WITH ME?
NO.
THEY'RE REALLY UNDERSTANDING
PEOPLE,
AND THEY LOVE YOU.
MAYBE YOU DON'T NEED
TO LIE TO THEM.
(SIGHS)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
(Ooh-ooh-ooh)
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
ELI:
MY SHORT FILM SYNOPSIS
FOR YOUR PROOFING PLEASURE.
ONCE FAMED DIRECTOR BRET BARNETT
LOVES MY FILM -
WHICH HE WILL -
THAT REFERENCE LETTER'S MINE!
YOU WROTE THIS
THIS MORNING?
LAST NIGHT
AFTER I FINISHED EDITING.
YOU KNOW, YOUR STEPBROTHER
IS ACTUALLY PRETTY COOL.
HE HELPED ME GET OVER
MY WRITER'S BLOCK.
WHO KNEW WE'D HAVE SO MUCH
CREATIVE CHEMISTRY?
OH, WELL, MAYBE
YOU SHOULD BE DATING HIM.
HA!
OKAY. FIX THESE ERRORS
AND YOU ARE GOOD TO GO.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
THAT MANY CORRECTIONS?
IT READ PERFECTLY
LAST NIGHT.
SORRY.
GOOD LUCK IN CLASS.
(ELI SIGHS)
♪♪♪
(APPLAUSE)
ALL RIGHT.
WATCH OUT, SOFIA COPPOLA.
VERY NICE.
UP NEXT,
WE'VE GOT...
ELI.
LET'S CHECK IT OUT.
(TICKING)
OKAY.
JAKE ON SCREEN:
LOVE.
DESPAIR.
(CREEPY GROAN)
WHY?! WHY?
WHYYYYYYYYYYY?!
(DISTORTED)
WHYYYYYYYYYYYYYY?!
JAKE:
(CLAPS) THAT'S...
(CLEARS THROAT)
OKAY. I FEEL LIKE
I JUST WATCHED THE TAPE
FROM THE RING.
AM I GONNA DIE?
I FEEL LIKE I'M GONNA DIE.
UH... WHO'S-WHO'S ELI?
WHERE'S ELI?
AH, QUESTION GUY.
I CLEARLY SEE YOU DIDN'T TAKE
MY ADVICE ON STORY.
THERE WAS A STORY, UM,
ABOUT... LIFE.
OKAY, HOW DID ANY
OF THESE IMAGES
HAVE ANYTHING TO DO
WITH ANYBODY'S LIFE?
ELI:
IT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
ABOUT HOW UM...
LIFE HAS TWO SIDES?
IT'S ABSTRACT.
IT'S BRUTAL.
WELL, AT LEAST IT WASN'T
ABOUT LIPSTICK.
MARISOL:
IT WAS LIP-GLOSS,
EMO-BOY.
BRET:
MARISOL HAD SOME INSIGHT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU COULD LEARN A LOT FROM HER.
ALL RIGHT, WHO'S NEXT?
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
FIONA:
I KNOW DESIGNING YOUR OWN GOWN
IS A BIT RISKY,
BUT WITH YOUR BUDGET,
AND MY DESIGN SAVVY,
I THINK IT'S OUR BEST SHOT
AT THE PERFECT DRESS!
BIANCA:
AS FUN AS IT IS TO PLAY
PROJECT RUNWAY WITH YOU,
I'M NOT SURE I CAN GO THROUGH
WITH THIS.
FIONA:
OH, DON'T WORRY,
I'M NOT GONNA SEW IT MYSELF.
I KNOW A GREAT SEAMSTRESS-
BIANCA:
NOT THE DRESS,
THE WEDDING.
MAYBE AUDRA'S RIGHT.
MAYBE WE'RE TOO YOUNG
TO GET HITCHED.
FIONA:
DREW, TURN AROUND!
YOU CAN'T SEE
THE DRESS YET!
YOU'RE LETTING MY MOM
GET TO YOU.
FIONA:
DREW, I'M SERIOUS! TURN!
(KEYS CLINK)
BIANCA:
I COULDN'T SLEEP
LAST NIGHT.
I KEPT THINKING,
MAYBE WE SHOULD WAIT
A FEW YEARS.
CAN I TURN?
FIONA:
YEAH, TURN!
MY MOM
IS MANIPULATING YOU.
IS THAT HOW
YOU REALLY FEEL?
I DON'T KNOW.
I WANT TO MARRY YOU.
AND NOT IN A YEAR FROM NOW,
NOT IN FIVE YEARS FROM NOW,
BUT THIS SUMMER
LIKE WE'VE PLANNED.
I'LL LOVE YOU IN FIVE YEARS
JUST AS MUCH AS I DO NOW.
THE ONLY DIFFERENCE
IS YOUR MOM WON'T HATE ME.
SHE'LL GET OVER IT.
AND IF SHE DOESN'T?
WHAT IF I TALK TO HER FIRST,
WOMAN TO WOMAN?
FINE,
JUST DON'T GET
YOUR HOPES UP.
I LOVE YOU.
'TIL THE WORLD EXPLODES.
MOM, DAD,
THERE'S SOMETHING
I NEED TO TELL YOU.
MY BOYFRIEND, ADAM,
IS TRANS.
JENNA:
TRANS? LIKE TRANSIENT?
SWEETHEART,
ARE YOU SAYING ADAM'S HOMELESS?
ADAM:
HOMELESS?
THAT WAS BECKY'S REACTION
WHEN I TOLD HER.
HOMELESS?
REALLY, BECKY?
GUYS, THIS IS SERIOUS!
STAY IN CHARACTER,
PLEEEEASE!
CONTINUE, BUTTERCUP.
BECKY:
THANK YOU, DAD.
ADAM IS TRANSGENDER.
IT MEANS HE WAS BORN A GUY,
BUT HE GOT THE WRONG PARTS.
ARE YOU SURE
HE'S NOT JUST CONFUSED?
BECKY:
GOD DOESN'T MAKE MISTAKES.
HE MADE ADAM EXACTLY
WHO HE'S MEANT TO BE-
ADAM:
SO, A GIRL?
(SIGHS) I DON'T THINK
I CAN DO THIS.
YOU'RE DOING GREAT.
BECKY:
CAN I START AGAIN?
I GUESS WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY
IS I CARE ABOUT ADAM VERY MUCH.
THAT'S WHY I WANTED
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH.
BUT IT DOESN'T CHANGE ANYTHING.
ADAM IS A BOY.
PLEASE,
SOMEONE SAY SOMETHING.
DO YOU HATE ME?
NO, BUTTERCUP,
WE COULD NEVER HATE YOU.
OH, THANK GOODNESS.
I'M SO SORRY I LIED BEFORE.
I WAS WORRIED
YOU WOULDN'T APPROVE.
HONEY, WE LOVE YOU,
AND WANT YOU TO BE
THE HAPPIEST GIRL IN THE WORLD.
MR. BAKER:
I'M PROUD OF YOU
FOR TELLING US THE TRUTH;
THAT TAKES COURAGE.
DOES THAT MEAN
ADAM CAN COME OVER?
HE'S SUPPOSED TO HELP ME
WITH MY SPEECH
FOR THE FUNDRAISER.
(GIGGLES HAPPILY)
BIANCA:
SO I THOUGHT ABOUT
WHAT YOU SAID YESTERDAY.
REALLY, REALLY
THOUGHT ABOUT IT.
GLAD SOMEONE'S THINKING.
BIANCA:
AND I WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT COLLEGE
IS STILL THE PRIORITY
RIGHT NOW.
YEAH, AND AFTER
YOU GET YOUR DEGREE,
THEN YOU CAN TALK
ABOUT MARRIAGE.
NO. WE'RE STILL GETTING
MARRIED.
WE'RE IN LOVE.
BUT WE WON'T LET IT
AFFECT OUR FUTURE.
I PROMISE.
DREW ISN'T THINKING STRAIGHT
RIGHT NOW.
LOOK, THIS ISN'T LIKE BUYING
THAT MOTORCYCLE.
BIANCA...
(PATS COUCH CUSHION)
I KNOW HOW DIFFICULT
YOUR LIFE HAS BEEN,
AND I KNOW THAT YOU
HAVEN'T GROWN UP
WITH THE SAME PRIVILEGES
THAT DREW HAS,
THE STABILITY OF FAMILY.
WHAT DOES THAT HAVE TO DO
WITH ANYTHING?
YOU'RE LOOKING TO LATCH ON
TO SOMETHING.
SOMEONE.
BUT I WANT MORE FOR MY SON
THAN TO WORK AT THE MALL
AND BE TRAPPED IN
SOME TEEN MARRIAGE.
NOW I UNDERSTAND.
THANKS FOR THE COFFEE.
BECKY:
I DID IT.
I TOLD THEM,
AND THEY DIDN'T FLIP OUT
OR SCREAM.
THEY'RE REALLY OKAY
WITH THIS?
MY PARENTS WANT ME
TO BE HAPPY.
YOU MAKE ME HAPPY.
MR. BAKER:
ADAM. WELCOME.
IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
ADAM:
NICE TO SEE YOU TOO.
MR. BAKER:
I WAS HOPING,
BEFORE YOU TWO GET STARTED
ON YOUR FUNDRAISER WORK,
THAT WE COULD ALL HAVE
A QUICK CHAT.
PLEASE, TAKE A SEAT.
IS THERE ANYTHING
I CAN GET YOU?
SOME MILK? JUICE?
I'M GOOD, THANKS.
IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS
ABOUT THE WHOLE
TRANSGENDER THING,
I'M HAPPY TO ANSWER THEM
FOR YOU.
MY PARENTS TOOK A LONG TIME
TO WRAP THEIR HEADS AROUND IT.
MR. BAKER:
THAT WON'T BE NECESSARY, ADAM.
NOW, MRS. BAKER AND I WOULD
LIKE YOU BOTH TO KNOW
THAT WE'LL SUPPORT YOU
ON YOUR PATH TO HEALING.
HEALING?
MR. BAKER:
I WANT YOU TO CONSIDER
REPARATIVE THERAPY.
BECKY:
DAD, HOW COULD YOU?!
ADAM:
"GUARANTEED TO REPAIR YOUR
CHILD'S SEXUAL ORIENTATION."
I'M NOT GAY, SIR.
I'M A GUY.
YOU'RE CONFUSED,
BUT THIS WILL HELP.
THE LORD WILL LEAD THE WAY.
I DON'T NEED TO BE REPAIRED.
LET ME EXPLAIN-
LET ME EXPLAIN.
WE WANT WHAT'S BEST
FOR OUR DAUGHTER.
AND THAT'S
BRAINWASH CAMP?!
WATCH IT.
BECKY:
WAIT! ADAM, I'M SORRY.
(DOOR SLAMS)
I TRUSTED YOU.
WELCOME TO THE FIRST ANNUAL
DEGRASSI FUNDRAISER GALA!
THE SILENT AUCTION
ENDS AT EIGHT,
FOLLOWED BY OUR LIVE AUCTION
FOR OUR PREMIERE PRIZE:
A TRIP FOR SEVEN
TO LAS VEGAS!
AND STARTING IN A FEW MOMENTS,
WHILE YOU OPEN YOUR HEARTS
AND YOUR WALLETS,
YOU'LL BE ABLE ENJOY
THE MUSICAL STYLINGS
OF WHISPERHUG!
(APPLAUSE)
YOU OKAY?
EXHAUSTED.
I LOCKED MYSELF IN MY ROOM
LAST NIGHT,
CRIED A LOT.
DID YOU SORT ANYTHING OUT
WITH YOUR PARENTS?
I DIDN'T EVEN
TALK TO THEM.
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
THEY TRICKED US LIKE THAT.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS,
WE'LL GET THROUGH THIS.
TOGETHER.
I SHOULD HIT THE STAGE.
IF YOU WANT ANOTHER KISS,
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS ASK.
BECKY:
NO, LOOK.
ADAM:
NEED ME TO STAY?
I CAN STAY.
I'M A BIG GIRL;
I HAVE TO FACE THIS.
ADAM:
HEY! WE ARE WHISPERHUG!
(STUDENTS APPLAUD,
WHISPERHUG STARTS TO PLAY)
♪ TELL ME WHERE,
TELL ME WHEN ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE
UNTIL THE END ♪
♪ SAY THE WORD,
SAY IT LOUD ♪
♪ I'LL BE WAITIN' ♪
♪ UP UP IN A CLOUD ♪
BIANCA:
HAVE YOU SEEN DREW?
FIONA:
UM, HE'S AROUND,
TRYING HIS BEST NOT TO BID ON
ALL THE SPORTS GEAR.
I USED TO HAVE A DOZEN PAIRS
OF THESE SKIS -
A SET TO MATCH
EVERY SKI SUIT.
SO FRIVOLOUS!
I CAN'T EVEN BELIEVE
HOW MUCH I'VE CHANGED.
APPARENTLY,
I HAVEN'T CHANGED AT ALL.
AUDRA BASICALLY TOLD ME
THAT I WASN'T GOOD ENOUGH
FOR DREW.
SHE NEVER WANTS US
TO GET MARRIED.
"NEVER" NEVER?
AFTER EVERYTHING I'VE DONE
TO SHOW HER
HOW MUCH I'VE GROWN,
AND SHE STILL SEES ME
AS BAD-NEWS BIANCA.
MARRYING ME WOULD BE
THE BIGGEST MISTAKE
DREW COULD EVER MAKE.
OH GOD, I HATE THIS.
I DON'T CRY.
I HAVE TO ADMIT,
I HAD A CERTAIN PERCEPTION
OF YOU
BEFORE DREW MOVED IN.
THIS IS YOUR PEP TALK?
OKAY, LOOK.
WHO IS THIS WEDDING
REALLY ABOUT? AUDRA?
NO. ME AND DREW.
SO MAYBE THAT'S
ALL THAT MATTERS.
WANT ME TO HELP YOU
TRACK HIM DOWN?
ACTUALLY, COULD YOU HELP ME
WITH SOMETHING ELSE?
♪ I'LL MEET YOU THERE ♪
♪ I'LL MEET YOU WHEN ♪
♪ EVER YOU WANT TO BE
MORE THAN FRIENDS ♪
(PARENTS MURMURS QUIETLY)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
UM, WHY DON'T WE-
WE'LL SEE YOU IN A BIT?
WE'LL TALK IN A BIT,
OKAY?
WELL, I THOUGHT I BID
ON THOSE POWER TOOLS.
THEY'LL BE A GREAT HELP
WHEN WE BUILD HOMES
FOR THE NEEDY.
IF YOU'RE HERE TO BRING ME
BACK TO FLORIDA,
OR TO SEND ME TO DO THAT
BRAINWASHING STUFF,
YOU CAN TURN RIGHT AROUND
AND GO HOME.
THAT'S NOT WHY WE'RE HERE.
SO WHAT,
YOU'RE HERE TO DISOWN ME?
MRS. BAKER:
WE LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
ALL WE WANT FOR OUR LITTLE GIRL
IS TO SEE YOU HAPPY.
ADAM MAKES ME HAPPY.
WE KNOW YOU FEEL
THAT WAY NOW,
BUT HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT
WHAT A FUTURE WITH ADAM
WOULD BE LIKE?
MRS. BAKER:
DO YOU WANT TO HAVE KIDS?
OF COURSE I DO.
BECAUSE YOU COULDN'T
WITH ADAM.
I GUESS THERE'S ADOPTION.
SO MANY KIDS
NEED GOOD HOMES.
MRS. BAKER:
AND WHAT ABOUT YOUR FAITH?
ARE YOU READY TO GIVE UP
YOUR RELATIONSHIP WITH GOD?
I WOULD NEVER.
MR. BAKER:
BECKY, IN THE EYES OF GOD,
ADAM IS A GIRL.
YOU KNOW WHAT THE BIBLE SAYS
ABOUT HOMOSEXUALITY.
BUT ADAM'S A BOY.
BECKY, ADAM MAY DRESS
AND ACT LIKE A BOY,
BUT UNDERNEATH
ALL OF THAT ARMOR,
SHE IS A GIRL.
I HAVE TO ANNOUNCE THE WINNERS
FOR THE SILENT AUCTION SOON.
IF YOU WANNA BID,
YOU BETTER DO IT NOW.
♪ ...NEVER GONNA COME DOWN ♪
CLARE:
(SIGHS)
ELI, YOU'RE DWELLING.
MY ARTISTIC CAREER
IS OVER.
CLARE:
I'M SURE IT WASN'T THAT BAD.
LET ME SEE IT.
NO!
I DELETED IT.
NO ONE'S EVER SEEING THAT
PIECE OF JUNK EVER AGAIN.
YOU'RE OVERREACTING.
IT'S THE WORST THING
I'VE EVER SEEN
IN MY ENTIRE LIFE -
AND I MADE IT.
YOU JUST OVER-THOUGHT IT,
THAT'S ALL.
NO, I UNDER-THOUGHT IT.
I DON'T FOLLOW.
OKAY, I WAS FREAKING OUT
REALLY HARD
THE OTHER NIGHT
AND I DID SOMETHING REALLY,
REALLY STUPID...
STUPIDER THAN CASTING
MY STEPBROTHER
AS THE LEAD
IN YOUR SHORT FILM?
I SMOKED WEED WITH JAKE.
YOU WHAT?
I KNOW - SO DUMB.
I'M LUCKY
I DIDN'T GET CAUGHT.
YOU'RE LUCKY IT DIDN'T
MESS WITH YOUR MEDS!
I PANICKED!
I JUST WANTED
TO IMPRESS BRET.
HE'S NEVER GONNA WRITE ME
THAT REFERENCE LETTER NOW.
WAIT.
JAKE SMOKES MARIJUANA?!
CLARE, FOCUS.
IF I CAN'T FIGURE OUT
A TWO MINUTE SHORT,
HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO SURVIVE NYU?
THE DIRECTING PROGRAM'S
REALLY TOUGH.
WHAT IF ROMEO AND JULES
IS THE BEST THING I EVER DO?
OKAY.
WHAT DOES ALFRED SAY
TO BATMAN?
WHY DO WE FALL DOWN,
MASTER WAYNE?
SO WE CAN PICK OURSELVES
BACK UP.
OKAY, BUT WHAT IF
I'M NOT GOOD ENOUGH?
ELI,
YOU CAN DO ANYTHING.
EVEN IF YOU DON'T
KNOW IT YET,
I DO.
C'MON, I KNOW SOMETHING
THAT'LL HELP.
THAT'S WHAT JAKE SAID.
BECKY:
A BIG ROUND OF APPLAUSE
FOR WHISPERHUG!
(APPLAUSE)
NOW THE LIVE BIDDING
FOR THE BIG PRIZE:
AIRPLANE TICKETS
TO LAS VEGAS.
WHO WILL BE OUR LUCKY SEVEN?
DO I HEAR ONE THOUSAND?
I'M SORRY.
I'VE BEEN OBSESSING
OVER YOUR MOM TOO MUCH.
NO, I'M SORRY.
I GET IT.
SHE'S IMPORTANT TO YOU.
NO.
BECK:
ONE THOUSAND SEVEN HUNDRED!
DO I HEAR TWO THOUSAND?
YES, AND I SHOULD
HAVE LISTENED.
IF YOU NEED AUDRA'S
APPROVAL-
SCREW AUDRA!
DREW:
OKAY, WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
TWO THOUSAND FIVE HUNDRED?
THREE THOUSAND!
THREE THOUSAND -
GOING ONCE, GOING TWICE...
SOLD TO FIONA COYNE!
(APPLAUSE)
THANK YOU, EVERYONE,
FOR YOUR GENEROUS DONATIONS!
AND HERE'S WHISPERHUG
TO PLAY US...
THREE THOUSAND DOLLARS?
FIONA DOESN'T HAVE
THAT KIND OF MONEY.
THAT'S WHY YOU NEED
TO WRITE HER A CHEQUE.
WHAT?
I DON'T WANNA WAIT
FIVE YEARS,
OR EVEN 'TIL SUMMER.
I WANNA MARRY YOU
ON SPRING BREAK,
IN LAS VEGAS,
IN FRONT OF FIVE FRIENDS,
NO MATTER WHAT
AUDRA SAYS.
SCREW AUDRA.
SCREW AUDRA!
WE'RE...
WE'RE GETTING MARRIED!
♪ ...WHO YOU REALLY ARE ♪
(CRYING)
WE RAISED FIFTEEN GRAND!
CRUSHED OUR GOAL.
YOU SHOULD BE HAPPY!
I SHOULD GET THOSE
VEGAS TICKETS TO FIONA.
ADAM HAD THEM
FOR SAFE-KEEPING.
DO YOU SEE HIS BAG?
WHOA! THOSE AREN'T
TEARS OF JOY, ARE THEY?
I WISH EVERYTHING
WASN'T SO COMPLICATED.
HONEY...
I'LL BE FINE.
UH, JUST HELP ME
FIND THE BAG.
HERE IT IS.
OH...
WHAT'S WRONG?
BOYS DON'T GET
THEIR PERIODS.
♪♪♪
♪ All the reasons are good ♪
♪ To be free ♪
♪ We swore we'd see it coming
but we didn't ♪
♪ Ah-ah-ahhh ♪
♪ Another along the way ♪
♪ What a feeling ♪
♪ So kiss me
like you never did ♪
♪ Hold me like
you'll never leave ♪
♪ Make sure it'll never end ♪
NOW THAT'S A SHORT!
YEAH.
IT'S ABOUT MY GIRLFRIEND.
I'M LEAVING NEXT YEAR,
AND SHE'S STAYING HERE.
YEAH, AND YOU'RE SCARED ABOUT
HOW YOU'LL FARE WITHOUT HER.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M ACTUALLY KINDA
TERRIFIED.
HOW'D YOU KNOW THAT?
YOU JUST TOLD ME.
SO SIMPLE,
SO EFFECTIVE.
GOOD ENOUGH FOR NYU?
I'M HOPING TO GO THERE
NEXT YEAR.
THAT'S VERY COMPETITIVE.
WELL, A REFERENCE LETTER
FROM ONE OF ITS MOST SUCCESSFUL
ALUMNUS WOULD HELP.
YEAH, I DON'T NORMALLY DO
THAT SORT OF THING.
IT'S OKAY.
I UNDERSTAND.
BUT YOU TOOK MY CRITICISM
TO HEART,
AND YOU CAME BACK
AND PROVED YOURSELF.
I THINK NYU WOULD BE LUCKY
TO HAVE YOU.
WOW. UH...
THAT'S-THAT'S AMAZING!
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY!
PERHAPS IT'S BEST JUST TO QUIT
WHILE YOU'RE AHEAD.
(BELL RINGS,
STUDENTS CHATTER)
FIONA:
A BIG CONGRATULATIONS GOES OUT
TO THE STUDENT COUNCIL
AND THE FUNDRAISING COMMITTEE.
WE RAISED A WHOPPING
FIFTEEN THOUSAND DOLLARS
FOR THE SCHOOL!
ADAM:
HEY.
HOW ARE YOU?
NOT WELL.
A MESS, ACTUALLY.
I'VE DECIDED TO ACCEPT
MY PARENTS' HELP.
I'M GOING TO TRY
THE THERAPY.
WHAT?!
I CAN'T CHOOSE YOU
OVER MY FAMILY,
MY FAITH.
THIS IS CRAP!
YOU DON'T NEED TO BE FIXED.
YOU'RE PERFECT.
I'M NOT.
I'M CONFUSED.
YOU CONFUSED ME.
IF THERAPY COULD WORK,
I HAVE TO TRY.
IT'S FOR THE BEST.
BECKY, PLEASE.
I'M SORRY, ADAM.
(SLAMS HIS LOCKER)
(CRYING)