IN SUMMARY, MY INTERNSHIP
AT THE "TORONTO INTERPRETER"
WAS...
-IS A VALUABLE LEARNING
OPPORTUNITY.
ANY QUESTIONS?
MS. OH:
WHAT'S THE MOST IMPORTANT THING
YOUR MENTOR TAUGHT YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
ASHER:
CLARE.
STOP IT PLEASE.
CLARE, NO ONE HAS TO KNOW.
CLARE:
NO, I'M-
ASHER:
CLARE, YOU'RE OVERREACTING!
IF YOU CARE ABOUT YOUR CAREER,
YOU'LL KEEP YOUR MOUTH SHUT!
MS. OH:
CLARE?
SORRY, COULD YOU REPEAT
THE QUESTION?
MS. OH:
WHAT DID YOU LEARN
FROM ASHER SHOSTAK?
THAT NO ONE WILL BELIEVE
YOUR STORY
UNLESS YOU HAVE FACTS
TO BACK IT UP.
(BELL RINGS)
ALLI:
WELL, YOU MANAGED TO FAKE
YOUR WAY THROUGH THAT ONE.
CLARE:
I CAN'T TELL MS. OH I GOT FIRED
UNTIL I HAVE PROOF
THAT ASHER SEXUALLY HARASSED ME,
AND THE ONLY WAY TO DO THAT IS-
ALLI:
FIND ANOTHER VICTIM,
BUT WHAT IF YOU DON'T?
YOU'VE ALREADY TALKED
TO THE LAST FIVE INTERNS!
CLARE:
MAYBE NUMBER SIX
WILL BE THE CHARM.
LOOK, I'VE GOTTA HIDE OUT
BEFORE SOMEONE SEES ME.
ALLI:
CLARE, THIS ISN'T LIKE YOU.
HIDING OUT, OBSESSING.
ONCE I FIX THIS, EVERYTHING
WILL GO BACK TO NORMAL.
OKAY?
(SCOFFS)
WHOA! ARE YOU CHASING
A CRIMINAL?
(HALF LAUGHS)
I'M...I'M JUST REALLY
LATE FOR CO-OP,
AND I FORGOT SOMETHING
IN MY LOCKER,
SO I HAVE TO GO.
OH WELL,
CAN I GET A KISS
BEFORE YOU GO SPEND
ALL YOUR TIME
WITH ASHER "PIERCING
BLUE EYES" SHOSTAK?
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
OH, THAT'S IT?
RIP OFF!
I'M SORRY,
I'M JUST SO LATE!
(DOOR CLICKS)
(DOOR SLAMS)
(SIGHS)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
MRS. COHEN:
OR YOU CAN USE ETHANOL
INSTEAD OF WATER.
YOU CAN JUST GENTLY...
SWIRL IT LIKE THAT.
(STUDENTS TALK QUIETLY)
HEY!
HOW DID YOU GET PAST SECURITY
WITHOUT YOUR ID TAG?
DREW:
WELL, OFFICER TURNER AND I
GO WAY BACK.
WHAT'S UP, BRO?
IONIC COVALENT BONDING.
YEAH, IT SOUNDS BORING.
BIANCA:
IT IS, BUT MY STUDY BUDDY CLOWN
IS KEEPING ME ENTERTAINED.
OWEN:
OH, YEAH.
WHAT'S UP?
PISTONS TICKETS?
DREW:
I THOUGHT WE COULD DRIVE
DOWN THERE TOMORROW,
MAYBE HIT UP AN OUTLET MALL,
STAY IN A HOTEL ROOM...
SETTLE DOWN, BIG SPENDER.
WELL, I GOT MY FIRST COMMISSION
CHEQUE LAST NIGHT.
AND LET'S JUST SAY
I AM FLUSH WITH CASH.
IT SOUNDS AWESOME BUT I HAVE A
HUGE CHEMISTRY TEST THIS WEEK.
REALLY?
COME ON,
I NEVER SEE YOU ANYMORE.
WELL, WE STARTED
A STUDY GROUP,
SO WE'RE ALL GONNA BE WORKING
AT THE LOFT TOMORROW.
DOES THAT COUNT?
YEAH, I GUESS.
MRS. COHEN:
AHEM!
DREW TORRES, YOU'RE NO LONGER
A STUDENT HERE,
GOODBYE!
OWEN:
HEY BRO, DON'T WORRY.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF YOUR GIRL
WHILE YOU'RE AT WORK.
(OWEN AND BIANCA SNICKER)
BIANCA:
STOP!
MADAM.
CLARE:
JENNIFER?
HI, UM MY NAME IS CLARE,
I LEFT YOU A BUNCH
OF VOICEMAILS?
OKAY, YEAH UM,
SO AS I SAID,
I JUST HAVE A COUPLE
QUESTIONS FOR YOU
ABOUT YOUR INTERNSHIP
WITH "THE INTERPRETER."
HOCKEY PLAYERS:
(HOLLERING AND LAUGHING)
YEAAAAAAH!
YEAH! I'M READY!
AWESOME.
OH...HEY.
UH, CAN YOU CLEAR OUT?
I WAS HERE FIRST.
LUKE:
HEY, WHATEVER.
PLAYER:
LET'S GO, LET'S GO.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
IT'S HAPPY HOUR.
IT'S ELEVEN AM!
WISH MY MOM TAUGHT ME
HOW TO TELL TIME!
(GUYS HOLLER)
DALLAS:
YEAH, BUDDY!
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
SORRY, UH, MY PHONE CUT OUT.
YOU GONNA BRING BLONDIE
IN HERE, BAKER?
I MIGHT, I MIGHT.
LUKE:
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU HAVE ANY LUCK
WITH DEGRASSI GIRLS.
THAT'S BECAUSE DEGRASSI GIRLS
BE CRAZY.
OKAY, HI.
I'M ON THE PHONE HERE,
DO YOU MIND?
DO YOU WANT ONE?
MIGHT LOOSEN YOU UP
A LITTLE BIT.
DALLAS:
HEY, LET HER BE.
CLARE:
OH!
YOU CAN MEET ME RIGHT NOW?
THAT'S GREAT, I WILL TEXT YOU
THE ADDRESS RIGHT AWAY.
THANK YOU.
AWW, DON'T LEAVE US!
SORRY, I'VE GOT A BIGGER
CHAUVINIST PIG TO ROAST.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO,
LET'S CHUG THIS.
DAVE AND TRISTAN:
♪ IT WON'T TAKE
ANOTHER SUMMER, ♪
♪ ANOTHER SPRING,
ANOTHER FALL, ♪
♪ NOT A MOMENT LONGER! ♪
DAVE AND TRISTAN:
♪ AND NOW I HAVE YOU... ♪
TORI:
♪ COME, WE MUST GO! ♪
DAVE AND TRISTAN:
♪ DON'T NEED ANYTHING
AT ALL... ♪
SAVE IT FOR THE STAGE,
KISSY-FACE!
BREAK TIME!
TORI:
DAVE, YOU'RE NAILING
ROMEO TODAY!
YOU'RE VERY TALENTED.
DAVE:
ARE YOU FLIRTING WITH ME?
NO! I HAVE A ROCK STAR
BOYFRIEND.
I HAVE A GIRLFRIEND.
TORI:
ARE YOU STILL GOING OUT
WITH ALLI BHANDARI?
SHE NEVER COMES BY REHEARSALS.
UH, SHE'S FAST-TRACKING
TO GRADUATE THIS YEAR.
IT'S A LOT OF EXTRA
SCHOOL WORK.
O M TO THE G!
PIZZA SO PIZZA JUST TWEETED,
THEY'RE HOLDING
A CONTEST AT THE MALL.
AND THE PRIZE
IS A GUEST ROLE
ON "WEST DRIVE!"
I'M DYING!
I'M SO DEAD!
DEAD!
UH, WE SHOULD ALL GO TOGETHER.
I CAN DRIVE.
AW GUYS, I LOVE
OUR CAST SHOWMANCE!
ME TOO!
BUT YOU LOSERS KNOW I'M
LANDING THIS GUEST ROLE.
NO, HELL NO,
IT'S TOTALLY MINE.
(GIGGLES)
DELUDED MUCH?
IT'S SO MINE!
THANKS FOR MEETING ME,
JENNIFER.
I FOUND A TON
OF YOUR ARTICLES ONLINE.
HOW DID YOU BECOME
SO SUCCESSFUL SO YOUNG?
HARD WORK, DEDICATION,
PLUS, A GLOWING REFERENCE
LETTER FROM ASHER SHOSTAK
OPENS A LOT OF DOORS.
YOU INTERNED DURING YOUR
SENIOR YEAR OF HIGH SCHOOL?
YEP, AND THROUGH UNIVERSITY.
AFTER THAT, I GOT HIRED
FULL TIME.
DID YOU WORK CLOSELY
WITH ASHER?
UM...
I FACT-CHECKED,
SHADOWED MOST
OF HIS INTERVIEWS,
ASSISTED WITH EDITING.
DID YOU EVER STAY LATE?
SURE. SOMETIMES.
DID YOU EXPERIENCE ANY...
INAPPROPRIATE BEHAVIOR?
BY ANYONE?
BY ASHER?
YOU SAID THIS IS FOR
A CLASS PRESENTATION?!
IT'S ON SEXUAL HARASSMENT
IN THE WORKPLACE.
JENNIFER:
OH MY GOD,
YOU'RE CLARE EDWARDS.
THAT INTERN THAT GOT FIRED!
NO WAIT, PLEASE, I JUST NEED
TO KNOW IF YOU EVER-
NO! NOTHING LIKE THAT
EVER HAPPENED TO ME
AT "THE INTERPRETER."
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(BELL RINGS)
CLARE:
JENNIFER WAS THE LAST
OF ASHER'S INTERNS.
I'M AT A DEAD-END.
ALLI:
SO, PLEASE SAY YOU'LL TELL
MS. OH NOW.
AFTER ALL THIS TIME,
WILL SHE EVEN BELIEVE ME?
I MESSED UP NOT REPORTING
ASHER RIGHT AWAY.
NOW HE'S JUST GONNA TAKE
EVERYTHING I SAY,
AND TWIST IT AROUND
SO IT'S MY FAULT ONCE AGAIN.
I'M TRAPPED.
WELL, WHAT ABOUT ELI?
HE'S A WEEK FROM
OPENING NIGHT,
IT'LL JUST UPSET HIM.
YEAH, BUT HE'LL BE EVEN
MORE UPSET
ONCE HE FINDS OUT
THAT YOU'VE LIED.
(SIGHS)
CLARE:
I JUST WANT THIS SO BAD.
ASHER:
WELL, I'M HAPPY TO TEACH
WHEN THE STUDENT IS AS EAGER
AS YOU ARE.
CLARE:
I AM VERY, VERY EAGER.
YOU OKAY?
NO, I AM NOT.
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU COULD
USE A BEER.
LET'S GO.
HAVE A GREAT DAY.
WHAT BUG CRAWLED UP YOUR BUTT?
I STOPPED BY MY HIGH SCHOOL
THE OTHER DAY,
AND I JUST-
I FELT SO OUT OF THE LOOP
WITH EVERYTHING.
MY CLASSES, MY FRIENDS.
YOUR CRAZY-HOT GIRLFRIEND?
IT MUST BE HARD TO SEE HER
SURROUNDED BY GUYS
WHO HAVEN'T DROPPED OUT.
DO YOU THINK BIANCA
THINKS I'M A LOSER?
UH, NO!
HOW COULD SHE?
YOU'VE GOT THE CASH MONEY.
SPOIL HER!
WELL, I PLANNED
AN OVERNIGHT TRIP,
BUT SHE COULDN'T DO IT.
THERE'S MORE THAN ONE WAY TO
SPLASH YOUR MONEY AROUND, DT.
YOU COULD BUY HER A MOTORCYCLE.
NO, TOO DANGEROUS.
A HOVERCRAFT.
TOO RIDICULOUS.
A PONY!
WAIT, WHY ARE YOU STUCK
ON MODES OF TRANSPORTATION?
I DON'T KNOW,
IT'S MY GO-TO.
WELL, BIANCA'S HOLDING
A STUDY GROUP
AT MY PLACE TODAY.
I'VE GOTTA DO SOMETHING
WHILE SHE'S THERE
TO PROVE TO HER
I'M NOT A LOSER.
OOH.
(SIGHS)
DAVE:
HEY CATHERINE,
YOUR HEATHCLIFF HAS A REQUEST.
THIS BOOK IS TORTURE.
WHY SO MANY PAGES?
DOES EMILY BRONTE
HAVE ANY IDEA
JUST HOW MUCH GRADE 12
CALCULUS HOMEWORK I HAVE?
SO THEY'RE HAVING
A TALENT CONTEST
TONIGHT AT THE MALL,
AND THE WINNER GETS
A GUEST ROLE ON "WEST DRIVE."
COME CHEER ME ON?
UM...I HAVE...
OH, FORGET IT.
LOOK I'M SORRY,
MAYBE YOU CAN COME OVER
TO MY PLACE AFTERWARDS,
AND GIVE ME A MINUTE
BY MINUTE RECAP?
WHAT TIME?
AFTER I'M DONE
MY READING,
I'LL TEXT YOU
IF IT'LL WORK.
(SIGHS)
AND APPARENTLY,
HE'S HAD SIX INTERNS,
BUT I'M THE ONLY ONE
HE'S EVER TRIED TO KISS,
BUT MAYBE NOT.
MAYBE I'M THE ONLY ONE
WHO COMPLAINED ABOUT IT,
SO I'M THE ONLY ONE
WHO GOT FIRED.
EVERY OTHER GIRL JUST TOOK
THE REFERENCE LETTER,
AND WENT MERRILY
ON THEIR MERRY WAY.
DALLAS:
HMM. THAT SOUNDS INTENSE.
AND YOUR BOYFRIEND KNOWS
NOTHING ABOUT IT?
(GULPS)
NO... NO,
HE WOULD LOSE IT.
HMM.
(DRUNKEN GIGGLE)
YOU DON'T DRINK
VERY MUCH, DO YOU?
CLARE:
NO, NOT- NOT EVER, NO.
I'M DRINKING AT SCHOOL,
THAT IS NOT GOOD.
I SHOULDN'TVE TOLD YOU
ALL THAT STUFF,
I'M JUST GONNA STOP TALKING.
TALKING IS OVERRATED.
I HEARD THAT.
AAAH!
OH! WHAT THE-
WHAT THE HELL?!
CLARE: YOU'RE SO GROSS!
WHY WOULD YOU THINK
THAT WE WOULD...
YOU KICKED OFF YOUR SHOES!
AND THAT'S SOME SECRET CODE
FOR LET'S MAKE OUT?!
UNBELIEVABLE!
YOU INVITE ME
INTO A SECRET ROOM,
GET HAMMERED OFF
OF ONE BEER,
AND I'M UNBELIEVABLE?!
CLARE:
UGH!
(SIGHS)
♪♪♪
♪ I'm living
on a bullet train ♪
♪ Spending every day
goin' insane ♪
♪ Livin' like Coltrane ♪
♪ Tryin' to keep up with
the latest sensations ♪
JAKE:
OKAY, SO I'LL START SWEEPING,
AND YOU CAN ORGANIZE
THE PLANTS
THAT NEED TO BE RE-POTTED.
KATIE:
OH OKAY,
ANYTHING ELSE, BOSSY?
YEAH, ONE MORE THING.
UH, HEY.
AREN'T YOU SUPPOSED
TO BE AT CO-OP?
UM...IT WAS CANCELLED TODAY.
ANYWAY, I'VE GOTTA GO!
BUT YOU GUYS ARE CUTE.
BYE!
UH, WHERE ARE YOUR SHOES?
AND WHY DO YOU SMELL
LIKE BEER?
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
♪ Goin' out of my head ♪
♪ I'm goin' out
goin' out ♪
♪ Going out of my head ♪
CLARE:
AND THEN HE TRIED
TO KISS ME,
LIKE HE COULD GET AWAY WITH IT,
WITH ANYTHING.
EXCUSE ME, I HAVE TO GO
KILL A GUY.
UH WAIT, WHAT?
NO, NO, DALLAS IS HARMLESS.
HARMLESS?
CLARE, LOOK WHAT HE DID!
MIKE DALLAS WRECKED
THIS PLACE?
YEAH, HIM AND HIS
HOCKEY GOONS.
WELL, WHAT IS SIMPSON
DOING ABOUT IT?
WELL, WE HAVEN'T
TOLD HIM YET,
WE HAVE NO PROOF, IT WOULD
JUST BE A WILD ACCUSATION
THAT DALLAS CAN DENY.
LET'S SEE HOW HE DENIES IT
AFTER I REARRANGE HIS FACE.
KATIE:
THAT'S NOT GONNA DO ANYTHING
EXCEPT GET YOU IN TROUBLE.
JAKE:
YEAH, BUT WE HAVE
TO DO SOMETHING.
(CAMERA BEEPS)
MY JOURNALISM SENSES
ARE TINGLING.
THAT COULD BE THE BEER.
THE HOCKEY PLAYERS NEED TO BE
HELD ACCOUNTABLE FOR THIS.
THEY'RE NOT ABOVE THE RULES,
AND I'M GONNA MAKE SURE
EVERYBODY KNOWS IT.
JAKE:
HOW?
AN INTERVIEW,
WITH YOU, ON THE RECORD.
HMM.
(BELL RINGS)
♪♪♪
TORI:
♪ YOU DON'T HAVE
TO DO ANYTHING, ♪
♪ SOMETIMES WRONG
CAN FEEL SO RIGHT ♪
♪♪♪
(PHONE BEEPS)
♪ DON'T DO ANYTHING ♪
(CROWD APPLAUDS)
VERY GOOD.
NEXT!
YOU'RE UP, DAVE!
HERE'S A LITTLE SOMETHING
I COOKED UP
ON A DEEJAY APP
LAST NIGHT.
♪ YOU ARE THE SUN ♪
♪ THE MOON IN THE NIGHT, ♪
♪ YOU ARE MY EVERYTHING, ♪
♪ EVERYTHING'S SO RIGHT... ♪
(MUSIC WARPS INTO BEATS)
(RAPPING)
♪ I DON'T NEED ANOTHER SPRING, ♪
♪ I DON'T NEED ANOTHER FALL, ♪
♪ GIRL, IF I'VE GOT YOU, ♪
♪ YEAH, THEN I GOT IT ALL. ♪
(CROWD CHEERS)
♪♪♪
(CROWD CHEERS AND CLAPS)
DONE!
(APPLAUSE)
(STUDY GROUP CHATTERS)
DREW: HEY GUYS!
IMOGEN: HEY.
HOLY CANNELLONI!
FIONA:
WHAT'S HAPPENING ON MY WALL?
WELL YOU KNOW WHAT, I THOUGHT
WE NEEDED A NEW TV.
SO, ARE YOU GUYS READY TO GET
YOUR 3D ON?
OH DUDE, SICK!
DREW:
YEAH, I KNOW.
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE STUDYING.
WHAT, YOU CAN'T STUDY
AND WATCH MOTOCROSS
IN THE BACKGROUND?
AND THE FOREGROUND?
(LAUGHS)
WOW.
IT'S LIKE I'M ACTUALLY
RIGHT THERE!
YEAH, I KNOW.
ALL RIGHT GUYS, GET READY,
BECAUSE I HAVE TONS OF SNACKS!
BIANCA:
IT'S SO AWESOME.
IT'S REALLY COOL.
OWEN:
WOW, IT IS THE LIKE BIKE
IS COMING OUT OF THE SCREEN.
(FIONA LAUGHS)
♪♪♪
♪ Being a woman's
not being a man ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Not being lost
in no man's land ♪
♪♪♪
(KEYS CLICK)
ELI:
THANKS FOR WAITING FOR ME
TO FINISH TECH REHEARSAL.
THE JANITOR'S LOOKING
TO LOCK UP THE SCHOOL.
ALMOST DONE HERE.
ELI:
WHOA!
THOSE ARE SOME SERIOUS
ACCUSATIONS.
CLARE:
WITH BULLETPROOF FACTS
TO BACK THEM UP.
I HAVE JAKE AND KATIE'S
STATEMENTS,
PLUS I FOUND TWO GRADE 12 GIRLS
WHO SAW DALLAS AND LUKE
LEAVE THE GARDEN
RIGHT AFTER THE VANDALISM.
YOU MIGHT MAKE SOME SERIOUS
ENEMIES WITH THIS, CLARE.
CLARE:
THE ICE HOUNDS ACT
LIKE THEY'RE UNTOUCHABLE.
800 COPIES OF THIS WILL PROVE
THAT THEY'RE NOT.
♪♪♪
♪ So act like a woman
if you can ♪
OKAY, CAN I PLEASE HAVE
NUMBER THREE,
NUMBER TWENTY FIVE,
AND NUMBER SEVENTEEN,
STEP FORWARD.
CONGRATULATIONS,
YOU ARE OUR FINALISTS.
(APPLAUSE)
JUDGE:
YOU EACH WIN A PIZZA SO PIZZA
PLATINUM CUSTOMER CARD,
THAT GETS YOU FREE SLICES
FOR A WHOLE YEAR!
(APPLAUSE)
ALL RIGHT, AND NOW...
THE WINNER OF THE GUEST
STARRING ROLE
ON AN UPCOMING EPISODE
OF "WEST DRIVE" IS...
NUMBER SEVENTEEN, DAVE TURNER!
(APPLAUSE AND CHEERING)
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
YAAAY!
SO, PIZZA SLICES ON DAVE?
YEAH, SURE!
GONNA CALL ALLI
TO COME JOIN US?
NAH LOOK, IF SHE WANTED
TO BE HERE,
SHE'D BE HERE ALREADY.
LET'S GO CELEBRATE!
RIGHT ON!
YOU'RE GONNA BE ON
THE "WEST DRIVE!"
ZIG:
THAT WAS AMAZING!
(BIKES RUMBLE)
IMOGEN:
IT'S LIKE I'M RIDING THE BIKE!
WHOA, IT IS WAY LATER
THAN I THOUGHT.
BUT WE DIDN'T STUDY
AT ALL.
OH, I'VE GOTTA JETTISON TOO.
DREW: ALL RIGHT, BUDDY.
OWEN: HEY, DREW.
GUYS, WHAT ABOUT
THE CHEM TEST?
GUESS WE'RE WINGING IT.
OWEN:
SEE 'YA.
DREW.
NOW IT'S FRISKY TIME!
NO, IT'S POUNDING
ENERGY DRINKS
AND CRAMMING ALL NIGHT
BY MYSELF TIME!
COME ON, JUST STAY,
IT'S ONE TEST.
BIANCA:
ONE FLUNKED TEST MIGHT MEAN
NO UNIVERSITY FOR ME.
CAN YOU PLEASE STOP TALKING
ABOUT SCHOOL FOR ONE SECOND?
IT'S A BIT OF A DRAG.
NO, IT'S CALLED GROWING UP.
WELL, I'M MAKING MONEY,
YOU SHOULD BE HAPPY.
I SHOULD BE HAPPY
THAT YOU DROPPED OUT?
SO THERE IT IS,
YOU THINK I'M A LOSER.
NO, I THINK YOU
MADE A MISTAKE.
ONE THAT YOU CAN UNDO.
AND HOW'S THAT?
MAKE UP WITH YOUR MOM,
MOVE HOME,
AND COME BACK TO SCHOOL!
DREW:
YOU'RE SERIOUS?
THE ONLY WAY YOU'LL BE HAPPY IS
IF I DO EVERYTHING THAT I HATE?
I'M JUST WORRIED
ABOUT YOU, DREW.
AUDRA SAID THAT-
"AUDRA SAID?"
OH SO, YOU AND MY MOM
ARE TALKING BEHIND MY BACK?
WELL, THAT'S JUST GREAT!
OKAY,
I NEED TO GO STUDY,
CAN WE JUST TALK ABOUT THIS
TOMORROW, PLEASE?
DREW:
WHY BOTHER?
I'M PRETTY CLEAR
ON WHERE YOU STAND.
♪♪♪
YOU WANTED TO SEE ME, SIR?
I WANNA TALK TO YOU
ABOUT THIS ARTICLE.
I WROTE THE TRUTH,
THEY RUINED THE GARDEN.
THAT'S OUTRAGEOUS!
JAKE MARTIN AND KATIE MATLIN
SPOKE TO ME ON THE RECORD.
DALLAS:
YOUR STEP-BROTHER,
AND THE DISGRACED EX-PRESIDENT.
RELIABLE SOURCES!
KATIE'S HAD A VENDETTA
AGAINST US SINCE DAY ONE,
AND FRANKLY, MY TEAM'S
STARTING TO HATE THIS SCHOOL.
DALLAS, I APOLOGIZE.
BUT I HAVE PROOF!
EYEWITNESS STATEMENTS,
AND PHOTOS OF THE BEER
IN THE PROPS ROOM!
OF EMPTY CANS,
NOT MY GUYS!
I PERSONALLY SAW THEM
BRING ALCOHOL
ONTO THE SCHOOL PROPERTY,
AND DRINK IT!
YOU WERE ENJOYING THEM
YOURSELF JUST FINE YESTERDAY!
SO YOU ADMIT THE BEER
WAS YOURS?
FINE, YES.
BUT NOT THE GARDEN.
IT'S CALLED REASONABLE DOUBT.
(SIGHS) DAMN.
MR. SIMPSON:
THIS ARTICLE WAS PUBLISHED
WITHOUT MY PERMISSION.
YOU'LL SERVE ONE WEEK
DETENTION.
AND THEN ANOTHER TWO WEEKS
FOR DRINKING ON SCHOOL PROPERTY.
YOU CAN GO NOW.
DALLAS, LET'S MAKE A CALL
TO YOUR COACH.
(SIGHS)
♪ Call a doctor ♪
♪ Check my pulse ♪
(BIKE ENGINE ROARS)
♪ Ears are ringing ♪
♪ But I feel no pain ♪
♪ Just the sweet sensation
running through my veins ♪
BIANCA'S VOICEMAIL:
HEY, IT'S BIANCA,
LEAVE A MESSAGE.
HEY BIANCA, GOOD LUCK
ON YOUR BORING CHEM TEST.
I SPENT MY DAY
GETTING MY M1 LICENSE,
AND BUYING A MOTORCYCLE.
SO, SUPER BUSY BEING AWESOME!
BYE.
(SIREN BLARES)
MY ARTICLE WORKED!
SIMPSON AND THE ICE
HOUNDS COACH
ARE DOLING OUT PUNISHMENTS
AS WE SPEAK.
KATIE:
WAIT, JUSTICE ACTUALLY
PREVAILED?
JAKE:
I'M STUNNED!
THANKS, CLARE.
AND HERE COMES THE BACKLASH.
DALLAS:
CONGRATULATIONS.
THREE WEEKS DETENTION
FOR OUR STARTING LINE-UP,
MEANING WE MISS THREE GAMES.
WITH OUR STAR
ROOKIE INJURED,
WE CAN PROBABLY KISS
A PLAYOFF SPOT GOODBYE!
OH, DON'T BE ALL DEFEATIST.
EVER HEARD OF A COMEBACK?
YOU SCREWED US OVER!
KATIE:
YEAH WELL, NOW YOU KNOW
WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO HAVE SOMETHING YOU CARE
ABOUT TAKEN AWAY FROM YOU.
AREN'T YOU TWO
JUST THE CUTEST?!
I DID NOTHING TO YOU!
YOU MESS WITH MY FRIENDS,
YOU MESS WITH ME.
JUST BACK OFF, DALLAS.
IT'S OVER.
YOU LIKE TO AIR OTHER PEOPLE'S
DIRTY LAUNDRY IN PUBLIC?
HOW WOULD YOUR BOYFRIEND HERE
LIKE TO KNOW YOURS?
WHAT'S HE TALKING ABOUT?
UH, DALLAS FOUND OUT
THAT UM...
I GOT FIRED FROM
"THE INTERPRETER"
A FEW WEEKS AGO.
SEE, I KNEW THERE WAS
SOMETHING GOING ON WITH YOU.
WHAT HAPPENED?
ASHER UH...
HE...
DIDN'T THINK
I WAS GOOD ENOUGH.
HE SAID I WAS A BAD WRITER.
BUT THAT DOESN'T MAKE
ANY SENSE.
I THOUGHT WRITING
THIS ARTICLE
AND EXPOSING THE HOCKEY TEAM
WOULD HELP ME GET OVER IT,
BUT IT DIDN'T,
I FEEL WORSE.
WHAT CAN I DO?
YOU CAN'T DO ANYTHING.
NO ONE CAN.
(BELL RINGS)
I HAVE MATH.