(LOW HUM OF EXCITED CHATTER)
(DRILL WHIRS,
HAMMER BANGS)
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
I THINK SHE MIXED UP
OUR COSTUMES.
I COULD ALWAYS EAT
A BUNCH.
JUST SWITCH.
ADAM, COME HERE.
WE'RE READY FOR TECH REHEARSAL.
CAN WE START WITH THE PUPPETS?
(SIGHS) OKAY.
CAN I GET SOME PLAYBACK?!
(MUSIC STARTS PLAYING)
OUR YOUNG LOVERS DIE
IN EACH OTHERS' ARMS,
THEN EMBRACE, IN HEAVEN.
TRUE LOVE.
(PUPPET THUDS ON FLOOR)
(CAST AND CREW LAUGH)
"ROMEO AND JULES"
OPENS TOMORROW.
WHAT ELSE CAN GO WRONG?!
HEY.
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH, IT...
IT'S NOTHING.
I WAS JUST WONDERING
IF YOU'D THOUGHT ABOUT ASHER
AT ALL.
YEAH,
NOT IF I CAN HELP IT.
THE IDEA OF HIM TOUCHING YOU
MAKES ME SICK.
NO, I MEAN ABOUT OUR PLAN
TO TAKE HIM DOWN.
YOU WANNA DO THAT
RIGHT NOW?
I KNOW YOU'RE BUSY,
BUT EVERY DAY I LET THIS GO,
I JUST FEEL WORSE.
YOU USUALLY HAVE
A MILLION SCHEMES
SWIMMING AROUND
IN THAT HEAD.
OKAY,
I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
WE'LL GET THROUGH THIS
TOGETHER.
(SIGHS)
(PUPPETS THUD ON THE FLOOR)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh! ♪
(Ooh-ooh-ooh)
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
THIS IS HOW WE'LL TAKE DOWN
THE MUSICAL -
AN OLD-FASHIONED PROTEST!
LUKE:
NO ONE STEALS MY SISTER'S
FAVOURITE PLAY FROM HER
AND GETS AWAY WITH IT.
HEY.
WE'RE GONNA USE THESE?
BECKY:
THE PRINCIPAL MAY ALLOW
THIS KIND OF FILTH,
BUT HIS STUDENTS NEED TO KNOW
THEY CAN STILL FOLLOW
A RIGHTEOUS PATH.
AFTER ELI BUSTED MY NOSE,
AND HIS LITTLE GIRLFRIEND
MADE ME MISS THREE GAMES,
I'M ALL FOR TAKING DOWN
THE PLAY.
BUT THESE?
THESE'LL NEVER WORK.
WHY NOT? I MEAN,
THEY'RE CLEAR, DIRECT.
THEY'RE MAD HOMOPHOBIC.
THE ONLY PLACE WE'LL BE
PICKETING WITH THESE BAD BOYS
IS IN DETENTION.
BECKY:
SO THEY'RE ALLOWED TO TAKE
A CLASSIC PLAY AND TURN IT GAY,
BUT WE CAN'T EVEN EXPRESS
OUR OWN OPINIONS?
NOT THIS OPINION,
AND NOT IN THIS SCHOOL.
BUT THERE ARE OTHER AVENUES
WE CAN EXPLORE.
I'M SORRY,
BUT I STILL BELIEVE
IN FREEDOM OF SPEECH.
I'LL WAVE TO YOU
FROM THE PICKET LINE.
BECKY, WAIT.
DALLAS:
LEAVE HER.
I'VE GOT SOMETHING ELSE,
AND I NEED YOUR HELP.
ELI:
HAVE EVERY CAPULET
CHORUS MEMBER
SWITCH COSTUMES
WITH A MONTAGUE.
SERIOUSLY?
WE HAD TO SWITCH
ROMEO AND JULES;
IT HAS TO MATCH.
NEXT... (WINCES)
CAN YOU?
I REALLY HURT MYSELF
ON THAT DUMB JOCK'S FACE!
ALL RIGHT,
SEE IF YOU CAN
GET SOME STAGEHANDS
OUT OF CLASS
TO HELP IMOGEN
WITH THE PAINTING.
MAYBE THAT TATTOO GUY.
ADAM:
AND WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I TOLD YOU,
I HAVE TO HELP CLARE.
RIGHT, WITH SOMETHING
SUPER SECRET.
ADAM, IT'S SERIOUS.
SO YOU'RE GONNA RISK
THE PLAY?
(SIGHS)
SIMPSON MADE US STOP
SELLING TICKETS,
AND HE WANTS TO TALK
TO YOU, ASAP.
SEEMS SERIOUS.
HERE.
STAGEHAND:
CUE THE MUSIC!
♪♪♪
♪ YOU ARE THE SUN ♪
♪ THE MOON IN THE NIGHT ♪
♪ YOU ARE MY EVERYTHING,
EVERYTHING... ♪
TORI:
♪ THIS ISN'T RIGHT.
PLEASE HURRY! ♪
DAVE AND TRISTAN:
♪ IT WON'T TAKE ANOTHER SUMMER,
ANOTHER SPRING, ANOTHER... ♪
TORI:
♪ NOT A MOMENT LONGER ♪
DAVE AND TRISTAN:
♪ NOW I HAVE YOU... ♪
TORI:
♪ COME, WE MUST GO ♪
DAVE AND TRISTAN:
♪ DON'T NEED ANYTHING AT ALL ♪
♪♪♪
AND THEN WE KISS,
AND SCENE.
YOU DON'T WANNA PRACTICE
THAT PART?
UH, WE'LL WING IT.
IT'LL SEEM
MORE SPONTANEOUS.
DAVE:
FINE. I'M NOT IN THE MOOD
TO GET ALL LOVEY DOVEY ANYWAYS.
TORI:
ARE YOU REALLY GONNA DO THE SHOW
WITHOUT REHEARSING THE KISS?
I DON'T WANT MY FIRST KISS
TO BE WITH...DAVE.
I WANT IT TO BE SWEET,
AND ROMANTIC,
AND BEAUTIFUL!
YOU'VE NEVER KISSED ANYONE?
MAYBE SOME CUTE GUY
WILL SEE YOU IN THE PLAY
AND FALL MADLY IN LOVE.
GREAT! AFTER I'VE LOST
MY LIP VIRGINITY
TO SOME RANDOM GUY
IN FRONT OF TWO HUNDRED PEOPLE.
WELL, THE PLAY'S NOT
TILL TOMORROW, RIGHT?
YOU'VE STILL GOT TIME
TO FIND SOMEONE.
DON'T YOU HAVE HOMEWORK
TO FINISH?
I CAN TAKE A HINT.
SORRY, MY DOOFUS BOYFRIEND
HAS NO CONCEPT
OF HOW HARD IT IS
TO BE OUT IN GRADE NINE.
MAYBE NOT,
BUT HE'S RIGHT.
THE PLAY DOESN'T OPEN
TILL TOMORROW.
BEFORE THEN,
I HAVE TO FIND SOMEBODY
TO BE MY FIRST KISS.
ELI:
YOU HAVE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME!
ELI, SIT DOWN!
YOU WANT ME TO REVIEW
THE PLAY'S SUBJECT MATERIAL
THE DAY BEFORE OPENING NIGHT?!
IT'S NOT ME, OKAY?
SOME STUDENTS HAVE COMPLAINED,
AND NOW...
SOME PARENTS ARE INVOLVED.
OH YEAH, LET ME GUESS.
THE BAKERS!
MR. SIMPSON:
AMONGST OTHERS.
ELI, WOULD YOU SIT DOWN?!
NOW, THESE ARE JUST CONCERNED
MEMBERS OF THE SCHOOL COMMUNITY
WHO WANT YOU TO WALK THEM
THROUGH THE MATERIAL.
I WILL DEFEND THIS PLAY
UNTIL MY DYING BREATH.
WELL, THAT'S A BIT EXTREME,
DON'T YOU THINK?
THEY JUST WANT YOU TO DO IT
DURING THE LUNCH HOUR.
AND IF THEY STILL DISAPPROVE?
WHAT?
WE SHUT DOWN PRODUCTION?
I BELIEVE IN THIS PLAY,
OKAY?
I REALLY DOUBT
IT'S GONNA COME TO THAT.
BUT IT COULD.
WORST CASE SCENARIO,
I SUPPOSE.
(BELL RINGS)
GO AHEAD.
ELI:
URGH!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
HEY.
SO I GUESS THIS MEANS
WE'RE NOT GOING TO THE PLAY
TOGETHER?
BECKY:
OH, DID I NOT FORMALLY CANCEL?
WHERE ARE MY MANNERS?
HIDING BEHIND
THREE FEET OF HAIR?
AT LEAST I SEE NO NEED
TO HIDE THE FACT
THAT I'M A GIRL.
I'M NOT A GIRL,
I'M TRANS.
AND YOU'RE A REAL
PIECE OF WORK.
MADE PERFECTLY
BY THE HANDS OF GOD...
AS WE ALL ARE.
IF YOU'D ACCEPT
HOW GOD MADE YOU,
YOU'D BE HAPPIER.
JEEZ,
I NEVER THOUGHT OF THAT.
GOD MADE ME BRUNETTE,
BUT BLONDES HAVE MORE FUN.
JOKE ALL YOU WANT,
BUT I REALLY THINK
I GOT THROUGH TO ADAM
WITH THAT ONE.
IF YOU SAY SO.
PEOPLE, TIME TO ASSIGN GROUPS
FOR THIS WEEK'S PRESENTATIONS.
ADAM AND BECKY,
YOU'LL BE GROUP ONE.
UM, MRS. COHEN, NO.
ADAM AND I ARE JUST...
TOO DIFFERENT.
MRS. COHEN:
LIKE OIL AND VINEGAR
YOU MAY NOT MIX EASILY,
BUT YOU'LL MAKE
A DELICIOUS SALAD DRESSING.
AND YOUR SALAD IS...
"GLOBAL WARMING,
EFFECTS ON FAUNA."
JENNA?
ELI:
LOOK, I KNOW YOU'VE HEARD
THE RUMOURS,
BUT THIS PLAY WILL NEVER BE
SHUT DOWN
BY A FEW SMALL-MINDED
INDIVIDUALS!
(APPLAUSE AND CHEERING)
HOMOPHOBIA WILL BE DEFEATED
AND LOVE WILL TRIUMPH!
CAST AND CREW:
YEAH! RIGHT!
KEEP REHEARSING AS THOUGH
WE OPEN TOMORROW...
BECAUSE WE DO!
CAST AND CREW:
(CLAPPING AND CHEERING)
YOU SURE YOU'RE NOT WORRIED,
MAN?
DAVE, I DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR THIS.
IF SOME PARENTS
DON'T LIKE GAY PEOPLE,
I'M SORRY,
THEY'RE GONNA BE OFFENDED!
ARE YOU SURE
THAT'S THE REASON
THEY'RE AGAINST THE PLAY?
THE BAKERS?
BECKY BAKERS' PARENTS.
YEESH.
THAT GIRL GAVE ME
A "PRAY THE GAY AWAY"
PAMPHLET.
AND I THINK
HER DAD'S A MINISTER.
SO WE'RE DEAD.
NAW, MAN.
BRO, LOOK, YOU GOT THIS.
I MEAN THE IRONY IS,
ISN'T THIS PLAY
ABOUT STICKING UP
FOR THE LITTLE GUY?
ISN'T THAT WHAT JESUS
WOULD DO?
HE WOULD,
WOULDN'T HE?
♪♪♪
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
DALLAS:
MY FAVOURITE GAL PALS!
UH, YOU CAN'T JUST START
A FIGHT AT MY PARTY
AND THINK WE'RE
STILL BUDDIES.
HOW MANY "SORRYS"
DO YOU NEED?
YOU CAN STUFF YOUR SORRYS
IN A SACK!
(BOTH GIGGLE)
TRISTAN:
AHEM!
HI. UM, IMOGEN AND FIONA,
RIGHT?
YES. CAN WE HELP YOU?
UM, WHEN YOU STARTED
LIKING HER,
HOW DID YOU KNOW
SHE WOULD...
GO FOR A GIRL?
AWWWWWW...
DO YOU HAVE A CRUSH?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW HOW
TO FIND SOMEONE
TO HAVE A CRUSH ON.
FIONA:
WELL, FIRST YOU FIND SOMEONE
WITH SIMILAR INTERESTS.
AND THEN YOU BECOME
BEST FRIENDS...
AND THEN YOU FEEL THAT SPARK.
BZZZT!
AWW! I WANT BZZT!
JUST KEEP DOING
THE THINGS YOU LOVE.
I'M SURE THAT SPECIAL SOMEONE'S
ALREADY IN YOUR ORBIT.
YOU THINK?
AWWW!
YOU ARE SUCH A BUTTON!
CUTE, NICE, POLITE.
YOU COULD LEARN A THING OR TWO
FROM THIS ONE!
SO...
ELI:
"HATRED STIRS UP STRIFE,
BUT LOVE CONQUERS ALL."
PROVERBS 10:12.
"WHOEVER DOES NOT LOVE
DOES NOT KNOW GOD,
BECAUSE GOD IS LOVE."
JOHN 4:8.
IT SHOULD NOT MATTER
THAT THESE YOUNG LOVERS
ARE BOTH YOUNG MEN,
ONLY THAT THEIR COMMUNITY
LEARNS TO SUPPORT THEM,
LIKE THIS COMMUNITY
SHOULD SUPPORT THIS PLAY!
(APPLAUSE)
WHY ARE YOU DRESSED
AS THE FRIAR
FROM ROMEO AND JULIET?
IS THIS SOME SORT OF JOKE
AT MY EXPENSE?
NOT AT ALL, MR. BAKER.
I UNDERSTAND YOU'RE A MAN
OF THE CLOTH,
AND I WANTED TO SHOW
THAT JESUS HIMSELF
WOULD CHOOSE LOVE OVER HATE,
AND HE WOULDN'T CANCEL
THIS PLAY
JUST BECAUSE
IT'S ABOUT TWO GUYS!
MR. BAKER:
WELL, ADMITTEDLY WE AREN'T, UH,
ECSTATIC ABOUT THE PLAY'S
HOMOSEXUAL AGENDA...
OH! HERE WE GO.
I PERSONALLY APPROVED
THE CHANGES MADE
IN "ROMEO AND JULES."
DEGRASSI HAS BEEN AN ACCEPTING,
INCLUSIVE SCHOOL.
BUT THAT ISN'T
OUR ONLY CONCERN.
IT'S NOT?
THESE FINE BOYS BROUGHT UP
A VERY IMPORTANT POINT
ABOUT THE PLAY,
IN A TIME WHEN SO MANY TEENS
ARE TAKING THEIR OWN LIVES,
IS IT WISE TO STAGE A PLAY
THAT GLORIFIES SUICIDE?
I-I MEAN...
OKAY, THERE IS SUICIDE
IN THE PLAY,
BUT IT'S A CLASSIC!
I MEAN, YOUR OWN DAUGHTER
CHOSE IT!
AND WE'D FEEL THE EXACT SAME WAY
EVEN IF SHE WERE INVOLVED.
IT'S IRRESPONSIBLE.
MAYBE WE CAN WATCH
THE FINAL SCENE
BEFORE WE MAKE
ANY DECISIONS?
HOW ABOUT THAT?
LET'S DO IT.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS)
MONTAGUES AND CAPULETS:
♪ THEIR DEATH ♪
♪ OUR PAIN... ♪
♪ BLOOD SHED IN VAIN ♪
♪ A PRECIOUS CHILD ♪
♪ A PRECIOUS SON ♪
♪ THROUGH OUR HATE ♪
♪ THEIR LIVES UNDONE ♪
♪ HEAVEN HELP A WORLD
WHERE LOVE BRINGS SUCH PAIN ♪
♪ A PLAGUE ON BOTH
OUR HOUSES ♪
♪ TRUE LOVE WILL REMAIN! ♪
DALLAS:
THE LOVERS FIND LOVE IN DEATH?
THE FAMILIES PUT DOWN
THEIR ARMS?
THIS DEFINITELY GLORIFIES
SUICIDE.
NO, YOU'RE RIGHT!
THIS VERSION CAN'T BE STAGED.
HOW COULD I NOT SEE IT?
SO WHAT DO WE DO FROM HERE?
CANCEL?
ELI:
NO, NO, NO, I CAN FIX THIS!
CAN I HAVE UNTIL THE END
OF THE DAY
TO PROPOSE A NEW ENDING?
WE'LL REVIEW IT,
AND DECIDE THEN.
I THINK
IT'S ONLY FAIR.
CAST AND CREW:
(WHISPERING AND MURMURING)
AMEN.
(LAUGHS)
EVERYTHING OKAY?
JUST ASKING FOR GUIDANCE
ON HOW TO SHOW ADAM THE WAY.
WHY DO YOU CARE SO MUCH?
BECAUSE I CAN'T WORK
WITH SOMEONE WHO'S...
LIKE ADAM.
I'M PRETTY SURE
IT'S NOT A SIN
TO DO A PROJECT
WITH A TRANSGENDER GUY.
JENNA, WE NEARLY
WENT ON A DATE!
AND WHAT IF I DEVELOP
FEELINGS FOR HER?
WHAT IF SHE TURNED ME GAY?
ADAM IS NOT GAY.
ADAM IS A GIRL
WHO LIKES GIRLS!
HE IS TRANSGENDER.
THAT'S DIFFERENT.
WAIT, IS THIS WHY
YOU'RE SO HELL-BENT
ON PROTESTING THE PLAY?
THE PLAY'S WRONG, JENNA.
OKAY, CAN'T YOU JUST FINISH
THE SCIENCE PROJECT,
THEN IGNORE ADAM FOREVER?
I WISH.
BUT ADAM IS REALLY CONFUSED.
(BELL RINGS)
GOD MADE US PARTNERS
FOR A REASON.
(EXASPERATED SIGH)
♪♪♪
(HARD THUMP)
I THINK I'VE GOT IT!
REALLY?
THE LOVERS' SPIRITS
WON'T EMBRACE AT THE END.
THEY'LL MISS EACH OTHER,
EVEN IN HEAVEN...
TORN APART.
STAGE MANAGER:
LET'S DO IT ONE MORE TIME.
CUE THE MUSIC!
NO GOOD?
NO...
I WAS JUST HOPING
YOU MEANT A PLAN
TO TAKE DOWN ASHER.
LET ME FINISH
THE NEW ENDING,
THEN I'LL FIGURE
SOMETHING OUT.
OKAY, UM...
BUT I THINK I ACTUALLY
MIGHT BE ON TO SOMETHING.
ELI:
THE TORONTO JOURNALISM AWARDS?
IT'S TOMORROW,
WHICH MEANS AN EMPTY
"INTERPRETER" OFFICE.
WE CAN SNEAK IN
AND PLANT SOMETHING
ON ASHER'S COMPUTER.
NO, THAT WON'T WORK!
HE HAS EVIDENCE
AGAINST ME!
I'M GONNA NEED
SOMETHING ON HIM
IF I'M EVER GONNA
CLEAR MY NAME.
NO, THE PLAY!
AH...
OPENING NIGHT, RIGHT.
MAYBE THERE'S A WAY
TO DO BOTH.
I KNEW YOU WERE THE ONE PERSON
I COULD COUNT ON.
THANK YOU!
(SIGHS)
UM...
BEFORE WE START
ON OUR PROJECT,
I WANTED TO SAY
A COUPLE OF THINGS.
OKEY-DOKE.
EVERYONE HERE ACTS LIKE
HOW I FEEL IS CRAZY,
BUT THERE ARE A HUNDRED MILLION
OTHER BAPTISTS,
AND TWO BILLION
OTHER CHRISTIANS.
EVEN I WENT TO CHURCH
AS A KID.
YOU DID?
WHICH IS WHY I KNOW
NOT ALL CHRISTIANS
SHARE THE SAME BELIEFS
AS YOU DO.
THE BIBLE SAYS THAT
HOMOSEXUALITY IS WRONG,
BUT THE BIBLE ALSO OFFERS
A PATHWAY TO A GREAT LIFE.
I'M JUST TRYING TO HELP PEOPLE
FIND THEIR WAY.
OKAY, MY TURN.
I THOUGHT THAT WE COULD USE THIS
FOR OUR PROJECT.
A FOSSILIZED AMMONITE.
SEVENTY MILLION YEARS OLD!
WOW!
THAT'S INCREDIBLE!
INCREDIBLE
AS IN NOT CREDIBLE?
AS IN
YOU DON'T BELIEVE ME?
WHY WOULDN'T
I BELIEVE YOU?
WELL, DOESN'T THE BIBLE
SAY THE EARTH
IS ONLY 6000 YEARS OLD?
BUT...ISN'T THAT SORT OF
A METAPHOR?
I MEAN, JUST 'CAUSE
I'M A GOOD CHRISTIAN,
DOESN'T MEAN
I CAN'T LOVE SCIENCE.
SO YOU'LL LOOK PAST THE BIBLE
FOR A MOLLUSC,
BUT NOT WHEN YOU SEE A PLAY
ABOUT TWO DUDES IN LOVE?
IT'S JUST UNNATURAL.
BECAUSE OF INTOLERANCE
LIKE YOURS,
I'VE BEEN THROWN OUT
OF WASHROOMS,
BEATEN UP BAD.
I WOULD NEVER DO
ANY OF THAT.
BUT THE STUFF YOU SAY
MAKES PEOPLE THINK
IT'S OKAY
TO BULLY KIDS WHO ARE GAY,
OR TRANSGENDER,
OR DIFFERENT IN ANY WAY!
I THINK WE SHOULD WORK
SEPARATELY.
I'LL SEND YOU THE DATA,
AND YOU CAN MAKE
FRILLY CHARTS.
I FOUND LOVE...
IN A HOPELESS PLACE!
WELL, IN A THEATRE,
WITH THAT CUTE STAGEHAND.
THE BRAZILIAN GUY WITH
THE MOHAWK AND THE MUSCLES?
YEAH-HUH.
TORI:
DID YOU GET HIS NAME?
WELL,
WE DIDN'T EXACTLY TALK.
YOU JUST KISSED?!
WE SHARED...A LOOK,
BUT THERE WAS A SPARK.
NOW I JUST HAVE
TO TALK TO HIM.
TALKING TO CUTE GUYS
ISN'T EXACTLY YOUR STRONG SUIT.
TRISTAN:
WHY ARE YOU BEING
SO NEGATIVE?
DON'T YOU NOT WANT ME
TO HAVE MY DREAMY, ROMANTIC,
PERFECT FIRST KISS?
I JUST DON'T WANT YOU
TO GET YOUR HOPES UP.
SO YOU GET TO BE IN LOVE,
AND MAYA GETS TO BE IN LOVE,
BUT I DON'T?
TORI:
YOU WILL! I JUST DON'T WANT YOU
TO GET HURT
BEFORE OPENING NIGHT.
THANKS FOR LOOKING OUT
FOR ME,
BUT I'M GONNA GET THAT BOY
TO KISS ME,
MARK MY WORDS.
ROMEO AND JULES' SUICIDES
CAN'T BE ROMANTIC.
SO AFTER THEY KILL THEMSELVES,
THEIR SPIRITS SHOULD RISE
FROM THEIR BODIES,
THEN BE TORN APART
HALFWAY UP,
SEPARATED FOREVER...
WE'LL NEED LONGER POLES.
IT'LL TAKE ME A FEW HOURS
TO RIG UP.
HOURS?!
BUT WE STILL NEED
TO TEST IT
BEFORE I SUBMIT MY PROPOSAL
TO MR. SIMPSON!
(WINCES)
AGH!
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH, I'M FINE!
THERE'S JUST NO TIME.
I NEED TO SAVE THE PLAY,
AND THEN THERE'S CLARE.
WHOA! DEJA VU.
I'M NOT HAVING
A MANIC EPISODE,
IF THAT'S WHAT
YOU'RE GETTING AT.
BUT CHANGING THE END
OF A PLAY,
DOING EVERYTHING
FOR CLARE...
I'M GLAD I'M NO LONGER
CAUGHT UP IN HURRICANE ELI.
AM I REALLY THAT BAD?
YOU'RE LIKE ROMEO -
PASSIONATE, IMPULSIVE.
HE'LL DO ANYTHING
FOR THE THINGS
AND PEOPLE THAT HE LOVES.
BUT FOR ALL HIS CRAZY
ROMANCE...
ROMEO STILL ENDED UP DEAD.
WHY IS SIMPSON LEAVING US
HANGING LIKE THIS?
I HANDED THAT PROPOSAL IN
TWELVE HOURS AGO!
IMOGEN:
HE PROBABLY HAS TO DISCUSS
HIS DECISION WITH THE BAKERS.
AWESOME.
DALLAS:
NERVOUS?
MR. SIMPSON:
ELI.
GREAT JOB ON THE REWRITE.
CAN'T WAIT TO SEE IT
TONIGHT.
(RELIEVED SIGH)
ELI: YAY!
DALLAS: THIS AIN'T OVER.
EXCUSE ME A SECOND?
(SIGHS)
IT LOOKS LIKE
YOU GOT GOOD NEWS.
YEAH,
THE PLAY'S GOING FORWARD.
WELL THEN,
WHY THE MOPEY FACE?
BECAUSE REWRITING THE END
OF THE MUSICAL MADE ME REALIZE
"ROMEO AND JULES"
IS ABOUT TEENAGERS
WHO MAKE
AN IMPULSIVE DECISION
AND IT GOES HORRIBLY WRONG.
NO, ELI, NO!
I STAYED UP ALL NIGHT
READING CASE LAW
ON WORKPLACE HARASSMENT.
I KNOW HOW
WE CAN GET ASHER.
THIS IS A SOLID PLAN!
I'VE HAD PLANS, TOO.
FITZ AND THE FAKE IDS,
VEGAS NIGHT, LOVE ROULETTE!
THEY NEVER END WELL.
SO YOU'RE JUST GONNA
LET ASHER
GET AWAY WITH EVERYTHING
HE DID TO ME?
NO!
I'VE COME UP
WITH SOMETHING BETTER.
WHAT IS IT?
YOU'RE GOING TO TALK
TO MS. OH.
NO!
NO, I CAN'T TELL HER!
I ALREADY DID.
SHE'S WAITING
TO GO OVER YOUR STORY.
♪♪♪
I TRIED TO TALK TO THAT CUTE
STAGEHAND AFTER SCHOOL,
BUT I GOT SO NERVOUS
I TURNED TO RUN AWAY,
TRIPPED,
AND FELL INTO A SHRUB.
(LAUGHS)
DID HE NOTICE?
NO, THANK HEAVENS.
BUT SITTING IN THAT SPRUCE,
IT GAVE ME TIME TO THINK.
MAYBE TORI'S RIGHT,
MAYBE I CAN'T TALK TO GUYS.
HEY, YOU STILL HAVE YOUR OPENING
NIGHT TONIGHT, RIGHT?
SHUT UP!
APOLOGY FROM TORI?
IT'S A LETTER
FROM...A SECRET ADMIRER.
"TRISTAN,
A ROSE BY ANOTHER NAME,
BUT STILL AS SWEET.
I'VE BEEN WATCHING YOU
AND I WANT TO MEET."
THIS GUY LIKES YOU!
AND HE WANTS TO MEET ME
RIGHT NOW?
DON'T YOU HAVE REHEARSAL
IN LIKE HALF AN HOUR?
IT COULD MEAN GETTING
MY FIRST KISS
BEFORE I HAVE TO KISS
DAVE TONIGHT!
I WOULDN'T WANNA RISK
LETTING THAT MANY PEOPLE DOWN.
OH, ME NEITHER.
BUT...ON THE OTHER HAND,
(SIGHS)
IT'S FOR LOVE!
(LAUGHS)