♪ Well I-I-I had enough ♪
♪ When will I feel your touch ♪
KATIE:
ONE SEC.
HEY! YOU WANNA EXPLAIN
THE VIDEO
YOU POSTED ON
YOUR FACERANGE WALL?
OH, SURE.
UH, IT'S A VIDEO OF ME
KISSING A GUY.
I THOUGHT IT WAS
PRETTY STRAIGHTFORWARD.
IT'S GROSS.
I GOT TWENTY-TWO
"LIKES."
AND PEOPLE ARE TALKING
ABOUT YOU.
IT'S ALMOST THE END
OF THE YEAR;
IS THIS HOW YOU WANNA BE
REMEMBERED?
MAYA:
PEOPLE HAVE BEEN TALKING
ABOUT ME FOR WEEKS.
AT LEAST NOW
IT'S ABOUT SOMETHING I DID.
MAYA,
DELETE THE VIDEO.
MAYA:
JUST RELAX.
NO ONE CARES!
WHAT IF MOM AND DAD
FIND OUT?
I BLOCKED THEM
SO THEY WON'T BE ABLE
TO SEE IT.
SO UNLESS SOMEONE WANTS
TO TELL THEM ABOUT IT...
(BELL RINGS)
(SIGHS)
YOUR ORCHESTRA
AUDITION'S TODAY?
YEAH. I HAVEN'T PLAYED
IN A WHILE.
WHAT IF I BLOW IT?
MAYA, CELLO'S ALWAYS BEEN
THERE FOR YOU, 'KAY?
YOU'RE GONNA DO GREAT.
COME HERE.
AND I'M TAKING THIS
AS A SIGN
THAT MAKING OUT WITH A RANDOM
WAS A ONE-TIME THING, OKAY?
AND IF IT DOES HAPPEN AGAIN,
I AM GONNA TELL MOM.
AYE-AYE, CAPTAIN!
BREAK A LEG.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(CHUCKLES TO HERSELF)
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes P
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
(Ooh-ooh-ooh)
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
CHANGING STRATEGIES
DURING YOUR CAMPAIGN,
THAT'S RISKY.
YOU SHOWED UP AT MY HOUSE
AND BEAT ME AT MY OWN GAME,
EDWARDS.
THIS ISN'T OVER.
SO YOU'RE TAKING IT
SERIOUSLY NOW?
WELL, I FIGURED
IF MY CONCUSSIONS
ARE GONNA KEEP ME
FROM PLAYING SPORTS
ALL NEXT YEAR,
I MIGHT AS WELL FILL MY TIME
WITH BEING PRESIDENT.
WELL, GOOD LUCK
THIS AFTERNOON.
THANKS.
AT THE DEBATE.
YEAH, YEAH.
NO, I KNEW THAT!
DO YOU HAVE A HANDLE ON
THE STUDENT CONSTITUTION
AND COUNCIL
BUDGET CONCERNS?
YOU'RE GONNA TALK ABOUT
ALL THAT STUFF?
OH, WE'RE GONNA TALK
ABOUT A LOT OF STUFF.
(BELL RINGS)
DUDE, I'M IN TROUBLE.
LISTEN, DON'T WORRY.
JUST STAY FOCUSED
ON THE MESSAGE.
WHAT'S YOUR SLOGAN?
"LET'S DO IT TOGETHER!"
AND HOW DO YOU PLAN
ON DOING THAT?
ASKING WHAT THE STUDENTS WANT
AND... GIVING IT TO THEM.
PERFECT!
(SIGHS) OKAY,
I CAN DO THIS.
(BACH CELLO SUITE NO.1 -
PRELUDE PLAYS)
HEY, OBOE GIRL.
(LAUGHS)
IT'S A CELLO.
HARRY:
THAT THING'S BIGGER
THAN YOU ARE.
YOU THINK IT'S NERDY?
HARRY:
NO WAY! IT'S...
IT'S SO ANGST.
I HAD FUN AT THE PARTY.
ME TOO.
I HEARD THERE'S THIS ROOM
BY THE THEATRE
WHERE THEY KEEP OLD PROPS.
UH, IT'S PRETTY PRIVATE.
(SIGHS) I...
I HAVE THIS CELLO THING.
ALL RIGHT.
MAYBE SEE YOU AROUND.
SURE.
ALLI:
...IT IS WHAT IT IS.
CONNOR:
HI, JENNA. HI, ALLI.
I'M SORRY I TRIED
TO SET YOU UP WITH ELI.
I DON'T WANNA TALK
ABOUT IT.
SERIOUSLY, CONNOR.
ENOUGH.
YOU PISSED A LOT
OF PEOPLE OFF.
DOES THAT MEAN
YOU WANNA BREAK UP WITH ME?
(LAUGHS) NO.
BUT YOU SEEM MAD.
(SIGHS)
I'M NOT MAD.
SO WHAT'RE YOU GUYS
TALKING ABOUT?
JENNA:
CLARE; WHETHER HER AND ELI
SHOULD GET BACK TOGETHER.
ELI'S JUST BEING A JERK.
ELI WAS BEING HONEST.
HE TOLD CLARE
THAT SHE WAS ANNOYING HIM,
AND IF SHE DIDN'T WANT HIM
TO BREAK UP WITH HER,
SHE SHOULD'VE STOPPED!
CLARE:
THANKS FOR THE ADVICE,
CONNOR.
NICE ONE.
NOW I'M MAD AT YOU.
(SIGHS)
MAYA:
(NERVOUS SIGH)
GOOD MORNING.
I MEAN, AFTERNOON.
MUSIC DIRECTOR:
NICE TO MEET YOU, MAYA.
LET'S START
WITH THE PIECE FIRST
AND THEN WE'LL MOVE ON
TO THE INTERVIEW PORTION.
OKEY-DOKEY.
(EXHALES)
(STARTS PLAYING
BACH CELLO SUITE NO.1)
CLARE:
A VOTE FOR CLARE EDWARDS
IS A VOTE FOR
FISCAL RESPONSIBILITY.
IF ELECTED,
I WILL SPEND RESPONSIBLY
ON FUN SCHOOL DANCES,
WHILE STILL SUPPORTING
OUR MOST POPULAR TEAMS
AND CLUBS.
(SMATTERING OF APPLAUSE)
SIMPSON:
YOUR THOUGHTS, MR. TORRES?
DREW:
(CLEARS THROAT)
IF I AM ELECTED,
I WILL LISTEN TO WHAT
THE STUDENTS WANT
AND THEN,
THAT'S WHAT WE'LL DO.
(YAWNS)
UH... I'M SORRY.
DO WHAT?
DREW:
UM, ALL OF IT!
STUDENTS:
(MURMURING QUIETLY)
LET'S DO IT TOGETHER,
DEGRASSI!
BIANCA:
WOO! (APPLAUDS LOUDLY)
CLARE:
UH, I'M SORRY,
CAN I REBUT?
UH... PFFT.
WHAT IF THE DRAMA CLUB WANTS
TO ACCESS TO THE GYM IN MAY
FOR A ONE ACT PLAY?
THEN I WILL BE THE FIRST ONE
IN LINE BUYING TICKETS.
BUT THE POWER SQUAD PRACTICES
IN THE GYM TOO.
WHAT IF THEY MAKE
THE REGIONAL CHEER FINALS
NEXT SPRING?
BEING PRESIDENT MEANS
MAKING HARD DECISIONS SOMETIMES.
YOU CAN'T PLEASE EVERYONE
ALL THE TIME.
(STUDENTS CLAP)
(MAYA CONTINUES PLAYING
THE BACH CELLO SUITE)
♪♪♪
MUSIC DIRECTOR:
THAT WAS A BEAUTIFUL
PERFORMANCE.
THANK YOU.
I WILL WORK SO HARD
IF I'M LUCKY ENOUGH
TO GET A SPOT, OF COURSE.
MUSIC DIRECTOR:
ALL OF OUR MUSICIANS
HAVE TO BE COMMITTED
TO UPHOLDING THE INTEGRITY
OF THE NYMO
IN ALL ASPECTS
OF THEIR LIVES.
OF COURSE.
ARE YOU FAMILIAR
WITH OUR CODE OF CONDUCT?
MAYA:
UM...
I HAVEN'T READ IT YET,
NO.
MUSIC DIRECTOR:
WE SCREEN ALL OUR CANDIDATES
CLOSELY.
YOU KNOW YOUR FACERANGE PROFILE
IS PUBLIC?
NEEDLESS TO SAY,
THIS VIDEO GIVES US PAUSE.
I DIDN'T THINK
IT WOULD MATTER.
EVERYTHING MATTERS.
HERE TO SET ME UP
WITH ANYONE ELSE?
CONNOR:
DO I SMELL FEET,
OR IS THAT SALT AND VINEGAR
CHIPS?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
YOUR BREAK-UP IS INTERFERING
WITH MY RELATIONSHIP
WITH JENNA.
ELI, YOU NEED TO GET
BACK TOGETHER WITH CLARE.
WHAT?
YOUR BREAK-UP IS INTERFERING
WITH MY-
NO, CONNOR,
I HEARD YOU.
THIS IS REALLY
NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
ELI, YOU'RE A MESS.
I JUST SPILLED SOME PUDDING
ON MY T-SHIRT.
NO! YOU REMIND ME OF ME
WHEN I WAS UNHAPPY -
ALONE, ON A COMPUTER,
SMELLY.
I'M MISERABLE.
TALK TO CLARE.
TELL HER THAT.
OH, SHE'S NEVER GONNA
TAKE ME BACK.
I MIGHT'VE LOST CLARE
FOR GOOD.
MAYBE NOT.
I CAN TALK TO ALLI
AND JENNA,
FIND OUT WHERE SHE STANDS.
WHY DO YOU CARE SO MUCH
ABOUT ME AND CLARE?
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT JENNA
TO ASK ME FOR A BREAK.
(THUNDER RUMBLES,
RAIN PATTERS)
MAYA:
DON'T GO!
ZIG:
MAYA, I DON'T WANNA FIGHT
WITH YOU!
I DON'T WANNA FIGHT
WITH YOU EITHER!
REALLY? BECAUSE THIS
PRETTY MUCH SOUNDS
LIKE WE'RE FIGHTING!
(HUFFS) LOOK, I'M SORRY
I POSTED THE VIDEO, OKAY?
I TOOK IT DOWN.
IT'S OVER.
YOU KNOW,
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU ACTUALLY LIKE
THAT TOOL HARRY.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW HIM!
THEN WHY WERE YOU
WITH HIM?
BECAUSE HE DIDN'T SAY NO!
MAYA...
MAYA, THIS ISN'T YOU.
I AM SO SICK OF PEOPLE
TELLING ME
WHO I'M SUPPOSED TO BE!
EVEN THE MUSIC DIRECTOR
FOR THE YOUTH ORCHESTRA
WANTS ME TO EXPLAIN MYSELF
OR HE WON'T GIVE ME
A SPOT, ZIG!
SO JUST TELL THEM
ABOUT CAM.
PLAY THE "GIRLFRIEND OF
THE DEAD GUY" CARD, ZIG?
I POSTED THAT VIDEO
BECAUSE I WANTED TO!
MAYBE THIS IS ME NOW!
IT'S NOT, MAYA!
YOU'RE JUST MAD!
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
MAYA, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOUR PARENTS ARE GONNA FLIP!
MAYA:
LET 'EM FLIP!
I DON'T CARE!
I'M QUITTING!
AND I'M DONE!
(THUNDER RUMBLES,
RAIN PATTERS)
DREW:
THAT'S VERY INTERESTING NEWS.
OKAY, THANK YOU.
BIANCA:
YOU DISAPPEARED
AFTER THE DEBATE.
ARE YOU OKAY?
DREW:
I'M GOOD.
I WAS A LITTLE BIT HUMILIATED,
BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER
ANYMORE.
I GOT OFF THE PHONE
WITH MY DOCTOR.
AND?
HE CLEARED ME TO PLAY
NON-CONTACT SPORTS!
(GASPS)
THAT'S AWESOME, BABE!
YEAH!
SO I CAN DROP OUT
OF THE ELECTION,
NOT MAKE A BIGGER FOOL
OF MYSELF.
DROP OUT?
THE VOTE'S TODAY.
YEAH, BUT IF I CAN
PLAY SPORTS,
I DON'T NEED
STUDENT COUNCIL.
DREW, YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE
A PRO ATHLETE,
BUT THIS LEADERSHIP THING,
IT COULD TAKE YOU PLACES.
PEOPLE DON'T TAKE ME SERIOUSLY,
ALL RIGHT?
AND I DON'T...
I DON'T WANNA DISAPPOINT YOU.
IMPOSSIBLE.
AND THIS ISN'T ABOUT
WINNING,
IT'S ABOUT TRYING.
(BELL RINGS)
HI, JENNA.
ARE YOU STILL MAD AT ME?
WELL, THAT DEPENDS.
IS ONE OF THOSE LATTES
VANILLA?
OF COURSE.
IT'S YOUR FAVOURITE.
LOOK, JENNA,
I DON'T WANT US
TO EVER GET INTO FIGHTS,
OR GO ON BREAKS -
EVER.
I LIKE YOU TOO MUCH
FOR THAT.
I LIKE YOU TOO.
SO WHO'S THE THIRD FOR?
ALLI:
(SIGHS)
GOT YOUR TEXT, CONNOR.
WHAT'S UP?
CONNOR:
I GOT US COFFEES.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
A GOSSIP SESSION TOGETHER.
OH! I EVEN GOT SOUR KEYS.
BUT THERE'S NOTHING LEFT
FOR US TO GOSSIP ABOUT.
ALLI:
SERIOUSLY, WE'VE EXHAUSTED
THE TOPIC OF CLARE AND ELI.
IT'S OVER.
CONNOR:
NO. I TALKED TO ELI.
THERE ARE FURTHER DEVELOPMENTS.
ALLI:
GO ON.
CONNOR:
WELL, HE SAYS THAT
HE MISSES CLARE
AND HE THINKS HE MADE
A HUGE MISTAKE.
YEAH, BUT IS HE JUST
SAYING THAT?
CONNOR:
NO. HE WANTS TO KNOW
IF CLARE WOULD TAKE HIM BACK.
ALLI:
WELL, TELL HIM TO TALK
TO HER, NOW!
CONNOR:
BUT WILL SHE SAY YES?
ALLI:
OF COURSE SHE WILL.
ARE YOU KIDDING?!
JENNA:
(LAUGHING) YAY!
MARISOL: (OVER PA)
LAST CHANCE, PEOPLE!
MAKE SURE YOU GET OUT AND VOTE!
TODAY'S THE DAY!
MAYA:
HEY!
SO IT'S POSSIBLE
I'M A CRAZY GIRL.
I DOUBT IT.
WELL, I CHUCKED MY CELLO
IN A DUMPSTER.
(LAUGHING) DUDE,
THAT'S SO PROPER!
I JUST NEED SOMETHING NEW
IN MY LIFE RIGHT NOW,
YOU KNOW?
I GET YOU.
SO MY DAD'S WORKING LATE
TONIGHT
AND MY MOM AND MY SISTER
ARE OUT SHOPPING.
UH-HUH.
SO DO YOU MAYBE WANNA
COME OVER
AND WATCH A MOVIE
OR SOMETHING?
OR SOMETHING.
SEE YOU TONIGHT.
CONNOR:
MAYBE WE COULD GO TO THE DOT
AFTER SCHOOL?
THEY HAVE REALLY GOOD
CHICKEN NUGGETS.
JENNA:
I LIKE THE DOT,
BUT SPACE IS FUN TOO-
OH! TH-THERE'S ELI.
THERE'S ELI.
ELI!
I'VE GOT INTEL.
I TALKED TO ALLI
AND SHE SAYS THAT
IF YOU TALK TO CLARE,
THERE'S A GOOD CHANCE
AT REUNIFICATION.
WHY AREN'T YOU
MORE EXCITED?
I THOUGHT THIS IS
WHAT YOU WANTED.
I'VE JUST BEEN THINKING.
MAYBE THIS BREAK'S
FOR THE BEST.
I'M SO CONFUSED.
WHY?
DO YOU LIKE CLARE?
OF COURSE.
DO YOU LOVE HER?
MORE THAN ANYONE.
THEN WHY DON'T YOU WANNA
BE WITH HER?
HOW'D THAT GO?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
ELI AND CLARE
ARE SO COMPLICATED.
AND WE'RE SIMPLE?
YEAH, IF THAT'S OKAY
WITH YOU?
IT'S ACTUALLY
THE BEST.
♪ Pound on the floor ♪
♪ Stuff your notes
under my door ♪
♪ I just cover my... ♪
I DON'T THINK WE'RE GONNA
WATCH THE MOVIE.
(MUFFLED LAUGH)
PROBABLY NOT.
SO WE JUST KEEP KISSING
FOREVER?
WELL... WE CAN DO
OTHER STUFF.
OH. UM...
I'VE NEVER DONE THAT
BEFORE.
JUST GO WITH IT.
TRUST ME.
(DOOR OPENS)
KATIE:
UH, WHAT THE HELL?!
MAYA:
OH MY GOD!
KATIE:
YOU. RUN!
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
(DREW SIGHS HEAVILY)
HEY! UH, CAN WE TALK
ABOUT THE ELECTION?
UH, YOU'RE UH...
YOU'RE PROBABLY GONNA WIN.
WELL, SOME PEOPLE VOTE
FOR THE MOST POPULAR PERSON,
SO WHO KNOWS?
WHATEVER HAPPENS,
I UH...
I WANT YOU TO CHOOSE ME
TO BE YOUR VICE PRESIDENT.
YOU'RE KIDDING.
I THINK SPORTS ARE OVER
FOR ME, CLARE.
I NEED TO TRY
SOMETHING ELSE.
SO WHEN THEY ANNOUNCE
YOUR VICTORY TOMORROW,
I WANT YOU TO CHOOSE ME
TO BE YOUR VEEP.
IT'S V.P., DREW.
(BELL RINGS)
NEVER MIND.
MRS. MATLIN:
YOU ARE 14-YEARS-OLD.
MAYA:
BRAND NEW INFORMATION!
MRS. MATLIN:
DO YOU THINK SASSY REMARKS
ARE APPRECIATED RIGHT NOW?
KATIE:
BETWEEN THIS AND THAT VIDEO
YOU POSTED ON FACERANGE...
MRS. MATLIN:
WHAT VIDEO?
OF HER AND THAT JERK
KISSING AT A PARTY.
WHAT PARTY?
MAYA:
THE ONE I SNUCK OUT TO.
DREW'S CAMPAIGN PARTY.
OH YEAH, PERFECT.
MAYA:
WHAT CAN I SAY?
THE MATLIN GIRLS
LIKE TO GET BUSY
AT THE TORRES HOUSE,
SINCE WE'RE GETTING
ALL HONEST.
KATIE: SHUT UP!
MAYA: MAKE ME!
MRS. MATLIN:
YOU WATCH YOUR TONE,
YOUNG LADY.
I DON'T THINK YOU UNDERSTAND
HOW WORRIED WE ARE.
MAYA:
CAN YOU JUST GROUND ME
OR WHATEVER
SO I CAN GO TO MY ROOM?
WHAT IS GOING ON WITH YOU
AND THIS BOY?
HARRY MAKES ME FEEL GOOD.
IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG
WITH THAT?
IT'S SCARY.
MAYA: SCARY?
KATIE: YES, MAYA.
IT'S SCARY FOR YOU
TO BE HOOKING UP
WITH SOME GUY
YOU BARELY KNOW!
MRS. MATLIN:
KATIE-
YOU CAN'T REPLACE CAM!
WHY NOT?
HE BROKE UP WITH ME
BY KILLING HIMSELF!
I HATE HIM!
I FEEL LIKE I'M NEVER
GONNA BE HAPPY AGAIN.
AND EVERY DAY
IT JUST GETS WORSE AND WORSE!
I CAN'T MISS HIM ANYMORE.
I CAN'T!
I DON'T WANT TO!
HE NEVER EVEN SAID GOODBYE.
(SOBS)
MAYA:
"I'M MESSED UP.
I TRIED HARD NOT TO BE
FOR AS LONG AS I COULD,
BUT EVENTUALLY
EVERYTHING EXPLODED."
IT'S GOOD.
GOOD.
'CAUSE THAT'S PART
OF THE LETTER
I WROTE TO THE YOUTH ORCHESTRA
EXPLAINING WHY
I POSTED THE VIDEO.
THE WORST PART IS,
I TREATED YOU LIKE CRAP
AND YOU DIDN'T DESERVE IT.
NOW IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I HAVE TO GO DUMPSTER DIVING.
IF MY PARENTS FIND OUT
I CHUCKED
A THOUSAND DOLLAR INSTRUMENT
IN THE GARBAGE,
I'M TOAST.
UM, YOUR CELLO'S
NOT IN THE DUMPSTER.
IF IT ALREADY GOT PICKED UP,
I'M A DEAD GIRL.
NO, NO, NO.
I MEAN, YOUR CELLO'S
NOT IN THE GARBAGE
BECAUSE IT'S IN
THE MUSIC ROOM.
I FISHED IT OUT
BEFORE THE TRUCK CAME BY
AND ASKED MS. OH
TO LOCK IT UP
UNTIL YOU CAME
TO YOUR SENSES.
YOU DID THAT FOR ME?
♪ Wade in rising water ♪
♪ Walk in the sinking sand ♪
♪ Crawl through
the shadow valley ♪
♪ To try to understand ♪
♪ I climbed a Jacob's Ladder ♪
♪ I fell down
all your stairs... ♪
MAYA...
SAYING NO TO YOU
WAS THE HARDEST THING EVER
BECAUSE...
I REALLY LIKE YOU.
I ONLY WANT US
WHEN IT'S WHAT YOU WANT TOO.
AND I DON'T KNOW
WHEN THAT'LL BE.
(SIGHS) I KNOW.
SO I'LL WAIT.
♪ I saw a hall of mirrors ♪
♪ I saw a burning wheel ♪
♪ I saw rain of arrows ♪
♪ I lost the way to feel ♪
♪ I saw a million faces ♪
♪ Stare at a fallen star ♪
♪ I saw the last horizon ♪
♪ The end of time ♪
SIMPSON:
AND YOUR GRADE TWELVE REP
IS MITCHELL T. CANCER???
AND NOW, IT'S TIME
FOR THE RESULTS
OF THE PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION.
I AM PLEASED TO ANNOUNCE
THAT NEXT YEAR'S
STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT IS...
DREW TORRES!
(STUDENTS CHEER)
DREW: YES!
BIANCA: BABE, YOU WON!
DREW:
THIS WOULDN'T HAVE HAPPENED
WITHOUT YOU.
(SIGHS, ELATED)
GIVE ME A SEC, OKAY?
BIANCA:
OKAY.
(HALLWAY BUZZES
WITH EXCITED CHATTER)
(WEEPING QUIETLY)
I DIDN'T THINK
YOU'D BE THIS UPSET.
IT'S NOT JUST
THE ELECTION.
EVERYTHING
IS FALLING APART.
(AWKWARDLY)
THERE, THERE.
SORRY.
BIANCA HARDLY EVER CRIES.
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE.
I NEED TO ASK YOU
SOMETHING FIRST.
WILL YOU BE MY VEEP?
IT'S V.P, DREW!
NO. I KNOW!
I JUST LIKE SAYING IT
THAT WAY.
BUT I'M SERIOUS.
YOUR SMARTS, MY FUN.
THIS... THIS COULD WORK.
ELI:
HEY.
UM, LOOK, I'M SORRY ABOUT
THE ELECTION, YOU KNOW...
LOOK, I'VE GOT NEWS.
I GOT INTO NYU.
CONGRATS.
ALL YOUR DREAMS
CAME TRUE.
GUESS YOU WERE BETTER OFF
WITHOUT ME.
NO, I'M NOT.
I MISS YOU LIKE CRAZY.
I DON'T WANT IT
TO END UP LIKE THIS.
I WANT A HAPPY ENDING.
WE'RE NOT A FAIRY TALE,
ELI.
'KAY, PLEASE,
CAN WE JUST-
DON'T.
HAVE A GOOD SUMMER,
AND I HOPE NEW YORK
IS EVERYTHING
YOU HOPED IT WOULD BE.
NOW IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I HAVE A SCHOOL TO VEEP.
(LAUGHS)
(SNIFFLES)
YOU'RE IN?
I AM IN.
OKAY!
V.P.!
PREZ.
(LAUGHING)
WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
HONESTLY, SO MANY THINGS...
I DON'T EVEN KNOW.
PROMISE ME WE'RE GONNA BE OKAY
NEXT YEAR?
OF COURSE WE ARE,
MR. PRESIDENT.