THERE'S NOT A LOT OF TIME
BEFORE THE BIG EVENT.
EVERYONE HAS TO KNOW
THEIR ROLES,
EVERYTHING MUST BE PERFECT!
THE CUING,
THE LIGHTS,
THE...BIG SURPRISE.
ADAM:
WHATCHA TALKING ABOUT, ELI?
I DON'T THINK IT'S THE MUSICAL.
CLARE'S NEWSPAPER INTERNSHIP
DIDN'T WORK OUT.
SHE'S PRETTY UPSET ABOUT IT
BUT WE'RE GONNA CHEER HER UP,
WITH A SURPRISE 17TH
BIRTHDAY PARTY TONIGHT,
AND YOU'RE ALL GONNA HELP.
UM...I BARELY KNOW CLARE,
AND I DON'T REALLY CARE
ABOUT HER BIRTHDAY,
SO WHY AM I EXPECTED TO HELP?
BECAUSE THE PARTY WILL BE
AT YOUR LOFT.
AND YOU'RE PLANNING IT.
I DON'T THINK SO.
I WILL GIVE YOU MONEY TO SPEND.
LAST MINUTE PARTY PLANNING
WITH A BUDGET?!
WHY DIDN'T YOU SAY SO?
ELI:
AND REMEMBER,
IT'S A SURPRISE.
WELL, YOU'RE TAKING THIS
WHOLE CLARE-ASHER THING
SHOCKINGLY WELL.
THAT JERK OBVIOUSLY
DOESN'T KNOW A GREAT WRITER
WHEN HE SEES ONE.
YEAH, IT MUST'VE BEEN
REALLY HARD FOR CLARE
TO ADMIT THAT SOMEONE THOUGHT
HER WRITING WAS SUB-PAR.
SO YOU'LL GET CLARE
TO THE PARTY FOR ME?
YEAH, I'LL SURPRISE HER
WITH A SPA BIRTHDAY TREAT.
ELI:
PERFECT! THANKS, ALLI.
THIS IS GONNA BE A BIRTHDAY
CLARE WILL NEVER FORGET!
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ I can make it throug ♪h
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
TORI:
DO YOU THINK YOUR "WEST DRIVE"
SCENE IS WITH BROCK LANGLEY?
HE'S SO PERF!
THEY SAID THEY'D SEND
MY SCRIPT PAGES
IN A WEEK OR SO.
WELL, WANNA HANG OUT
AT LUNCH
AND WILDLY SPECULATE
SOME MORE?
TORI:
UH, GIRLFRIEND
AT TWELVE O'CLOCK.
THINK SHE'S MAD YOU
BLEW HER OFF LAST NIGHT?
DAVE:
YEAH, PROBABLY.
I WOULD JUST DIE
IF ZIG DID THAT TO ME,
JUST DIE.
ALLI:
HEY!
MIND IF I PULL YOU AWAY
FROM YOUR NINER FAN CLUB
FOR A MINUTE?
(TRISTAN SIGHS)
I FIGURED YOU'D LOST WHEN YOU
DIDN'T COME OVER LAST NIGHT.
NO, ACTUALLY, I WON.
WE WENT OUT TO CELEBRATE.
YOU WON?
WHY DIDN'T YOU CALL ME?
SORRY, I GOT A LITTLE
SWEPT UP.
SORRY IF YOU FEEL LIKE
I BLEW YOU OFF.
NO, IT'S OKAY.
I'M HAPPY FOR YOU.
(BELL RINGS)
YOU'RE FINE WITH THAT?
YEAH, WHY?
WELL, I THOUGHT YOU'D BE
MAD SINCE I DITCHED YOU.
NO, IT'S NO BIG DEAL,
IT HAPPENS.
CONGRATS, AND I'LL SEE YOU
IN ENGLISH?
YOU KNOW HOW ROMEO NEVER
GOT THE MESSAGE FROM JULIET
ABOUT HER FAKING HER DEATH?
YES, IT LED TO THE WHOLE
SUICIDE THING.
POSTAL SYSTEM REALLY LET
THOSE TWO KIDS DOWN.
I THINK ALLI'S TRYING
TO GIVE ME A MESSAGE,
AND I DON'T WANNA END UP
DRINKING POISONED GRAPE JUICE.
YOU'RE SPENDING WAY
TOO MUCH TIME WITH ELI.
LOOK, NEITHER OF US ARE
THINKING ABOUT THE OTHER FIRST.
THAT'S A PROBLEM.
OKAY, MESSAGE RECEIVED.
NOW WHAT?
YOU BREAK UP?
NO, NO!
I LOVE HER WAY TOO MUCH.
TONIGHT, ALLI AND I ARE
GETTING OUR SPARK BACK!
(KNOCKING)
A MOTORCYCLE?
OH...
A CARELESS DRIVING CHARGE?!
I BEGGED THE COP
NOT TO CALL YOU.
OH! WELL, THAT MAKES ME
FEEL MUCH BETTER.
I CAN PAY THE TICKET MYSELF,
THIS ISN'T EVEN YOUR BUSINESS.
YOU HAVE MULTIPLE
HEAD INJURIES!
I KNOW,
I'M GETTING BETTER.
I BARELY GET DIZZY ANYMORE,
AND MY MEMORY IS IMPROVING.
THIS PLACE HAS A WASHER
AND DRYER?
YOU SURE BIANCA HASN'T
TOLD YOU ALL THIS
IN HER WEEKLY REPORTS?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT?
WELL, I KNOW YOU TWO
ARE TALKING.
THAT'S WHY SHE WANTS ME
TO MOVE HOME,
AND GO BACK TO SCHOOL.
YOU'RE INFLUENCING HER
AGAINST ME!
(LAUGHS DERISIVELY)
UM, HAVE YOU MET BIANCA?
SHE HAS HER OWN MIND.
IF SHE DOESN'T SUPPORT
YOUR DECISION,
THAT'S NOT MY FAULT.
SHE'S SUPPOSED TO BE
ON MY SIDE!
WELL, YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
HER ROCK.
BUT INSTEAD YOU'RE MAKING
RASH DECISIONS,
AND BEING RECKLESS.
(SIGHS)
MAYBE IT'S TIME FOR THIS LITTLE
EXPERIMENT OF YOURS TO END.
I WOULD FEEL BETTER,
SO WOULD BIANCA.
THERE'S THE BIRTHDAY GIRL!
WAIT, DID YOU AGE OVERNIGHT?
I'LL ALWAYS BE YOUNGER
THAN YOU, OLD TIMER.
YOU WON'T MAKE THOSE JOKES WHEN
YOU'RE CLEANING HIS DENTURES.
ELI:
LOOK, I THOUGHT WE'D SPEND
YOUR BIRTHDAY EVENING TOGETHER,
BUT ALLI AND HER DUMB
SPA SURPRISE.
SHE ASKED YOU IF IT WAS OKAY?
TO BE HONEST, I DON'T REALLY
FEEL LIKE CELEBRATING
MY BIRTHDAY MUCH.
GO, IT'LL BE FUN.
CLARE:
I JUST DON'T SEE
WHAT THE POINT IS.
ELI:
CLARE, YOU HAVE TO LET THIS
WHOLE "INTERPRETER" THING GO,
IT'S JUST A STUPID CO-OP.
AND "ROMEO AND JULES"
IS JUST A STUPID MUSICAL.
HOW WOULD YOU FEEL IF THAT GOT
TAKEN AWAY FROM YOU?
IT'S HER BIRTHDAY,
SHE CAN BITE YOUR HEAD OFF
IF SHE WANTS.
ZIP IT, ADAM!
WHOA.
"CHEER CLARE UP" IS OFF
TO A ROARING START.
SUPER.
ALL WILL BE FORGIVEN TONIGHT.
A PARTY WON'T MAKE UP
FOR WHAT I JUST SAID.
WHAT ARE YOU GIVING HER?
A GIFT ALWAYS HELPS.
I'M GIVING HER A PARTY!
BUT NO GIFT?
BUT...
OH, DAMN. CRAP!
WHAT DO I GET HER?
WHAT DOES SHE WANT?
I DON'T KNOW,
HER INTERNSHIP BACK?!
WAIT.
I HAD A GOOD RAPPORT
WITH HER MENTOR
WHEN HE INTERVIEWED ME,
MAYBE I CAN CONVINCE HIM
TO GIVE CLARE A SECOND CHANCE!
IT'S WORTH A SHOT.
(TRAFFIC RUMBLES, HORN HONKS)
ASHER:
THE ONLY REASON THE MAYOR
EVEN ENTERTAINS HIM...
ELI:
OH, THANK YOU.
ASHER:
IS BECAUSE HE PRACTICALLY
PROPOSES MARRIAGE TO HIM
IN EVERY OP-ED.
WOMAN:
(LAUGHS) I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
ELI:
ASHER? HI, SORRY TO INTERRUPT.
HEY...
OH, HEY!
UH, ELI UM...
THE UH, THE MUSICAL GUY.
YEAH.
HOW GOES "ROMEO AND JULIET?"
UH, JULES.
RIGHT, HOW COULD I FORGET?
EVERYTHING WITH THE PLAY
IS EXCELLENT,
OPENING NIGHT
IS NEXT WEEK.
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU'RE NOT HERE TO COMPLAIN
ABOUT THE PRESS.
NO! THE ARTICLE YOU AND CLARE
WROTE WAS AMAZING.
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU?
I WANTED TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT...HER.
I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING TO SAY.
IN FACT, I'M LATE
FOR A PRESS CONFERENCE.
ELI:
CLARE LOVED THIS INTERNSHIP,
SHE WAS LEARNING SO MUCH
FROM YOU.
NOT ENOUGH TO KEEP HER JOB,
UNFORTUNATELY.
WELL, IS THERE ANY WAY
YOU'D CONSIDER RE-HIRING HER?
THIS IS THIS A JOKE.
SHE WOULD BE SO GRATEFUL
FOR A SECOND CHANCE.
YOU DON'T KNOW, DO YOU?
ELI, CLARE IS OBSESSED
WITH ME.
WELL SURE,
SHE IDOLIZES YOU.
NO, SHE IS IN LOVE WITH ME,
IT CAUSED A LOT OF PROBLEMS.
THE ONLY SOLUTION WAS
FOR HER TO BE FIRED.
YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
SORRY YOU HAD TO FIND OUT
LIKE THIS.
(HORN HONKS, CARS RUMBLE)
FIONA: HEY.
DREW: OH, HEY.
I BOUGHT YOU A KIDS' COMBO,
AND ACCIDENTALLY GOT YOU
THE GIRLS' TOY.
THAT'S UNEXPECTED,
BUT UH, THANKS.
WHAT?
I'M HOSTING AN EMERGENCY
SURPRISE BIRTHDAY PARTY
FOR CLARE EDWARDS
AT THE LOFT TONIGHT.
AND ALSO,
THIS IS AWKWARD,
HENCE THE FREE LUNCH,
CLARE'S STEP-BROTHER JAKE
IS BRINGING
HIS NEW GIRLFRIEND
TO THE PARTY.
KATIE.
KATIE?
WHAT, THEY'RE DATING NOW?
WOW, HE'S BRAVE.
YEAH, SO CAN YOU BE
SCARCE TONIGHT?
KEEP THINGS TENSION FREE?
FINE. OH, JUST A HEADS UP,
I MIGHT BE MOVING OUT.
OKAY OVERREACTOR,
YOU CAN COME TO THE PARTY
IF YOU WANT.
NO, MY MOM AND BIANCA
WANT ME BACK HOME,
AND IN SCHOOL.
I KEEP TRYING TO PROVE TO THEM
THAT I DID THE RIGHT THING,
IT JUST BACKFIRES ON ME.
SO YOU'RE GIVING UP?
I BOUGHT A MOTORCYCLE.
SO? I BOUGHT A VESPA ONCE.
DO YOU KNOW HOW MANY TIMES
I'VE BEEN TOLD TO GO HOME,
GIVE UP, LET SOMEONE ELSE
TAKE CARE OF ME?
MORE TIMES THAN
I CAN COUNT.
IF YOU WANT PEOPLE
TO TAKE YOU SERIOUSLY,
THEN BE SERIOUS.
(PHONE BEEPS)
OOH! I'VE GOT
A CONFETTI CANNON
BEING DELIVERED IN TWENTY.
DALLAS:
HEY, FIONA.
GOOD TALK.
WHERE'S SHE OFF TO?
UH, SHE'S PLANNING
A BIRTHDAY PARTY
FOR THIS GIRL CLARE
AT OUR HOUSE TONIGHT.
CLARE EDWARDS?
YEAH, WHY?
YOU KNOW HER?
SURE, WE'RE LIKE, BFFS!
REALLY?
I AM SO OUT OF THE LOOP.
YEAH, I SHOULD STOP BY
THAT PARTY.
WISH CLARE A HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
DREW:
YEAH WELL,
I'LL BE HERE CLOSING.
TRYING TO FIND A WAY
TO BE SERIOUS.
♪♪♪
(PARTY GUESTS LAUGH, CHATTER)
DAVE: HELLO, BABY!
IMOGEN: OH, HEY!
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
OKAY, SHE'S HERE!
SHE'S HERE!
HAS ANYONE SEEN ELI?
UM, I'LL TEXT
HIM AGAIN.
IT'S SO WEIRD THAT
HE'S NOT HERE YET.
OKAY IMMY,
LIGHTS AND CONFETTI?
AYE-AYE!
I'M GONNA MAKE IT RAIN!
OH! THERE YOU ARE!
YOU ARE SO LATE, ALLI TEXTED
TO SAY THEIR CAB PULLED UP!
THEY DIDN'T SEE YOU,
DID THEY?
OH, I HATE SPOILERS!
I DON'T THINK SO.
HIDE!
WHAT'S WRONG?
CLARE'S IN LOVE WITH HER
JOURNALISM MENTOR.
NOW I HAVE TO TALK TO HER
AND SEE WHAT'S UP.
FIONA:
OKAY, MAYBE DON'T BRING IT UP
TONIGHT?
IT'S HER BIRTHDAY.
ALLI:
I DON'T KNOW,
I THINK THIS IS THE PLACE.
CLARE:
ALLI, THIS DOES NOT LOOK
LIKE A SPA.
ALL:
SURPRISE!
OH MY GOD!
(GRUNTING WITH EFFORT)
GUY:
WHOO! YEAH!
THIS IS SO GREAT, THANK YOU.
PARTY GOERS:
HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU DID THIS!
I LOVE YOU.
WAIT, WHAT'S WRONG?
I SAW ASHER TODAY.
YOU WHAT?!
I WENT TO "THE INTERPRETER"
TO SEE IF HE CAN GIVE YOU
A SECOND SHOT.
AND WHAT DID HE TELL YOU?
YOU WERE IN LOVE
WITH HIM.
OBSESSED, HE SAID,
AND THAT'S WHY YOU GOT FIRED.
IT'S NOT TRUE.
ELI-
TELL ME IT'S NOT TRUE!
DALLAS:
HELLO!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, SWEETHEART!
GOT YOUR FAVOURITE BRAND.
WHAT'S THAT JOCK TALKING ABOUT?
I GUESS THERE'S A LOT YOUR
GIRLFRIEND DOESN'T TELL YOU.
OOH, IS THAT
A BUFFET TABLE?
ELI:
OKAY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
COME ON CLARE,
TALK TO ME!
KATIE:
I CANNOT BELIEVE THAT ASS
CRASHED YOUR BIRTHDAY!
YEAH, WE HAVE TO KICK THEM OUT!
NO! JUST DON'T PROVOKE THEM,
IT'S FINE.
IT'S FINE?!
WHY THE HELL DID
HE GIVE YOU BEER?
DALLAS IS JUST BEING
A JERK, OKAY?
DALLAS:
NAME CALLING?
THAT'S NOT VERY NICE.
SHUT UP!
DALLAS:
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO ABOUT IT?
WRITE ANOTHER ARTICLE
IN THE SCHOOL PAPER?
CAN YOU JUST LEAVE?!
OOH WEEE!
THIS IS DRAMATIC!
DID CLARE FINALLY FESS UP
ABOUT HER MENTOR?
ACTUALLY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
NEVER MIND.
I CAN KEEP A SECRET.
THERE IS MORE, I KNEW IT!
WHAT HAPPENED BETWEEN YOU
AND ASHER?
TELL ME!
I CAN'T.
ALLI:
ELI, YOU CAN'T LEAVE,
IT'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK!
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO KNOW
WHAT TO THINK?
SHE'S BEEN LYING TO ME
FOR WEEKS!
CLARE IS COMPLETELY MESSED UP
RIGHT NOW,
SHE NEEDS YOU!
SHE WON'T EVEN TALK TO ME!
SO MAKE HER!
PLEASE!
BIANCA:
OOH! OOH!
BE RIGHT BACK, MAN.
DREW: HEY.
BIANCA: HI!
THANKS FOR COMING.
I TALKED TO MY MOM, AND SHE
GAVE ME A LOT TO THINK ABOUT.
ABOUT MY SITUATION,
ABOUT US.
SHE THINKS YOU NEED ME
TO BE MORE SERIOUS.
I GUESS I DO.
OKAY.
THEN, LET'S HAVE A SERIOUS
CONVERSATION, BIANCA.
SIT DOWN.
BIANCA:
OKAY...
I LOVE YOU.
AND I WANT TO SPEND THE REST
OF MY LIFE WITH YOU.
DREW...
WILL YOU,
BIANCA L. DESOUSA,
MAKE ME THE HAPPIEST
MAN ALIVE,
AND...
OPEN A JOINT SAVINGS
BANK ACCOUNT WITH ME?
WHAT?!
I'M GONNA DEPOSIT ALL
MY COMMISSION INTO IT.
IT'S FOR YOUR TUITION,
CAR REPAIRS,
WHATEVER WE NEED.
I'M GONNA TAKE CARE OF US,
I PROMISE.
THERE'S ONLY ABOUT
A HUNDRED DOLLARS IN THERE NOW,
BUT THERE'LL BE MORE ONCE
I SELL THE MOTORCYCLE TOMORROW.
OH, YOU'RE GONNA SELL IT?
CONCUSSIONS, REMEMBER?
WELL, I DON'T HAVE
ANY CONCUSSIONS.
DAVE:
THERE'S MY GIRL! OH!
DAVE, SERIOUSLY?!
I'LL CLEAN IT UP,
YOU GUYS GO GET YOURSELF
ANOTHER PLATE.
I'M SORRY.
ALLI:
WOW, SOMEONE NEEDS
TO GET A ROOM.
WHAT, I THINK IT'S KIND
OF SWEET.
ALLI:
WOW, THAT MUSICAL HAS DONE
A NUMBER ON YOUR HEAD, HUH?
LOOK, WE NEED TO TALK.
I HAVE TO GO PEE.
PEE FIRST, TALK AFTER?
YEAH...
♪ Well, you make a fist
burnin' ♪
♪ And you're falling apart ♪
♪ You can take it out on me
you can give me a scar ♪
♪ Don't run away... ♪
I THOUGHT YOU LEFT.
ALLI MADE ME STAY.
SHE'S BEEN BEGGING ME
TO TELL YOU.
THEN DO IT!
I DON'T-
YOU HAVE TO TELL ME
RIGHT NOW.
IT'S GONNA CHANGE
EVERYTHING.
I DON'T CARE!
I CAN'T DO THIS ANYMORE.
THE NIGHT THAT ASHER AND I
RE-WROTE THE ARTICLE
ON THE PLAY,
HE KISSED ME.
WE TALKED,
AND HE APOLOGIZED,
AND I THOUGHT
I'D HANDLED IT.
BUT THEN HE TRIED AGAIN.
SO I COMPLAINED TO HIS BOSS,
AND I GOT FIRED.
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
I DON'T KNOW!
JUST ADD IT TO THE LIST
OF THE OTHER THINGS
I'VE DONE WRONG!
I IDOLIZED ASHER-
WRONG!
I DIDN'T FILE A FORMAL
COMPLAINT RIGHT AWAY,
I DIDN'T GO TO THE POLICE-
WRONG, WRONG!
(SOBS)
I FEEL SO GROSS
AND GUILTY.
ASHER WAS RIGHT TO FIRE ME,
IT'S MY FAULT IT HAPPENED.
NO.
THAT BASTARD ABUSED
HIS POSITION,
AND YOU GOT SCREWED.
SO YOU DON'T BLAME ME?
NO.
YOU THOUGHT I'D GO CRAZY,
DIDN'T YOU?
INSTEAD, I WENT CRAZY
ON MY OWN.
WE'LL GET THROUGH THIS.
(SOBBING)
(BIKE RUMBLES)
(ENGINE IDLES, CUTS OFF)
YOU SAID TEN MINUTES
LIKE, A HALF AN HOUR AGO.
BUT IT WAS JUST SO AWESOME!
I KNOW, BUT IT'S STILL GETTING
SOLD TOMORROW.
WHEN DID YOU BECOME
SO RESPONSIBLE?
♪♪♪
♪ All we do is mess around ♪
♪ But I know that it's love
we've found ♪
(SIGHS)
♪ And I know that it's here
to stay... ♪
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
(SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
COME HERE.
WHAT?
DREW:
JUST COME HERE, TRUST ME.
MARRY ME.
SURE, DUMMY.
I'M SUPPOSED TO BE SAVING
ALL OUR MONEY,
SO...THIS WILL HAVE TO DO
FOR NOW.
YOU'RE ACTUALLY PROPOSING
TO ME RIGHT NOW?
YES, I'M-I'M SERIOUS.
I LOVE YOU, YOU KNOW THAT.
I LOVE YOU TOO.
OR DOES...
DOES THAT MEAN IT'S A NO?
NO.
NO, IT'S NOT A NO?
NO, IT'S NOT A NO.
WHAT?!
YES. YES!
IT'S A YES.
♪ It's like a big blue wave ♪
♪ Don't tell me
that we've come this far ♪
(PARTYGOERS CHATTER)
I FEEL BAD
LEAVING EVERYONE.
THEY'LL GET OVER IT.
DALLAS:
BIRTHDAY GIRL DITCHING
HER OWN PARTY?!
OKAY, HAVEN'T YOU DONE
ENOUGH DAMAGE?
GET THE HELL OUT OF MY WAY!
YOUR GIRL SHOULDN'TVE MESSED
WITH MY HOCKEY SEASON.
HEY, WHY DON'T YOU JUST LEAVE?!
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
SHUT YOUR DAMN MOUTH!
YOU KNOW WHAT, DUDE, I HAVE
SERIOUSLY HAD ENOUGH OF YOU!
OH, YOU WANNA GET INTO IT
TOO, TREE HUGGER?
DALLAS:
YEAH, THIS IS MORE LIKE IT!
LET'S SEE WHAT GARDEN BOY
AND THEATRE GEEK-
OOF!
(PARTYGOERS EXCLAIMING LOUDLY)
GUYS, STOP IT!
(GUYS GRUNT WITH EFFORT)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
OH!
YOU GUYS, STOP IT!
GET OFF OF HIM!
CLARE:
LET GO!
OH! OH!
ALLI:
DAVE! LET GO, LET GO OF ME!
IMOGEN:
GUYS!
HOCKEY PLAYER:
OW!
(EXPLOSION NOISE)
IMOGEN:
FIONES!
I MADE IT RAIN!
FINALLY!
FIONA:
DALLAS, GET OUT BEFORE
I CALL THE COPS!
FIONA-
DON'T!
JUST LEAVE!
SEE EVERYONE AT SCHOOL!
(GROANS)
YOU'RE GOING DOWN, ELI!
ARE YOU OKAY?
I'M FINE.
MY HAND,
ON THE OTHER HAND...
WELL, YOU CERTAINLY SWOOPED IN
AND RESCUED ME BACK THERE.
DO YOU WANT A HANDSHAKE
OR SOMETHING?
WHAT IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
LOOK, I WOULD NEVER
LET ANYBODY HURT YOU.
BUT THINGS HAVE CHANGED, ALLI.
THIS ISN'T HAPPENING.
WE'RE GROWING APART.
AND I KNOW YOU KNOW THAT,
AND I CAN'T KEEP PRETENDING.
BUT I DO LOVE YOU, DAVE!
BUT BETWEEN YOUR CLASSES,
YOUR STUDY BREAKS-
IT'S NOT ALL GONNA BE
AN EPIC ROMANCE!
MAYBE NOT, BUT I DON'T WANT
TO SETTLE FOR LESS.
SO THIS IS ALL MY FAULT?!
YOU'VE CHECKED OUT EVER SINCE
YOU GOT INTO MIT!
WELL, EXCUSE ME
FOR HAVING A FUTURE!
I'VE ALWAYS SUPPORTED
YOUR FUTURE.
YOU KNOW THAT.
I JUST CAN'T KEEP DEALING WITH
YOU TREATING ME LIKE CRAP!
FINE.
YOU WANNA TALK?
I ALREADY HAVE.
WE'RE DONE.
(ELI GROANS)
CLARE:
I KNOW IT HURTS,
BUT IF YOU HADN'T PUNCHED
DALLAS I WOULD HAVE.
THE GUY'S FACE
IS LIKE A BRICK WALL.
IT WAS STUPID OF ME
TO GO AFTER THE HOCKEY TEAM
WHEN ASHER IS REALLY
THE PROBLEM.
SO MUCH FOR PROJECTING.
HE HAS TO PAY FOR
WHAT HE DID.
I WISH!
THAT'S ALL
I EVER THINK ABOUT.
ASHER JUST SITS IN HIS
BIG OFFICE AT "THE INTERPRETER"
AND THE WORLD CONTINUES
TO THINK HE'S WONDERFUL.
HE'S GOTTEN AWAY WITH IT.
I DON'T ACCEPT THAT.
ARE YOU GONNA DO
SOMETHING TO HIM?
NO.
WE ARE.
TOGETHER.