(VIDEO GAME ACTION MUSIC PLAYS)
ELI:
WE NEED TO DESTROY
THE TITAN.
MO, CREATE A DIVERSION.
I'M GOING IN
WITH A FORCE BLAST.
JAKE:
NO, NO, NO! DON'T DO IT.
IT'S TOO RISKY.
NO, I HAVE TO!
FORCE FIELD'S UP.
MO:
YOO-HOO! OVER HERE, SUCKERS!
BY THE TIME
I'M THROUGH WITH YOU,
YOU'LL BE NOTHING
BUT LIFELESS BODIES.
NOW'S YOUR CHANCE, ELI!
COME ON, GO, GO, GO, GO!
JAKE:
(WHISPERING LOUDLY)
LIFELESS BODIES?
YOU CAN'T SAY CRAP
LIKE THAT!
HE'S STILL GETTING OVER
FINDING CAM'S BODY
IN THE GREENHOUSE.
I CAN HEAR YOU.
SORRY.
BACK TO HOVER-CAR RACING.
ELI:
FORCE FIELD'S UP.
ALL:
(YELLING OVER EACH OTHER)
YOU HAVE 'EM ON THE LEFT!
GO, GO, GO, GO!
(TV CLICKS OFF)
ELI: NOOOO! WHAT?!
MO: NO! COME ON!
MO:
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME!
JAKE:
I DON'T WANNA PLAY THIS GAME
ANYMORE.
FIONA:
GAME OVER, NERDS.
WHAT DID YOU
JUST CALL US?
I HAVE A FILM PROPOSAL
FOR YOU.
MY CAREER'S ON HOLD,
REMEMBER?
CLARE SAID THAT WORKING ON
MY ZOMBIE MOVIE
WOULDN'T BE GOOD FOR ME.
FIONA:
I GUARANTEE A BIG AUDIENCE.
YOU'LL MAKE 'EM LAUGH,
CRY, AND...
FIFTY YEARS FROM NOW,
THEY'LL STILL BE WATCHING!
(SIGHS)
ARE YOU GONNA TELL ME
WHAT IT IS?
NOT UNTIL YOU AGREE
TO DO IT.
JAKE:
YEAH, DO IT!
I REALLY WANNA KNOW.
ME TOO.
(SIGHS)
THIS BETTER BE GOOD.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
(Ooh-ooh-ooh)
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
DO THEY REALLY HAVE TO BARRICADE
THE GARDEN?
IT'S SO MISERABLE.
ELI:
CRAZIEST THING
YOU'VE DONE ALL YEAR?
UH... ME AND MARISOL SNUCK
INTO HOME EC ONE TIME
FOR A MAKE-OUT SESH,
AND WELL...
WAIT, WHO'S GONNA BE
SEEING THIS?
ELI:
NOW TELL ME
YOUR BIGGEST REGRET.
UM... NO COMMENT.
DO MY EYES DECEIVE ME?
ELI:
I HAVE A NEW PROJECT:
VIDEO YEARBOOK.
IT'S SO MUCH BETTER
THAN VIDEO GAMES, NO?
WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU GOT FIONA TO ASK ME
TO DO THIS, DIDN'T YOU?
WELL, I THOUGHT IT'D BE
GOOD FOR YOU.
IT'S BEEN OVER A WEEK
SINCE THE...GREENHOUSE,
AND WE HAVEN'T REALLY
TALKED ABOUT IT.
IT'S NOT EXACTLY
MY FAVOURITE TOPIC.
YOU KNOW,
I SHOULD UM...
I SHOULD GET BACK
TO THIS.
(RECORD BUTTON BEEPS)
OKAY.
ELI:
HEY! SWEATPANTS GIRL!
WHERE DO YOU SEE YOURSELF
IN TEN YEARS?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
BUT I DO KNOW WHERE I'LL BE
TOMORROW NIGHT.
(CAMERA BEEPS)
AND MY NAME'S TALIA,
CAMERA BOY.
KATIE:
HEY! UM, SO THINGS ARE
REALLY LOOKING UP!
I GOT APPROVED
FOR A $10,000 LOAN,
ALL I NEED IS A KICK-ASS
SUMMER JOB
AND THEN I CAN GO
TO STANFORD!
GOD, MY LIFE IS
FALLING APART
AND YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT TUITION.
WHAT'S WRONG?
GOD, EVERYTHING!
I WAS ON THE PHONE WITH MO
FOR HOURS LAST NIGHT, CRYING.
OH, THIS BREAK UP
IS THE WORST!
OH MY GOD!
I DIDN'T REALIZE YOU AND MO
WERE HAVING PROBLEMS.
NOT ME AND MO!
YOU AND JAKE.
OKAY, WOW,
YOU REALLY NEED A HOBBY.
WHENEVER I ASK MO TO HANG OUT,
HE ASKS IF YOU'RE COMING,
AND WHEN YOU ARE
HE CAN'T INVITE JAKE,
AND THEN MO'S SAD,
AND THEN LIFE SUCKS.
WHY IS THIS MY PROBLEM?
WELL, BECAUSE IT'S THE END
OF THE SCHOOL YEAR!
WE HAVE TO BE A BIG
HAPPY FAMILY AGAIN.
DO YOU HAVE TO REFER TO US
AS A FAMILY?
IT'S LIKE INCEST-Y
AND... UGH!
OKAY,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN,
AND I KNOW YOU MISS JAKE.
WHY DON'T WE ALL HAVE
LUNCH TOGETHER,
LIKE OLD TIMES?
OKAY. FINE.
OH! HERE.
DON'T BE A BYSTANDER!
STOP BULLYING!
AND REMEMBER,
THERE'S ALWAYS SOMEONE
WHO CARES ABOUT YOU.
FRIENDS, FAMILY,
THE GUY UPSTAIRS...
LUKE:
YOUR BEST FRIEND'S BROTHER?
DIDN'T KNOW YOU CARED ABOUT ME.
HOW COULD YOU SAY THAT?
YOU KISSED ME
THEN PUSHED ME AWAY,
REMEMBER?
YEAH, WELL,
PEOPLE CAN CHANGE.
WHY NOT? HERE.
SO HOW'VE YOU BEEN
SINCE EVERYTHING?
WEIRD.
I'VE BEEN PRAYING A LOT.
TEAM'S DIFFERENT
WITHOUT HIM.
WELL, IF YOU EVER
NEED TO TALK...
(LOUD CRASH,
STUDENTS LAUGH)
(LAUGHS)
DO YOU THINK ANYONE
WILL EVER CARE ABOUT HIM?
EXCUSE ME?
COME ON,
IT WAS A JOKE.
AM I LAUGHING?
CONNOR'S WAY COOLER
THAN YOU'LL EVER BE.
LIKE YOU'VE EVER EVEN
TALKED TO HIM.
HERE.
WHY DID YOU JUST KISS ME?
JUST GO WITH IT.
THANKS.
ANYTIME.
DON'T BE A BYSTANDER!
STOP BULLYING!
REMEMBER, THERE'S ALWAYS SOMEONE
WHO CARES ABOUT YOU!
SUCKS THEY BOARDED UP
YOUR GARDEN.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA
DO NOW?
JAKE:
I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, DOES WHISPERHUG
NEED A SINGER?
(SINGING BADLY)
♪ EVERYBODY STAND UP,
EVERYBODY MEANS YOU! ♪
MARISOL:
KATIE! YOU MADE IT!
KATIE:
HEY.
I GUESS MARISOL
DIDN'T TELL YOU GUYS
I WAS COMING.
LOOK, I REALLY WANT
TO APOLOGIZE FOR VEGAS.
MO:
LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT.
YOU WANNA APOLOGIZE
FOR BEING A-
MO!
ALMOST, BUT WITH AN H
INSTEAD OF AN M.
(UNDER HIS BREATH)
HO.
MARISOL:
ANYWAYS!
SO, KATIE, ANY LUCK
FINDING A SUMMER JOB?
KATIE:
UM, YEAH, ACTUALLY,
MY MOM KNOWS SOMEONE
WHO MIGHT NEED
AN AU PAIR.
I DON'T KNOW
HOW MUCH IT PAYS YET, BUT...
(WHISPERING AND LAUGHING)
IS SOMETHING FUNNY?
UH... NO,
JUST CURIOUS, KATIE.
ARE YOU GONNA PUT "PRO"
ON YOUR RESUME?
ARE YOU REFERRING
TO PROSTITUTION?
MO:
(LAUGHING) YEAH.
KATIE:
UH, NO,
BECAUSE I DIDN'T SLEEP
WITH ANYONE.
AND YOU GUYS ARE BEING
INCREDIBLY RUDE.
JAKE:
OH, WE'RE RUDE? OKAY.
JAKE, I'M JUST TRYING
TO APOLOGIZE.
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
GOOD FOR YOU, KATIE.
I HOPE YOU FEEL BETTER,
OKAY?
'CAUSE I DON'T.
JAKE, DUDE.
♪ Slow down ♪
♪ There's nothing after you ♪
♪ Back down ♪
IMOGEN: I'M IMOGEN!
FIONA: I'M FIONA!
IMOGEN:
AND... WE'RE GIRLFRIENDS!
BOTH:
(LAUGHING)
TRISTAN:
FACERANGE PROFILE PIC.
(LAUGHS)
IMOGEN:
AT THE FESTIVAL!
FIONA:
FESTIVAL 2011!
(VIDEO REWINDS)
♪ Calm down ♪
♪ There's nothing after you ♪
♪♪♪
(PANICKED BREATHS,
LAPTOP SNAPS SHUT)
HI, JENNA.
UM, I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT RECOMMENDED GIFT
FOR GIRLS YOU'D PREFER,
SO I GOT YOU
ONE OF EACH.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO THANK ME, CONNOR.
OH! THIS ISN'T
A THANK YOU.
UM, I'M ASKING YOU OUT.
DO YOU WANNA GO ON
A DATE WITH ME?
I CAN'T.
ARE YOU SEEING
SOMEONE ELSE?
NO.
DID YOU LIKE HANGING OUT
WITH ME
DURING ROMEO AND JULES?
YEAH. WE HAD SOME
GOOD LAUGHS, BUT-
DO YOU THINK
I'M ATTRACTIVE?
WAIT! HOLD ON.
WHAT ABOUT NOW?
(LAUGHS)
YOU'RE CUTE, YES.
EVEN WITH THE GLASSES ON.
SO THERE'S NO REASON
FOR YOU TO SAY NO,
IS THERE?
I GUESS NOT.
IT'S A DATE!
(BELL RINGS)
(LAUGHS)
♪♪♪
(GLUGGING SOUND)
(LIQUID DRIPS)
(MUTED SCREAM)
AGGGGHHHHHHHHHHH!
AGGGHHHHHH!
ELI:
THANKS FOR MEETING ME
SO EARLY.
DR. WESTON:
OF COURSE. IT'S ALWAYS GOOD
TO SEE YOU, ELI.
I THINK SOMETHING'S WRONG
WITH ME.
WHAT MAKES YOU SAY THAT?
OKAY, FIRST, MY EX, JULIA,
NOW CAM?
I THINK I ATTRACT DEATH.
BUT IT'S A PART OF LIFE,
ELI,
AND YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND
IT HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH YOU.
IT'S JUST HOW MANY TIMES
DO I ACTUALLY HAVE
TO RELIVE IT, YOU KNOW?
MANY THINK THAT TALKING
IS THE ONLY WAY
TO DEAL WITH TRAUMA.
IT'S NOT.
FOR SOME,
IT'S JUST AS IMPORTANT
TO FOCUS ON
DAY-TO-DAY LIVING.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
I SHOULD DO?
WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK
IS BEST FOR YOU?
NOT TALK ABOUT CAM
SO MUCH.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE GO ON
A FUN DATE WITH CLARE.
I'M ALLOWED TO HAVE FUN,
RIGHT?
YES. ABSOLUTELY.
OKAY.
ALLI:
I ALMOST FORGOT
IT WAS FRIDAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS!
YOUR PARENTS HAVE
SALSA DANCING,
WHICH MEANS
YOU'RE COOKING.
I'M THINKING CORN CHOWDER
TO START,
AND STUFFED MAYO-CRAB
MUSHROOMS -
MINUS THE FOOD POISONING
THIS TIME.
TEMPTING,
BUT I HAVE PLANS.
IT'S A DATE, ACTUALLY.
OH! WELL, THAT EXPLAINS
THE CUTE HAIR
AND HINT OF CLEAVE!
WHO'S THE LUCKY GUY?
CONNOR.
CONNOR...
CONNOR CONNOR?
AS IN CONNOR DELAURIER?
OH! UM... WELL...
(CHUCKLES)
CONNOR IS... NICE...
AND TALL...
AND OVER THAT WHOLE
UNDERWEAR-STEALING PHASE,
I HOPE.
THAT WAS
A LONG TIME AGO,
AND LIKE YOU'VE NEVER DONE
SOMETHING CREEPY
YOU DON'T REGRET,
SEXTER!
OKAY,
ALSO A LONG TIME AGO.
IT'S ONE INNOCENT DATE
AFTER SCHOOL.
HE KNEW WHAT HE WANTED
AND HE WOULDN'T TAKE NO
FOR AN ANSWER.
HIS PERSISTENCE WAS...
SEXY.
SEXY?
HEY! ARE WE STILL ON
FOR AFTER SCHOOL?
AFFIRMATIVE.
THIS IS FOR YOU.
(CHUCKLES)
UM, TO WEAR OVER
YOUR CLOTHES LATER.
(LAUGHS AND COUGHS)
JENNA:
WHERE ARE WE GOING?
SPACE.
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
TRISTAN:
...GO AHEAD. DON'T SAY ANYTHING
IF I CAN TAKE YOUR SANDWICH.
OH, YOU WIN!
KATIE:
HEY, HEY, HEY!
TRISTAN AND TORI:
OH, HEY!
MAYA:
WHERE ARE YOUR FRIENDS?
UM, I'D RATHER SIT
WITH YOU GUYS.
SO, UM, WHAT'RE YOU GUYS
UP TO TONIGHT?
WANNA SEE A MOVIE
OR SOMETHING?
TORI:
OH! WE'RE GOING
TO LITTLE MISS STEAKS
TO WATCH MAYA AT OPEN MIC.
MAYA:
MOM AND DAD SAID
IT WAS OKAY.
WELL, YOU GUYS MIND
IF I CRASH?
IF THIS IS ABOUT CAM
AND MY WELL BEING,
MY BEING IS WELL.
LOOK.
WHAT? I CAN'T WANNA SPEND TIME
WITH MY LITTLE SISTER?
JUST DON'T EMBARRASS ME,
'KAY?
OKAY.
THANKS.
COME HERE.
FIONA:
ROMEO AND JULES WAS HUGE
THIS YEAR.
IMOGEN:
I BUILT THE SETS!
TRISTAN:
UM, I GOT THE LEAD IN
THE MUSICAL ROMEO AND JULES.
WELL, I DON'T MEAN TO BRAG,
BUT LIKE EVERYONE LOVED IT.
IT WAS PRETTY MUCH
THE BEST MUSICAL EVER!
DALLAS:
WE LIVE FOR THIS SYMBOL.
THAT IS MY LIFE.
BOTH:
GO ICE HOUNDS!
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
DAVE:
ICE HOUNDS!
(BARK-LIKE GRUNTS)
MAYA:
YEAH, WHISPERHUG,
ONLY LIKE THE BIGGEST BAND
AT DEGRASSI, EVER!
(VIDEO PAUSES)
DALLAS:
WHERE'S CAM?
ELI:
I DIDN'T INCLUDE HIM.
OH, WELL,
I THOUGHT WE'D GIVE HIM
A SMALL TRIBUTE
OR SOMETHING.
I'M NOT SURE A TRIBUTE'S
REALLY WARRANTED.
IT'S WEIRD MESSAGING.
OKAY, FINE.
BUT TO CROP HIM OUT ENTIRELY?
HE DID STILL GO HERE.
CAN YOU PUT HIM
BACK IN?
YEAH.
YEAH, OF COURSE.
(BELL RINGS)
ARE YOU GONNA BE OKAY
DOING THAT?
ELI:
YEAH, I'LL JUST RUSH
THROUGH IT TONIGHT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'S FRIDAY.
LET'S GO OUT.
WHERE DID YOU GET THAT?
A RANDOM GIRL
GAVE IT TO ME.
SHOULD BE FUN.
YOU WANNA GO PARTY
WITH RANDOM PEOPLE?
A RANDOM ADVENTURE.
UH, A RANDVENTURE!
I THINK YOU'RE AVOIDING
THE YEARBOOK.
DO YOU WANT ME TO STAY
AND HELP YOU?
UM... YOU KNOW WHAT?
UM, IT'S OKAY.
I'LL JUST FOCUS
ON TONIGHT
AND, UH, GET 'ER DONE.
OKAY.
WELL, IF YOU CAN'T DO IT ALONE,
JUST UH... JUST CALL ME.
I'LL COME STRAIGHT OVER
AND WE'LL TALK, OKAY?
(MO AND JAKE CHATTER)
JAKE:
ELI!
MO:
YO! FATAL INERTIA TOURNAMENT
TONIGHT?
ELI:
NAH, GUYS, I'M EDITING.
JAKE:
(DISAPPOINTED) OH...
UNLESS...
YOU GUYS CAN FIGURE
THIS OUT.
OH! I'VE HEARD OF
THESE BEFORE.
THIS IS SICK.
WATCH THIS.
ELI:
THINGS JUST GOT SCI-FI
UP IN HERE.
JAKE:
YOU ARE BLOWING MY MIND.
I'M BLOWING MY OWN MIND.
IT'S A SECRET PARTY.
MY COUSIN WENT TO ONE.
THEY'RE SUPPOSED TO BE SICK.
SO WE HAVE TO GO THEN!
MARISOL'S GONNA
LOVE THIS, DUDE.
TEXTING CLARE?
MO, SINCE OUR MAN JAKE'S
SINGLE,
I THINK WE SHOULD KEEP IT
A GUYS' NIGHT.
NO GIRLFRIENDS?
NO GIRLFRIENDS.
WOO! BOYS NIGHT OUT!
(LAUGHS)
(AWKWARDLY)
SORRY.
(DRAMATIC FILM MUSIC)
♪♪♪
JENNA:
WHOA.
HEADSET.
(COMPUTER BEEPS AND WHIRS)
READY?
OKAY.
(BUTTON CLICKS)
FIVE, FOUR, THREE...
IGNITION!
AND LIFTOFF.
(SIMULATOR ENGINES RUMBLE)
AMAZING!
MAYA:
♪ DO-DO-DO-DO DO! ♪
♪ LA-LA LA ♪
♪ CHANGE IT UP,
DO SOMETHING NEW ♪
♪ DON'T LET YOURSELF
GET AWAY FROM YOU ♪
SO DID YOU DUMP JAKE
OR DID HE DUMP YOU?
TORI:
TRISTAN!
UM, IT'S COMPLICATED.
LET'S JUST SAY
I GOT AN OFFER
THAT I THOUGHT
WAS A GOOD THING.
TURNS OUT IT COULD'VE
RUINED MY LIFE,
AND I LOST JAKE
IN THE PROCESS.
BUT WHATEVER, RIGHT?
(LAUGHS, EMBARRASSED)
(UNDER HIS BREATH)
WOW.
MAYA:
♪ DO-DO-DO-DO DO ♪
♪ LA-LA LA ♪
(EVERYONE CLAPS)
TORI: YAY!
TRISTAN:
WOO!
KATIE: SHE'S JUST SO GOOD!
TORI: THAT WAS SO AMAZING.
THAT WAS SO BEAUTIFUL.
TRISTAN:
OH MY GOD, I'M CRYING.
LOOK.
LOOK. THIS GUY GAVE ME
HIS BUSINESS CARD
HE SAID I CAN COME HERE
AND PLAY WHENEVER I WANT.
PRETTY COOL, RIGHT?
WAIT. WHO GAVE YOU
HIS BUSINESS CARD?
HIM.
HE'S ONE OF THE MANAGERS HERE.
HE SAID I HAD A NATURAL CHARM
WITH THE AUDIENCE.
(GIGGLES, PLEASED)
HMM...
I'M SURE HE DID.
JENNA:
UM, WHAT'S THAT BUNDLE
OF TWINKLY THINGS OVER THERE?
THAT RIGHT THERE?
THAT'S A STAR CLUSTER.
GLOBULAR, TO BE EXACT.
YOU REALLY KNOW
YOUR SOLAR SYSTEM.
CONNOR:
YEAH, WELL, I GOT A TELESCOPE
FOR MY EIGHTH BIRTHDAY
AND STAYED UP ALL NIGHT
SEARCHING FOR
EXTRATERRESTRIAL LIFE,
HOPING THAT THEY MIGHT BE
LIKE ME.
WHY HAVE YOU NEVER HAD
A GIRLFRIEND?
MR. SIMPSON SAYS
THAT MY BRUTAL HONESTY
AND PASSION FOR SCIENCE
ARE THINGS THAT GIRLS
MAY NOT APPRECIATE
IN HIGH SCHOOL,
BUT WILL LATER ON
IN LIFE.
WELL, AFTER BEING LIED TO
BY A FEW GUYS,
I CAN GET BEHIND
BRUTAL HONESTY.
YOU'RE JUST SAYING THAT
BECAUSE I HAVEN'T
OFFENDED YOU YET.
(LAUGHS)
YOU CAN TELL ME
IF I'M WRONG, BUT...
YOU SEEM LIKE
YOU WANT TO KISS.
AM I THAT OBVIOUS?
CONNOR:
OBVIOUS IS GOOD,
BUT...
SHOULD I MOVE IN?
♪ We can see the eye and life
of the storm ♪
♪ Under silvery stars
we'll burn ♪
DID I...
DID I DO IT RIGHT?
UM, LET'S TRY IT AGAIN.
JUST THIS TIME,
DON'T STOP.
♪♪♪
(DOOR BANGS SHUT)
ELI:
ALL RIGHT, THE MAP SAYS
WE'RE HERE,
AND I CAN HEAR MUSIC.
ALL RIGHT,
FOLLOW ME.
MO:
WAIT... INTO THE DARKNESS?
JAKE:
OH, NO, NO, NO.
DON'T BE SCARED,
JUST HOLD ONTO MY WAIST.
MO: OKAY.
JAKE: THERE YOU GO.
(ELECTRONICA MUSIC PLAYS,
PEOPLE CHATTER)
MO:
IS THIS SOME SORT OF
TEEN PURGATORY OR SOMETHING?
I DUNNO...
BUT I LIKE IT!
MO:
(LAUGHING EXCITEDLY)
(BUCKET CLATTERS,
ELI GRUNTS)
JAKE:
ELI! YOU GETTING IN ON THIS?
UH, YEAH, YEAH.
UM... DO YOU HAVE ANY WEED
ON YOU?
UH, NO, NO.
I'M DRY.
WHY? ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH, YEAH.
UM, SOMEBODY ASKED ME, SO.
OH, OKAY. OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
I MIGHT BE ABLE
TO HELP YOU.
WHAT, YOU HAVE A JOINT?
MDMA. TADA!
UH, I'M OKAY.
REALLY?
LOOK, I DON'T MEAN TO GO
ALL PEER PRESSURE ON YOU.
IF YOU WANT IT,
YOU KNOW WHERE TO FIND ME.
WAIT.
WAIT!
SHOW ME YOUR TONGUE.
TRISTAN:
YEAH, I'M SURE YOU GOT THEM
ALL ON THE BULL'S EYE AGAIN.
MAYA: SHUT UP!
TORI: SURE!
MANAGER:
MAYA, DON'T FORGET TO CALL,
OKAY?
KATIE: UNGH!
MANAGER: OH!
DIRTBAG!
WE NEED TO GET OUTTA HERE.
MANAGER:
WHAT THE HELL?!
MAYA:
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?!
KATIE:
NO GUY JUST HANDS OUT
HIS BUSINESS CARDS
WITHOUT WANTING SOMETHING
IN RETURN.
MAYA:
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU
IN VEGAS?
WE NEED TO LEAVE!
EVER SINCE YOU GOT BACK,
YOU'VE BEEN ACTING DIFFERENT.
YOU'RE AVOIDING JAKE,
YOU'RE NOT TALKING
TO YOUR FRIENDS...
YOU'RE HIDING SOMETHING!
WOULD YOU STOP BEING
SO NAIVE?
I'M TRYING TO HELP YOU!
KATIE, YOU JUST FLIPPED A GUY
ON THE GROUND FOR NO REASON!
I'M NOT THE ONE
THAT NEEDS HELP.
YOU DO.
(ELECTRONICA MUSIC PLAYS)
ELI:
I DON'T FEEL ANYTHING.
WAIT FOR IT.
ANY SECOND NOW.
STILL NOTHING.
WELL, HOW ABOUT NOW?
♪ Hundred angles lost ♪
♪ Fleeing from the beat
and the pulse ♪
(GASPS)
OKAY, ARE YOU HEARING THIS
RIGHT NOW?
WAIT UNTIL YOU GET
IN THE PAINT.
♪ Laughing like a fool ♪
♪ Playing for the heart
and the soul ♪
♪ And the soul ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Feel it break ♪