(STRUMS GUITAR)
GUESS WHO?!
HAPPY FOUR MONTHS
AND ONE DAY!
LAST NIGHT WAS PERFECT.
I'M GLAD.
YOU DESERVED IT.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE
WHAT YOU DO
FOR OUR FIVE, SIX, SEVEN,
EIGHT, NINE,
TEN MONTH-I-VERSARIES!
BUT WE'LL TAKE IT
ONE AT A TIME.
(CHUCKLES)
THE ONLY THING
THAT MATTERS
IS THAT WE GET TO SPEND
EACH ONE TOGETHER.
SO NOW THAT OUR RELATIONSHIP
IS SO TIGHT,
MAYBE I CAN MEET YOUR MOM?
OH NO, YOU THINK
SHE WON'T LIKE ME?
NO, NO,
SHE'LL LOVE YOU,
BUT, UH,
SHE'S JUST REALLY BUSY
WITH THE STORE AND ALL.
MAYA:
YOU GUYS, YOU'LL NEVER GUESS
WHAT MARISOL TOLD ME!
STUDENT COUNCIL'S
ORGANIZING A DANCE
AND THEY WANT WHISPERHUG
TO PLAY!
(EXCITED SQUEAL)
OUR FIRST DANCE!
AND OUR FIRST GIG!
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
WE HAVE FRENCH.
AU REVOIR!
MARISOL:
(CLEARS THROAT)
YOU KNOW WHO PAYS
THE BILL
WHEN SOMEONE DINES
AND DASHES?
UH, YOU HAVE
THE WRONG GUY.
YOU'RE IN A BAND
WITH MY BOYFRIEND
AND YOUR GIRLFRIEND
IS ON POWER SQUAD...
WITH ME.
OKAY, PLEASE,
PLEASE DON'T TELL TORI, OKAY?
LOOK, I CAN PAY YOU BACK,
I SWEAR.
FIFTY BUCKS.
THE BILL WAS THIRTY-FIVE!
I THINK I DESERVE
A GENEROUS TIP.
LOOK, I DON'T HAVE
THAT ON ME, OKAY?
YOU HAVE TWENTY-FOUR HOURS
OR I TELL TORI
AND THEN SEND MO
TO COLLECT,
AND HE'S A WRESTLER
AND A FOOTBALL PLAYER.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
(Ooh-ooh-ooh)
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
FIONA:
HOW'S IT GOING HERE?
DALLAS:
STEADY.
BUT A PRETTY FACE MIGHT
BOOST TICKET SALES.
YEAH, WELL,
I HAVE A GYM TO SET UP,
A BANNER TO HANG-
MY GUYS ARE ALREADY
ON IT.
FOR SOME REASON,
BO AND INGVAR
JUST LOVE TO DECORATE.
YOU SHOULD, UH,
COME TAKE A BREAK.
YOU'RE GOING ABOVE AND BEYOND
HERE, DALLAS.
YEAH, THAT'S HOW I ROLL.
I ALWAYS GIVE 150 PERCENT.
THERE'S NO SUCH THING
AS 150 PERCENT.
I SHOULD KNOW BETTER
THAN TO USE TRITE SPORTS CLICHES
AROUND YOU.
EITHER YOU STAYED UP LATE
READING THE DICTIONARY
OR YOU HAVE A BETTER VOCABULARY
THAN THE AVERAGE JOCK.
CAREFUL,
YOU'RE VERY CLOSE TO ADMITTING
YOU WERE WRONG ABOUT ME.
(CHUCKLES)
IMOGEN:
UM...
OH, HEY, IMMY,
WHAT'S UP?
IT CAN WAIT.
DALLAS:
I'LL GO, UH, CHECK ON BO
AND INGVAR.
WHAT IS IT?
IMOGEN:
I JUST THOUGHT MAYBE
WE COULD TALK,
BUT OBVIOUSLY YOU'RE TOO BUSY
FLIRTING WITH A GUY FOR THAT.
WE WERE JOKING AROUND.
IT'S HARD WORK
PLANNING A DANCE,
YOU KNOW,
SO YOUR BAND CAN PLAY.
WHEN MO TOLD ME
ABOUT THIS DANCE,
I KNEW IT.
YOU ORGANIZED IT FOR ME,
BUT YOU SAID
MY BAND WAS SILLY.
AND THIS IS MY APOLOGY.
SO IS THAT THE PLAN,
FIONA?
YOU'RE GONNA THROW
AN EVENT FOR ME
EVERY TIME YOU CAN'T
TALK TO ME?
WE CAN TALK
WHENEVER YOU WANT.
NO, WE CAN'T!
YOU CAME BACK FROM NEW YORK
AND DECIDED EVERYTHING.
WE NEED TO SPEND
EVERY MINUTE TOGETHER,
I'M A LESBIAN,
I'M YOUR GIRLFRIEND,
LET'S BROADCAST IT
TO THE WORLD!
YOU'RE HAVING
SECOND THOUGHTS.
I CARE ABOUT YOU
MORE THAN ANYONE-
WELL, IT DOESN'T
SOUND LIKE IT!
BUT YOU'RE PRESSURING ME!
FINE!
PRESSURE'S OFF.
LET ME KNOW
WHAT YOU DECIDE.
SOMETHING YOU NEED
TO TELL ME?
UH...
BECKY GAVE IT TO ME
IN CASE BEING IN THE MUSICAL
TURNS ME GAY.
I DON'T THINK THAT'S
HOW THAT WORKS.
(CHUCKLES)
THAT GIRL'S WACK.
SHE HAS A POINT THOUGH.
EVERYONE'S GONNA SEE ME
IN THE MUSICAL,
AND TODAY WE'RE TAKING
PHOTOS FOR POSTERS
THAT ARE GONNA BE PLASTERED
ALL OVER THE SCHOOL.
WHAT ARE PEOPLE
GONNA THINK?
WHO CARES?
THE PEOPLE THAT LOVE YOU
KNOW WHO YOU ARE.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I MEAN, THE WHOLE REASON
WHY I'M DOING THIS MUSICAL
IS BECAUSE OF PEOPLE
LIKE BECKY BAKER.
AND BECAUSE YOU LOOK
SO GOOD IN TIGHTS.
DAVE:
(LAUGHS)
UH...
DAVE:
WHAT'S THAT?
THESE ARE MY BIRTH
CONTROL PILLS.
SO I GUESS YOU'RE TAKING THEM
FOR YOUR...?
MY PARENTS ARE GOING OUT
TO A DINNER PARTY TONIGHT.
I THOUGHT MAYBE WE COULD SKIP
OUT OF THE DANCE EARLY
AND...
ONLY IF YOU WANT TO.
UH...
I FEEL SO PRESSURED.
BOTH:
(LAUGH)
I DON'T KNOW.
SEEING YOUR CONFIDENCE
ON STAGE YESTERDAY
REALLY CONVINCED ME
THAT IT WAS...TIME.
(CHUCKLES)
I LOVE YOU,
DAVE TURNER.
(HAPPY CHUCKLE)
I LOVE YOU TOO.
HOLY CRAP, I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS HAPPENING!
(LAUGHS)
TORI:
YOUR MOM MUST BE
SO PROUD OF YOU,
BEING A ROCK STAR NOW.
SORRY, WHAT?
YOUR MOM?
I BET SHE'S PROUD OF YOU.
(NONCOMMITAL SIGH)
THINK I CAN MEET HER
AFTER THE DANCE?
UH, NO.
SORRY.
SHE'S SUPER BUSY.
OH, THAT'S OKAY.
SOMEDAY!
(CHUCKLES)
LISTEN, TORI,
I NEED TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING.
OH, LOOK!
THEY'RE SELLING TICKETS
TO THE DANCE!
WHISPERHEART'S FIRST
PUBLIC PERFORMANCE.
IT'S WHISPERHUG.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
HMM.
IT DOESN'T SEEM LIKE
THERE'S ANYONE HERE.
YOU'LL HAVE TO COME BACK.
TORI:
I HOPE THEY HAVEN'T SOLD OUT.
MAYBE I SHOULD WAIT A MINUTE,
SOMEONE WILL SHOW.
DON'T WORRY.
I'M A ROCK STAR NOW,
I CAN GET YOU IN V.I.P.
THANK YOU!
YOU'RE THE BEST!
MUAH!
(NERVOUS EXHALE)
DAVE:
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S DO THIS THING!
ELI:
SOMEBODY'S IN A GOOD MOOD.
DAVE:
IT'S THE BEST DAY EVER
AND IT'S ABOUT TO GET
EVEN BETTER!
YEAH, WELL, JUST TONE IT DOWN
FOR THE PHOTOS.
ROMEO'S KIND OF TORTURED,
REMEMBER?
RIGHT, RIGHT.
NOW LET'S GET YOU
UP THERE, OKAY?
DAVE:
RIGHT.
OKAY, AWESOME.
NOW LOOK FAR OFF.
(CAMERA SNAPS)
ALL RIGHT,
NOW LOOK INTO EACH OTHER'S EYES.
(CAMERA SNAPS)
THAT'S AWESOME.
UM, REMEMBER,
TWO PEOPLE IN LOVE.
HOCKEY PLAYER:
YO, CHECK IT OUT.
LUKE:
WHAT?
GAY!
LUKE:
DAVE:
HEY, WE GOT ENOUGH, ELI?
HEY, GUYS,
I'D APPRECIATE
IF YOU KEPT YOUR COMMENTS
TO YOURSELF, OKAY?
LUKE:
OH, WHATEVER, MAN.
ELI:
THIS IS FOR THE SCHOOL MUSICAL.
LUKE:
HEY, ARE YOU ELI?
ELI:
YEAH.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD KEEP
YOUR GAY STUFF
A LITTLE MORE PRIVATE.
SORRY, NO CAN DO.
SOON THIS SCHOOL WILL BE COVERED
WITH POSTERS, OKAY,
SO...
DEAL WITH IT.
LUKE:
(SMIRKS)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
ZIG:
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT'S THIS?
CLASS'S BEEN POSTPONED.
LOCKER SEARCHES.
SOME MONEY'S GONE
MISSING.
(NERVOUS EXHALE)
DUDE, IT WAS YOU?
SHUT UP.
GOOD LUCK, MAN.
ZIG, DID YOU HEAR?
UH, HEAR WHAT?
APPARENTLY SOMEONE STOLE
SOME OF THE DANCE
TICKET MONEY.
I'M NOT SURPRISED.
REMEMBER WHEN WE TRIED
TO BUY TICKETS
AND NO ONE WAS MANNING
THE BOOTH?
HOW DO YOU KNOW
IT WAS STOLEN?
I MEAN,
MAYBE IT GOT LOST.
CAN YOU OPEN YOUR LOCKER,
SON?
(LOCK CLANKS)
TAKE OUT THAT GUITAR CASE.
WAIT A MINUTE.
OPEN THE CASE,
PLEASE.
(ZIPPER UNZIPPING)
YOU'RE FREE TO GO.
(RE-ZIPS ZIPPER)
(BREATHING NERVOUSLY)
MAYA:
IS THAT THE DANCE TICKET MONEY?
I NEEDED IT.
IT WAS A MISTAKE, OKAY?
YOU STOLE!
MAYA:
AND YOU'RE IN A LOT OF TROUBLE
IF THEY FIND OUT IT WAS YOU!
ALL THE MONEY'S THERE.
TURN ME IN
IF YOU HAVE TO.
MAYA:
WE WON'T.
WE'LL SAY WE JUST FOUND IT
LYING AROUND.
ZIG:
FINE.
NO, NOT FINE!
WHY, ZIG?
I FEEL LIKE
I BARELY KNOW YOU!
YOU DON'T.
(CAR ENGINE REVS)
(OVERLAPPING STUDENT VOICES)
♪ You're gonna get
what you deserve ♪
♪ When you such a liar,
play with fire ♪
♪ (Unclear) ♪
♪ I think I'm so in love ♪
FIONA:
HAVE FUN, GUYS.
EVERYONE'S HERE TO HAVE
A GOOD TIME, FIONA.
MAYBE A SMILE?
WHAT'S THE POINT?
THE POINT IS YOU PROMISED ME
A PERFECT EVENT
AND YOU'RE OVER THERE
ACTING LIKE THE GRIM REAPER.
(SIGHS)
WELL, IMOGEN AND I-
THE ONLY THING MORE COMPLICATED
THAN ONE GIRL, IS TWO.
WE WERE PERFECT FRIENDS,
BUT THEN I RUINED EVERYTHING
WHEN I KISSED HER.
IS SHE A LESBIAN,
BISEXUAL,
JUST VISITING?
OR IS SHE A STRAIGHT GIRL
HAVING A MOMENT?
COULD THIS BE
ANY MORE COMPLICATED?
NO, IT CAN'T.
AND IF YOU'RE CONFUSED,
IMAGINE HOW CONFUSED
SHE IS RIGHT NOW.
SOUNDS LIKE YOU JUST NEED
TO TALK TO HER.
SO MUCH TALKING.
WHY CAN'T WE JUST BE
KISSING AGAIN?
NOW YOU SOUND
LIKE A GUY.
LOOK, CHICKS...
THEY LIKE TO TALK A LOT.
IF YOU CAN SURVIVE THAT,
THEN YOU CAN GET
TO THE KISSING.
THANKS, DALLAS,
FOR SURPRISINGLY
GOOD ADVICE.
SURE.
BUT NOW YOU OWE ME
TWO DANCES.
(LAUGHS)
(BOTTLES RATTLE LOUDLY)
DIJANA:
YOU BREAK IT, YOU BUY IT.
(BOTTLES RATTLE LOUDLY)
HERE, LET ME FINISH.
YOU NEED TO GET READY
FOR YOUR DANCE.
I'M NOT GOING.
DIJANA:
IS YOUR BAND NOT PLAYING?
I DID SOMETHING BAD, MOM.
I STOLE MONEY
FROM THE STUDENT COUNCIL.
ZIGMUND!
DON'T WORRY.
I GAVE IT ALL BACK
BEFORE ANYONE FOUND OUT.
WHY WOULD YOU DO THIS?!
ZIG:
I OWED SOMEONE FIFTY BUCKS.
I HAD NO OTHER WAY
OF GETTING THE CASH.
TORI, MY FRIENDS,
THEY CAN ALL BUY
WHATEVER THEY WANT
AND I HAVE TO ACT
THE SAME WAY
OR ELSE THEY'LL
LOOK DOWN ON ME!
I HATE BEING POOR!
ZIGMUND,
YOUR FRIENDS DON'T CARE
HOW MUCH MONEY YOU HAVE.
THAT'S CRAP!
WELL, IT IS!
A LOT OF PEOPLE CARE!
NOT TRUE FRIENDS.
(SIGHS) GET READY
FOR YOUR SHOW.
I CAN'T SHOW MY FACE THERE,
EVERYONE HATES ME.
ESPECIALLY TORI.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
PEOPLE ARE COUNTING ON YOU.
(REGISTER DINGS)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
TO PAY YOUR DEBT.
BUT WE COULD BARELY COVER RENT
LAST MONTH.
NOVAKS OWN UP
TO THEIR MISTAKES.
GO GET READY
FOR YOUR DANCE.
♪ Oh, oh! ♪
♪ I don't want to... ♪
WHERE'S YOUR DATE?
OH, SHE'S IN THE WASHROOM
TRYING ON JENNA'S
NEW LIPSTICK.
I DIDN'T EXPECT
TO SEE YOU HERE.
YEAH, CLARE'S ON A NEWSPAPER
THING WITH HER MENTOR,
BUT SHE WANTS ME
TO SHOW ADAM OUR SUPPORT.
PLUS I WANT TO MAKE SURE
EVERYONE SEES THE DEBUT
OF OUR AWESOME POSTERS!
I LET FIONA USE
OUR REHEARSAL SPACE
TO THROW THIS DANCE
IN EXCHANGE
FOR A LITTLE PROMOTION.
A LITTLE PROMOTION?
THAT IS A FREAKIN' BILLBOARD!
ELI:
YEAH, IT'S AWESOME,
HUH?
HOCKEY PLAYER:
(LAUGHS MOCKINGLY)
SO, TONIGHT'S THE NIGHT.
YEAH, YEAH,
I'M EXCITED.
ALLI:
WELL, DO YOU LIKE MY DRESS?
YEAH, YOU LOOK STUNNING.
YEAH, THE GREEN REALLY
BRINGS OUT MY EYES.
YEAH.
DOES THIS LOOK LIKE
A GREEN DRESS TO YOU?!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
HOCKEY PLAYER:
DID YOU JUST LOOK AT MY BUTT?
WATCH OUT!
THIS DUDE'S A BUTT LOOKER!
NO, I'M NOT.
GAY!
OH, I'M GAY,
RIGHT?
YEAH, THAT'S WHY
I'M HAVING SEX TONIGHT
WITH MY GIRLFRIEND.
TONS OF HETERO SEX!
JERKS.
MAYBE, BUT THEY HAVE
A BETTER SHOT
OF HAVING SEX TONIGHT
THAN YOU DO.
DAVE:
ALLI, ALLI, I'M SORRY.
FIONA:
HEY...
CAN WE TALK
BEFORE YOU GO ON STAGE?
OR YOU COULD TALK
AND I COULD TRY LISTENING
FOR A CHANGE.
I'LL MEET YOU GUYS
BACKSTAGE.
I WANNA BE
YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
I LIKE HOW THIS
IS STARTING.
BUT IT HAS TO BE SLOW,
LIKE SUPER-SLOW,
AND I'M WORRIED
THAT'S NOT GONNA BE
GOOD ENOUGH FOR YOU.
OKAY, YOUR TURN.
MY WORLD IS A MESS.
EVERYTHING THAT'S GOING ON
WITH MY FAMILY RIGHT NOW
IS SO UP-IN-THE-AIR...
AND I WAS LOOKING
FOR SOLID GROUND WITH YOU.
BUT I PUSHED TOO HARD.
SO WHATEVER SPEED
YOU'RE ON,
I CAN BE ON
THAT ONE TOO.
THAT MEANS NO MORE EVENTS
IN MY HONOUR.
(CHUCKLES)
I PROMISE.
SO, UM, DOES THIS
SUPER-SLOW SPEED
MEAN NO KISSING?
JUST NOT IN FRONT
OF JOCKS, OKAY?
OKAY.
(CHUCKLES)
DALLAS:
(WOLF WHISTLES AND CLAPS)
FINALLY!
ARE YOU HERE TO CASH IN
ON THOSE TWO DANCES I OWE YOU?
NO, I'M GOOD.
MO:
T-MINUS-TEN
TO WHISPERHUG'S DEBUT!
WHERE'S IMOGEN?
IMOGEN:
I'M HERE!
AND SO IS MY GIRLFRIEND.
MO:
GREAT.
WHAT ABOUT THE ZIG-MAN?
MAYA:
I'M NOT SURE
HE'S COMING.
MMM.
BET I KNOW WHY.
MO:
OKAY, WELL, SOMEBODY CALL HIM.
GROUPIE, WHAT ARE YOUR
BOYFRIEND'S DIGITS?
TORI:
MY EX-BOYFRIEND
DOESN'T HAVE A CELL.
WHAT IDIOT DOESN'T HAVE A CELL?
ZIG:
AN IDIOT WHO CAN'T AFFORD ONE.
SORRY I'M LATE, GUYS.
MARISOL,
HERE'S YOUR MONEY.
THANKS.
FIONA:
HEY, YOU GUYS READY
FOR YOUR INTRO OR WHAT?
MO:
LET'S DO IT.
WHY DID YOU GIVE MARISOL
THAT MONEY?
'CAUSE UM...
I DIDN'T PAY FOR OUR DINNER
AT "LITTLE MISS STEAKS."
WE DINED AND DASHED?
I DON'T HAVE MONEY,
OKAY?
BUT YOUR PARENTS
OWN A STORE.
A CONVENIENCE STORE...
THAT BARELY MAKES ENOUGH
TO PUT FOOD ON THE TABLE.
LOOK, THE REASON
THAT I TRIED TO CANCEL
OUR FOUR MONTH ANNIVERSARY...
IS BECAUSE I COULDN'T AFFORD
TO TAKE YOU OUT.
YOU JUST LIED
ABOUT EVERYTHING?
MAYA:
ZIG, WE'RE ON.
I JUST DIDN'T WANT
TO LOSE YOU.
FIONA:
AND NOW, FOR THE FIRST TIME
ANYWHERE,
GIVE IT UP FOR WHISPERHUG!
STUDENTS:
(CHEER AND CLAP)
(BAND STARTS PLAYING)
ZIG:
♪ EVER FEEL YOU'RE GOIN' OUT
OF YOUR HEAD ♪
♪ FLYING OFF
TO SOMEWHERE ELSE ♪
♪ INSTEAD OF BEING
WHO YOU REALLY ARE? ♪
(WHISPERS)
A ROCKSTAR SUPERSTAR!
ZIG AND IMOGEN:
♪ EVERY DAY I FEEL
I'M MEETING NEW PEOPLE ♪
♪ A LOT OF NEW PEOPLE ♪
♪ AND LOST AMONG PEOPLE
AND... ♪
♪ EVERY DAY I FEEL
I'M TRYIN' TO BE SOMEONE ♪
♪ FORGETTING THAT SOMEONE ♪
♪ PLEASE BE MY SOMEONE ♪
♪ EVERYBODY STAND UP ♪
♪ EVERYBODY MEANS YOU ♪
♪ THIS IS IT,
THIS IS OURS ♪
♪ COME ON, SHINE THROUGH... ♪
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
TURNING THIS
TO FACE THE WALL.
IT'S EMBARRASSING.
ELI:
IT'S PROMOTING THE MUSICAL!
DAVE:
IT'S PROMOTING ME AS GAY,
AND A BUNCH OF THOSE
HOCKEY DUDES DEFACED IT.
ELI:
YEAH, I CAN SEE THAT.
ZERO POINTS FOR ORIGINALITY.
DAVE:
LOOK, ELI,
I'D LIKE TO BELIEVE
I'M ABOVE CARING,
BUT I'M NOT.
OKAY, THE NAME-CALLING,
THE HECKLING,
IT BOTHERS ME.
SO YOU'RE GONNA LET
THOSE DUMB JOCKS WIN?
THIS MUSICAL IS RUINING THINGS
BETWEEN ME AND ALLI.
TONIGHT,
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO...
YOU KNOW, DO IT,
FOR THE FIRST TIME TOGETHER.
SO LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT.
YOU'RE HERE WORRYING ABOUT
WHAT A BUNCH OF JERKS THINK
WHEN YOU COULD BE HAVING SEX
WITH YOUR GIRLFRIEND INSTEAD?
I'M AN IDIOT.
WHAT DO I DO?
GO HAVE SEX
WITH YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
ZIG AND IMOGEN:
♪ EVERYBODY STAND UP,
EVERYBODY MEANS YOU ♪
♪ THIS IS IT,
THIS IS OURS ♪
(STUDENTS CLAP)
♪ COME ON, SHINE THROUGH ♪
♪ EVERY DAY I FEEL
I'M TRYING TO BE SOMEONE ♪
♪ FORGETTING THAT SOMEONE ♪
♪ BE SOMEONE AND LET GO! ♪
♪ EVERYBODY STAND UP ♪
♪ EVERYBODY MEANS YOU ♪
♪ THIS IS IT,
THIS IS OURS ♪
♪ COME ON, SHINE THROUGH ♪
♪ EVERY DAY I FEEL
I'M TRYING TO BE SOMEONE ♪
♪ FORGETTING THAT SOMEONE ♪
♪ PLEASE BE MY SOMEONE ♪
STUDENTS:
(CHEER AND APPLAUD LOUDLY)
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
HI. JENNA LET ME IN.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
NOT SURE WHAT YOU CAN SAY
IN PERSON
THAT THE FOURTEEN
TEXTS CAN'T.
I KNOW I EMBARRASSED YOU,
ALLI.
I'M SORRY.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE LET THOSE
HOMOPHOBIC JERKS GET TO ME,
BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT ANYBODY ELSE THINKS
AS LONG AS I HAVE YOU.
NOW ARE YOU JUST
SAYING THAT
'CAUSE YOU WANNA HAVE
SEX WITH ME TONIGHT?
NO, IT'S TRUE.
I SWEAR.
RIGHT ANSWER.
(SIGHS) I GUESS
ONE LITTLE MISTAKE
DOESN'T EXACTLY CHANGE
THE WAY I FEEL ABOUT YOU.
SO DOES THAT MEAN...?
MY PARENTS ARE GONNA BE HOME
IN LIKE 20 MINUTES.
THAT'S ENOUGH TIME,
RIGHT?
PLENTY OF TIME.
DAVE:
OH SHOOT!
CONDOMS ARE IN MY CAR.
NO TIME.
I'M ON THE PILL.
OH MY GOD, I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS HAPPENING!
SOMEONE'S HOME EARLY.
YEAH, I LEFT AFTER
THE BAND FINISHED PLAYING.
GUESS THINGS DIDN'T WORK OUT
WITH THE GIRL?
GO IN AND WATCH TV,
MOM.
I'LL WORK UNTIL CLOSE.
DON'T WORRY.
NOW, I WORRY.
GOOD NIGHT, MA.
(SIGHS) LISTEN,
GO HOME, MAN.
I DON'T REALLY FEEL
LIKE COMPANY.
YOU CAN TELL HER THAT.
SHE STALKED ME
OUT AT THE DANCE,
BEGGED ME
TO BRING HER HERE.
THANK YOU.
SO THIS IS
YOUR PARENT'S STORE?
(NERVOUSLY)
YEAH.
PRETTY IMPRESSIVE,
HUH?
LISTEN...
I'M SORRY I LIED.
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
DO YOU REALLY THINK
I'M THAT SHALLOW?
YOU TREAT ME
LIKE A ROCK STAR.
I DIDN'T WANT THAT
TO CHANGE.
YOU WERE A ROCK STAR
TONIGHT.
DIJANA:
ZIG, (SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN)
WHO'S THIS?
UH, MOM,
THIS IS, UH, TORI...
MY GIRLFRIEND?
I'M ACTUALLY, LIKE,
SO EXCITED TO FINALLY MEET YOU!
TORI AND DIJANA:
(LAUGH)
(LAUGHING)
IT'S GOOD TO MEET YOU TOO!
♪ Forgetting that someone ♪
♪ Be someone and let go! ♪