IMOGEN:
HURRY! HURRY!
ELI:
WHAT'S THE RUSH?
IMOGEN:
FIONES WANTED THE MENUS
BY 12:00.
IT'S 11:59.
IF WE'RE A FEW MINUTES LATE,
BIG DEAL.
HUMONGOUS DEAL.
FIONA SLAVED FOR MONTHS
TO MAKE PROM PERFECT,
AND I, IMOGEN MORENO,
REFUSE TO DISAPPOINT.
OOH! AGH! FIDDLESTICKS!
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH. SORRY.
DON'T BE SORRY.
YOU STILL HAVEN'T OPENED
YOUR REPORT CARD?
IT MUST'VE SLIPPED
MY MIND.
IS THAT YOUR FINAL
ANSWER?
THE CONTENT OF THIS ENVELOPE
SEALS MY FATE.
IF I PASS,
I GO TO DESIGN SCHOOL
WITH FIONA.
AND IF I FAIL,
I SPEND ANOTHER YEAR AT DEGRASSI
ALONE.
JUST OPEN IT.
(SHOCKED EXHALE)
FIONA:
THERE YOU ARE!
DO YOU HAVE THE MENUS?!
NOT A WORD.
I DON'T WANNA RUIN
PROM NIGHT.
YEAH.
I'M SENSING
A CONSPIRACY BREWING.
DON'T TELL ME THE PRINTERS
GOT THE FONT WRONG.
IMOGEN:
STOP BEING SUCH A WORRYWART.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
OKAY, TIME FOR
THE GRAND REVEAL.
(SHOCKED GASP)
IS IT TOO MUCH?
FIONES, IT'S...
IT'S LIKE A MOVIE.
AND WE'RE THE STARS.
ARE YOU READY TO HAVE
THE TIME OF OUR LIVES?
SO THIS PLACE IS PRETTY SPOOKY
WITH THE HALL ALL EMPTY, EH?
YEAH. CAN'T BELIEVE HIGH SCHOOL
IS FINALLY OVER.
SO LOCKER'S ALL CLEANED OUT.
NEED HELP WITH YOURS?
NAH, I GOT IT.
KATIE:
CAN YOU BELIEVE
THIS IS OUR LAST NIGHT TOGETHER?
NO. NO MORE GOSSIPING
BEFORE HOMEROOM,
SKIPPING TO THE MALL
ON SPARES.
KATIE:
I KNOW, BUT WE'LL MAKE
NEW MEMORIES
WHEN YOU COME VISIT ME
AT STANFORD.
MARISOL:
YES, AND WE WILL START TONIGHT,
WHICH WILL BE
THE BEST NIGHT EVER!
KATIE:
I KNOW! I'M SO EXCITED!
(GIRLS SQUEAL)
KATIE: I'M SO HAPPY.
MARISOL: I KNOW.
MO: SO...
JAKE: YUP.
PRETTY CRAZY, HUH?
I MEAN,
IT REALLY IS THE END.
BUT AT LEAST
WE HAVE PROM NIGHT, UNH?
UH, YOU KNOW, I'M NOT GOING,
BUT HAVE FUN THOUGH.
KATIE:
THE LIMO'S COMING TO MY HOUSE
AT 8:00...
MARISOL: EIGHT.
KATIE: SO MEET ME THERE.
MARISOL: OKAY!
KATIE: I'LL SEE YOU.
JAKE'S NOT COMING TO PROM.
BUT I'LL BE THERE!
AND I'VE REQUESTED
OUR FAVOURITE SONG
SO WE CAN CREATE
OUR OWN MOVIE MAGIC MOMENT.
THAT'S GREAT, BABY.
OKAY, IF YOU'RE GONNA BE
THIS MOPEY AT PROM,
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
A PROBLEM.
WHAT IF, AFTER GRADUATION,
ME AND JAKE
NEVER TALK AGAIN?
WHAT IF WE JUST DON'T TALK?
OKAY, WELL, YOU NEED
TO LOCK DOWN
A BROMANCE, YOU KNOW?
TELL HIM HOW YOU FEEL.
GUYS DON'T DO WHAT YOU
AND KATIE DID, OKAY?
WITH THE WHOLE...
"OH MY GOD! MEMORIES!
IT'S JUST LIKE...
I LOVE YOU FOREVER!"
MARISOL:
HEY, SUIT YOURSELF.
BUT IF YOU FROWN ONCE
AT PROM,
I'M GONNA MAKE YOU EAT
A CORSAGE.
IMOGEN:
OH, I CAN'T DECIDE.
HAIR UP LIKE THAT...
OR HAIR DOWN?
FIONA:
HMM. DEFINITELY UP.
YOU DON'T WANT IT TO COMPETE
WITH YOUR NECKLACE.
IMOGEN:
BUT I DON'T HAVE A NECKLACE.
(SQUEALS)
FIONA:
DON'T GET TOO EXCITED.
IT'S NOT CARTIER,
IT'S COYNE.
IMOGEN:
THAT'S EVEN BETTER.
FIONA:
ISN'T THIS UNREAL?
TONIGHT'S PROM,
TOMORROW'S GRADUATION,
AND PRETTY SOON
WE'RE GONNA BE AT UNIVERSITY.
BUT THAT'S STILL
MONTHS AWAY.
YEAH, BUT SUMMER
IS GONNA FLY BY.
I THINK WE NEED
TO GET NEW WARDROBES.
I'M THINKING THRIFT-STORE CHIC.
BLACK MOSTLY,
A FEW BOHO ACCESSORIES.
MAYBE A SCARF.
IMMY, WHAT'S WRONG?
NOTHING.
EVERYTHING'S PERFECT.
THE MOUTH'S SAYING
ONE THING,
TEARS ANOTHER.
I FLUNKED ALL MY CLASSES.
BUT YOU'RE SO SMART.
TEACHERS CAN'T GRADE ASSIGNMENTS
YOU DON'T HAND IN.
FIONA:
WE'LL STILL BE IN
THE SAME CITY,
AND I CAN VISIT
BETWEEN CLASSES,
AND I'LL BE YOUR SOPHISTICATED
COLLEGE GIRLFRIEND.
I LOVE YOU,
FIONA COYNE.
(DOOR OPENS)
WHAT WAS THAT SOUND?
THE PITTER-PATTER
OF MY HEART.
LARA COYNE:
FI-FI?
FIONA:
MOM?!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?!
OH! I MISSED YOU
SO MUCH!
WAIT! YOU'RE NOT
ON THE LAM, RIGHT?
(LAUGHS) NO!
BUT I HAVE NEWS,
AND IT'S GONNA
CHANGE EVERYTHING.
♪♪♪
ALLI:
OOH LA LA!
WHAT ABOUT THIS ONE?
CLARE:
ALLI, I TOLD YOU,
I'M NOT GOING TO PROM.
JENNA: BUT WHAT ABOUT-
CLARE: DON'T YOU DARE SAY HIS-
ALLI:
ELI?
HASN'T HE SENT YOU
LIKE A DOZEN VOICE MAILS?
YEAH, WELL, HE WANTED SPACE
SO I'M GIVING HIM LOTS.
ALLI:
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY,
LOOKING GOOD
IS THE BEST REVENGE.
(SIGHS)
CLIFF:
SHE'S RIGHT, YOU KNOW.
CLARE:
SORRY. HAVE WE MET?
CLIFF:
CLIFF JACOBS.
I'M IN YOUR HISTORY CLASS.
OH, RIGHT. SORRY.
SEE YOU AROUND.
OKAY.
JENNA:
WHAT ABOUT ALL THE PEOPLE
WHO WANT YOU TWO TOGETHER?
WHAT PEOPLE?
JENNA:
YOU GUYS ARE FINALISTS
FOR PROM KING AND QUEEN.
CLARE:
OKAY.
FOR THE LAST TIME,
ELI AND I ARE DONE.
ALLI:
FOR THE LAST TIME,
I DON'T BUY IT.
CLARE:
HEY, CLIFF?
DO YOU HAVE A DATE
FOR PROM?
OKAY, INFORMATION OVERLOAD!
SO OUR LEGAL TROUBLE'S
ARE RESOLVED
AND OUR ASSETS
ARE UNFROZEN?!
BUT I HAVEN'T GOTTEN
TO THE BEST PART YET.
ON THE PLANE RIDE HOME
FROM NEW YORK,
I SAT NEXT TO
FEDERICO CAVALIERI.
WHO?
THE HEAD DESIGNER
AT MERMOZI!
HIS SPRING COLLECTION
MADE ME WEEP!
I SHOWED HIM THE SKETCHES
OF THE DRESSES
YOU DESIGNED FOR PROM,
AND IT TURNS OUT
HE'S LOOKING
FOR A JUNIOR DESIGNER...
IN ROME.
(GASPS) WHAT?!
ITALY!
BUT THAT'S HUNDREDS
OF MILES AWAY.
THOUSANDS.
I KNOW HOW MUCH YOU LOVE
LA DOLCE VITA.
OH, MORNING ESPRESSO
IN THE CAFE
AND LEISURELY LUNCHES
IN THE PIAZZA.
LARA:
AND THE SHOPPING!
DON'T FORGET THE SHOPPING!
OKAY, IF WE DON'T SKEDADDLE,
WE'LL BE LATE FOR PROM!
IMMY'S RIGHT.
CAN WE TALK MORE ABOUT THIS
TOMORROW?
NO. FEDERICO IS ONLY
IN TOWN TONIGHT.
YOU NEED TO CALL HIM.
YOU NEED TO GET DRESSED NOW.
(FIONA GIGGLES EXCITEDLY)
♪ Curiosity...
will never let me ♪
♪ Go-oh oh-oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh-oh oh ♪
CLARE:
SO DO YOU THINK CLIFF IS SHORT
FOR CLIFFORD OR CLIFTON?
UH, HEATHCLIFF.
NO. NO. NO TORTURED
ROMANTIC HEROES.
TONIGHT IS ABOUT FUN.
NEW PEOPLE,
NEW EXPERIENCES.
JENNA:
AND MAKING ELI JEALOUS?
(LAUGHING)
CLARE:
ALLI, CAN YOU ZIP ME UP?
YEAH, SURE.
UM...
WHAT?
IS THE ZIPPER STUCK?
ALLI:
NO, THERE'S LIKE A LUMP
OR SOMETHING.
A LUMP?
ALLI:
OR A BUMP?
JENNA, COME FEEL THIS.
JENNA:
OH! OH...
YEAH, YOU SHOULD GET THAT
CHECKED OUT.
MY AUNT HAD SOMETHING
LIKE THAT.
TURNED OUT IT WAS CANCER.
ALLI:
OKAY, IT'S PROBABLY NOT CANCER.
JUST A CYST OR SOMETHING.
CLARE:
WELL, AT LEAST IF I DIE,
I'LL NEVER HAVE TO HEAR
ELI'S NAME AGAIN.
JAKE:
CLARE! YOUR PROM DATE'S HERE!
CLARE:
ZIP ME UP! ZIP ME UP!
(GIGGLING)
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY? GOOD?
(SWORD CLUNKS)
NO.
NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO, NO.
(NERVOUS EXHALE)
YOU SAID WE WEREN'T
A FAIRY TALE;
I'M HERE TO PROVE YOU WRONG.
(HORSE SNORTS)
(ALLI AND JENNA GIGGLE)
WHO ARE YOU?
CLIFF, HER PROM DATE.
ELI:
ELI.
HER SOUL MATE.
OH MAN...
(EXHALES)
(LOW BUZZ OF EXCITED CHATTER)
♪ I know, I know,
I know you got the key ♪
♪ You know, you know,
you know that it's for me ♪
♪ Well, I think that we
should try it out to see ♪
♪ Yeah, curiosity ♪
♪ So don't break me tonight ♪
♪ There's this crazy love ♪
♪ And you know I'm gonna
follow you ♪
OOH! THAT MUST BE
THE FORTUNE TELLER.
WOW! FIONA REALLY
OUTDID HERSELF.
TAKE A PICTURE
OF ME AND MO.
OKAY. SMILE!
AW!
THAT WAS A FAKE SMILE.
I TRIED.
NO, YOU ARE NOT ALLOWED
TO BE SAD TONIGHT.
I CAN'T JUST PRETEND!
THEN GO HOME!
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
IS SHE SERIOUS?!
KATIE:
THIS IS MARISOL
ON PROM NIGHT.
SHE'S SERIOUS.
FINE. YOU WANT ME TO GO,
I'M GONE.
HEY, HANDSOME.
WHAAAAAAT?
(MOUTHS)
HE CAME.
I CAN'T HANDLE SEEING
MY MAN SAD.
(LAUGHING)
HE CAME!
IMOGEN:
SO THEN MRS. COYNE SWOOPED IN
LIKE MUSSOLINI
AND FORCED FIONA TO TAKE
THIS STUPID OPPORTUNITY.
BIANCA:
A JOB IN ITALY?
DREW:
MAMMA MIA.
BIANCA:
WE COULD VISIT.
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO SEE
THE LEANING TOWER OF PISA.
FOCUS, PEOPLE.
MAMA COYNE:
RUTHLESS DICTATOR;
FIONA: INDENTURED PLEBE.
DISCUSS.
FIONA:
IMMY, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
FEDERICO PROBABLY WON'T EVEN
CALL BACK.
YOU CALLED HIM?
YEAH, BUT I GOT
HIS VOICE MAIL, SO...
(DREW HUMS TO COVER AWKWARDNESS)
YOU WANNA DANCE?
I LOVE DANCING!
OKAY.
JUST REMEMBER
THOSE ROMANS ARE BRUTAL.
THEY FEED PEOPLE
TO LIONS.
THAT WAS THOUSANDS
OF YEARS AGO.
YEAH, WELL, THERE'S NO PROOF
THEY'VE CHANGED.
LET'S NOT EVEN TALK
ABOUT THIS
UNTIL FEDERICO
CALLS BACK.
I HAVE TO GO ANNOUNCE
PROM KING AND QUEEN.
ARE YOU COMING?
I'LL JUST GUARD
THE PURSES.
♪ And you are sorry
for it all ♪
♪ And I care ♪
♪ Nothing is my fault ♪
♪ You're leaving as I say ♪
YOU KNOW WHAT I LOVE
ABOUT YOU?
YOU'RE DEPENDABLE.
I'VE KNOWN YOU TWELVE HOURS
AND YOU HAVEN'T BROKEN
A COMMITMENT.
BEST PROM DATE EVER!
CLIFF:
WHAT ABOUT THE PRINCE CHARMING
GET-UP?
THE CARRIAGE?
SO ROMANTIC!
CLARE:
YOU KNOW WHAT'S NOT ROMANTIC?
BREAKING UP WITH SOMEONE
AFTER YOU TELL THEM
THAT YOU'RE ALL IN.
WE HAD A PLAN.
HE WAS GONNA GO
TO NYU,
I WAS GONNA FOLLOW
TO COLUMBIA.
WE'D GET A STUDIO APARTMENT
IN BROOKLYN...
CLIFF:
SOUNDS DREAMY.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
DATE HIM.
MAN, I WISH.
(REALIZING, LAUGHS)
YOU'RE GAY.
IT'S CLEAR YOU STILL
LOVE THE GUY,
SO WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
FIONA:
OKAY, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
ARE YOU READY TO MEET
YOUR PROM KING AND QUEEN?
(APPLAUSE AND CHEERING)
OKAY, DRUM ROLL, PLEASE.
THE COUPLE
WITH THE MOST VOTES...
IS ELI GOLDSWORTHY
AND CLARE EDWARDS.
(APPLAUSE)
YOU'VE GOTTA BE KIDDING ME!
ELI? CLARE?
COME UP AND GET CROWNED.
(APPLAUSE)
FIONA:
ALL RIGHT,
WE'VE GOT OUR KING.
HAS ANYONE SEEN OUR QUEEN?
(ROOM BUZZES WITH CHATTER)
OKAY, LET'S JUST GIVE HER
A MINUTE OR TWO.
(DANCE MUSIC BEGINS TO PLAY)
(PHONE RINGS)
HELLO?
YOU'RE LOOKING
FOR FIONA COYNE.
SHE'S UM...
SHE'S ME.
SURE.
I CAN MEET NOW.
MMM! THIS IS
THE BEST CHOCOLATE...
YOU GOTTA TASTE THIS.
TRY THAT.
PUT THAT IN YOUR FACE.
WE CAN DO IT.
MMM.
IT'S GOOD.
THIS ONE IS GOOD.
MAN, I DON'T WANT THESE
GOOD TIMES TO END, DUDE.
I'M GLAD YOU CAME.
YEAH, ME TOO.
THIS WAS THE BEST DEAL
EVER.
WHAT YOU MEAN, DEAL?
FIFTY BUCKS TO SIT
AT YOUR TABLE.
MARISOL SAID
THAT SHE WANTED TO FILL
ONE OF THE EMPTY SEATS
SO YOU GUYS DIDN'T LOOK
LIKE LOSERS.
MAYBE IT WAS PROM POLITICS,
I DON'T KNOW.
MARISOL PAID YOU
TO COME?
WELL, HAD I KNOWN THE FOOD
WAS THIS GOOD,
I WOULD HAVE COME
FOR FREE, MAN.
GLAD TO KNOW MARISOL THINKS
SO HIGHLY OF ME.
WHAT WAS THAT?
OH, RELATIONSHIP DRAMA?
RELATIONSHIP DRAMA.
YEAH.
THAT'S IT.
SEE YOU AROUND.
(PARISIAN MUSIC PLAYS)
MAN AND WOMAN:
AGH!
MAN:
EXCUSE ME.
WOMAN:
HEY!
HELLO!
YOU MUST BE FEDERICO.
FEDERICO:
CIAO, FIONA.
COME STAI, BELLA.
MM!
I PREFER MISS COYNE.
AFTER ALL,
MY FAMILY IS REALLY RICH.
BUT YOU ALREADY KNEW THAT,
RIGHT?
SI.
SO THAT'S WHY YOU WANT ME
TO WORK FOR YOU?
BECAUSE OF MY "CONNECTIONS"?
SCUSI?
(SIGHS)
I'M ONTO YOU, FEDERICO.
YOU ITALIANS ARE
A SNEAKY BUNCH,
AND DON'T EVEN GET ME
STARTED ON THE LIONS.
MISS COYNE,
ARE YOU INEBRIATED?
I THOUGHT YOU WOULD
NEVER OFFER.
UM, CAN WE GET
ANOTHER GLASS?
SO, TELL ME ABOUT
THE JOB...
MA CHE COSA DICI?!
I'VE NEVER SEEN
SUCH RUDE BEHAVIOUR.
OH! I'M THE RUDE ONE?
YOU INTERRUPTED MY PROM
WITH MY GIRLFRIEND
TO TALK ABOUT THIS
STUPID OPPORTUNITY,
SO LET'S TALK.
OPPORTUNITY?
THERE IS NO OPPORTUNITY
FOR YOU.
IN FACT, I HOPE I NEVER LAY EYES
ON FIONA COYNE AGAIN
IN MY LIFE.
PORCA MISERIA.
NOTHING WOULD MAKE ME HAPPIER.
(SATISFIED EXHALE)
ANYA, THE HOTTEST GIRL,
WAS MY DATE LAST YEAR.
THIS YEAR,
THREE NOT AS HOT GIRLS
TURNED ME DOWN.
THREE.
THIS IS MY LAST NIGHT OUT
FOR A WHILE.
THIS SUMMER...
I'M ON FULL-TIME DADDY DUTY.
NO MORE DATES FOR ME.
♪ Now I had
the time of my life ♪
MARISOL REQUESTED THIS SONG
FOR US.
♪ I've never felt
like this before ♪
♪ Yes, I swear ♪
SHE WANTED TO HAVE
THIS STUPID ROMANTIC MOMENT.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S NOT ROMANTIC?
PAYING JAKE TO COME TO PROM
WITH US BEHIND MY BACK.
GIRLS, MAN.
THEY'RE JUST NOT WORTH IT.
SEE? MARISOL DOESN'T GOTTA
PAY ANYONE TO BE MY FRIEND.
I GOT YOU GUYS!
HEY... OKAY.
(SOBBING)
THINGS DIDN'T WORK OUT
WITH YOUR DATE?
PLEASE,
YOU NEED TO STOP.
CLARE, I WAS MESSED UP
AFTER CAM.
I WASN'T THINKING.
BUT A DAY HASN'T GONE BY
I HAVEN'T MISSED YOU.
ME TOO.
THEN WHY CAN'T YOU FORGIVE
AND FORGET?
BECAUSE YOU BAILED ON ME!
I'M A PRODUCTION ASSISTANT
ON BRET BARNETT'S NEW FILM.
I LEAVE TOMORROW.
TOMORROW?
SO WE ONLY HAVE
ONE NIGHT LEFT?
WHAT DO YOU SAY,
MY QUEEN?
(PANTING)
♪ Have I found you ♪
♪ Flightless bird ♪
HEY, STRANGER.
SORRY I BAILED
FOR A BIT.
MY DAD SOUNDED REALLY WEIRD
ON THE PHONE
SO I WENT TO GO
CHECK ON HIM.
BUT IT WAS A FALSE ALARM.
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE
HIDING OUT
BECAUSE OF ITALY.
TRUTH? I WISH THIS STUPID
OPPORTUNITY DIDN'T EXIST.
WELL, I'M NOT SURE
THAT IT DOES.
FEDERICO DIDN'T EVEN
CALL BACK.
BUT I'M NOT GONNA LET IT
RUIN PROM.
MAY I HAVE THIS DANCE?
(PHONE RINGS)
WAIT. WHY DO YOU HAVE
MY PHONE IN YOUR PURSE?
UM, YEAH, MINE DIED,
SO I BORROWED YOURS.
WHO IS IT?
MY MOM.
CAN WE JUST LET IT RING?
I REALLY LOVE THIS SONG.
NO. MAYBE SHE HEARD
FROM FEDERICO.
I'LL MEET YOU
ON THE DANCE FLOOR, OKAY?
HI, MOM.
ELI:
WHO'D HAVE THUNK IT?
THE GUY WHO USED TO DRIVE
A HEARSE
AND DRESS ALL IN BLACK
WOULD END UP PROM KING.
I DON'T BELIEVE THAT
ALL THESE PEOPLE VOTED FOR US.
ELI:
CORRECTION.
SOME OF THEM VOTED FOR US.
I KNEW YOU RIGGED IT!
HOW?
ELI:
LET'S JUST SAY
I OWE FIONA A HUGE FAVOUR.
BUT IT WAS WORTH IT.
SO WHAT DO THE KIDS DO
ON PROM NIGHT THESE DAYS?
ELI:
OH, I DON'T KNOW...
GET DRUNK.
GET A ROOM.
HAVE SEX?
HI.
GUYS!
YOU NEED SOMETHING,
MORENO?
YEAH. ADVICE.
DREW'S MADE A LOT OF MISTAKES,
RIGHT?
AND HE'LL PROBABLY MAKE
A LOT MORE.
I'M RIGHT HERE.
I DID A BAD THING -
A TERRIBLE,
TERRIBLE THING -
AND WHEN FIONA FINDS OUT
SHE'LL NEVER FORGIVE ME.
JUST TELL HER
THE TRUTH
AND TELL HER
YOU'RE SORRY.
THAT'S YOUR EXPERT ADVICE?!
WHAT? LOVE CONQUERS ALL,
RIGHT, B?
YOU'RE SUCH A SAP.
HEY.
YOU DIDN'T GO CHECK
ON YOUR DAD.
NO.
YOU IMPERSONATED ME
AT A MEETING WITH FEDERICO!
FEDERICO JUST CALLED MY MOM
TO SAY THAT I WAS DRUNK.
DO YOU KNOW
HOW WORRIED SHE WAS?
PRETTY WORRIED,
I BET.
HOW COULD YOU DO THIS?
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT YOU
TO GO.
KIND OF ROMANTIC, HUH.
NO, IT WAS SELFISH
AND IMMATURE.
YOU'RE THE ONE THAT MADE
ALL THESE PROMISES
ABOUT NEXT YEAR,
THEN THE MOMENT YOU
GET A BETTER OFFER-
I WAS BY YOUR SIDE
THROUGH EVERYTHING.
IT'S JUST SOME STUPID JOB,
FIONA!
IT'S MY FUTURE,
AND I EXPECT MY GIRLFRIEND
TO UNDERSTAND THAT.
CAN'T WE JUST KISS
AND MAKE UP?
IT'S PROM
AND WE SHOULDN'T WASTE IT
FIGHTING.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
TO HAVE THE TIME
OF MY LIFE.
♪ But there's nothing to grab ♪
♪ So I let go ♪
♪ I think I finally
had enough ♪
♪ I think I maybe
think too much ♪
♪ I think this might be it
for us ♪
♪ Blow me one last kiss ♪
♪ You think
I'm just too serious ♪
♪ I think you're full of it ♪
♪ My head is spinning ♪