(PAPER RUSTLES)
(KNOCK AT THE DOOR)
MRS. BHANDARI:
DO YOU WANT TO TELL HER?
MR. BHANDARI:
IT WAS MY IDEA.
MRS. BHANDARI:
YES, BUT I WAS THE ONE
WHO MADE IT HAPPEN.
MOM, DAD,
I DON'T MEAN TO BE RUDE,
BUT I'M KINDA
UNDER THE GUN HERE.
BHANDARIS?
IT'S KINDA EARLY,
ISN'T IT?
MR. BHANDARI:
OH, IT'S NEVER TOO EARLY
FOR A SURPRISE,
WHICH WE HAVE FOR ALLI -
A BIG ONE.
MRS. BHANDARI:
ALLI'S BEEN WORKING SO HARD
TO GO TO M.I.T. NEXT YEAR,
WE WANTED TO MAKE HER LIFE
A LITTLE EASIER.
OKAY, YOU GUYS ARE KILLING ME!
WHAT IS IT?!
(BOTH LAUGH)
(HORN BLASTS)
CLARE:
YOU GOT A CAR?!
ALLI:
WELL, YOU KNOW,
MY REWARD FOR HAVING NO LIFE!
CLARE:
THINK OF ALL THE PLACES
THAT WE CAN GO!
MUSEUMS,
ART GALLERIES...
OR...YOU KNOW,
SOMEWHERE FUN.
YEAH. LIKE I HAVE TIME
FOR ANY OF THAT.
CLARE:
DO YOU STILL HAVE TIME
FOR...
A JAY-Z CONCERT?
YOU MEAN THE CONCERT THAT YOU,
ELI, ME AND DAVE
WERE SUPPOSED
TO DOUBLE-DATE TO?
I COULD BE YOUR DATE.
NO OFFENSE, JENNA,
BUT I WAS REALLY
LOOKING FORWARD
TO GOING WITH DAVE.
I STILL WANT TO GO
WITH DAVE.
BUT YOU GUYS ARE
BROKEN UP.
WELL, MAYBE,
IF I BUST MY BUTT,
I CAN AFFORD A NIGHT OFF
FOR A DATE.
IF DAVE SAYS YES.
THEY'RE JAY-Z TICKETS.
(SIGHS)
WHO WOULD SAY NO?
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
(Ooh-ooh-ooh)
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
HEY! GREAT RAPTORS GAME
LAST NIGHT, HUH?
(LAUGHS)
THEY DIDN'T EVEN PLAY.
SO WHAT,
ARE WE TALKING AGAIN?
WELL... WE KIND OF
HAVE TO.
JAY-Z!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I FORGOT ABOUT THAT.
SO YOU STILL WANNA GO?
WON'T IT BE
UNCOMFORTABLE?
BECAUSE OF THE HARD
PLASTIC SEATS?
(CHUCKLES)
BECAUSE OF THE FEELINGS.
THERE ARE STILL FEELINGS?
WELL, YEAH!
I MEAN, IT...
DOESN'T CHANGE OVERNIGHT.
BUT LAST I CHECKED,
YOU'RE STILL ALL-WORK,
NO-PLAY GIRL.
PLEASE, JUST GIVE ME
ANOTHER CHANCE.
IT'S WING NIGHT
AT THE DOT.
TONIGHT?
I'M TUTORING.
VOLUNTEER HOURS -
I NEED THEM TO GRADUATE.
BUT MY PARENTS
GOT ME A CAR,
AND IF I DO MY ENGLISH ESSAY
AT LUNCH,
AND SCRAMBLE TO DO
MY HISTORY PROJECT
BEFORE BED,
I CAN MAKE AN HOUR
STARTING AT SIX...THIRTY.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
I'LL SEE YOU THEN.
SEE YOU THEN.
TRISTAN:
I HEARD YOU'RE WORKING
ON A MOVIE.
WHATEVER IT IS,
I WANT THE LEAD.
TRISTAN,
YOU'RE A REALLY GOOD ACTOR.
BUT...?
ELI, I WAS MAGNIFICENT
IN THE MUSICAL.
PEOPLE RAVED.
THERE WAS RAVING.
YOU KNOW I CAN DO THIS.
TO BE HONEST,
I HAVE SOME CONCERNS.
WHATEVER IT IS,
I CAN DO IT.
ACTING CLASSES?
NO, TRISTAN-
OKAY, UM... IMPRESSIONS!
I'LL BE BACK!
I'LL NEVER LET GO,
JACK!
I'LL MAKE HIM AN OFFER
HE CAN'T REFUSE.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEAN.
WELL, THEN WHAT?
CRYING ON CUE?
LOOK, I KNOW YOU CAN HANDLE
THE EMOTIONAL STUFF,
BUT CAN YOU HANDLE
THE PHYSICAL DEMANDS?
IT'S A ZOMBIE MOVIE.
PUH-LEASE. EVEN MY DOG
CAN PLAY DEAD, ELI.
AH, BUT THE LEAD IS
THE CHAMPION OF THE LIVING,
THE ZOMBIE SLAYER,
A TRUE ACTION HERO.
LIKE CHRIS HEMSWORTH?!
YEAH, THERE'LL BE RUNNING,
ZOMBIE FIGHTING,
RESCUING DAMSELS
IN DISTRESS.
ELI, I SIMPLY MUST HAVE
THIS PART!
I WILL BEG.
OKAY, TRISTAN,
I NEED AN ACTOR
WHO CAN HANDLE TAKE AFTER TAKE
OF NON-STOP PHYSICAL ACTIVITY;
SOMEONE IN TOP SHAPE.
UH, NO PROBLEM.
MOVIE STARS
TRAIN FOR ROLES
ALL THE TIME!
I WILL PROVE TO YOU
THAT I DESERVE THIS ROLE!
FIONA:
AM I MAKING
A GOOD IMPRESSION?
IMOGEN:
ON ME;
YOU'RE CUTE WHEN YOU HAVE
THE JEEBIE-JEEBIES.
(LAUGHS) I'M PRETTY SURE
IT'S THE HEEBIE-JEEBIES.
BUT SERIOUSLY, IMOGEN,
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
I'VE REALLY TALKED TO YOUR MOM!
I'M NERVOUS!
I NEED TO MAKE
A GOOD IMPRESSION.
(SIGHS)
YOU'RE DOING FINE.
NATALIE:
I HAD TO ASK
TWO DIFFERENT PLACES
JUST TO GET SOY SAUCE.
FIONA:
WELL, THE SUSHI HERE
IS PRETTY GOOD FOR MALL FOOD.
THE SPICY TUNA'S
MY MOM'S FAV.
DO YOU AND YOUR MOTHER
COME HERE OFTEN?
FIONA:
WE USED TO,
BUT SHE HAD TO GO BACK
TO NEW YORK.
I MISS HER TONS.
WORK?
FIONA:
UH, SORT OF.
SHE'S UNDER HOUSE ARREST.
BUT IT'S REALLY NO BIG DEAL.
YOU KNOW HOW THE I.R.S IS,
ALWAYS OVERREACTING
WHEN TAX FRAUD IS INVOLVED...
AND MY DAD'S THERE
HELPING OUT,
AND I HAVE A GREAT ROOMMATE,
DREW.
HE WORKS RIGHT OVER THERE.
NATALIE:
SO YOU LIVE ALONE,
WITH NO PARENTAL SUPERVISION,
WITH A BOY-
IMOGEN:
WHOA, NATALIE!
SIMMA.
FION'S TURNED LEMONS
INTO LEMONADE!
FIONA:
UH, WELL, WHO WANTS GREEN TEA
ICE CREAM FOR DESSERT?
ME!
NATALIE:
IT'S GETTING LATE.
OH! UM... WELL,
IT WAS REALLY GREAT
GETTING TO KNOW YOU BETTER,
MS. GRANGER.
AGREED.
COME ON, IMOGEN.
LET'S GO.
BYE.
ALLI:
OKAY, LIST THE FIRST
TEN ELEMENTS IN ORDER,
AND THEN WE CAN BOTH
GET OUTTA HERE.
CAM:
(SIGHS)
HYDROGEN, HELIUM...
LITHIUM...
OXYGEN?
YOU MISSED BORON...
(SIGHS)
AND BERYLLIUM.
CAM:
WHY CAN'T I REMEMBER THESE?
ALLI:
MAYBE THIS WILL HELP YOU.
HARRY, HE LIKES
BEER BOTTLE COLD,
NOT OVERLY FROTHY.
CAM:
WHAT?
HARRY - HYDROGEN;
HE - HELIUM;
LIKES - LITHIUM.
SEE?
YOU DO THE REST.
BEER - BERYLLIUM;
BOTTLE - BORON;
COLD - CAR...
CAR...
CAR... TOONIUM?
...BON. CARBON.
OKAY, WELL,
I HAVE TO GO,
BUT WE CAN JUST PICK THIS UP
TOMORROW, OKAY?
CAM:
WAIT. YOU'RE LEAVING?
NO, NO. NO, NO, NO.
PLEASE.
I HAVE A HUGE TEST TOMORROW.
(SIGHS)
OKAY, (LAUGHS)
WE CAN...
GO OVER IT
ONE MORE TIME.
(SIGHS, RELIEVED)
(TEXT BEEPS)
TRISTAN:
MY FIRST YOGA CLASS!
OH, I LOVE IT ALREADY.
I'M SO EXCITED TO TRAIN
FOR MY MOVIE ROLE.
SHUT UP!
MAYA:
NO ONE SAID ANYTHING.
TORI:
I THINK TRIS WAS TALKING
ABOUT HIM.
MAYA:
OH! YOUR CRUSH
FROM THE MUSICAL.
WHAT'S HIS NAME, AGAIN?
FAB.
I DIDN'T KNOW
HE'D BE HERE.
HEY.
OH, HEY.
YOU'RE IN YOGA CLUB?
YEAH!
UH, YOGA'S MY FAV.
HERE.
MADAME JEAN-AUX:
OKAY, LET'S START WITH
SURYA NAMASKAR A.
STAND IN MOUNTAIN POSE
WITH HANDS TOGETHER
AT THE HEART,
IN PRAYER POSITION.
INHALE, ARMS OVERHEAD.
EXHALE, BEND FORWARD,
HANDS TOUCHING FEET,
THEN JUMP OR STEP BACK
INTO PLANK POSITION.
BREATHE.
AND ONE...
AND TWO...
AND THREE -
LIFT THE BELLY...
(TRISTAN GRUNTS,
STRUGGLING)
AND FOUR...
AND FIVE.
TERRIFIC, EVERYONE!
LET'S HOLD FOR FIVE MORE.
YOU OKAY?
OH, TOTALLY.
JUST DON'T WANT TO MAKE YOGA
SEEM TOO EASY,
IN CASE THERE'S ANY NEWBIES
IN THE CLASS.
MADAME JEAN-AUX:
AND FOR SIDE PLANK...
AND ONE...
TWO -
LEGS REALLY STRONG...
FAB:
IF YOU CAN'T SUPPORT
YOUR BODY WEIGHT,
THERE'S A MODIFIED POSITION.
JUST PUT ONE KNEE DOWN,
LIKE THIS.
THANKS.
MADAME JEAN-AUX:
...FIVE -
BELLY TO YOUR SPINE.
GOOD!
OKAY, LET'S GO
FROM THE TOP.
LET'S STAND IN MOUNTAIN POSE
WITH HANDS TOGETHER.
TELL ME EVERYTHING YOUR MOM SAID
ABOUT DINNER.
IMOGEN:
YOU'VE REACHED
THE IMOGEN HOTLINE.
TO SPEAK TO THE FANTABULOUS
IMOGEN MORENO,
PLEASE PRESS ONE.
TO DEAL WITH THE DREADFUL
NATALIE GRANGER,
PLEASE PRESS TWO-
FIONA:
IMOGEN! COME ON!
DID I COMPLETELY BLOW IT?
DOES SHE HATE ME?
NATALIE DOESN'T HATE ANYTHING,
EXCEPT FOR
MY BEDROOM RENOVATIONS.
SHE SAID SHE WANTED ME
TO MOVE IN,
BUT CLEARLY
I'M A HUGE INCONVENIENCE.
FIONA:
SO DINNER WENT OKAY?
WE ATE FOOD.
NO ONE BARFED.
I GUESS THAT USUALLY MEANS
"GOOD MEAL," RIGHT?
THEN WHAT?
COME ON!
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
TELL ME!
SHE'D PREFER IF I DIDN'T
HANG OUT AT YOUR LOFT ANYMORE.
(GASPS) IT'S WORSE
THAN I THOUGHT.
FIONES,
WHY DO YOU CARE SO MUCH?
BECAUSE SHE'S YOUR MOM,
AND I NEED TO HAVE
A RELATIONSHIP WITH HER.
WHY? I BARELY DO.
IT'S NO BIG DEAL,
FIONA.
TRUST.
(SIGHS)
(CAR RUMBLES,
HORN HONKS)
ALLI:
HEY! SORRY I'M LATE.
MUAH!
THE KID I'M TUTORING
IS REALLY STRUGGLING.
IT'S ALWAYS SOMETHING,
ISN'T IT?
DAVE, I'M TRYING.
IT'S NOT LIKE
I HAVE A CHOICE.
YOU DO HAVE A CHOICE
AND YOU'VE MADE IT,
AND I'VE GOTTA MAKE MINE:
I'M NOT DOING THIS.
NOT ANYMORE.
BUT DAVE...
CAN I GET THE BILL,
PLEASE?
(SNIFFLING)
DALLAS:
YOU GONNA EAT ALL THESE WINGS
BY YOURSELF?
(ALLI SIGHS)
ALLI:
YOU KNOW, I ALWAYS PICTURED
MY LAST YEAR OF HIGH SCHOOL
TO BE FUN, FRIENDS,
AND FESTIVITIES,
AND NOW I GET WORK, WORK,
AND MORE WORK.
WING?
UGH! I CANNOT BELIEVE
I AM POURING MY HEART OUT
TO THE ICE HOUND
THAT TRASHED
MY BEST FRIEND'S BIRTHDAY.
WHY CAN'T I BE KNOWN
AS THE ICE HOUND
WHO SAVED YOU
FROM LOSING IT IN PUBLIC?
YOU'RE WELCOME,
BY THE WAY.
WELL, THANK YOU
FOR LISTENING,
BUT MY HISTORY PROJECT
AWAITS.
DALLAS:
NO, NO, NO.
I'VE BEEN LISTENING
TO YOU TALK NON-STOP
ABOUT HAVING NO FUN.
I'M NOT LETTING YOU
LEAVE TONIGHT
WITHOUT SHOWING YOU
A GOOD TIME.
DALLAS, I AM NOT MAKING OUT
WITH YOU.
WHOA!
I'M NOT THAT EASY.
(LAUGHS)
WELL, WHAT DO YOU
HAVE IN MIND?
HOW GOOD ARE YOU
AT CLIMBING FENCES?
FENCES?
I'LL GIVE YOU A BOOST.
(GRUNTS OF EFFORT)
ALLI:
THIS IS BEAUTIFUL.
DALLAS:
THIS IS WHERE I COME
TO CLEAR MY HEAD.
ALLI:
IT FEELS LIKE WE'RE
A MILLION MILES AWAY.
IT'S A SHAME
I FORGOT MY BATHING SUIT.
WHO NEEDS SUITS?
(LAUGHS)
YOU COMING?
WELL, TURN AROUND.
DALLAS:
MODESTY CARD, BHANDARI?
(CHUCKLES DRYLY)
I DON'T REALLY CARE!
OH!
(ALLI SHRIEKS, LOUD SPLASH)
(DALLAS AND ALLI CHUCKLE)
TRISTAN:
CHRIS HEMSWORTH
WOULD NEVER DO YOGA.
TORI:
HE DOES.
I HEARD THAT'S HOW
HE PREPARED FOR THOR...
BUT MAYBE I READ IT
INCORRECTLY.
TRISTAN:
THANK YOU. (SIGHS)
I COMPLETELY
EMBARRASSED MYSELF.
PROBABLY BLEW IT
WITH FAB.
IT WAS YOUR FIRST TIME!
ALL YOU NEED IS SOME PRACTICE
AND A NEW YOGA OUTFIT.
BECAUSE BLACK
IS SO SLIMMING.
OKAY, WHAT'S WRONG?
FAB PRETTY MUCH TOLD ME
I WAS FAT
DURING OUR YOGA SESH.
THAT JERK!
BUT HE'S RIGHT.
THAT'S PROBABLY WHY
ELI DIDN'T WANT ME
FOR HIS MOVIE.
WHO WANTS A FATSO
FOR AN ACTION STAR?
STOP FREAKING, TRIS.
IT WAS ONE BAD YOGA CLASS!
IT'S NOT JUST THE YOGA CLASS.
I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT THIS
FOR A WHILE.
I WANT LOVE,
AND MAYBE I'M NOT FINDING IT
BECAUSE I'M BIGGER.
WHAT DO I DO?
YOU COULD GO
ON A DIET.
TORI!
I'M JUST TRYING TO HELP!
COME ON, TRIS,
JUST TRY THE SHIRT ON.
IT'LL MAKE YOU
FEEL BETTER.
NO.
I'M NOT IN THE MOOD.
RETAIL THERAPY WON'T HELP
THIS LARDO.
NOTHING WILL.
FIONA:
SO IMOGEN'S MOM
BASICALLY HATES ME!
DREW:
HEY, FIONA.
YOU MAY HAVE NOTICED
WE'RE WATCHING A MOVIE.
AND YOU REMEMBER
WHAT WE DISCUSSED, ROOMIE?
DON'T INTERRUPT YOU
DURING SEXY TIME.
(GASPS) EW! WAS THAT
WHAT YOU GUYS WERE DOING?!
DREW:
UH... NO.
THE OTHER THING
WE DISCUSSED...
IX-NAY ON THE MOM TALK-AY?
THAT'S NOT PIG LATIN.
THAT WASN'T ANYTHING
LATIN.
(SIGHS,
SHUTS OFF THE TV)
SO IT'S COOL THAT I DON'T
HAVE A RELATIONSHIP
WITH MY GIRLFRIEND'S MOM,
RIGHT?
WELL, B DOESN'T HAVE ONE
WITH MINE ANYMORE;
THAT'S WORKING GREAT.
ACTUALLY,
IT KINDA SUCKS.
NEWS TO ME.
ADMIT IT,
IT WAS EASIER
WHEN YOUR MOM AND I
WERE FRIENDLY.
UH, YEAH, MAYBE.
DEFINITELY.
WHENEVER I NEEDED HELP,
YOUR MOM WAS THERE.
PLUS THERE WERE
ALL THE FAMILY EVENTS:
SUNDAY NIGHT DINNER,
GAMES NIGHTS...
I LOVE BOARD GAMES.
AUDRA WAS LIKE
A SUBSTITUTE MOM.
DREW:
SERIOUSLY?
I BET SHE GAVE
GREAT ADVICE, TOO.
SHE REALLY DID.
ALL RIGHT,
IT'S SETTLED.
I NEED TO HAVE A RELATIONSHIP
WITH IMOGEN'S MOM.
I HAVE TO FIX THINGS
WITH NATALIE!
(LAUGHING)
(SARCASTICALLY)
THANK YOU!
THANK YOU.
(SIGHS)
WELL, THIS WAS FUN.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE
LEAVING TALK.
YEAH, WELL, I SHOULD'VE
BEEN HOME HOURS AGO.
YOU GOT SOME
CRAZY CURFEW?
NO, I HAVE A CRAZY AMOUNT
OF HOMEWORK TO DO.
I'M FAST-TRACKING
CUZ I GOT INTO THIS
SPECIAL PROGRAM AT M.I.T.
I'M SLOW-TRACKING.
I'M GONNA TAKE A VICTORY LAP,
MAYBE TWO.
MUST BE NICE.
DALLAS:
IT IS!
HIGH SCHOOL'S AS GOOD
AS IT GETS.
WHY RUSH IT,
BHANDARI!
I DID IT YOUR WAY ONCE.
WENT AND GOT MYSELF
HOOKED ON THESE PILLS
TO KEEP MYSELF AWAKE
'CAUSE I WAS SO BUSY.
WELL,
CAN YOU HOOK ME UP?
DALLAS:
YOU DON'T NEED PILLS,
BHANDARI.
WHAT YOU NEED
IS A BALANCE.
YOU KNOW,
SO YOU DON'T GO INSANE.
SPEAKING OF INSANE,
MY TO-DO LIST ISN'T
GETTING ANY SHORTER,
SO HISTORY PROJECT...
HERE I COME!
JAY-Z TICKETS?
I WAS ONLINE FOR HOURS
TRYING TO SCORE ONE.
I'LL PAY DOUBLE
WHAT YOU DID.
TAKE IT.
SERIOUSLY?
A THANK YOU
FOR CHEERING ME UP!
♪ That I have been
the best MC ♪
♪ He or she has ever
been facing ♪
♪ I'm just saying
I'll that I need is... ♪
♪ Realize the realization ♪
♪ And every single face
that I'm facing ♪
♪ That I have been the best... ♪
JENNA:
ALLI! ALLI? ALLI!
WHAT TIME IS IT?!
JENNA:
TIME FOR SCHOOL.
YOU OVERSLEPT YOUR ALARM.
ALLI:
CRAP! CRAP, CRAP, CRAP!
WE CAN STILL MAKE IT.
YOU HAVE A CAR, NOW,
REMEMBER?
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I'M SCREWED!
MY ENGLISH READING,
MY... UGH!
TUTORING WORKSHEETS
FOR CAM.
GOD, MY HISTORY PROJECT!
I SHOULD'VE NEVER TAKEN
A NIGHT OFF.
I GUESS YOUR DATE WENT WELL
WITH DAVE?
ACTUALLY,
QUITE THE OPPOSITE.
HE PRETTY MUCH DUMPED ME
ALL OVER AGAIN.
IT WAS TERRIBLE.
THEN WHO KEPT YOU OUT
SO LATE LAST NIGHT?
DALLAS.
MIKE DALLAS?!
YOU'RE INTO HIM NOW?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
I DON'T HAVE TIME
TO BE INTO ANYBODY,
ESPECIALLY
IF I FALL ASLEEP
INSTEAD OF DOING
A HISTORY PROJECT!
MAYBE PERINO WILL GIVE YOU
AN EXTENSION?
HAVE YOU MET PERINO?
(SIGHS)
FIONA:
HI, I'M LOOKING
FOR DOCTOR GRANGER.
NATALIE:
FIONA?
LOOK, I KNOW THAT
YOU DON'T LIKE
MY LIFE SITUATION,
BUT I WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT I'M NOT A BAD PERSON.
I WASN'T TRYING
TO JUDGE, FIONA.
I WAS ONLY TRYING
TO BE A GOOD MOM.
(SIGHS) I KNOW,
I GET THAT.
I'M SURE MY MOM WOULD'VE
FELT THE SAME WAY.
BUT IMOGEN AND I ARE
A GOOD FIT,
AND I'D REALLY LIKE
ANOTHER CHANCE TO SHOW YOU.
THIS WEEK IS REALLY BUSY,
AND I'VE GOT THE RENOVATIONS
AT HOME...
I WILL BEG.
(LAUGHS)
I'M BEGINNING TO REALIZE
WHAT MY DAUGHTER SEES IN YOU.
OKAY, GIVE ME
YOUR CELL PHONE NUMBER.
WHEN THINGS CLEAR UP,
YOU AND IMOGEN AND I
CAN ALL GO SHOPPING.
IT'D BE A GREAT WAY
FOR US ALL TO BOND.
UH, IMOGEN LIKES SHOPPING,
RIGHT?
ARE YOU KIDDING?
(LAUGHS)
SHE'D SLEEP AT THE MALL
IF THEY'D LET HER.
TORI:
HEY, TRIS!
HOW ARE YOU
FEELING TODAY?
I SPENT ALL NIGHT OBSESSING
ABOUT YOUR DIET ADVICE.
I'M SO SORRY.
DON'T BE.
I FOUND THE PERFECT WAY
TO LOSE WEIGHT:
THE MAGICAL CLEANSE!
MAYA:
A CLEANSE?
THAT'S A TERRIBLE IDEA!
I'M TOTALLY IN.
MAYA:
GUYS, THESE CRASH DIETS
ARE SO NOT HEALTHY.
FIRST OF ALL,
IT'S NOT A DIET,
IT'S A CLEANSE.
SECOND OF ALL,
CELEBS DO IT
ALL THE TIME.
OH, CELEBRITIES DO IT.
THEN IT MUST BE HEALTHY.
TRISTAN:
OH, PSHAW!
MAYA, YOU'RE A STICK.
I DON'T EXPECT YOU
TO UNDERSTAND.
THERE ARE SAFER WAYS
TO GET IN SHAPE -
EXERCISE,
EATING RIGHT...
TRISTAN:
THAT SOUNDS SLOW AND HARD.
THIS CLEANSE IS FAST
AND EASY.
I'LL LOSE WEIGHT.
FAB WILL LIKE ME.
ELI WILL CAST ME.
EVERYTHING WILL BE SUNSHINE
AND UNICORNS.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
(CAR ZOOMS,
TIRES SCREECH)
ALLI:
MR. PERINO!
JUST THE PERSON
I WAS LOOKING FOR.
EAGER TO HAND IN YOUR
ASSIGNMENT, MS. BHANDARI?
UM, ACTUALLY, I WAS HOPING
FOR AN EXTENSION.
I'M NOT IN THE HABIT
OF GRANTING EXTENSIONS
TO PEOPLE WHO ALMOST
RUN ME OVER.
I HAVE SO MUCH
ON MY PLATE.
I JUST NEED
A FEW EXTRA DAYS.
DAYS? PLURAL?
I'LL GIVE YOU ONE DAY
AT MOST.
I HAVE NEVER ASKED YOU
FOR AN EXTENSION EVER.
WHICH IS THE ONLY REASON
I'M GIVING YOU THE DAY.
JUST HAVE IT ON MY DESK
FIRST THING IN MORNING.
AND DRIVE A LITTLE MORE
CAREFULLY, OKAY?
ALLI:
I'M DEAD.
I'LL NEVER GET THAT
ASSIGNMENT DONE IN TIME.
I NEED MORE HOURS
IN THE DAY.
YOU COULD ALWAYS GIVE UP
SLEEPING?
HEY, DALLAS?
I NEED A FAVOUR.
TRISTAN:
WELCOME TO OUR FIRST
CLEANSE VLOG!
WITH YOUR SUPPORT,
WE'RE GONNA LOSE SEVEN POUNDS
IN SEVEN DAYS.
NOW, ALL WE'RE GONNA CONSUME
FOR THE NEXT WEEK
IS A LEMONADE MADE OF WATER,
LEMON JUICE,
BROWN SUGAR,
AND OIL OF OREGANO.
TORI:
THAT SOUNDS DISGUSTING.
TRISTAN:
NO PAIN, NO GAIN, BABY.
MAYBE THIS ISN'T
SUCH A GOOD IDEA, TRIS.
LIKE WHO CARES ABOUT ELI'S
STUPID ZOMBIE MOVIE?
THIS ISN'T JUST ABOUT
THE MOVIE.
I WANT LOVE!
AND YOU THINK YOU NEED
TO LOSE WEIGHT TO FIND IT?
IF I DON'T LIKE MYSELF,
HOW CAN ANYBODY LIKE ME?
LOOK, I'M DOING
THIS CLEANSE,
WITH OR WITHOUT YOU.
OKAY.
LET'S DO IT.
(HAPPY SIGH)
DEGRASSI'S FAVOURITE
FAST-TRACKER.
WHAT'S UP?
THIS A...
THIS A BOOTY CALL?
ALLI:
NO!
BUT I WAS THINKING
ABOUT LAST NIGHT...
AND ABOUT THE PILLS
YOU MENTIONED.
(SIGHS) YOU DO NOT
WANNA GO THERE.
YES, I DO.
LAST NIGHT CREATED
THIS HUGE BACKLOG
OF WORK I DIDN'T DO
AND THE ONLY WAY
TO CATCH UP
IS TO FIND MORE HOURS
IN THE DAY.
NO, BHANDARI.
I TOLD YOU HOW MUCH
THOSE PILLS MESSED ME UP.
I ONLY NEED THE PILLS
FOR A FEW DAYS.
I'LL OWE YOU.
OKAY.
I KNOW A GUY.
(RELIEVED EXHALE)