(KEYS CLACK)
OKAY,
DID YOU SEE THAT?
I SAW SOMETHING.
I TOOK IT IN ON
MY OFF-WING
AND I ALMOST SCORED.
ALL RIGHT,
NOW WATCH THIS.
(KEYS CLACK)
MAYA:
OH...
THAT DID NOT LOOK GOOD.
CAM:
EXACTLY. THIS KEEPS HAPPENING
WHEN I PLAY ON THE LEFT WING.
I CARRY THE PUCK IN,
THE D WIPES ME OUT.
SO YOU WANNA PLAY
RIGHT WING.
YEAH.
IT FEELS MORE NATURAL,
I CAN SEE THE ICE BETTER.
BUT THE COACH KEEPS PUTTING ME
ON THE LEFT WING
BECAUSE I SHOOT LEFT.
WHAT HAPPENED THERE?
OH, I'M JUST BANGED UP
FROM LAST NIGHT.
WHEN THE GUYS
DRAGGED YOU OFF?
I'M SO SORRY.
WAS IT BAD?
WELL, UH, THEY SKATED ME
PRETTY HARD,
BUT I SURVIVED.
I'M NOT GONNA MOAN
ABOUT IT.
I DESERVE IT
FOR SKIPPING PRACTICE.
YOU'RE TAKING IT WELL.
WELL, I'M TIRED OF FEELING
DOWN ON MYSELF.
I JUST NEED TO PLAY BETTER
AND WIN,
THEN I'LL FEEL BETTER.
AND YOU THINK THIS LEFT WING/
RIGHT WING THING'S GONNA HELP?
I HOPE SO.
TALK TO YOUR COACH.
DALLAS:
HEY!
NO, HE WON'T TAKE ADVICE
FROM A ROOKIE.
BUT OUR CAPTAIN MIGHT.
HOCKEY PLAYER:
IT IS MAN VERSUS ANIMAL,
IN THE STAMPEDE!
DALLAS:
DOWN, MORONS!
YOU WANNA MISS
THE REST OF THE SEASON
BECAUSE OF A BROKEN LEG?
YOU SERIOUS?
YEAH!
HEY, DALLAS.
UH...
LOOK, I KNOW YOU GUYS AREN'T
MY BIGGEST FANS RIGHT NOW...
HEY, YOU TOOK
YOUR MEDICINE.
SOMETIMES A ROOKIE
JUST NEEDS TO BE TAUGHT
A LESSON IS ALL.
BLANK SLATE GOING FORWARD.
OKAY.
'CAUSE I THINK I KNOW HOW
I CAN HELP THE TEAM,
IF YOU'RE WILLING
TO LISTEN.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
(Ooh-ooh-ooh)
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
CONNOR:
SHE'S ALLOWED TO DRINK.
I MEAN, YOUR MOM IS AN ADULT,
RIGHT?
YEAH,
BUT SHE'S AN ADDICT.
WELL, AN EX-ADDICT,
AND THEY'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO.
AND YOUR DAD
MADE HER DRINK?
NOT EXACTLY.
WHEN SHE'S AROUND HIM,
SHE DOESN'T THINK STRAIGHT.
YOUR DAD'S OUT OF JAIL?
AND I THOUGHT...
IT COULD WORK OUT,
THAT WE COULD FINALLY BE
A FAMILY,
BUT NOTHING'S CHANGED.
KC, I'M SO SORRY.
LOOK,
MAYBE CONNOR'S RIGHT.
MY MOM'S A BIG GIRL,
SHE CAN HANDLE IT.
YOUR MOM LET HIM BACK
INTO YOUR LIVES?
YEAH.
IT SOUNDS TO ME
LIKE SHE MIGHT BE
THE REAL ISSUE HERE.
(BELL RINGS)
IMOGEN:
IS THAT AN ASSIGNMENT?
DID I FORGET?
QUICK, LET ME SEE!
RELAX, GIRL!
IT'S A LIST.
PRETTY SHORT LIST.
I'M THINKING OF WAYS
TO GET BACK AT DREW.
FOR WHAT?
ONLY CLEANING HALF
THE CONDO!
YEAH, WHAT A JERK.
IMOGEN!
WHAT?
YOU EACH PAY HALF THE RENT,
AND HALF THE BILLS,
SO YOU SHOULD SHARE
THE CLEANING, NO?
HE'S A BOY.
BOYS ARE GENETICALLY
MORE SLOVENLY,
AND I'M NOT GONNA BE
HIS MAID.
IT'S ABOUT TIME GUYS HAD
A TASTE OF THE HOUSEWORK
THAT WOMEN HAVE BEEN SUFFERING
THROUGH FOR GENERATIONS.
OH, YOU ARE QUITE
THE FEMINIST.
I THOUGHT YOU'D HAVE MY BACK
IN THIS SITUATION.
I DO!
BUT DO YOU WANNA KNOW
WHAT I'D DO IN YOUR SITUATION?
DON'T SAY, "CLEAN MY HALF
OF THE CONDO."
OKEY DOKEY.
♪♪♪
(CHEERING)
(SKATES SWISH)
LUKE:
HEY.
IF YOU GOT ME SWITCHED
TO THE LEFT WING
SO YOU COULD TRY SUCKING
AT RIGHT WING TOO,
I'M GONNA MAKE LIFE
ROUGH FOR YOU.
(FANS CHEER)
YAY! CAM!
ANNOUNCER:
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
YOUR TORONTO ICE HOUNDS!
(FANS CHEER)
LISA:
HONEY, I KNOW...
I LET YOU DOWN.
I'M SO SORRY.
YOUR DAD WANTED
TO CELEBRATE,
AND I-I JUST GOT CAUGHT UP!
SO THAT'S IT?
HE GETS OUT,
AND YOU START DRINKING
AGAIN?
WHAT IF NEXT TIME
HE WANTS TO SMOKE SOME CRACK?
IT WAS A ONE-TIME MISTAKE!
I MET WITH MY SPONSOR
THIS MORNING.
IT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN
ANYMORE.
YOU PROMISED ME
THAT YOU WOULDN'T DRINK AGAIN,
EVER!
AND AS LONG
AS DAD'S AROUND...
HE WON'T BE.
WHAT, DID HE MESS UP
HIS PAROLE ALREADY?
I'VE ASKED HIM
TO STAY AWAY.
FOR REAL?
(RELIEVED SIGH)
THANK GOD!
IT WAS UNFAIR OF ME
TO THROW YOU
IN THE MIDDLE OF EVERYTHING,
I'M-I'M SORRY!
(BOTH SIGH DEEPLY)
KC:
ALL I CARE ABOUT
IS THAT YOU'RE SAFE, MOM.
I'M SORRY.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
KEVIN:
HELLO? ANYBODY IN THERE?
COME ON, I KNOW YOU GUYS
ARE IN THERE!
YOU'RE DRUNK!
KEVIN:
I RAN INTO A BUDDY.
KC:
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE HERE!
KEVIN:
(BANGING ON DOOR)
COME ON!
WE'RE FAMILY, FOR PETE'S SAKE!
LET ME IN!
MAYBE WE SHOULD
JUST LET HIM IN.
KC:
MOM, NO!
KEVIN:
(SHOUTING)
LET ME IN!
KC:
CALL 911, NOW.
I CAN'T!
FINE, I'LL DO IT.
KEVIN:
UNLOCK THE DOOR,
OR I'LL BREAK IT DOWN!
GET INTO THE BEDROOM!
GO! GO!
KEVIN:
(SHOUTING) YOU CAN'T KEEP ME
OUT OF YOUR LIVES!
(KICKING DOOR)
(CROWD CHEERS AND CLAPS)
MAYA:
SEVEN SECONDS LEFT,
I CAN'T WATCH!
ARE YOU KIDDING?
THIS IS SO EXCITING!
CAM ALREADY HAS TWO GOALS,
YOU LUCKY CHARM, YOU!
(CROWD CHEERS)
(PANTING)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
SENDING MORE LUCK.
DALLAS:
TAKE THE DRAW,
COACH WANTS CAM ON HIS OFF WING.
IT'S BEEN WORKING ALL GAME,
NO POINT IN CHANGING IT NOW.
LOOK AT HIM,
HE'S SUCKING WIND
AFTER THAT LAST SHIFT.
(BREATHLESSLY) IT'S FINE.
I'VE BEEN THROUGH WORSE.
I'M READY.
♪ Action ♪
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(CROWD CHEERS)
(STICKS BANG)
♪ You can party like a rock star
honey ♪
♪ When you're in my scene ♪
COME ON, CAM!
COME ON!
♪ Don't need money
'cause you are somebody ♪
♪ When you're in my scene ♪
♪ Come on, yeah! ♪
(BUZZER BUZZES)
(PLAYERS AND CROWD CHEER)
PLAYERS:
WOOO!
CAM:
OH YEAH!
YEAH!
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
HOCKEY PLAYERS:
RIGHT ON! YEAH!
WOOO!
♪ Come on, yeah!
Come on, yeah! ♪
♪ Come on, yeah! ♪
♪ And do my scene ♪
DREW:
THE MESS IS STILL HERE, HUH?
FIONA?
HEY, ARE...
ARE YOU CRYING?
(SNIFFLES) NO.
DREW:
LOOK, IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
A LITTLE SCRUBBING,
AND IT'LL BE GOOD AS NEW.
YEAH, BUT IT'S JUST,
EVERYTHING'S CHANGED SO FAST.
I'M BROKE,
I HAVE TO SHARE MY HOME
JUST TO MAKE ENDS MEET.
MY WHOLE LIFE'S
TURNED UPSIDE DOWN.
IT'S JUST SOME LIGHT
HOUSEWORK.
BUT I ALWAYS HAD SOMEONE -
MY MOM, OR AU PAIRS,
THE CLEANING STAFF -
AND NOW I'M ALL ALONE,
AND I HAVE TO TAKE CARE
OF MYSELF.
IT'S SCARY.
I KNOW.
SO DOES THAT MEAN
YOU'LL CLEAN MY HALF
OF THE CONDO?
NO WAY.
BUT I'VE NEVER
DONE IT BEFORE,
I DON'T KNOW HOW.
I SPENT YEARS BEING TRAINED
BY MRS. CLEAN HERSELF,
AUDRA TORRES.
I'LL HAVE YOU BUFFING
LIKE A CHAMP IN NO TIME!
OKAY?
LUKE:
HEY, GOOD GAME!
KEEP IT UP ALL YEAR,
AND WE'LL WIN THE CUP!
(SIGHS)
YOUR LIFE'S GONNA TAKE OFF
IF YOU KEEP PLAYING LIKE THAT.
EVER THOUGHT ABOUT GETTING
A MANAGER OR AN AGENT?
UH... NO, NOT YET.
THERE'S GONNA BE
A LOT OF PEOPLE
WANTING A PIECE
OF CAM SAUNDERS.
SOMEONE'S WAITING FOR YOU.
CAM:
FOR ME?
YEAH, YOU'D BETTER
GET USED TO THIS.
REPORTERS:
OH HEY! CAM! CAM!
MALE REPORTER:
YOU GOT THE MONKEY
OFF YOUR BACK.
WHAT MADE THE DIFFERENCE
TONIGHT?
(FLURRY OF CLICKING SHUTTERS)
WELL, CAM HAD THE PLAN
THAT MADE IT HAPPEN.
TELL 'EM HOW YOU DID IT.
REPORTER:
DO YOU THINK IT WAS A FLUKE,
OR WILL YOU KEEP UP THE PACE
WITH THE WIZARDS IN TOWN
THIS WEEKEND?
CAM?
UH, ROOKIE'S GOT A LITTLE
STAGEFRIGHT.
I'LL HANDLE QUESTIONS.
(REPORTERS CHATTER LOUDLY)
(DOOR SLAMS)
(HYPERVENTILATING)
(CHOKES BACK A SOB)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CRYING)
(SOBBING)
MAYA:
I'VE SENT CAM LIKE TEN TEXTS,
LEFT THREE MESSAGES...
WELL, I'M SURE THERE'S
A LOGICAL EXPLANATION.
WHAT IF SOMETHING'S WRONG?
MAYBE IT'S SERIOUS!
OR MAYBE HE'S PLANNING
A BIG SURPRISE.
YOU DID HELP HIM
GET HIS MOJO BACK.
(BELL RINGS)
(MAYA SIGHS)
MAYA:
UH, EXCUSE ME, DALLAS?
I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU'VE SEEN CAM.
DALLAS:
NOT SINCE LAST NIGHT.
PROBABLY WENT HOME
WITH SOME PUCK BUNNY.
NOW I NEED TO FIND OUT
WHERE HE LIVES.
ARE YOU JEALOUS?
NO!
I'M JUST WORRIED.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
MR. TOWNSEND:
WHEN WAS THE BATTLE
OF VIMY RIDGE?
1917.
WHICH CONFLICT WAS KNOWN
AS THE WAR-
SO YOUR DAD'S BACK IN JAIL
FOR VIOLATING HIS PAROLE?
YEAH, FOR A NIGHT.
TWO, TOPS.
HE'LL KEEP COMING BACK.
YOU'LL BE AT THE UNIVERSITY
OF BRITISH COLUMBIA NEXT YEAR,
AND THAT JERK WILL BE OUT
OF YOUR LIFE FOR GOOD.
BUT NOT MY MOM'S.
WHAT IS THE ANSWER,
KC?
VANCOUVER.
MR. TOWNSEND:
VANCOUVER IS THE SITE
OF THE FIRST EVER
NUCLEAR BOMB TEST?
REALLY?
UM, I HAVE TO GO.
I'M SORRY.
MOVING ON.
♪ They tell you
that they own it ♪
♪ I know that you can see it ♪
♪ I know that you can beat it ♪
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
♪ I swear today ♪
♪ I won't forget the moment ♪
♪ They told you to believe it ♪
♪ They promised
you'd believe it ♪
♪ True calling is... ♪
♪ For us, for us, for us ♪
♪ For us, for us ♪
♪ For us ♪
♪ True calling is... ♪
(BREATHING SHALLOWLY)
♪ Down... ♪
♪ We all let down ♪
(SIGHS) OKAY.
MY HALF OF THE CONDO
AND THE BATHROOM, ALL DONE.
YOU SEE? IT WASN'T
THAT BAD, WAS IT?
IT WAS BAD ENOUGH.
I'M JUST GLAD I WON'T HAVE
TO DO IT FOR ANOTHER WEEK.
DREW:
OH, UM, HOW DID THE TUB DRAIN?
SLOWLY, AS ALWAYS.
THE CLOG?!
NO! NO, I CAN'T.
THAT THING IN THERE
IS A YEAR'S WORTH
OF YOUR HAIR,
NOT MINE.
(WHIMPERS)
I HATE YOU.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
EW, EW, EW, EW, EWWW!
OH, COME ON,
IT'S JUST A GIANT WAD OF HAIR,
MIXED WITH SOME DEAD SKIN,
SOAP SCUM,
AND IT PROBABLY LOOKS
LIKE A FERRET.
FIONA:
YOU'RE NOT HELPING!
OKAY,
I'M PUTTING THE HOOK IN.
EW, EW!
IT'S GOING IN SO FAR!
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT,
NOW, UH, PULL IT OUT SLOWLY.
FIONA:
EW, EW, EW, EW!
(WATER GURGLES)
(WATER DRAINS)
DREW:
DID YOU GET IT?
I DID.
THANKS FOR YOUR SUPPORT,
I REALLY COULDN'T HAVE DONE
ANY OF THIS WITHOUT YOU.
CHANGE IS HARD.
THIS IS PRETTY SCARY
FOR ME, TOO.
BUT TOGETHER,
I THINK WE CAN GET
THROUGH THIS.
AW! ROOMIE HUG?!
UM...
WHAT WAS THAT?
FIONA:
UM, JUST A LITTLE
HOUSEWARMING GIFT!
OH NO, THE CLOG!
WHAT? IT'S JUST, YOU KNOW,
MY HAIR,
AND SOME DEAD SKIN,
AND SOAP SCUM
THAT KINDA LOOKS
LIKE A FERRET.
COME ON, PLEASE,
PLEASE TAKE IT OUT!
OKAY, SO YOU LET IMOGEN
AND I HAVE A DATE NIGHT,
AND THIS TIME,
YOU STAY OUT LATE.
YES, YES, ANYTHING!
OKAY.
(WHIMPERING)
THANKS AGAIN!
UGH!
GOING SOMEWHERE?
CAM:
HEY.
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
I TOLD YOUR BILLET DAD
I WAS JUST BRINGING YOU
YOUR HOMEWORK.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I'M GOING HOME.
I'M DONE WITH HOCKEY.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND,
YOU WON THE GAME.
PLAYING BETTER WAS SUPPOSED
TO MAKE YOU HAPPY.
AND IT DIDN'T,
OKAY?
I'M JUST, I'M...
I'M SAD...
AND I JUST WANT IT
TO GO AWAY.
WELL, EVERYBODY GETS SAD
ONCE IN A WHILE.
I MEAN, ISN'T QUITTING
A LITTLE EXTREME?
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE
SUPPORTIVE.
I JUST DON'T WANNA SEE YOU
MAKE A DRASTIC DECISION
BECAUSE YOU'RE SAD!
YOU THINK I WANNA FEEL
LIKE THIS?
I AM ALL OUT OF IDEAS,
MAYA!
IT'S LIKE MY HEAD
ISN'T SCREWED ON RIGHT.
MAYBE YOU NEED
TO TAKE A BREAK.
YOU KNOW, BALANCE HOCKEY
WITH OTHER THINGS...
LIKE MORE KARAOKE NIGHTS
WITH YOUR FRIENDS.
I JUST WANNA BE HAPPY,
MAYA.
GOOD!
THEN BE HAPPY.
HMM?
THAT'S REAL HOMEWORK,
BY THE WAY.
(HALF LAUGHS)
SEE YOU AT SCHOOL
TOMORROW?
YEAH.
HEY, MAYA?
YEAH?
THANKS.
(SNIFFS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
JENNA:
HEY, I GOT YOUR TEXT,
AND I SEE YOUR MOM
IN THE OFFICE?
WHAT'S UP?
I NEED YOU TO VISIT TY.
ER, DOUG.
IT'S IMPORTANT.
OKAY, YOU'RE BEING
A LITTLE INTENSE RIGHT NOW.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
UH, MY MOM AND I ARE
MOVING TO BC.
WHAT?! WHY?
BECAUSE MY DAD CAN'T.
HE HAS TO STAY IN THE CITY
'CAUSE OF HIS PAROLE.
SO YOU'RE JUST RUNNING AWAY?
AREN'T THERE ANY OTHER OPTIONS?
RIGHT NOW,
WE'RE JUST WAITING FOR HIM
TO ATTACK ONE OF US,
OR FOR MY MOM TO START
TAKING DRUGS AGAIN.
SO HE'S THE LOSER,
AND YOU'RE THE ONES THAT
HAVE TO LEAVE EVERYTHING?
I NEED TO PROTECT
MY MOM.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY.
WELL, THAT'S NOT FAIR!
HEY, I WANTED TO GO
TO UBC ANYWAY,
SO NOW I'LL JUST BE
HEADING WEST
A LITTLE SOONER
THAN EXPECTED.
HOW SOON?
TODAY.
MY AUNT'S GOT
THE PULL-OUT COUCH ALL SET UP
FOR WHEN WE GET THERE,
AND MR. SIMPSON, UM...
RECOMMENDED A LOT
OF GOOD SCHOOLS IN THE AREA.
I'LL VISIT TY,
AND I'LL SEND
SO MANY PICTURES.
LISA:
WELL, THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
SIMPSON:
THE BRIGHT SPARKS ARE GOING
TO MISS YOU.
A LOT OF US ARE GOING
I'LL MISS YOU TOO.
(SIGHS)
(BELL RINGS)
AND NOW I HAVE ALGEBRA.
AND I HAVE TO CLEAN OUT
MY LOCKER.
LIFE GOES ON, HUH?
♪♪♪
FIONA:
HAPPY FIONA COYNE DAY!
IMOGEN:
I THOUGHT WE ALREADY HAD
FIONA COYNE DAY.
I'M TAKING A PAGE
OUT OF YOUR BOOK.
EVERY DAY CAN BE
A SPECIAL "ME" DAY!
AREN'T YOU A DOSE OF HAPPY.
I'VE EXPERIENCED
PERSONAL GROWTH
THROUGH HONEST HARD WORK.
(GASPS) YOU CLEANED!
VERY MUCH SO!
AND MY ROOMMATE SITUATION
HAS STABILIZED FOR NOW,
AND DREW'S EVEN GONNA GIVE US
SOME ALONE TIME TONIGHT.
I'D LOVE TO,
IT'S JUST...
I HAVE TO PRESENT
MY SET DESIGNS
FOR THE MUSICAL TOMORROW.
ELI'S BEEN ON MY CASE,
AND I HAVE TO STAY HOME
AND WORK.
OKAY, WELL, I'LL COME OVER
AND WATCH, OR HELP!
NO, I GET IT DONE QUICKER
BY MYSELF,
NO OFFENCE,
PLUS MY DAD'S GOT DINNER PLANS
FOR US, SO...
OKAY, I GET IT.
YOU DON'T WANT ME
AT YOUR HOUSE!
IT'S NOT THAT.
WELL, WE'VE BEEN MORE
THAN FRIENDS FOR WEEKS NOW,
AND I'M STILL WAITING
FOR MY INVITE.
I'M SORRY,
IT'S JUST REALLY BAD TIMING.
(TAKING DEEP BREATHS)
OKAY.
(TAKING FAST, SHALLOW BREATHS)
(BREATHING HARD,
PSYCHING HIMSELF UP)
(EXHALES A SLOW, SHAKY BREATH)
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
OKAY.
(BREATHING HARD)
OKAY...
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(STIFLES A SCREAM)
(DULL THUD)
UNGH!
(CRYING IN PAIN)
(MOANING)
OH, WHAT HAPPENED?
IS IT YOUR ARM?
(MOANS IN PAIN)
MS. OH:
I'LL GO GET HELP.
(PANTING)
(CAR DOOR SLAMS)
WE'VE GOT THREE DAYS OF DRIVING
AHEAD OF US,
SO, GET COMFY.
JENNA:
KC, WAIT!
CLARE:
JENNA TOLD US
YOU'RE LEAVING?
SO IT'S REALLY TRUE?
ALL PACKED
AND READY TO GO.
BIANCA:
YOU KNOW, IF YOU'RE SCARED
ABOUT NATIONALS,
THERE ARE OTHER OPTIONS.
I WOULD'VE KILLED THEM.
I KNOW.
HEY, COME HERE.
(SIGHS)
GET IN HERE.
(ALL LAUGH)
ALL RIGHT, ENOUGH...
ENOUGH SADNESS.
NEVER HEARD OF THE INTERNET?
WE'LL KEEP IN TOUCH.
SHOULDN'T YOU GUYS
BE IN CLASS?
WASHROOM PASSES.
CONNOR:
YEAH, WE ALL REALLY HAD TO GO.
(LAUGHS)
THANKS, YOU GUYS.
LISA, YOU'D BETTER
MAKE SURE HE CALLS,
EMAILS,
AND CHECKS FACERANGE.
I'M ALL OVER IT.
BYE, JENNA.
(DOOR SLAMS)
ARE YOU SURE
ABOUT THIS, KID?
YEP.
LET'S GO.
(CAR STARTS)
(SIREN WAILS)
NURSE:
JUST SIGN RIGHT HERE.
GREAT.
LET'S GO, BIRDMAN.
YEAH.
MAYA: CAM!
CAM: HEY, YOU CAME!
WHAT HAPPENED?
UH... HAD A LITTLE FALL.
YEAH, FOOLING AROUND
ON THE CATWALK,
LIKE THE REST OF THE MORONS
ON MY TEAM.
CAM:
AGH! I'M SUCH A KLUTZ.
YEAH, NOW WE DON'T HAVE
OUR BEST PLAYER
FOR SIX TO EIGHT WEEKS.
ALL RIGHT, STAY HERE.
I'LL GET US A RIDE.
AND MAKE SURE BIRDMAN
DOESN'T SLIP ON A WET FLOOR
AND BREAK HIS OTHER ARM.
(LAUGHS)
I GOT A NEW NICKNAME.
THIS IS NOT WHAT I MEANT
WHEN I SAID YOU NEEDED A BREAK!
CAM:
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT!
DO YOU SWEAR?
MAYA, I'M NOT SOME LOSER
WHO TRIES TO HURT HIMSELF.
BESIDES, THIS WILL
GIVE ME MORE TIME
TO HANG OUT WITH YOU
AND THE GUYS.
IS THAT COOL?
WELL, IT DEPENDS;
ARE YOU GONNA BE HAPPY?
I HAVE NO REASON
NOT TO BE.
SO WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOUR ARM GETS BETTER
AND YOU GO BACK
TO HOCKEY?
MAYA, I'M HAPPY NOW...
WITH YOU.
I'M JUST SO GLAD
YOU'RE OKAY.
YEAH, I AM.
I'M GREAT.