(STATIC)
(ZOMBIE MOANING)
RAAARGH!
(BONES CRACK)
RAAAARRRGGHHH!
ZOMBIES:
RAAAAAAAAARRRRRRGGHHHHH!
AND TO THINK,
I WANTED YOU TO LIKE ME
FOR MY BRAINS.
ZOMBIES:
GRRRRAARRRRHHH!
ELI:
CUT! CUT!
(STUDENTS LAUGH)
OKAY. OKAY.
L-LET'S GO AGAIN.
BUT THIS TIME GIVE IT
ALL YOU'VE GOT, OKAY?
IT'S THE LAST SHOT.
IT HAS TO BE PERFECT.
LET'S GET BACK TO ONES!
EW! DON'T TOUCH ME
WITH YOUR STUB.
HEY, COME ON!
MR. STUMPY IS VERY SENSITIVE!
YOU KNOW THAT.
YOU NAMED HIM?!
YOU'RE SO HAPPY
YOU GET TO LOSE A LIMB.
IT'S NICE
TO SEE YOU HAPPY.
WHAT? ME?
I'VE NEVER BEEN UNHAPPY.
SEE?
OOOOH...
PRETTAAY!
SO DO YOU MAYBE WANNA
GO CHECK OUT
THE NEW JOSEPH GORDON LEVITT
MOVIE
AFTER WE FINISH THIS SCENE?
SUPPOSED TO BE TRIPPY.
DID YOU ALREADY ASK TORI
AND TRISTAN?
NO. I WAS THINKING
IT'D JUST BE YOU AND ME.
LIKE A FRIEND DATE?
LIKE A DATE-DATE.
BUT WHAT ABOUT CAM?
YEAH.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I MEAN WE SHOULD PROBABLY
MAKE SURE
IT'S OKAY WITH HIM TOO.
OH, WAIT...
ELI:
IT'S THE LAST DAY
OF SHOOTING PEOPLE, OKAY?!
LET'S GET 'ER DONE!
WHOA!
I'M SO SORRY!
IT'S OKAY.
ANYTIME, REALLY.
SEXY TIE.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
(Ooh-ooh-ooh)
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
KATIE:
HEY, YOU RIDING WITH ME?
MAYA:
YEP.
KATIE:
UH, NICE BRA.
MAYA:
THANKS!
I'M SURE YOUR TEACHERS
WILL LOVE IT TOO.
I'M PRETTY SURE
WE'RE NOT ALLOWED
TO SHOW UNDERWEAR
AT SCHOOL.
WELL, IF I GET CAUGHT,
I'LL JUST SAY...
"OOPSY, I DIDN'T REALIZE IT
WAS SEE-THROUGH! TEE-HEE!"
KATIE:
AND YOU REALLY THINK
THAT'LL WORK, MAYA?
GIRLS IN MY GRADE
DO IT ALL THE TIME.
KATIE:
PLEASE DON'T TELL ME
YOU'RE GOING THROUGH
ONE OF THOSE PHASES
WHERE YOU START DRESSING SLUTTY
AND ACT WAY DUMBER
THAN YOU ACTUALLY ARE?
MAYA:
I'M NOT.
BECAUSE I CAN GET MARISOL
TO TELL YOU
HOW MUCH SHE REGRETS
HER GRADE NINE LOOKS.
SHORT PINK SKIRT,
OVER THE SHOULDER TOP.
NO BRA.
WOW.
YEAH.
IT WAS A LOT.
AM I A BAD PERSON,
KATIE?
FOR WHAT?
UGLY FASHION?
NO, FOR BEING FINE
WITH EVERYTHING.
OH. UH, YOU MEAN CAM.
EVERYONE SEEMS TO THINK
MY WAY IS WRONG.
BECAUSE I'M NOT SITTING
IN A CORNER,
CRYING EVERYDAY,
WEARING A BLACK VEIL
OR WHATEVER.
WELL, THAT'S OKAY.
SO IF I WANTED TO DATE
SOMEONE NEW?
(CHORTLES) UM...
(SIGHS)
THAT'S A NO.
LOOK, I...
ONLY IF YOU THINK
YOU'RE READY. I...
BUT IF NO ONE ELSE
THINKS IT'S RIGHT...
SINCE WHEN HAVE EVER CARED
WHAT OTHER PEOPLE THINK?
TRUTH.
COME ON,
WE HAVE SCHOOL.
♪♪♪
(GIGGLING)
DREW:
HEY! EVERY ONE!
LISTEN UP!
BIANCA:
OW! OWWW!
DREW:
ARE YOU-
BABE, ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH, YEAH.
(GIGGLES)
OKAY. SORRY.
EVERYONE! MY FIANCEE GOT
INTO WILFRED LAURIER!
(APPLAUSE)
YOU'RE TAKING THIS SO WELL,
DREW.
YOU GOT IN
TO UNIVERSITY!
I KNOW,
BUT I'LL BE A HUNDRED MILES AWAY
NEXT YEAR.
AND THE DOCTOR...
SAID I COULDN'T PLAY
FOOTBALL,
HASN'T SAID NO
TO OTHER SPORTS.
BIANCA:
YET. BUT IN CASE HE DOES,
MAYBE YOU SHOULD FIND
ANOTHER ACTIVITY.
DREW:
YEAH.
MARISOL:
GOOD MORNING, DEGRASSI.
SOMETHING TO DISTRACT YOU
FROM YOUR LOOMING EXAMS.
THE ANNOUNCEMENT OF
THE CANDIDATES FOR PRESIDENT:
CLARE EDWARDS
AND... DREW TORRES?!
ANYWAYS GET OUT THERE
AND VOTE!
(CLASS LAUGHS)
DUDE, YOU NOMINATED ME?
MAN, I HAD NOTHING TO DO
WITH THAT.
RIGHT.
THAT'S HILARIOUS.
NO, I SWEAR!
I ACTUALLY DIDN'T.
BUT YOU SHOULD
TOTALLY ACCEPT.
IT'LL BE HILARIOUS!
IT COULD BE AWESOME.
RUNNING THE SCHOOL?
SERIOUSLY?
I'M RUNNING
FOR PRESIDENT?
OKAY, EVERYONE!
I AM RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT!
MY NAME IS DREW TORRES
SO VOTE FOR ME, OKAY?
(APPLAUSE)
AND CLARE SAID ELI WAS LIKE,
"I NEED SPACE."
HE'S ALLERGIC
TO HAPPINESS.
CONNOR:
(CLEAR HIS THROAT LOUDLY)
YOU "NEED SPACE?"
FROM WHAT?
THE LOVE OF YOUR LIFE?
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT YOU NEED:
TO GET OVER YOUR DAMN SELF.
CONNOR:
(CLEAR HIS THROAT LOUDLY)
IS SOMETHING
BOTHERING YOU?
CONNOR:
YES. THIS CONVERSATION
IS EXTREMELY BORING,
AND IT'S CUTTING INTO
MY JENNA TIME.
IT'S JUST A LITTLE GOSSIP,
CONNOR.
WELL, IT FEELS LIKE A LOT.
SOMETIMES WHEN WE GET GOING,
IT CAN BE HARD TO STOP.
WELL, IF ALLI LEAVES,
THE CONVERSATION WILL END
BY DEFAULT, WON'T IT?
CONNOR!
WANT ME TO LEAVE?
JENNA: NO.
CONNOR: YES.
ALLI:
J-ROD, TEXT ME.
ALLI'S CRUSHED
BECAUSE THINGS DIDN'T WORK OUT
WITH MIKE DALLAS.
SHE NEEDS HER FRIENDS.
I NEED MY GIRLFRIEND.
I KNOW,
AND I NEED YOU.
BUT WE NEED TO BE THERE
FOR ALLI TOO.
CONNOR:
SHE WOULDN'T BE AROUND SO MUCH
IF SHE HAD A BOYFRIEND.
JENNA:
MAYBE NOT.
BUT RIGHT NOW SHE'S SAD
AND LONELY.
SHE NEEDS US.
WHAT SHE NEEDS
IS A BOYFRIEND.
DREW:
OKAY.
I GUESS I'M GONNA NEED LIKE,
LIKE A POSTER OR SOMETHING?
IT CAN SAY
"DREW IS FOR YOU!"
WE'LL CALL THAT
A "FIRST IDEA."
(SIGHS)
ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
I NEED IDEAS.
YOU GOTTA SHOW HOW
YOU'RE DIFFERENT FROM CLARE.
SHE'S ORGANIZED,
SHE CAN SPEAK,
SHE CAN WRITE.
PLUS, ADULTS LIKE HER.
SHE MUST HAVE
SOME WEAKNESSES.
YEAH,
SHE'S WAY TOO SERIOUS!
ALL RIGHT.
BINGO.
I NEED TO SHOW THE SCHOOL
THAT A YEAR WITH ME
AS PRESIDENT
IS A YEAR OF NON-STOP
GOOD TIMES.
I'M PICKING UP
WHAT YOU'RE PUTTING DOWN.
AUDRA AND OMAR
ARE AWAY TONIGHT.
PARTY!
MEET DREW, PARTY WITH DREW,
VOTE FOR DREW?
WE GOTTA SEND
THOSE INVITATIONS OUT ASAP.
BIANCA:
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
THEY DON'T CALL IT
A POLITICAL PARTY FOR NOTHING.
♪ You can ride my unicorn ♪
♪ Carelessly ♪
♪ I see the way
that you been look at me ♪
♪ I wore my ?? intentionally ♪
♪ I wanna... ♪
♪ I wanna ride
on my audio flight ♪
♪ If you're flippin'
and you're spittin' ♪
♪ You're not gettin' is right ♪
♪ Eat pizza ♪
♪ About time
we be throwin' around ♪
♪ Aren't you living ?? ♪
TRIS... HEY!
WHOA! OOF!
TRISTAN:
STILL STRUGGLING
IN THOSE HEELS?
BEING FOUR INCHES
OFF THE GROUND IS TRICKY.
WELL, THEN WHY NOT
SWITCH TO SNEAKS?
BECAUSE I HAVE
A NEW MISSION.
OPERATION MEET CUTE BOYS.
OOH! I'M IN!
REALLY?
WHAT ABOUT FAB?
AGH!
HE CALLED FASHION WEEK
"SHALLOW."
THAT'S THE POINT,
GRANOLA CRUNCHER.
SO WHAT'S THE PLAN?
I WAS HOPING YOU'D COME UP
WITH THAT.
WHERE DO WE MEET
CUTE BOYS?
THE MALL?
AGH...
WE'RE IN GRADE NINE!
IT'S NOT LIKE
WE CAN GO CLUBBING.
MAYA:
OY.
BOY:
HERE YOU GO, MAN.
DREW TORRES CAMPAIGN PARTY
AT HIS HOUSE.
ADDRESS IS ON THE BACK.
WE JUST GOT INVITED
TO A SENIOR PARTY!
CUTE BOYS HANG OUT
AT SENIOR PARTIES!
YES, BUT...
WHY THE BOY CRAZY
ALL OF A SUDDEN?
WHY NOT?
I MEAN, I'M YOUNG,
I'VE GOT THESE BOOTS,
AND I DON'T HAVE A BOYFRIEND
ANYMORE, DO I?
UH, NO,
I GUESS YOU DON'T.
THEN LET'S TEAR IT UP!
(ZOMBIE MOANS AND GROANS)
HOW COME HE GETS
THE SWORD?
I GAVE YOU A GUN.
YEAH, BUT THE HERO
ALWAYS GETS A SWORD.
MEN, I JUST BROUGHT YOU HERE
FOR THE EDITING.
CONNOR: HELLO, DAVE.
DAVE: WHOA! AGH!
CONNOR, HOW MANY TIMES
I GOTTA TELL YOU
YOU CAN'T JUST SNEAK UP
ON PEOPLE LIKE THAT!
CAN WE TALK?
DAVE:
YEAH. BE RIGHT BACK.
YEAH,
WHAT IS IT?
I NEED YOU TO DATE
ALLI AGAIN.
WHAT?!
SHE'S SAD AND LONELY
AND HOGGING JENNA.
NO, MAN.
DUDE, LOOK...
WE'VE GROWN APART
FROM EACH OTHER.
WE'RE TWO DIFFERENT
PEOPLE NOW.
SO IT'LL BE LIKE DATING
A COMPLETELY BRAND NEW PERSON.
NO, NO. MAN, LOOK,
WE GOT NO COMMON INTERESTS.
NEITHER DO JENNA AND I,
BUT WE MAKE IT WORK.
I THINK IT'S JUST BETTER
IF WE JUST LEAVE IT
AS A CLEAN BREAK,
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYIN'?
I DON'T WANNA BE LIKE
ELI AND CLARE.
BREAK UP,
GET BACK TOGETHER AGAIN,
THEN BREAKING UP AGAIN.
I MEAN LOOK AT HIM.
HE'S A MESS.
(SIGHS)
ALL BURIED IN HIS MOVIE
BECAUSE HE'S SAD
AND LONELY.
I COULD SET ELI UP
WITH ALLI.
YEAH.
YEAH, THEN MAYBE FIRE
AND GASOLINE CAN HANG OUT.
ELI:
DAVE, I'M RETHINKING THE SWORD.
MRS. MATLIN:
WHOA! NICE BUM,
WHERE YA FROM?
WHAT?
YOU CAN'T SEE ANYTHING.
TRUST ME,
THERE'S CHEEK.
WHAT'S HAPPENING HERE?
WELL, ME AND TRISTAN
GOT INVITED TO UM...
A SENIOR PARTY.
A WHAT?
NO.
FINE. I'LL CHANGE!
IT'S NOT ABOUT
THE OUTFIT.
IT'S NOT ONLY ABOUT
MOM, I JUST WANNA
HAVE SOME FUN.
I KNOW YOU DO.
DOES THAT MEAN YOU'LL LET ME
GO TO THE PARTY?
IT MEANS YOU CAN
PRACTICE CELLO.
THE NATIONAL
YOUNG MUSICIANS ORCHESTRA
RESCHEDULED YOUR AUDITION.
THAT'S STILL SOMETHING
YOU WANT, RIGHT?
FINE. PRACTICE.
TRISTAN: HELLO.
MAYA: YEAH, HEY TRIS,
UM, I CAN'T GO
TO THE PARTY.
TRISTAN:
WHAT? I THOUGHT-
SEE YOU AT SCHOOL TOMORROW!
TRISTAN:
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE BAILING!
YOU SERIOUSLY
CAN'T GO TO THE PARTY?!
OF COURSE, WE'RE TOTALLY
GOING TO THE PARTY!
MEET ME AT THE CORNER
IN THIRTY.
(MUSIC PLAYS,
PARTY CHATTER)
DREW:
OKAY, SO YOU'RE GONNA VOTE
FOR DREW, RIGHT?
WELL, I GUESS NOW
YOU HAVE NO CHOICE.
WE'RE TALKING TO EACH OTHER
SO GIVE HER A LEI.
DUDE! HELLO!
(SNAPS FINGERS)
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
YOU'RE THE LEI MAN,
COME ON.
HERE WE GO.
(PARTY CHATTER,
LOUD MUSIC)
OKAY, WE'RE HERE.
NOW WHAT?
NO THANKS.
OH, I SEE DAVE.
I HAVE TO SAY HI.
WAIT! DON'T LEAVE ME!
YOU'LL NEED ONE OF THESE.
THANKS.
I'M MAYA BY THE WAY.
HARRY, RIGHT?
ALL DAY AND EVERYWHERE.
TALIA:
YOU DID NOT JUST USE
THAT LINE AGAIN.
MAYA LAUGHED.
YEAH.
MOST GIRLS DON'T.
MAYA:
I GUESS I'M NOT MOST GIRLS.
GOOD TO KNOW.
(BOTTLES CLINK)
(PHONE CHIMES)
HEY, CAN I TAKE A PIC?
YEAH.
YEAH, NO PROBLEM.
MAYA:
OKAY. COOL.
EVERYBODY SAY "WHA!"
ALL:
WHA!
YEAH. THANKS.
TRISTAN:
OOH! FANCY!
YEAH! VOTE DREW!
THERE'S POPCORN AND CHIPS
OVER THERE.
BEVERAGES IN THE MINI-FRIDGE.
AND IF ANYONE WANTS TO TAKE
A DIP IN THE KIDDIE POOL,
CLOTHING IS OPTIONAL.
DAVE:
I THOUGHT THIS WAS SUPPOSED TO
BE AN ELECTION PARTY FOR SCHOOL.
DREW:
OH NO, IT IS!
BUT IF YOU VOTE FOR ME,
THIS IS WHAT SCHOOL
WILL LOOK LIKE
ALL NEXT YEAR!
DALLAS:
ONE NON-STOP PARTY!
VOTE DREW!
BIANCA:
YOU THINK THIS IS WORKING?
YEAH. PEOPLE ARE HAVING
A BLAST.
ELECTION CAMPAIGN IS NOTHING
BUT A POPULARITY CONTEST.
EVERYONE KNOWS THAT.
NOT EVERYBODY.
CONNOR:
THAT PLATE OF NACHOS
CONTAINS 300%
OF YOUR DAILY SODIUM
REQUIREMENT.
JENNA:
GUESS YOU DON'T WANT ANY THEN.
I DEFINITELY
DID NOT SAY THAT.
THIS IS FUN,
JUST THE TWO OF US.
ALLI:
SORRY TO INTERRUPT
YOUR DATE.
JENNA:
AWWW! SOMEONE SENT YOU ROSES?
WAS IT DALLAS?
NO, THEY'RE NOT FROM DALLAS!
THEY'RE FROM ELI.
JENNA:
WHAT?!
"WILL YOU BE MY GIRLFRIEND?
XOXO, ELI."
ALLI:
HE'S PLAYING SOME SICK GAME
TO TRY TO GET TO CLARE
THROUGH ME.
WHEN I SEE HIM,
HE'S DEAD.
CONNOR:
ELI'S NOT SO BAD.
HE'S-HE'S SENSITIVE
AND ARTISTIC.
THOSE ARE BOTH REALLY
ATTRACTIVE QUALITIES.
I THINK HE WOULD MAKE
AN EXCELLENT BOYFRIEND.
ALLI:
OH MY GOD.
JENNA:
IT'S ELI.
ELI:
I DROPPED BY YOUR HOUSE
AND YOUR PARENTS SAID
I WOULD FIND YOU HERE.
ARE YOU LIKE STALKING ME
OR SOMETHING?
NO, I WANT YOU
TO EXPLAIN THIS.
"WILL YOU BE MY BOYFRIEND?
XOXO, ALLI."
ALLI:
I DID NOT SEND THOSE TO YOU.
CONNOR,
DID YOU DO THIS?
YES.
WHY?
BECAUSE YOU AND ELI ARE BOTH
SAD AND LONELY.
YOU GUYS ARE A PERFECT MATCH!
OKAY. I HAVE TO GET BACK
TO MY MOVIE.
I'M ON A DEADLINE.
LADIES...
WOMAN:
OW! THAT'S SO NICE.
CONNOR,
YOU'RE A JERK.
BECAUSE I WANT YOUR FRIEND
TO BE HAPPY?
BECAUSE YOU WANT MY FRIEND
TO STOP HANGING OUT WITH US!
GO HOME.
BUT WE WERE TOGETHER,
WE WERE HAVING FUN...
WH-WHY DO YOU WANT ME
TO LEAVE?
BECAUSE I'M NOT HAVING FUN
ANYMORE.
♪ Woo-ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Your love is a poison ♪
♪ Romeo just wants a bite ♪
WOO!
OH. HEY.
WHAT'S UP WITH MAYA?
SHE'S FINE.
GOSH, STOP INTERROGATING ME!
SHE'S HAD A FEW COOLERS.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
MAYA:
YO, YO, YO, ZIGMUND!
MEET MY NEW BESTIES:
HARRY AND TALIA!
ZIG:
MAYA. MAYA, LET'S GO.
OKAY?
YOU JUST GOT HERE, YO!
YEAH. BECAUSE YOU SENT ME
A WEIRD TEXT.
MAYA, THIS ISN'T YOU.
NO. IT'S THE NEW ME,
AND I'M SO MUCH BETTER!
OKAY. COME ON,
I'M GONNA WALK YOU HOME, OKAY?
WHY? SO YOU CAN
REJECT ME AGAIN?
YOU KNOW,
IF YOU HAD JUST SAID YES,
YOU WOULD'VE BEEN MY BOYFRIEND
RIGHT NOW.
BUT YOU REALLY,
REALLY BLEW IT!
YOU'RE A MEAN DRUNK.
BYE, BYE.
TRISTAN:
I'LL GET HER HOME,
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
MAYA:
ANYBODY WANNA HAVE ANY FUN?
HARRY:
I DO.
ALL:
WOOOO-HOOOO!
(LOUD DANCE MUSIC PLAYS)
WOO!
CLARE:
SO FIRST, I'VE LISTED ALL
MY EXTRACURRICULARS,
SO YOU CAN SEE THAT I'M VERY
QUALIFIED TO BE PRESIDENT.
(CLEARS THROAT)
VOTE CLARE!
YOU'RE CAMPAIGNING
AT MY HOUSE.
STUDENT COUNCIL
ELECTION RULES STATE
THAT NOMINEES HAVE TO HAVE
EQUAL ACCESS TO VOTERS.
DO I HAVE TO TELL SIMPSON
THAT YOU HAD A PARTY
AND EXCLUDED ME?
FINE. WHATEVER.
NO ONE IS GOING TO VOTE
FOR YOU
BECAUSE YOU BRIBED THEM
WITH SNACKS AND TIKI TORCHES.
THIS IS AN IMPORTANT JOB
AND YOU'RE NOT SMART ENOUGH
TO DO IT.
WELL, AT LEAST
I'M NOT BORING!
NO ONE WANTS A PRESIDENT
WHO'S ONLY RUNNING
TO AMUSE THEMSELVES.
WELL, THAT'S BETTER THAN
SOMEONE WHO'S ONLY RUNNING
BECAUSE THEY GOT DUMPED!
OOH! SO BAD!
BITTER GIRL
OR AWESOME GUY?
I THINK THE CHOICE
IS PRETTY CLEAR, PEOPLE.
VOTE DREW!
CLARE:
VOTE THIS!
(GASPS)
WHAT IS UP WITH SENIORS?
THEY ARE SO WEIRD!
MAYA:
WHOSE BED! WOO!
WHAT KIND OF PARTY IS THIS,
ANYWAYS?
TALIA:
A LOSER PARTY,
I THINK.
HARRY:
IS THAT WHY YOU CAME?
TALIA:
I CAME BECAUSE YOU MADE ME.
WHOA!
SETTLE DOWN, BOUNCY.
(LAUGHING)
MAYA:
SO ARE YOU GUYS BOYFRIEND
AND GIRLFRIEND?
HARRY:
TALIA AND I ARE
JUST GOOD FRIENDS.
TALIA:
I PREFER ALLIES
IN A CONTRADICTORY WORLD.
MAYA:
WELL, I'M SO GLAD
I MET YOU GUYS.
YOU JUST WANT TO HAVE FUN
AND YOU DON'T LOOK AT ME
WITH A "WORRY FACE"
ALL THE FREAKING TIME.
WHY ARE PEOPLE WORRIED?
MAYA:
YOU DON'T KNOW?
HARRY:
NO.
(SIGHS)
WHOA.
OH, SUICIDE DUDE.
YOU KNEW HIM?
MAYA:
YEAH.
EVERYONE THINKS I'M MESSED UP,
BUT I'M NOT.
SOMETIMES I JUST
WANNA SCREAM.
THEN SCREAM.
HARRY:
YOU CAN'T LET PEOPLE
TELL YOU WHAT TO BE,
JA FEEL?
(GIGGLES)
OKAY. LOOK,
LOOK, I'M SORRY THAT
I'M NOT CRYING ALL THE TIME,
BUT I NEVER CHOSE TO BE
THE GIRLFRIEND OF THE DEAD GUY.
OR I WOULD NEVER CHOOSE THAT.
EVER.
SO COULD WE ALL
JUST GET OVER IT?
JA FEEL?!
(LAUGHING)
TALIA:
HARRISONIAN,
WHY DO WE KEEP COMING TO THESE
STUPID HIGH SCHOOL PARTIES?
YOU KNOW, IF WE WERE TEENAGERS
IN ISRAEL RIGHT NOW,
WE'D BE TRAINING FOR THE ARMY
OR SOMETHING.
NOT GETTING DRUNK AT A DUMB
STUDENT ELECTION PARTY.
I MEAN,
LOOK AT ALL THIS STUFF...
IS THIS OKAY?
UM...
I DON'T REALLY KNOW YOU.
ISN'T THAT KIND OF
THE POINT?
(TALIA CONTINUES TO TALK)
DON'T MIND ME!
♪ Stranger days... ♪
DREW:
I CAN'T BELIEVE CLARE
CRASHED MY PARTY
AND DROP-KICKED ME
INTO MY OWN KIDDIE POOL.
BIANCA:
YEAH. SHE MADE YOU
LOOK LIKE A GOOF.
DREW:
WELL, ISN'T THAT WHAT I AM?
I'M NOT GONNA GRADUATE
'TIL I'M FORTY,
I CAN'T PLAY SPORTS,
AND I'M NOT GOOD
AT ANYTHING ELSE!
I MEAN THAT'S WHY SOMEONE
NOMINATED ME, RIGHT?
BECAUSE THE IDEA OF DREW TORRES
BEING PRESIDENT
IS HILARIOUS!
BIANCA:
OH MY GOD!
WAKE UP, DREW!
YOU MADE YOURSELF A JOKE.
IF YOU ACTUALLY TOOK THIS
ELECTION SERIOUSLY,
YOU COULD WIN!
YOU DON'T BELIEVE THAT.
BIANCA:
YES, I DO;
THAT'S WHY I NOMINATED YOU.
DREW:
YOU DID?
BECAUSE I THOUGHT
YOU'D BE GOOD AT IT,
AND I DON'T WANT YOU TO BE SAD
WHEN I'M AWAY NEXT YEAR.
I DON'T WANT TO BE
SAD EITHER.
SO BE BUSY AND HAPPY.
BE PRESIDENT.
YOU REALLY THINK
I CAN DO IT?
I KNOW YOU CAN.
LOOKS LIKE WE HAVE
A LOT OF WORK TO DO.
(DOOR CREAKS OPEN)
(THUMP,
OBJECT CLINKS)
OH. (LAUGHING)
(MUSIC PLAYS,
LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
(PHONE CHIMES)
(ANGRY SIGH)
♪ Your love is a poison ♪
♪ Your love,
your love ♪