LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
WE ARE GATHERED HERE TODAY
TO JOIN IN HOLY MATRIMONY,
DREW TORRES
AND BIANCA DESOUSA.
(SNORTED LAUGHTER)
PROMISE ME YOU GOOFS
WON'T HAVE A GIGGLE FIT
AT YOUR REAL WEDDING.
(LAUGHING)
BIANCA:
WE'RE GOOD.
FIONA:
OKAY, THEN CAN WE GET ALONG
WITH THIS REHEARSAL, PLEASE?
IF ANYONE HERE SHOULD OBJECT
TO THIS UNION,
LET THEM SPEAK NOW
OR FOREVER HOLD THEIR PEACE.
IMOGEN:
MEGA POTATO! MEGA POTATO!
ADAM:
GOT IT! HI-YAH!
OKAY, NO OBJECTIONS
SEEING AS MY MOM'S NOT HERE.
AND WON'T BE IN VEGAS,
EITHER.
FIONA:
RIGHT. AND NEXT UP, YOUR VOWS.
YOU'RE WRITING YOUR OWN?
WRITTEN!
UM... WORKING ON IT.
FIONA:
AND THEN YOU EXCHANGE
THE RINGS
AND KISS THE BRIDE!
NOW THAT I CAN HANDLE!
MAMA MIA!
FIONA:
OKAY! GOOD! STOP!
NOW, LET'S ALL GET READY
FOR LAS VEGAS!
YOU READY?
YUP. I JUST GOTTA GO HOME
AND GET MY SUIT.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
WHAT IS IT?
WELL, WE WON SEVEN
PLANE TICKETS TO VEGAS.
WE ONLY FILLED
FIVE SEATS.
IF WE TELL YOUR FOLKS
ABOUT THE WEDDING,
THEY'RE GONNA TRY
TO STOP IT, DREW.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
STUPID IDEA.
IT'S YOU AND ME
AGAINST THE WORLD, OKAY?
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT,
AND IN TWO DAYS,
WE'LL BE HITCHED.
NOTHING CAN STOP US!
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
(Ooh-ooh-ooh)
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
KATIE:
CAN YOU BELIEVE
THAT IN FIVE HOURS
WE'RE GONNA BE SWIMMING
IN THE OCEAN?!
YOU THINK YOU'LL BE
PACKED BY THEN?
WHAT, YOU'D RATHER
I BRING NO CLOTHES
TO PUERTO VALLARTA?
(LAUGHING)
MAYA:
EW! GROSS.
CAN'T YOU GUYS JUST WAIT
TILL YOU "GET A ROOM"?
AWWWW! YOU GUYS WANT
THE HOUSE TO YOURSELVES
SO YOU CAN HOLD HANDS?
CAM:
I'M ACTUALLY ON THE WAY
TO THE TRAIN STATION,
BACK TO KAPUSKASING.
BOYFRIEND GONE, SISTER GONE,
BAND SCATTERED,
AND NO OTHER FRIENDS
TO SPEAK OF...
WE'LL BE BACK
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
OH... SINCE YOU'RE BEING,
YOU KNOW, NICE FOR ONCE,
YOU DIDN'T APPLY,
DID YOU?
APPLY WHERE?
KATIE:
UH...
WELL, YOU KNOW,
WHEN I LOST SOCCER,
AND REHAB,
I DON'T KNOW,
I TOOK A RISK.
THERE'S NO WAY I...
I GOT IN.
OH MY GOD!
I GOT IN!!
(SQUEALING EXCITEDLY)
WHERE?
WHY ARE WE JUMPING?
MAYA:
STANFORD!
WHERE I ALWAYS WANTED
TO GO FOR SOCCER!
IT'S...
IT'S MY DREAM SCHOOL!
SO YOU'RE OFF TO BE
SOME SMARTY-PANTS
IN CALIFORNIA
NEXT YEAR!
AND WE CAN CELEBRATE
ALL WEEK IN MEXICO,
AFTER I TELL MY PARENTS
THE GOOD NEWS!
YEAH!
JUST THINK.
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT,
YOU'LL BE MR. BIANCA DESOUSA.
YOU'RE HILARIOUS.
NO, HILARIOUS WOULD BE
MOM FINDING OUT.
WELL, SHE CAN'T.
SHE'D STOP THE WEDDING.
SHE THINKS B'S
TRAILER TRASH.
I THINK THAT'S A BIT
OF AN EXAGGERATION.
UH, DO WE HAVE EVERYTHING
TO MAKE IT LOOK LIKE
WE'RE GOING CAMPING?
UH, TENTS, SLEEPING BAGS,
TARPS...
CRAP!
I FORGOT THE IPAD.
ADAM! HURRY UP, MAN!
SHE'LL BE HOME ANY SECOND!
I KNOW. I NEED TO SKYPE
BECKY WITH IT!
'KAY, GOT IT!
LET'S GO.
AUDRA:
ADAM, YOU STILL HERE?
SORRY.
ADAM?
OH! DREW!
LONG TIME, NO SEE.
MOM.
ACTUALLY, I'M GLAD
YOU GUYS ARE HERE.
I GOT YOU
A LITTLE SOMETHING.
A CAMP STOVE.
THANKS,
BUT I CAN START A FIRE.
WELL, WHAT IF IT RAINS?
WELL, THEN I'LL FIGURE IT OUT.
TRUST ME.
TRUST YOU?
WELL, THIS YEAR,
YOU'VE DROPPED OUT OF SCHOOL,
GOT ENGAGED...
WHO KNOWS WHAT CRAZY THING
YOU'LL DO NEXT?
(AWKWARD SILENCE)
MRS. MATLIN:
STANFORD?!
WE ARE SO PROUD OF YOU,
HONEY.
SO PROUD.
BUT...?
NO MATTER HOW WE RUN
THE NUMBERS,
EVEN WITH FINANCIAL AID,
A UNIVERSITY LIKE THIS
IS GONNA COST $20,000 A YEAR.
EIGHTY FOR FOUR.
OKAY, WELL,
WHAT IF I GOT A JOB?
I COULD FLIP BURGERS
OR...
A CRAPLOAD OF BURGERS.
MRS. MATLIN:
WITH OUR MORTGAGE
AND MY MEDICAL BILLS...
I KNOW.
IT WAS A PIPE-DREAM ANYWAY.
I'M SO SORRY,
SWEETIE-PIE.
THERE'S NO WAY
WE CAN AFFORD THIS.
IT'S OKAY, MOM.
I'LL JUST GO TO MEXICO
AND FORGET I EVEN APPLIED.
YOU HAVE A GOOD TIME
ON YOUR TRIP, OKAY?
THANKS. SEE YOU.
LOOK AFTER HER,
JAKE!
I WILL.
HEY. HEY...
SHE SAID THEY SAVED LIKE WHAT,
FIVE THOUSAND DOLLARS
FOR YOU TO STAY HOME
AND GO TO T.U.?
I MEAN, UNIVERSITY'S
UNIVERSITY, RIGHT?
YEAH. YOU KNOW,
LET'S JUST DROP IT.
I DON'T WANT THESE STUPID
MONEY PROBLEMS
TO RUIN OUR SPRING BREAK.
YEAH. OKAY.
DREW'S TWENTY MINUTES LATE!
WHAT IF HE RAN INTO AUDRA
AND SHE'S TALKING HIM
OUT OF IT?
I'M PINNING YOU.
STAY CALM.
OH MY GOODNESS.
WHAT?
WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU MAKE SUCH
A BEAUTIFUL BRIDE!
THANK YOU, BUT...
I WON'T BE CALM
UNTIL WE'RE ON THAT PLANE,
AWAY FROM ALL THE AUDRAS
AND KATIES,
AND ALL OF THE HATERS
WHO'VE EVER TRIED
TO COME BETWEEN US.
RELAX.
I TOLD EVERYONE THE FLIGHT WAS
20 MINUTES EARLIER THAN IT IS.
WE'LL MAKE IT,
WITH TIME TO SPARE.
I AM SO GLAD WE MADE YOU
OUR WEDDING PLANNER.
YOU'RE LIKE A
"BORING DETAILS" GENIUS.
(LAUGHING)
(PLANE ENGINES ROAR)
KATIE:
NO, NO, NO!
HOW CAN OUR FLIGHT
BE CANCELED?
(GROANS)
MO:
HURRICANE STEPHANIE
HIT THE GULF.
NO FLIGHTS IN OR OUT
OF MEXICO.
WELL, NOW WHAT?
A STAY-CATION?
DOES ANYBODY HAVE
INLINE SKATES?
KATIE:
NO, NO. WE'RE DEFINITELY
GOING SOMEWHERE, OKAY?
WE JUST HAVE TO SWITCH
OUR FLIGHTS AND HOTELS.
THEN WE JUST HAVE TO PICK
SOMEWHERE TO GO.
MARISOL:
SO... PARIS?
THAT'S A FEW MORE PESOS
THAN PUERTA VALLARTA.
VANCOUVER?
WE CAN SEE THOSE TREES
THAT ARE BIG ENOUGH
TO DRIVE CARS THROUGH!
AND SPEND SPRING BREAK
IN THE RAIN?
KATIE:
OKAY, POINT MARISOL.
UH...
WHAT ABOUT VEGAS?
JAKE:
REALLY? WE'RE UNDERAGE,
WE CAN'T DO MUCH THERE.
KATIE:
NO, NO, NO.
THERE'S LIKE PAINTBALLING
AND ROLLER COASTERS.
IT'S PRACTICALLY LIKE
A GIANT AMUSEMENT PARK THERE.
PLUS THERE'S POOLS, AND SPAS,
AND SHOPPING.
MMM...
KATIE:
PLUS I MIGHT BE ABLE TO WIN
MY TUITION AT BLACKJACK.
SAY WHAT?
KATIE:
OKAY, GUYS,
REMEMBER WHEN I LIKE RULED
THE BLACKJACK TABLE
AT DEGRASSI'S VEGAS NIGHT?
YEAH, YOU HAD CRAZY LUCK
THAT NIGHT.
KATIE:
NO, BUT IT WASN'T CRAZY LUCK.
MY GRANDFATHER LIVED
IN RENO
AND HE WON A SMALL FORTUNE
COUNTING CARDS,
AND HE TAUGHT ME.
ISN'T THAT ILLEGAL?
TECHNICALLY NO,
AND PLUS I HAVE LIKE FIVE HOURS
ON THE PLANE TO PRACTICE.
COME ON, GUYS,
I GOT INTO THE SCHOOL
OF MY DREAMS
AND I CAN'T AFFORD IT.
OKAY, I KNOW...
I KNOW IT SOUNDS CRAZY,
BUT I AT LEAST HAVE TO TRY,
RIGHT?
PLEASE, PLEASE,
PLEASE, PLEASE!
YAY!
♪♪♪
ADAM:
"YOU ARE THE LIGHT OF MY LIFE."
ISN'T THAT A BIT CLICHE?
IMOGEN:
SO I READ BIANCA'S VOWS.
SHE'S BASICALLY
LIKE SHAKESPEARE,
EXCEPT SHE'S FEMALE,
AND SHE'S LESS DEAD.
ADAM:
REMEMBER THAT ONE YEAR
THAT UNCLE TONY HAD
HIS GROOMSMEN SING HIS VOWS,
FOUR-PART HARMONY?
OH! THAT'S SO ROMANTIC.
MAYBE YOU COULD DO THAT.
YEAH, EXCEPT I HAVE
ONE GROOMSMAN,
AND, WELL,
HE CAN'T HOLD A NOTE.
FIONA AND IMOGEN:
(LAUGHING) OH!
ADAM:
HEY, WATCH IT!
TALK LIKE THAT
AND YOU WON'T HAVE ANY.
DREW:
(SIGHS) ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
CAN WE JUST STOP TALKING
SO I CAN WORK ON MY VOWS?
SORRY. I GUESS I'M JUST USED
TO BIG TORRES WEDDINGS
UP AT THE COTTAGE,
THE COUSINS RUNNING AROUND...
YEAH, WELL, UM...
THIS IS GONNA BE A DIFFERENT
TYPE OF WEDDING, ADAM.
BUT IT'LL BE GREAT
AS LONG AS BIANCA'S HAPPY.
MARISOL AND MO:
(BICKERING LOUDLY)
MARISOL:
I'M NOT TRADING MY HAT WITH YOU
FOR THIS SEAT!
MO:
OH, COME ON, TAKE IT OFF!
IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
OH DEAR GOD, NO!
IMOGEN:
WHAT A CRAZY COINCIDENCE!
OKAY,
IF MARISOL'S HERE,
THAT MEANS KATIE CANNOT BE
FAR BEHIND.
BIANCA CANNOT SEE HER.
ANNOUNCEMENT:
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
WELCOME ABOARD YOUR FLIGHT
FROM TORONTO TO LAS VEGAS.
PLEASE ENSURE YOUR LUGGAGE
IS SECURELY STOWED...
HOW ARE YOU
ON THIS PLANE?!
PLEASE, PLEASE TELL ME
KATIE IS NOT HERE.
WAIT...
WAIT, WHERE IS SHE NOW?
THE WASHROOM.
OH GOD... OH NO.
(LAUGHS)
NO. FREAKING. WAY!
DREW:
OH... NO.
OH, KATIE, WHAT ARE THE ODDS
YOU'RE ON THE SAME FLIGHT
WE'RE TAKING TO OUR WEDDING?
YOUR WEDDING?
WAIT, YOU'RE SERIOUS?!
DREW:
(BABBLING) I MEAN, YOU KNOW,
THIS DOESN'T HAVE TO BE WEIRD.
YEAH, SURE...
THREE MONTHS AGO,
WE DATED,
BUT A FEW MONTHS AGO
JAKE WAS WITH CLARE,
AND NOW THEY'RE KINDA RELATED
SO YOU AND...
YOU AND JAKE KINDA,
YOU KNOW, YOU GUYS DATE.
OKAY, WHAT I'M TRYING
TO SAY HERE,
YOU KNOW, IS THAT WE'RE
ALL FRIENDS, RIGHT?
AND WE'RE ALL GOING
TO VEGAS.
THIS SHOULD BE AWESOME.
YOU...
YOU GUYS SHOULD COME
TO THE WEDDING!
SERIOUSLY?!
DREW:
J-JAKE - JAKE AND MO -
YOU GUYS SHOULD COME
TO MY BACHELOR PARTY TONIGHT.
MO: OH, FUN!
DREW: YEAH!
AND UH, KATIE,
MAYBE YOU AND MARISOL COULD GO
TO BIANCA'S BACHELORETTE PARTY.
NO? NO? OR NOT.
OH...
I MEAN,
WE SHOULD ALL JUST... CHILL.
YUP.
(HORRIFIED SIGH)
OH GOD...
(CLEARS THROAT)
ARE YOU SURE
YOU DON'T WANT THE UH...
THE WINDOW SEAT
OR A BLANKET OR SOMETHING?
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
I WAS TRYING TO MAKE THINGS
LESS WEIRD.
BY INVITING YOUR EX
TO OUR WEDDING?
ADAM...
ADAM SAID STUFF ABOUT
A BIG TORRES WEDDING.
I THOUGHT A FEW MORE PEOPLE
WOULDN'T HURT.
BIANCA:
OKAY, SO...
YOU WANT A BIG WEDDING,
OR YOU DIDN'T WANT IT
TO BE WEIRD?
I DON'T KNOW, OKAY?
I PANICKED.
I DID IT FOR YOU.
YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU CAN DO FOR ME?
LEAVE ME ALONE
FOR THE NEXT FIVE HOURS
SO I CAN GET MY BEAUTY REST.
OH! AND DON'T GO INVITING
ANY OF YOUR EXES
TO COME SPOON ME, OKAY?
(WHISPERS)
THANK YOU!
THIS IS GONNA BE
A BUMPY RIDE.
(ENGINE ROARS
AS PLANE TAKES OFF)
♪ Turn it up ♪
♪ Let it play ♪
(Play!)
♪ I wanna hear that sound
'til my window breaks, yeah ♪
♪ Turn it up ♪
(Turn it up!)
♪ Let it play ♪
(ROLLER COASTER WHOOSHES,
RIDERS SCREAM)
♪ ...'til my windows break,
yeah ♪
♪ Let me hear you say,
"turn it up!" ♪
♪ Turn it up! ♪
ADAM:
THERE WERE SLOT MACHINES
IN THE AIRPORT!
I'VE SEEN SEVEN HUMMER LIMOS
SINCE I GOT HERE,
AND SHOWGIRLS JUST WALK AROUND
LIKE IT'S NOTHING!
LET'S GET THIS BACHELOR PARTY
STARTED!
UH... I THINK
I NEED A SECOND.
RIGHT. WHILE YOU DO THAT,
I'M GONNA SKYPE BECKY,
LET HER KNOW
WE GOT HERE SAFELY.
SOUNDS LIKE A PLAN.
YOU CAN'T STAY MAD FOREVER.
SOUNDS LIKE A CHALLENGE.
LOOK, COME ON,
I KNOW I MESSED UP,
BUT AT LEAST WE'LL HAVE
A FEW MORE PEOPLE
AT OUR WEDDING.
WHAT HAPPENED TO
"YOU AND ME AGAINST THE WORLD,
YOU'RE ALL I NEED"?
OKAY, BUT ISN'T IT
A LITTLE BIT WEIRD
WE'RE HAVING
SUCH A SMALL WEDDING?
SO MO, JAKE, MARISOL,
AND FREAKING KATIE
ARE YOUR IDEAL GUESTS?
DREW:
NO. NO!
BUT AT LEAST THEY'LL COME.
COME ON, THEY WANNA SUPPORT US.
THAT'S SOMETHING, ISN'T IT?
HI.
MADONNA DRAG QUEEN:
♪ LA-DA-DA...
ONLY FOOLS RUSH IN ♪
CURLY-HAIRED DRAG QUEEN:
♪ 'CAUSE I CAN'T HELP
LA-DA-DA-DA DA-DA ♪
THEY ARE SINGING
OUR SONG.
THAT MEANS YOU HAVE
TO FORGIVE ME.
FINE.
I FORGIVE YOU.
AS LONG AS YOU AND I
ARE AT THE ALTAR,
I GUESS IT DOESN'T REALLY MATTER
WHO ELSE IS THERE.
MADONNA DRAG QUEEN:
A WEDDING?
CAN WE COME TOO?
SURE! WHY NOT?
CURLY-HAIRED DRAG QUEEN:
OH GOODY! I LOVE ME A WEDDING.
SO YOU'RE NOT MAD ANYMORE?
NO.
GOOD.
DRAG QUEEN:
♪ AND I CAN'T HELP... ♪
DREW:
THANKS.
WHY DON'T WE TAKE
OUR HONEYMOON SUITE
FOR A LITTLE TEST-DRIVE?
ADAM'S WAITING TO TAKE YOU
TO YOUR BACHELOR PARTY.
FIONA:
AND WE'RE WAITING
TO TAKE BIANCA
TO HER BACHELORETTE PARTY!
OH! AND PHONE,
PLEASE!
YOU AND YOUR FIANCE
ARE INCOMMUNICADO
UNTIL THE WEDDING TOMORROW.
THANK YOU.
YOU'LL TAKE THE BAGS
UP TO THE ROOM?
YES, MA'AM.
HAVE FUN TONIGHT,
BUT NOT TOO MUCH FUN!
BIANCA: I LOVE YOU.
DREW: I LOVE YOU, TOO!
FIONA:
BYE, BOYS!
SEE YA!
KATIE:
MINUS ONE, PLUS ONE,
PLUS ONE...
PLUS SEVEN?
NAILED IT.
YES!
MO:
JACKPOT!
TINY SOAPS, BODY SCRUBS...
IT'S GONNA BE SICK.
MARISOL:
OH, THE SMALLEST THINGS
AMUSE YOU.
MO:
WHATEVER, LADY.
NO ONE LIKES
MY SILKY SMOOTH SKIN
MORE THAN YOU.
HEY, ARE YOU WEARING ANYTHING
UNDER THAT?
BAM!
(LAUGHING)
LIKE I'M GONNA LET YOU
SEE THE SHOW FOR FREE!
LET'S GO GET THOSE
BUFFET BRACELETS
BEFORE WE HEAD OUT!
HEY. THE ONLY REAL WAY
TO BEAT THE HOUSE:
PAY TWENTY-FIVE BUCKS
FOR A MEAL,
EAT FIFTY BUCKS OF FOOD.
JAKE, I CAN DO THIS, OKAY?
I KNOW IT.
OKAY. JUST BET CAUTIOUSLY,
OKAY?
'KAY.
BYE.
MARISOL:
SO... TELL ME AGAIN HOW YOU
PLAN ON WINNING TWENTY GRAND
OFF OF TWO HUNDRED DOLLARS
IN TRAVELERS CHEQUES?
UH, I'M GONNA USE
MY SAVINGS.
YOUR UNIVERSITY MONEY?
WELL, WHAT IF YOU LOSE?
I MEAN, COUNTING CARDS?
YOU'RE NO SHELDON COOPER!
NO. IT'S EASY.
YOU JUST KEEP A SINGLE NUMBER
IN YOUR HEAD
AND THEN YOU SUBTRACT ONE
FOR EVERY FACE CARD
OR TEN YOU SEE,
AND THEN ADD ONE
FOR EVERY NON-FACE CARD,
AND THEN BET BIG
WHEN THAT NUMBER'S HIGH.
BECAUSE YOU'RE MORE LIKELY
TO GET A TEN OR A FACE CARD?
EXACTLY! SEE?
EVEN YOU GET IT!
OKAY,
BUT WHAT ABOUT THIS?
YOU HAVE TO BE TWENTY-ONE
TO GAMBLE!
NOT IF YOU HAVE
A FAKE ID.
WHERE DID YOU GET THAT?
KATIE:
UM, WHEN BIANCA AND I WENT
TO THE CLUB.
OH, YOU MEAN BEFORE YOU TWO
WERE ARCH-ENEMIES?
YEAH.
ARE YOU READY TO LOOK OLDER,
OR WHAT?
MARISOL:
MMM...
♪ We still need
each other now ♪
♪ So help me out ♪
♪ If you wanted out,
just let it go ♪
♪ Once you buy out
you may not ever know ♪
♪ If you wanted out today
just let it go ♪
♪ Once you buy out,
you may not ever know ♪
PIT BOSS:
NOT SO FAST.
ID.
UH, YEAH.
(CLEARS THROAT NERVOUSLY)
MARIA ALVAREZ.
YOU'RE A GEMINI?
UH, TAURUS.
MAY 20TH IS ON THE CUSP.
HMM.
WHAT'S YOUR, UH, -
WHAT DO THEY CALL IT
IN WINNIPEG? -
POSTAL CODE?
DARRIN:
UH, EASY, HECTOR.
THEY'RE WITH ME. THANKS.
PIT BOSS:
OH. SURE THING, MR. HOWE.
DARRIN:
UH, YOU MIND IF I JOIN YOU,
MARIA?
KATIE:
UH, NOT AT ALL.
AS LONG AS YOU DON'T MIND
WATCHING ME WIN.
I DON'T MIND WATCHING YOU
AT ALL.
(BURLESQUE MUSIC PLAYS)
ADAM, MO AND JAKE:
DO IT! DO IT! DO IT!
DO IT! DO IT!
AGH!
OH!
JAKE:
FEEL THE BURN.
THERE YOU GO.
DREW:
(HOARSE VOICE)
I DON'T WANNA DO THAT AGAIN.
ARE YOU GUYS GONNA ROAST ME
OR SOMETHING?
MO:
UM... SURE. YEAH.
GETTING MARRIED AT EIGHTEEN?
HA!
THAT'S LIKE FINALLY GETTING
TO THE BUFFET OF LIFE
AND BEING LIKE,
"NO, IT'S COOL, MAN,
I'LL JUST HAVE THIS ONE
PIECE OF TOAST.
FOREVER."
(JAKE AND ADAM CHUCKLE
AWKWARDLY)
DREW:
NEW GAME.
UH...
FAVOURITE MEMORY OF ME.
(LAUGHING)
HOW ABOUT THAT TIME
YOU BROUGHT DOG BISCUITS
TO SCHOOL FOR LUNCH-
OKAY, I WAS EIGHT!
AND WE PROMISED
THAT WOULD NEVER GO PUBLIC.
MMM...
DREW:
UM... MO.
REMEMBER THAT TIME
YOU DRANK THE HOT SAUCE?
THAT WAS HILARIOUS!
THAT WAS RIGHT NOW.
A COUPLE SECONDS AGO,
YEAH.
JAKE? ANYTHING, BUDDY,
COME ON.
JAKE:
OKAY, UM...
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH...
THAT "I DID IT" VIDEO,
WHICH WAS...
YOU KNOW, WHICH WAS ACTUALLY
ABOUT YOU
S-SLEEPING WITH
MY GIRLFRIEND...
WE, WE DON'T...
GUYS, COME ON.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO MAKE THIS SPECIAL!
ANNOUNCER:
AT THIS TIME,
I'D LIKE TO CALL TO THE STAGE
TONIGHT'S BACHELORS,
MR. DREW TORRES
AND MR. STEVE PATEL!
(GUYS CHEER)
(GUYS LAUGH AND CHEER)
THEY'RE ALL WITH YOU?
STEVE PATEL:
LEAVE NO MAN BEHIND!
(CHEERING AND WHISTLING)
IT'S NOT THAT EASY,
IS IT?
EXCUSE ME?
UH, YOUR LIPS ARE MOVING.
IT'S OKAY,
I WON'T TELL ANYONE.
DO YOU WANNA HAVE
DRINKS AFTER?
HEY, PUT IT ON ICE,
PAL.
I'M SORRY,
I WAS TALKING TO...
MARIA ALVAREZ,
WAS IT?
UH...
MY NAME'S KATIE MATLIN.
DARRIN.
AND WHILE WE'RE BEING HONEST,
UM, I HAVE A BOYFRIEND,
AND I'M ACTUALLY HERE
TO WIN MY TUITION
FOR STANFORD NEXT YEAR.
HEY! GO CARDINALS!
I USED TO GO THERE
FOR TWO YEARS
UNTIL I HAD TO DROP OUT
BECAUSE MY START-UP BLEW UP.
OH MY GOD.
YOU'RE DARRIN HOWE?!
YOU INVENTED FACERANGE?!
DARRIN:
ANYWAYS, I GOT A THING.
UM...
IF WANT SOME ADVICE,
YOU WANNA WIN
YOUR TUITION BACK,
YOU GOTTA BET BIGGER.
RISK EQUALS REWARD.
THAT'S A THOUSAND DOLLARS!
YOU'RE WORTH IT.
IF YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND
ABOUT DRINKS...
♪ Once we know what matters ♪
♪ Then we really know
that nothing matters ♪
♪ Once we know what matters ♪
♪ It's the only thing
that really matters ♪
♪ We can be together now,
so help me out ♪
♪ Once we stay forever ♪
♪ That's the first
that we tell each other ♪
♪ Once we say forever ♪
♪ That's the first
that we tell each other ♪
♪ We can be together now ♪
♪ So help me out ♪
♪♪♪
KATIE, WHAT HAPPENED?
I JUST...
I HIT A BAD RUN,
BUT DON'T WORRY 'CAUSE
THE COUNT'S PLUS NINE NOW;
THAT MEANS THAT THERE'S MOSTLY
FACE CARDS LEFT, REMEMBER?
I'D LIKE TO SPLIT.
DEALER:
OKAY.
OKAY, BUT THAT'S ALL
OF YOUR MONEY.
KATIE:
I GOTTA GET OUTTA THIS HOLE,
MARE.
DEALER:
TWENTY. TWENTY.
OKAY.
COME ON, COME ON, COME ON,
COME ON, COME ON, COME ON...
DEALER:
...FIFTEEN, TWENTY-ONE.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
DEALER:
HOUSE WINS.
♪ It's a long way to fall ♪
♪ But you know we can live on ♪
THAT WAS EVERY CENT
MY PARENTS EVER SAVED FOR ME!
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?!
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU REALLY MESSED UP.
THANKS, MARE.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
COMFORTING ME.
HOW IS IT EVEN POSSIBLE
THAT STUPID DREW HAS HIS LIFE
MORE TOGETHER THAN I DO?
'KAY, THAT IS NOT TRUE.
HE HAS A JOB,
HE'S GETTING MARRIED.
I CAN'T EVEN AFFORD TO GO
TO T.U. ANYMORE!
LOOK, THIS IS VEGAS.
THERE HAS TO BE SOME WAY
YOU CAN GET THE MONEY BACK!
OH YEAH, LET ME JUST
BECOME A SHOWGIRL.
YOU KNOW... THERE...
THERE IS ONE THING
I COULD DO.
I DON'T KNOW, MARE,
HE'S A BILLIONAIRE.
MAYBE HE HAS A JOB FOR ME
OR SOMETHING.
HI, DARRIN.
UM, THIS IS KATIE.
REMEMBER HOW YOU TOLD ME
TO TAKE A RISK?
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS,
LOUD BUZZ OF CHATTER)
STEVE PATEL:
THIS HERE IS MY BROTHER, PAUL.
MY BRIDE-TO-BE ANGIE'S
BROTHER TODD,
THIS HERE'S MY DAD,
STEVE SR.
NICE! SO EVERYONE'S HERE
BUT YOUR MOM!
OH, YEAH, SHE'S OUT
WITH ANGIE RIGHT NOW.
PROBABLY STUFFING DOLLAR BILLS
IN A G-STRING, HUH?!
(GUYS CHEER)
WAIT, THEY'D DO THAT
TOGETHER?
THEY DO EVERYTHING TOGETHER.
THEY'RE FAMILY.
MY MOM AND FIANCEE,
THEY DON'T EVEN TALK.
ACTUALLY, MY MOM DOESN'T EVEN
KNOW I'M GETTING MARRIED.
I TELL MY MOM EVERYTHING.
YEAH. YEAH,
WE USED TO BE CLOSE.
AT MY FOOTBALL GAMES,
SHE WAS THE LOUDEST
CHEERLEADER.
WE USED TO GO CAMPING
ALL THE TIME.
I DON'T KNOW, LATELY,
SHE'S JUST BEEN ON MY CASE
FOR EVERYTHING.
SHE'S GOT MY DAD
ON HER SIDE TOO.
IF I ELOPED,
MY MOM WOULD DISOWN ME.
BUT, HEY MAN,
LOVE CONQUERS ALL, RIGHT?
(AWKWARDLY)
HEY, UH...
GOOD LUCK TOMORROW!
THANKS.
ALL RIGHT.
ADAM:
LIMO'S GONNA BE HERE
IN FIVE MINUTES
TO TAKE US
TO GLOW-IN-THE-DARK PAINTBALL!
(EXCITED)
YES!
YEAH, UH...
GIMME A MINUTE.
I NEED TO MAKE A QUICK CALL.
HEY.
I GUESS YOU'RE BUSY
RIGHT NOW.
I JUST...
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
I THINK WE'RE MAKING
A HUGE MISTAKE.