♪♪
♪ I went to the beach
with my old... ♪
MAYA:
GOOD. YOU GUYS GOT MY TEXT!
YOU KNOW, I'M HOPING
"THE HELP YOU NEED"
IS RUBBING SUNSCREEN ON
YOUR HARD TO REACH PLACES
'CAUSE I'M KIND OF
AN EXPERT.
TINY:
IT'S TRUE.
HE'S GOT A MAGIC TOUCH.
MAYA:
OOH, THAT'S TEMPTING,
BUT I HAVE A BETTER PLAN.
WE'RE GONNA FIND GLORIA.
YOU WANNA SPEND
YOUR FIRST DAY OFF
SEARCHING FOR
A MISSING GIRL?
MAYA:
WELL, I SAW HER AT LOLA'S
LAST NIGHT,
SO I KNOW SHE'S NOT MISSING.
YOU STILL THINK
I IMAGINED IT.
BECAUSE YOU FEEL RESPONSIBLE
ABOUT HER DISAPPEARANCE.
I SAID SOME TERRIBLE THINGS
TO HER.
YEAH, THAT DOESN'T MEAN
IT'S YOUR FAULT.
YOU DON'T KNOW THAT.
BUT I DO KNOW THAT
YOU'LL DO ANYTHING
TO AVOID SPENDING TIME
WITH ME.
MAYA:
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
WELL... COME ON,
I'LL BE AT THE FULL MOON PARTY
TONIGHT.
I'LL BELIEVE IT
WHEN I SEE IT.
TINY:
DON'T WORRY.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF ZIGMUND.
YOU TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
MAYA:
IT'S DAYLIGHT AND THERE
ARE LOADS OF PEOPLE AROUND.
WHAT COULD POSSIBLY HAPPEN?
A LOT, MAYA. A LOT.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh... ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
MILES:
CAN YOU BELIEVE
THAT IT WAS ONLY A YEAR AGO
THAT WE WERE HAVING FUN
IN PARIS?
ZOE:
(SNORTS) FUN? IS THAT WHAT
YOU CALL BEING DITCHED
FOR MAYA MATLIN?
WHATEVER HAPPENED
BETWEEN YOU TWO ANYWAY?
MILES:
SHE WAS ALWAYS TRYING
TO CHANGE ME.
ZOE:
AND TRISTAN DIDN'T?
MILES:
NO. HE WAS JUST HAPPY
TO HANG OUT.
ZOE:
AND YOU WERE FINE WITH THE
WHOLE BOY KISSING BOY THING?
LOVE THE PERSON,
NOT THE GENDER.
(KISSING)
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
ZOE: YOU DO?
MILES: YEAH. DON'T WORRY.
I'M NOT USING YOU TO FIGURE OUT
HOW I FEEL ABOUT DUDES.
GOOD. BECAUSE THAT
WOULD BE CRUEL.
SO CAN WE PLEASE STOP
TALKING ABOUT MY PAST
AND FOCUS ON MY PRESENT?
BECAUSE I CAN THINK
OF WAY BETTER THINGS
WE CAN DO WITH OUR LIPS.
(KISSING)
GRACE:
SO THIS LOGAN GUY RECEIVED
A VIDEO OF HIS GIRLFRIEND
PROMISING HER SAFE RELEASE
FOR TEN THOUSAND DOLLARS?
FRANKIE:
AS LONG AS HE DIDN'T GO
TO THE COPS.
TRISTAN: AND NOW HE'S MISSING?
FRANKIE: JUST LIKE
HIS GIRLFRIEND.
WAIT, YOU GUYS EACH GOT
FIVE THOUSAND DOLLARS
FOR YOUR BIRTHDAY?
CAN WE PLEASE JUST FINISH
OUR SCIENCE PROJECT?
MILES:
WE'LL MAKE A SAILOR
OUT OF YOU YET.
ZOE:
AS LONG AS I GET TO WEAR
THE CAPTAIN'S HAT.
I LOOK VERY GOOD
IN HATS.
YOU LOOK GOOD
IN EVERYTHING.
ZOE:
(GIGGLES)
GRACE:
CAN YOU GUYS PLEASE TAKE
THE PDA SOMEWHERE ELSE?
WE'RE TRYING TO GET
SOME WORK DONE HERE.
SORRY.
GIVE ME A SEC.
SORRY ABOUT LEAVING.
I'LL MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
UNTIL YOU GET A BETTER OFFER
FROM SOME DUDE AND DITCH ME.
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
OF COURSE IT IS.
DON'T WORRY,
I'M USED TO IT.
SO LET'S JUST STOP
PRETENDING TO BE FRIENDS.
NO.
COME TO THE FULL MOON PARTY
WITH ME, TONIGHT.
AREN'T YOU GOING
WITH MILES?
YEAH, BUT... WE COULD GO
ALL TOGETHER.
AND IF YOU HUNG OUT
WITH US TONIGHT,
YOU'D SEE THAT HE'S...
NOT THE WORST.
GRACE: OKAY.
ZOE: SERIOUSLY?
BUT I CAN LEAVE
WHENEVER I WANT.
DEAL.
(MARIACHI-LIKE MUSIC PLAYS)
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
(CARS RUMBLE IN THE STREET,
PEOPLE CHATTER)
(CAR RUMBLES BY)
MAYA:
GLORIA!
(PANTING)
(BREATHING HARD)
GLORIA?
(SHAKY BREATHS)
(RATTLING SOUND,
MAYA GASPS)
I JUST WANNA TALK TO YOU.
GLORIA: GO AWAY, MAYA.
MAYA: (FRIGHTENED GASP)
NO. NOT UNTIL I KNOW
THAT YOU'RE OKAY.
GLORIA:
YOU SHOULDN'T BE HERE.
YOU'LL ONLY MAKE THINGS WORSE.
MAYA:
I'M NOT LEAVING
UNTIL I HAVE ANSWERS.
I HAVE MY PHONE.
I'LL CALL THE POLICE.
(MAYA GASPS AND SCREAMS,
PHONE THUMPS ON THE GROUND)
(KIDS LAUGH AND CHEER)
♪ Rock this club... down! ♪
(DJ HOWLS)
♪♪
♪ Rock this club down! ♪
WINSTON: MUAH!
FRANKIE: WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
WINSTON:
SAYING HI TO MY GIRLFRIEND.
SORRY.
IT'S BEEN A WEIRD NIGHT.
OKAY, THEN LET'S
DANCE IT OFF.
NO, I'M NOT REALLY
IN THE MOOD.
BECAUSE YOU'RE WORRIED
ABOUT LOGAN.
I JUST NEED TO FIND A WAY
TO HELP HIM.
WINSTON:
UGH. CAN'T WE STOP TALKING ABOUT
THAT LOSER FOR LIKE, A MINUTE?
WINSTON, HE COULD BE
IN REAL TROUBLE!
YEAH, 'CAUSE HE SCAMMED MONEY
OFF STUPID YOU
INSTEAD OF GOING
TO THE COPS!
HE DIDN'T SCAM ME.
I OFFERED.
WHY DID YOU GIVE SOME GUY
YOU'VE KNOWN FOR A MONTH
TEN THOUSAND DOLLARS?
ADMIT IT, FRANKS.
YOU LIKE HIM.
FRANKIE: HE HAS A GIRLFRIEND.
WINSTON: THAT'S NOT AN ANSWER.
♪ Rock this club down! ♪
FINE.
YES, I LIKE HIM.
MORE THAN ME?
I DON'T KNOW.
OKAY.
THANKS FOR YOUR HONESTY.
♪ We, we love, love, we... ♪
(FIRE CRACKLES)
♪ We, we love, we... ♪
♪ We, we love, love, we... ♪
ZOE:
WHAT'S THAT BRIGHT LIGHT
OVER THERE?
MILES:
UH, JUPITER,
AND THAT ONE'S MARS.
WHEN I WAS A KID,
I DREAMT ABOUT GOING TO SPACE.
I UH... (LAUGHS)
WANTED TO GET AS FAR
FROM MY PARENTS AS POSSIBLE.
GRACE AND ZOE:
ME TOO.
ZOE:
(LAUGHS) SEE?
I KNEW YOU GUYS
WOULD GET ALONG.
GRACE:
ZOE WAS RIGHT.
YOU ARE "NOT THE WORST."
MILES: (LAUGHS)
DID SHE SAY THAT?
AREN'T YOU JUST
THE SWEETEST?
ZOE AND MILES:
(LAUGH AND START KISSING)
GRACE:
AND I THINK THIS IS
MY CUE TO LEAVE NOW.
ZOE:
UH, DON'T GO.
WE'RE... WE'RE HAVING FUN.
TONGUE WRESTLING'S
A TWO-PERSON SPORT.
DOESN'T HAVE TO BE.
YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
I REALLY, REALLY
HOPE NOT.
ZOE:
COME ON. WE SHOULD TOTALLY
KISS. IT'D BE HILARIOUS.
WAS THIS YOUR PLAN
ALL ALONG?
TO SET UP A THREESOME
FOR YOUR RICH BOYFRIEND?
ZOE:
WE'RE JUST KIDDING AROUND.
RELAX.
GRACE!
THIS IS WHY NO ONE LIKES YOU.
YOU'RE A USER.
YOU USE PEOPLE.
WELL, YOU'RE...
A LOVESICK LESBIAN!
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
ZIG: UH, ZOE,
HAVE YOU SEEN MAYA?
ZOE: WHAT?
I'M SUPPOSED TO MEET HER HERE
AND SHE'S NOT ANSWERING
HER PHONE.
I THINK SHE COULD BE
IN TROUBLE.
MAYA:
HELP! HELP!
SOMEBODY HELP US, PLEASE!
HEEEEEEEELLLLP!
GLORIA: YOU'RE WASTING
YOUR TIME.
WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE
OF NOWHERE.
BESIDES,
YOU'LL ONLY MAKE HIM MAD.
WHO'S HE?
GLORIA: I DON'T KNOW.
SOME GUY.
SOME GUY WHO KIDNAPS GIRLS
AND LETS YOU RUN OFF
ON YOUR OWN?
WHY DIDN'T YOU RUN?
BECAUSE HE KNOWS
WHERE I LIVE.
HE KNOWS EVERYTHING
ABOUT ME.
BESIDES,
I'VE GOT NOWHERE TO GO.
AFTER EVERYTHING I'VE DONE,
NO ONE WOULD WANT ME.
MAYA:
OH MY GOD, DID...?
DID HE HURT YOU?
GLORIA: CAN WE JUST NOT TALK?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
♪♪
ZOE:
...WAS IN HER STUPID
HOT DOG COSTUME.
MILES:
OKAY, WE NEED TO TRY
AND REMEMBER SOMETHING ELSE.
ZOE:
WELL, LIKE WHAT?
I DON'T KNOW WHERE SHE IS!
MILES:
WHAT DID MAYA'S MOM SAY?
SHHH!
ZIG:
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
SHE HASN'T HEARD FROM HER.
I THINK SHE MIGHT CALL
THE POLICE.
THIS IS MY FAULT
FOR LETTING HER GO OFF ALONE.
TRISTAN: HEY, DON'T WORRY.
ZIG: HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO NOT WORRY?!
THE GIRLFRIEND IS MISSING
AND THERE'S NOTHING
I CAN DO ABOUT IT.
WINSTON:
(SNAPS FINGERS) WE SHOULD WORK
THE SOCIAL MEDIA ANGLE.
GET THE WORD OUT
ON TWITTER AND FACERANGE.
TRISTAN:
HASHTAG-FIND-MAYA.
I LIKE IT.
WHERE DID YOU LAST SEE HER?
ZIG: UH... AT-AT THE BEACH.
BUT SHE WAS HEADED TO LOLA'S...
TO FIND GLORIA CHIN.
WHY DO I ALWAYS HAVE
TO GET INVOLVED?
ZIG'S PROBABLY FREAKING OUT
RIGHT NOW.
AND MY MOM?
SHE REALLY DOESN'T NEED THIS.
MUST BE NICE TO HAVE SO MANY
PEOPLE WHO CARE ABOUT YOU.
YOU HAVE PEOPLE
WHO CARE, TOO.
YEAH? LIKE WHO?
THOSE KIDS YOU BABYSAT,
FOR STARTERS.
GLORIA: LENA AND EVERETT?
MAYA: YEAH, THEY LOVED YOU.
GLORIA: REALLY?
MAYA: ESPECIALLY LENA.
I BET SHE'D BE THRILLED
TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
I CAN'T GO BACK.
IF WE WORK TOGETHER,
WE CAN FIND A WAY OUT.
AFTER ALL THE CRAP
I DID TO YOU?
EVERYONE DESERVES
A SECOND CHANCE.
BUT FIRST, WE HAVE TO FIND
A WAY OUT OF HERE.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
MILES:
TWITTER'S CATCHING ON.
TRISTAN:
HEY, YOU DON'T THINK BAIN
DID THIS, DO YOU?
WELL, HE WAS IN CLASS TODAY
SO IT HAD TO BE SOMEONE ELSE.
CAN... CAN YOU CALL GRACE
AND CHECK THAT SHE'S OKAY?
TRISTAN: I'M SURE SHE'S FINE.
ZOE: BUT WHAT IF SHE'S NOT?
THERE'S SOMEONE OUT THERE
TAKING GIRLS.
OMG. YOU LOVE HER.
ZIG:
OKAY, LOOK, I CAN'T JUST
SIT HERE AND DO NOTHING.
WE SHOULD GO OUT
AND LOOK FOR HER.
TRISTAN:
OKAY, WELL,
I KNOW THE FIRST PERSON
I'D WANT TO BE PART
OF A SEARCH PARTY.
RHYMES WITH "MACE..."
WHICH SHE PROBABLY HAS
IN HER PURSE.
(CHAIR CRASHES)
MAYA: UNGH!
(CHAIR SMASHES,
MAYA GRUNTS)
GLORIA:
SO WHAT EXACTLY
IS THIS ESCAPE PLAN?
(MAYA SMASHES THE CHAIR,
PIECES CLATTER)
MAYA:
I PLAY SICK.
YOU CALL THE GUY INTO THE ROOM,
WORRIED ABOUT ME.
AND WHEN HE LEAST
EXPECTS IT,
YOU'RE GONNA HIT HIM
OVER THE HEAD WITH THIS...
AND HARD.
(WOODEN PIECES CLATTER)
GLORIA:
HELP! (BANGS ON DOOR)
HELP!
(APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS)
HEY! WE'RE ALL TRYING
TO FIND MAYA. GONNA HELP?
WHAT IF I NEVER
SEE HIM AGAIN?
WINSTON?
HE'S JUST IN THE OTHER-
OH... YOU MEAN
THE OTHER GUY.
FRANKIE:
I KEEP TEXTING
AND THERE'S NO RESPONSE.
YOU COULD ALWAYS
JUST CALL.
(PHONE RINGS)
LOGAN: FRANKIE?
FRANKIE: LOGAN?
IS THAT YOU?
ARE YOU OKAY?
LOGAN:
UH... I'M SO GLAD YOU CALLED.
UM, THE COPS AREN'T WITH YOU,
ARE THEY?
FRANKIE: NO,
BUT I CAN CALL THEM.
LOGAN: OH, NO, NO. DON'T...
DON'T DO THAT.
IT'S JUST UM...
I STUCK MY NECK OUT FOR HER,
FRANKS,
UH, AND SHE TURNED ON ME.
FRANKIE:
GLORIA?
LOGAN:
YEAH, BECAUSE OF THAT
OTHER GIRL.
FRANKIE: WHAT OTHER GIRL?
LOGAN: NEVERMIND.
I- I NEED A LITTLE MORE MONEY.
NOT MUCH. UH-UH-UM... JUST...
JUST FIVE THOUSAND DOLLARS.
FRANKIE:
SO IT WAS ALL A SCAM?
YOU USED ME?
LOGAN:
OH, ARE WE SERIOUSLY
GONNA DO THIS RIGHT NOW?
I'M SORRY.
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS.
FRANKIE:
I THOUGHT YOU UM...
LOGAN:
WHAT, THAT I LOVED YOU?
THAT I WANTED TO BE WITH YOU?
YOU'RE JUST SOME STUPID
RICH GIRL
LOOKING FOR A LITTLE
EXCITEMENT.
'KAY, WELL, YOU GOT WHAT
YOU WANTED, DIDN'T YOU?
GLORIA:
HELP! I NEED YOUR HELP!
(BANGING ON DOOR)
PLEASE! PLEASE! HELP!
(DOOR LOCK UNLATCHES)
SHE JUST... COLLAPSED.
(WEAPON THUMPS INEFFECTIVELY,
GLORIA SCREAMS)
LOGAN:
WHAT THE HELL?!
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?!
GLORIA:
I DON'T KNOW!
I WANT THIS TO BE OVER!
LOGAN:
YEAH?! SO DID I!
BUT YOU THIS DUMB BLONDE
FOLLOW YOU HERE.
WE WERE-WE WERE SO CLOSE
TO GETTING AWAY WITH THIS.
MAYA:
WE?
YOU TWO STAGED
THE KIDNAPPING?!
NOW WHO'S THE DUMB ONE?
WHY DID I GO ALONG
WITH YOUR STUPID PLAN
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
LOGAN:
SO WE COULD BE TOGETHER
WITHOUT YOUR PARENTS
TRYING TO BREAK US UP!
WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING?
MAYA:
NO, NO, NO. PLEASE.
YOU CAN STILL BE TOGETHER,
JUST LET ME GO.
LOGAN:
YEAH? HOW CAN I TRUST YOU?!
I CAN'T TRUST ANYBODY!
LOGAN, PLEASE.
WE STILL HAVE THE MONEY,
WE CAN JUST RUN AWAY.
LOGAN:
TEN THOUSAND DOLLARS
IS NOT GONNA GET US FAR
WITH THE COPS ON OUR TAIL.
THERE'S GOTTA BE A WAY
WE CAN GET OUTTA THIS.
LOGAN:
YEAH.
WE NEED TO GET RID
OF HER.
MAYA:
(SHAKY BREATH)
MILES:
WE'VE PRINTED OFF
SOME PICS OF MAYA.
ZIG:
PERFECT. LET'S GO.
WINSTON:
NO, WAIT.
THE CITY'S HUGE.
HOW'RE WE GONNA COVER
ALL THAT TERRITORY?
GRACE:
YOU'VE GOT ONE MORE
BODY NOW.
ZOE: YOU CAME?
GRACE: OF COURSE.
MAYA'S MY FRIEND.
ZIG:
OKAY, WHERE-
WHERE DO WE EVEN START?
FRANKIE:
I MIGHT HAVE AN IDEA.
I TALKED TO LOGAN.
THAT'S GLORIA'S BOYFRIEND.
HE MENTIONED ANOTHER GIRL.
MILES: MAYA?
FRANKIE: I THINK SO.
HE SOUNDED DESPERATE.
ZIG:
W-WHAT'S THIS GUY
EVEN CAPABLE OF?
FRANKIE:
I DON'T KNOW. OBVIOUSLY,
I DIDN'T KNOW HIM AT ALL.
GRACE:
GIVE ME YOUR PHONE.
WE MIGHT BE ABLE TO FIGURE OUT
HIS EXACT LOCATION.
COME ON, COME ON, COME ON...
DAMN, HIS PHONE'S OFF.
HUNTER:
OKAY, WHAT ABOUT THAT VIDEO
ASKING FOR THE MONEY?
CAN WE LIFT ANY INFORMATION
OFF THAT?
FRANKIE:
I DON'T HAVE A COPY,
BUT IT LOOKED LIKE IT WAS
FILMED IN A WAREHOUSE.
TRISTAN:
THAT SOUNDS LIKE THE PLACE
GLORIA FILMS
HER FROZEN TREAT VIDEOS.
GLORIA: (ON VIDEO)
TODAY'S S'MORES-INSPIRED
FROZEN TREAT RECIPE
COMES FROM SAMANTHA
IN NEW JERSEY.
FRANKIE:
WAIT, IS THAT THE CN TOWER?
ZOE:
IF WE CAN FIND OUT
THE FOCAL LENGTH ON THE CAMERA
THAT SHE USED,
WE CAN FIGURE OUT HOW FAR AWAY
FROM THE CN TOWER SHE WAS
WHEN SHE FILMED IT.
GRACE:
USING THAT FORMULA
WE LEARNED IN SCIENCE CLASS.
NICE.
BUT HOW DO WE FIND
THE FOCAL LENGTH?
ZOE:
WELL, SHE PROBABLY SHOOTS
HER VIDEOS ON A SMARTPHONE.
(COMPUTER KEYS CLACK)
GRACE:
WHICH HAS A FOCAL LENGTH OF...
4.28.
AND THE HEIGHT OF
THE CN TOWER IS...
553.33 METRES.
ZOE:
SO WHEN SHE FILMED IT,
SHE WAS...
15.2 KILOMETRES AWAY,
FACING EAST.
GRACE: THE BLUFFS.
ZOE: THAT'S CLOSE
TO THE OLD SUGAR FACTORY.
ZIG: W-W-WE SHOULD GO.
WINSTON: NO.
WE SHOULD CALL THE COPS.
(DOOR OPENS)
HEY, WE NEED TO GO NOW.
(BAG RUSTLES)
GLORIA:
WHAT ABOUT MAYA?
LOGAN:
WE'LL TIE HER UP,
THEN LEAVE HER IN THE WOODS.
WE'LL BE LONG GONE
BY THE TIME THEY FIND HER.
GLORIA:
SHE COULD DIE.
WE CAN'T DO THAT.
MAYA: AGREED.
LOGAN: SHUT UP!
THIS DOESN'T CONCERN YOU!
MAYA: THAT'S DEBATABLE.
LOGAN: I SAID, SHUT UP, OKAY?
(MAYA STRUGGLES)
LOGAN: 'KAY, MOVE!
MAYA:
(SCREAMING) HELP ME!
'KAY, GLORIA! I'LL GET THE CAR,
YOU FINISH TYING HER UP.
MAYA:
(CRYING) GLORIA,
PLEASE DON'T DO THIS.
(CRYING)
PLEASE...
(SHAKY BREATHS)
MALE OFFICER:
THIS IS THE POLICE!
FEMALE OFFICER:
WE'RE COMING IN!
MALE OFFICER:
YOU! GET ON THE GROUND!
I SAID GET ON THE GROUND! NOW!
LOGAN:
OKAY! OKAY!
I DIDN'T HURT THEM!
FEMALE OFFICER:
GET ON THE GROUND!
MALE OFFICER: CLEAR!
(SIRENS WAIL OUTSIDE)
MAYA:
(CRYING TEARS OF RELIEF)
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
THERE WE GO...
NOW, THANKS TO THIS CLASS,
WE BROUGHT YOUR FRIEND
HOME SAFELY.
IF I HAD MY WAY,
I WOULD GIVE YOU ALL A'S.
MR. BAIN: (LAUGHS)
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH: MR. BAIN?
MR. BAIN:
UH... OH, VERY GOOD,
BUT I THINK WE WILL RELY
ON THE PERFORMANCES
FROM YOUR FINAL EXAMS.
(EVERYONE CLAPS)
TRISTAN:
OKAY.
ZOE: HI, MR. BAIN.
MR. BAIN: HEY.
ZOE:
I KNOW I HAVEN'T BEEN
THE EASIEST STUDENT,
BUT... I WANTED YOU TO KNOW
THAT I LEARNED A LOT.
MR. BAIN:
UH, OBVIOUSLY.
YOU CRACKED THE GLORIA CHIN
CASE BEFORE I DID.
I FANCY MYSELF
AN AMATEUR GUMSHOE.
THAT'S WHY YOU HAD
ALL THOSE MISSING GIRL FILES
IN YOUR TRUCK.
MR. BAIN:
MM-HMM.
I THINK THIS BELONGS
TO YOU.
ZOE:
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
I AM... SO SORRY
I CALLED THE COPS.
MR. BAIN:
APOLOGY ACCEPTED.
JUST REMEMBER THAT APPEARANCES
CAN BE DECEIVING.
IT'S ALWAYS BEST
TO TRUST YOUR GUT.
♪ ...working it out,
trying not to make a sound ♪
♪ Chasing another arrow
of light, ♪
♪ It's almost
the same somehow ♪
(WAVES LAP AT THE SHORE,
PEOPLE CHATTER)
♪ You love another... ♪
CAN WE TALK?
LOGAN WAS A JERK.
BUT YOU'RE NOT.
WHICH IS WHY I'M HOPING
YOU'LL GIVE ME SECOND CHANCE?
WINSTON: AT WHAT, FRANKIE?
FRANKIE: US, OBVIOUSLY.
THERE'S NO US ANYMORE.
FRANKIE:
WINSTON, COME ON.
IT'S NOT LIKE I CHEATED.
WINSTON:
NOT WITH YOUR LIPS.
BUT WHAT YOU DID...
WAS WAY WORSE.
SO I'M DONE TALKING.
LIKE, FOREVER.
♪♪
MAYA:
OOH... YOU'RE HOLDING ME
SO TIGHT.
ZIG:
AND I'M NEVER LETTING GO.
HAVE I TOLD YOU HOW HAPPY I AM
TO HAVE YOU IN MY LIFE?
MAYA:
ONLY LIKE A MILLION TIMES.
I WISH EVERYONE
WAS SO LUCKY.
YOU'RE THINKING OF GLORIA?
MAYA:
IF SHE HAD HAD GOOD PEOPLE
IN HER LIFE,
SHE WOULDN'T BE HEADED
TO JUVEY RIGHT NOW.
(SIGHS) OH, I JUST DON'T
WANT THE SAME TO HAPPEN
TO THOSE KIDS I BABYSAT FOR,
WHICH IS WHY I SENT
THEIR MOM A MESSAGE
BEGGING FOR MY JOB BACK.
YOU'LL SAVE THE WORLD,
MAYA MATLIN.
(KISSING)
EVERETT: EW!
LENA: HI, ZIG!
MAYA:
WHAT'RE YOU GUYS
DOING HERE?!
JORDYN:
IT TOOK SOME TIME...
BUT I REALIZED
YOU WERE RIGHT.
UH, I CAN BABYSIT AGAIN?
I'LL BE FREE WHEN SCHOOL
STARTS.
JORDYN:
AH, YOU MIGHT NOT.
I WAS HOPING YOU COULD
HELP ME OUT IN THE STUDIO,
DIGITIZING FILES AND STUFF,
SO I CAN SPEND SOME MORE TIME
WITH THE KIDS.
MAYA:
(SQUEALS EXCITEDLY)
ZIG:
I THINK THAT'S A YES.
JORDYN:
(LAUGHS)
MAYA:
(BREATHY) YES!
THE END.
OH, UM...
EXCEPT FOR ONE THING.
(PEOPLE CHATTER AND SHOUT,
WAVES LAP AT THE SHORE)
YOU SEEM ALL FAR AWAY.
WELL, BECAUSE THERE'S
ONE MORE THING WE NEED TO DO
BEFORE SUMMER'S OVER.
♪ Can you come closer... ♪
(Closer...)
♪ And show me
that you're mine ♪
♪ (That you're mine,
that you're mine) ♪
♪ I'm looking for some closure ♪
(Closure...)
♪ 'Cause we've been dancing
all night ♪
♪ So tell me if it's real ♪
(RECORD SCRATCHES ABRUPTLY)
(SIGHS)
THAT DIDN'T HAPPEN.
BUT THIS DID.
YOU SEEM ALL FAR AWAY.
(PEOPLE CHATTER,
SEAGULLS CRY)
THERE'S ONE THING I NEED
TO DO BEFORE SUMMER'S OVER.
(TAKES A DEEP BREATH)
(PEOPLE CHATTER,
WAVES LAP AT THE SHORE)
(WAVES LAP,
SEAGULLS CRY)
I'M SORRY FOR
CALLING YOU NAMES...
AND FOR ACTING
LIKE A TOTAL IDIOT.
WE DON'T HAVE TO DO THIS.
WE CAN ACCEPT THAT
WE'RE NOT MEANT BE FRIENDS.
YOU ARE THE MOST
FRUSTRATING PERSON
I HAVE EVER MET.
YOU MAKE FUN OF ME
ALL THE TIME. YOU TELL ME
I'M WRONG. YOU...
YOU SEE THE REAL ME.
THE GIRL I TRY SO HARD
TO HIDE, AND YOU LIKE HER.
I'M SURE OTHER PEOPLE
WOULD TOO.
SOMETIMES YOU MAKE ME FEEL
SO SPECIAL AND...
I'M SCARED THAT IF I LOSE YOU,
I'LL NEVER FEEL THAT WAY AGAIN.
(KISSING)
(PEOPLE CHATTER,
WAVES LAP)
ZOE:
DON'T SAY ANYTHING.
I'VE RUSHED THINGS BEFORE
AND I DON'T WANNA RUSH THIS.
SCHOOL STARTS IN A WEEK.
LET'S TALK THEN.
♪ Can you come closer ♪
(Closer...)
♪ And show me
that you're mine ♪
♪ (That you're mine,
that you're mine...) ♪
♪ I'm looking for some closure ♪
(Closure...)
♪ 'Cause we've been dancing
all night ♪
♪ So tell me if it's real,
baby ♪
♪ Tell me if it's not ♪
♪ (Not, not, not,
tell me if it's not...) ♪
♪ This is how I feel, baby, ♪
♪ I hope it never stops ♪
(Never stops, stops, stops...)
(RECORD SCRATCHES ABRUPTLY,
TRISTAN SNIFFLES)
AH. SORRY. I AM JUST A SUCKER
FOR A HAPPY ENDING.
BUT IT'S NOT OVER.
YOU WANT REAL DRAMA?
COME BACK WHEN SCHOOL STARTS.
IT ONLY GETS CRAZIER.
TRUST ME.
YOUR NEW BESTIE, TRIS.
(DANCE MUSIC RESUMES PLAYING)