DALLAS:
ALL RIGHT,
ZACK NEEDS A LIFT.
CAR 'A' TRAVELS AT A SPEED
OF 80 KILOMETERS PER HOUR;
CAR 'B' TRAVELS AT A SPEED
OF 60 MILES PER HOUR.
WHAT GETS ZACK HOME FIRST?
DREW:
A ROCKET SHIP?
DALLAS:
DID YOU STUDY
FOR THIS EXAM AT ALL?
DREW:
HUH?
(JENNA SQUEALS)
OH MY GOD!
CONNOR:
JENNA MIDDLETON,
I'D FLY YOU TO ANOTHER PLANET
BUT I HAVE YET TO COMPLETE
THE REQUIRED TRAINING.
INSTEAD, CAN I TAKE YOU
TO PROM?
JENNA:
YES! OF COURSE, YES!
DALLAS:
CONNOR KNOWS HOW
TO ROMANCE A GIRL.
DREW:
PFFT. WHO NEEDS A DATE FOR PROM
WHEN YOU GOT YOUR BEST BRO,
RIGHT?
OH, I BOOKED THE LIMO.
IT'S GOT A HOT TUB.
WHAT?
DALLAS:
I HATE TO DO THIS
THE DAY BEFORE PROM BUT...
ALLI ALREADY BOOKED THE LIMO.
DREW:
FINE. I'LL CANCEL MINE.
NO BIGGIE.
EXCEPT, THERE'S NO SPOT FOR ME.
DALLAS:
CLARE IS BRINGING ELI.
AND AFTER EVERYTHING
THAT WENT DOWN THIS YEAR,
ALLI DOESN'T THINK IT'S A GOOD
IDEA TO HAVE YOU TWO IN CLOSE
QUARTERS.
DREW:
OH WELL, AT LEAST WE'LL BE
AT THE SAME TABLE.
SERIOUSLY?
SO WHAT? I'M SUPPOSED SIT
WITH A BUNCH OF RANDOMS?
NO. NO, DALLAS,
I AM NOT THAT LOSER
WITH NO FRIENDS ON PROM NIGHT.
DALLAS:
I WISH THERE WAS SOMETHING
I COULD DO.
YES, THERE IS. PLEAD MY CASE
TO YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
BUT I PROMISED ALLI
A PERFECT PROM NIGHT.
DREW:
PLEASE, DALLAS. PLEASE.
DALLAS:
YOU KNOW I CAN'T RESIST
THAT FACE.
FINE.
WHAT DO I TELL HER?
DREW:
UM, TELL HER, YOU WON'T
PUT OUT UNLESS I'M THERE.
DALLAS: LIKE, IN THE ROOM?
DREW: SCRATCH THAT.
TELL HER THAT PROM WILL SUCK
WITHOUT YOUR BEST BRO
BY YOUR SIDE.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Ohh... ohh... ohh... ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(BELL RINGS)
ZOE:
WHAT?
MILES:
NOTHING. I LIKE YOUR SHOES.
YOU WERE STARING AT MY FACE.
HUNTER:
GIVE IT BACK!
I'M NOT FINISHED!
ZOE:
SOMEONE'S NOT A HAPPY CAMPER.
HUNTER:
JUST LET ME FINISH MY SENTENCE.
MR. PERINO:
YOUR TIME'S UP,
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH.
AS IS EVERYONE ELSE'S.
MILES:
HEY HEY HEY! RELAX!
IT'S JUST A STUPID EXAM!
HUNTER:
THIS DOESN'T CONCERN YOU!
MILES:
YEAH, IT DOES.
EVERYBODY IS STARING LIKE
YOU'RE SOME SORT OF FREAK.
HUNTER:
I DON'T CARE!
MILES:
YOU SHOULD.
YOU'RE EMBARRASSING YOURSELF.
HUNTER:
GO TO HELL!
MILES:
LOOK, I'M ONLY TRYING TO HELP.
YOU NEVER HELP, OKAY?
YOU ONLY MAKE THINGS WORSE!
DALLAS:
HEY!
ALLI:
OH, I'M GONNA ASK YOU SOMETHING
VERY IMPORTANT.
DON'T OVER THINK IT.
TRUST YOUR GUT.
SHOULD WE GO WITH
THE BLUE CHECK?
DALLAS:
SOMEONE'S NOT WORRIED
ABOUT THEIR CALCULUS FINAL.
ALLI:
DERIVATIVES ARE EASY.
MAKING PROM MAGIC IS NOT.
I HAVEN'T EVEN FINALIZED
THE CENTRE PIECES YET.
DALLAS:
LUCKILY YOU'RE NOT ONLY
THE SEXIEST GIRL AT DEGRASSI,
YOU ARE ALSO THE SMARTEST...
ALLI:
OH NO. YOU CALLED THE BOAT
COMPANY, DIDN'T YOU?
WHAT? DID THEY BOOK TWO PROMS
FOR THE SAME NIGHT?
OR WORSE, DID THEY FOLD?
THIS MUST BE WHAT A HEART
ATTACK FEELS LIKE.
DALLAS:
RELAX. I HAVEN'T CALLED THEM,
YET.
ALLI:
BUT YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO FINALIZE THE SEATING
ARRANGEMENTS THIS MORNING!
DALLAS:
AND I WILL, AS SOON AS YOU AGREE
TO LET DREW SIT AT OUR TABLE.
(SIGHS) HE MADE THE PUPPY DOG
FACE, DIDN'T HE?
HON, WE TALKED ABOUT THIS.
CLARE'S HAD A HORRIBLE YEAR.
SHE DESERVES A NIGHT TO
REMEMBER! AND SO DO I!
DALLAS:
DREW'S YEAR HASN'T BEEN
A CAKEWALK, EITHER.
I CAN'T LET HIM FLY SOLO.
ALLI:
WELL, THEN LET'S FIND HIM
A DATE?
(SMALL LAUGHS)
DALLAS:
I THINK WE'VE SOLVED
YOUR PROBLEM.
DREW:
I'LL BE ON MY BEST BEHAVIOR,
BHANDARI. I PROMISE.
ALLI:
I'M SURE BECKY WOULD
APPRECIATE THAT.
DREW:
BECKY?
ALLI: YOU STILL LIKE HER,
RIGHT?
DREW: YEAH. YEAH. OF COURSE.
DALLAS: AND SHE'D BE
THE PERFECT DATE?
DREW: ABSOLUTELY.
ALLI:
SHE JUST BROKE UP
WITH GUYLINER.
SO SHE'S PROBABLY LOOKING
FOR A SHOULDER TO CRY ON.
DALLAS:
YOU COULD BE THAT SHOULDER.
DREW:
WHAT, YOU REALLY THINK
SHE'D SAY YES?
ALLI:
WHO WOULDN'T WANT TO GO TO PROM
WITH DREW TORRES?
DALLAS:
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET CRACKIN'
ON YOUR PROMPOSAL.
THANK YOU.
(SMALL LAUGH)
CLARE:
QUIZ ME! ROOSEVELT SIGNED
THE NEUTRALITY ACT ON... CRAP.
FRANKIE:
MAY FIRST, 1937.
BUT HE DIDN'T EMBARGO ARMS
SHIPMENTS TO ASIA UNTIL
SEPTEMBER.
WINSTON:
FIRST OF ALL, I HAVE NEVER BEEN
MORE ATTRACTED TO YOU, SECOND;
SINCE YOUR EPIC SUSPENSION
IS DONE,
I GOT A CUE CARD FOR YOU.
FOR GRAD.
YOU WRITE DOWN WHAT
YOU'RE DOING NEXT YEAR
AND THEY'LL READ IT
WHEN YOU CROSS THE STAGE.
DO I HAVE TO DO IT NOW?
I'M KIND OF BUSY.
WINSTON:
OH, I SEE WHAT'S GOING ON.
YOU'RE STILL DECIDING
WHICH IVY LEAGUE TO ACCEPT.
CLARE'S SUPER SMART.
FRANKIE:
THEN YOU PROBABLY GOT
INTO SCHOOLS IN EUROPE.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO SCHOOL IN
PARIS, I AM TOTALLY JEALOUS.
WINSTON:
MAN, MUST BE NICE
TO HAVE SO MANY OPTIONS.
CLARE:
YEAH. YEAH, THAT'S ME.
JUST SWIMMING IN OPTIONS.
WINSTON:
OKAY THEN...
I'LL LEAVE THAT WITH YOU.
CLARE:
NOT A PROBLEM.
I JUST GOTTA PICK A LANE.
MILES:
WHAT DO YOU THINK HUNTER MEANT
WHEN HE SAID
I MAKE EVERYTHING WORSE?
ZOE:
HMM. THAT'S A TOUGH ONE.
WELL, HOW IS THAT EVEN POSSIBLE?
I BARELY INTERACT WITH HIM.
HE'S ALWAYS PLAYING WEIRDO
GAMES IN HIS ROOM
OR WORKING ON THAT DUMB
COMIC BOOK.
WITH DAD OUT OF THE HOUSE, WHAT
COULD POSSIBLY BE HIS PROBLEM?
ZOE:
YOU GUYS ARE IN FAMILY THERAPY.
HAS HE SHARED ANYTHING?
MILES:
TEEN-AGE BOYS DON'T SHARE.
ARLENE: DO YOU HAVE A PEN?
HUNTER: SURE. HERE YOU GO.
ARLENE: THANKS.
ZOE:
UNLESS IT'S WITH A GIRL.
HUNTER'S GOT A NERD CRUSH.
ZOE:
I THINK HER NAME'S ARLENE.
MILES:
WITH SCHOOL OUT, HUNTER
WON'T SEE HER FOR MONTHS.
ZOE:
UNLESS HE LOCKS IT DOWN
BEFORE THE BREAK.
MILES:
AND I CAN HELP HIM AT THE
HOLLINGSWORTH'S ANNUAL POST
EXAM EXTRAVAGANZA.
ZOE:
THAT'S A THING
YOUR FAMILY DOES?
IT IS NOW.
ELI:
THIS IS FOR A GIRL WHO'S
CRAMMING FOR HER HISTORY FINAL.
HAVE YOU SEEN HER?
CLARE:
ARRRRGHHHHH.
ELI:
COME ON, IT CAN'T BE THAT BAD.
YOU'RE AWESOME AT HISTORY.
CLARE:
IT'S NOT THAT.
EVERYONE'S GOING OFF TO DO
AMAZING STUFF NEXT YEAR.
I WAS SUSPENDED FOR TWO WEEKS!
AND YOU KNOW WHAT I THOUGHT
ABOUT EVERY SINGLE DAY?
MY PLAN. YOU KNOW WHAT I CAME
UP WITH? BUPKISS.
WELL, I GUESS I JUST KIND
OF FIGURED THAT YOU COME
TO NEW YORK.
CLARE: REALLY?
ELI: YEAH, I MEAN, WHY NOT?
CLARE:
BUT WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
ELI:
WHATEVER YOU WANT!
THE WORLD IS YOUR OYSTER!
CLARE:
I GUESS, I COULD READ ALL THOSE
BOOKS YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO READ
BEFORE YOU DIE...
ELI:
AND THERE ARE TONS OF AWESOME
COFFEE SHOPS NEAR MY APARTMENT
FOR YOU TO WRITE IN.
CLARE:
JUST TAKE THE YEAR TO READ
AND WRITE AND EXPLORE.
ELI:
AND THEN RE-APPLY TO COLUMBIA.
CLARE:
OR MAYBE BY THEN I'LL ALMOST BE
DONE MY FIRST NOVEL.
(CHUCKLES) AND BEST OF ALL,
WE'LL BE TOGETHER.
SO... DOES THAT SOUND
LIKE A PLAN?
CLARE:
YES. IT TOTALLY DOES.
MR. ARMSTRONG:
WHO WANTS TO GRADUATE?!
(STUDENTS APPLAUD)
GOOD.
THEN LET'S GET STARTED.
TURN OVER YOUR EXAMS.
DREW:
UH, BUT BEFORE YOU DO THAT!
I HAVE A QUESTION
FOR BECKY BAKER.
BECKY: (WHISPERS)
OKAY. WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
(CURTAINS SCRAPE BACK)
(SLOW MUSIC STARTS TO PLAY)
♪ Forget what's right ♪
♪ I need you
to catch me when I fall ♪
(STUDENTS LAUGH)
I'M SORRY... I CAN'T.
OKAY.
SHOW'S OVER, MR. TORRES,
YOU WANNA TURN
THE LIGHTS BACK ON?
UH, SURE.
("CAPITAN WHO" THEME SONG PLAYS)
(SMOKE HISSES)
SORRY. UM?
(COUGHS)
MR. ARMSTRONG:
OKAY, EVERYBODY LEAVE
YOUR EXAMS ON THE TABLE
WE NEED TO CLEAR THIS ROOM
UNTIL WE FIGURE THIS OUT.
LET'S GO.
MILES:
"ONE SMALL STEP FOR MAN,
ONE GIANT LEAP FOR MANKIND."
(BIG SPLASH)
WINSTON:
I DON'T THINK THAT'S
WHAT JFK HAD IN MIND.
FRANKIE:
YOU MEAN NEIL ARMSTRONG.
WINSTON:
THERE GOES MY 'B' IN HISTORY.
FRANKIE:
LOOK ON THE BRIGHT SIDE,
AT LEAST YOU'RE NOT STILL
AT SCHOOL WRITING AN EXAM
BECAUSE SOME GOOF FILLED
THE GYM WITH SMOKE.
MILES:
YES. INSTEAD, YOU'RE ABOUT
TO ENTER A CHICKEN FIGHT.
I BET ZOE AND I CAN TAKE
YOU AND FRANKENSTEIN.
FRANKIE:
WE ACCEPT THAT CHALLENGE.
WAIT. WAIT.
ARLENE NEEDS A PARTNER!
MILES: HUNTER - INTO THE WATER.
HUNTER: I'M GOOD. THANKS.
MILES:
COME ON, PUT DOWN
YOUR FUN SHIELD.
HUNTER:
STOP. YOUR HANDS ARE WET!
MILES:
LOOK, ARLENE NEEDS A PARTNER.
SEE? SHE LIKES YOU.
HUNTER:
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
MILES:
I KNOW YOU'RE HANGING OUT
ONLINE LIKE A LOSER
WHEN THE GIRL YOU'RE INTO
IS SITTING OVER THERE.
HUNTER:
GIVE IT BACK! MILES!
MILES GIVE IT BACK!
(SPLASH)
WINSTON:
NERD OVERBOARD!
MILES:
CALL TECH SUPPORT. I THINK
HE MIGHT HAVE FRIED HIS
MOTHERBOARD!
(CHUCKLING)
HUNTER:
WHAT IS YOUR PROBLEM?!
WHY CAN'T YOU
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE?
MILES:
COME ON, HUNTER,
WE'RE JUST JOKING AROUND.
MR. ARMSTRONG:
PENCILS DOWN!
CONGRATULATIONS ON COMPLETING
YOUR FINAL EXAM.
AND ONLY THREE HOURS LATER
THAN SCHEDULED
THANKS TO GOOD OLD
PRINCE CHARMING.
DALLAS:
HEY. DON'T BE MAD.
DREW:
WHAT? THAT YOU PUSHED ME
TO PROMPOSE
SO YOU WOULDN'T FEEL BAD ABOUT
DITCHING ME ON PROM NIGHT?
DALLAS:
I THOUGHT SHE'D SAY YES.
MAYBE I'LL JUST SKIP PROM.
YOU'RE SERIOUS?
DREW:
SITTING BY MYSELF IS JUST GONNA
REMIND OF EVERYTHING I'VE LOST
THIS YEAR.
AND I DON'T WANNA BUM
EVERYONE OUT.
DALLAS:
YOU KNOW WHAT?
SCREW THE GIRLS.
YOU'RE COMING IN OUR LIMO.
DREW: REALLY?
DALLAS:
AND YOU'RE SITTING
AT OUR TABLE, TOO.
AND IF ALLI DOESN'T LIKE IT,
I WILL -
TRY VERY HARD TO STAND UP
TO HER.
THAT'S GOOD ENOUGH FOR ME, MAN.
THIS NIGHT IS GONNA BE AWESOME!
DALLAS:
WE'RE GONNA MAKE MEMORIES
THAT LAST A LIFETIME.
DREW:
OOH! THAT'S ALL I WANTED.
MS. PILL:
(CLEARS HER THROAT)
MR. TORRES, I HEARD ABOUT
YOUR PROMPOSAL STUNT.
DREW:
YES, MS. PILL. I-I'M SORRY.
IT WAS SO STUPID.
MS. PILL:
AND IRRESPONSIBLE.
AND DANGEROUS.
THIS ACT CAN'T GO UNPUNISHED.
DREW:
O-KAY, UM, BUT SCHOOL'S OUT.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
BAN ME FROM PROM?
MS. PILL:
SOUNDS FAIR TO ME.
THAT- THAT WAS A JOKE.
ALLI:
OKAY, SO THE BOAT BOARDS
AT FOUR AND LEAVES THE DOCK
AT FIVE SHARP.
WE'LL TAKE THE FAVOURS
IN THE LIMO WITH US.
YOU GUYS WILL TAKE
THE CENTRE PIECES.
AND THE CATERING COMPANY
WILL DELIVER THE FOOD
TO THE DOCK.
CLARE:
WHAT ABOUT THESE TWINKLY
LIGHTS?
ALLI:
THEY STAY HERE.
UM, AM I FORGETTING
ANY IMPORTANT DETAILS?
DREW:
OH, YOU MEAN LIKE ME?
ALLI:
DREW, I TRIED TO CONVINCE
PILL TO LET YOU COME.
SHE WOULDN'T BUDGE.
DALLAS:
COME ON, THERE IS GOTTA BE
SOMETHING ELSE WE CAN DO
FOR MY BOY.
LIKE WHAT?
THREATEN TO BOYCOTT PROM?
DREW:
OH. YOU WOULD DO THAT FOR ME?
JENNA:
HE'S KIDDING, RIGHT?
CONNOR:
I'VE ALREADY RENTED MY TUXEDO
AND MY DEPOSIT IS NON
REFUNDABLE.
DREW:
WHAT ABOUT ALTERNATIVE PROM?
WE COULD HANG OUT
IN MY BACKYARD.
AT LEAST WE'D STILL
ALL BE TOGETHER.
CONNOR:
CAN I STILL WEAR MY TUXEDO?
DREW: YEAH. ABSOLUTELY...
ALLI: NOT!
I SPENT THE ENTIRE YEAR MAKING
THIS NIGHT MEMORABLE FOR THE
ENTIRE CLASS.
AND WE ARE NOT SKIPPING IT.
(PHONE CHIRPS, BUZZES)
OKAY. WELL, WE HAVE TO GO
TO OUR HAIR AND MAKE-UP
APPOINTMENTS!
JENNA:
OH MY GOD, YOU GUYS!
I CANNOT BELIEVE PROM
IS ACTUALLY HAPPENING?!
DALLAS:
I'M SORRY HOW THIS TURNED OUT.
DREW:
YOU CAN MAKE IT UP TO ME BY
SNEAKING ME ONTO THE BOAT.
DALLAS:
I CAN'T. MS. PILL'S FIRST NAME
ISN'T CHILL.
IF WE GET CAUGHT, WE COULD RUIN
THE PROM FOR EVERYONE ELSE.
DREW:
YOU MEAN I'LL RUIN IT
FOR THE PERSON
WHO HUMILIATED ME
IN THE GYM, YESTERDAY?
OR THE PERSON WHO WRECKED MY
SENIOR YEAR WITH A BABY SCARE?
DALLAS:
I MEAN YOU'LL RUIN IT
FOR YOUR FRIENDS,
AND YOUR BEST FRIEND WHO HELPED
YOU THROUGH THIS YEAR.
DREW:
OH! YOU MEAN THE ONE WHO KICKED
ME OUT OF HIS LIMO
FOR A GIRL WHO'S PROBABLY
JUST GONNA DUMP HIM AFTER
HE GRADUATES?
DALLAS:
YOU'RE OUT OF LINE.
DREW:
NO MAN! IT'S TRUE!
ALL RIGHT! WHO'S GONNA BE
AT YOUR WEDDING?
NOT HER. ME!
BEST MAN!
NOT ANYMORE!
DREW:
DALLAS, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
OH. I'M GETTING READY TO
CELEBRATE MY LAST NIGHT
WITH ALL OF MY FRIENDS.
(SIGHS)
MILES:
GOOD MORNING, FRANKENSTEIN.
HAVE YOU SEEN OUR BROTHER?
THOUGHT WE COULD GO
PAINT BALLING.
(SMIRKS)
WHAT?
FRANKIE:
FREAKING OUT, AND THEN TRYING
TO MAKE IT UP WITH GIFTS?
NICE ONE, DAD.
MILES: JUST TELL ME
WHERE HE IS.
FRANKIE: I DON'T KNOW.
HE WASN'T IN HIS ROOM
THIS MORNING WHEN I GOT UP.
YOU DON'T THINK
HE'D RUN AWAY?
ONLY IF HE FOUND
A PLACE WITH WIFI.
(SMALL CHUCKLE)
♪ I will remember ♪
CLARE:
I KNOW WE'VE BEEN
TO PROMS BEFORE,
BUT THIS ONE FEELS DIFFERENT,
YOU KNOW?
JENNA:
YEAH, BECAUSE IT'S OUR PROM.
(SIGHS)
I'M NOT FEELING THIS CLUTCH.
CAN I BORROW THAT BLACK SPARKLY
ONE OF YOURS?
YEAH SURE.
CLOSET, LEFT HAND SIDE.
CAN YOU CHECK MY BOW?
JENNA:
YES.
(LOUD CRASH)
ALLI:
NO CLUTCH, JUST DOZENS
AND DOZENS OF-
JENNA:
DIARIES!
CLARE:
NO! NO! NO! NO NEED TO LOOK
AT ANY OF THOSE!
ALLI:
"HIGH SCHOOL IS BOTH TUMULTUOUS
AND EXHILARATING."
JENNA: (LAUGHS)
CLARE: PLEASE...
THOSE ARE SOME TEN DOLLAR
WORDS, GRADE NINE CLARE!
ALLI:
"AM I THE ONLY ONE WHO IS
CONCERNED ABOUT MY ACADEMIC
FUTURE.
ALLI'S TOO BUSY BEING
BOY CRAZY.
I THOUGHT DATING A CERTAIN
LONG-HAIRED CRETIN
WOULD HAVE TAUGHT HER BETTER,
BUT APPARENTLY NOT."
JENNA:
OH SNAP!
ALLI:
TO BE FAIR,
JOHNNY'S HAIR WAS TERRIBLE.
CLARE: JENNA DON'T!
JENNA: OH LOOK...
"I BET BOYFRIEND STEALING
JENNA IS GOING TO FIND HERSELF
PREGNANT
WITH KC'S BABY IN NO TIME."
ALLI:
WELL, YOU KIND OF DID.
"HOW ARE YOU SUPPOSED
TO GET INTO ALL THE IVYS
AND GET TO BE VALEDICTORIAN
IF YOU SPEND ALL YOUR TIME
BEING A BOY CRAZY IDIOT?
I'LL NEVER LET A GUY GET
IN THE WAY OF MY DREAMS."
(THEY GIGGLE,
CAR HONKS OUTSIDE)
JENNA:
OH, LIMO'S HERE!
ALLI:
WE HAVE LIFETIME MEMORIES
TO MAKE.
CAN'T WAIT!
♪ I will remember ♪
♪ Every time we said
it would last forever ♪
♪ I will remeber ♪
ALLI:
OKAY! GROUP SELFIE!
YOU HAVE THE LONGEST ARMS.
CONNOR:
FINE, ALTHOUGH THIS TECHNICALLY
ISN'T A SELFIE AT ALL.
MORE ACCURATE TERM WOULD BE
A "GROUPIE" SINCE THE PHOTOGRAPH
OF ALL OF US-
JENNA:
SHHH, SWEETIE, IT'S OKAY.
CONNOR:
OKAY. OKAY.
ALLI:
CUTE!
ELI:
YOU LOOK ABSOLUTELY BEAUTIFUL,
AS ALWAYS.
CLARE:
THANKS. LOOK,
CAN WE TALK FOR A SECOND?
ELI:
OKAY. UH, ME FIRST.
EVERYONE, IF I COULD HAVE YOUR
ATTENTION FOR JUST A MOMENT.
CLARE, YOU'RE THE LOVE
OF MY LIFE.
AND WE'VE BEEN THROUGH A LOT,
BUT I KNOW WE'RE MEANT TO BE.
SO THAT'S IS WHY...
ALLI: OH MY GOD.
JENNA: OH MY GOD.
CLARE: OH MY GOD.
ELI:
I WANT TO ASK IF YOU
WOULD DO ME THE HONOUR...
OF MOVING IN WITH ME.
(RELIEVED SIGHS)
HAD YOU GOING THERE,
DIDN'T I?
ALLI: YOU CERTAINLY HAD ME!
CLARE: ELI...
ELI:
C'MON, I WAS JUST JOKING
AROUND.
LAST YEAR, I BROUGHT YOU
A HORSE AND CARRIAGE.
I HAD TO DO SOMETHING.
CLARE:
I'M NOT GOING TO FOLLOW YOU
TO NEW YORK.
THAT CAN'T BE MY PLAN.
THEN WHAT IS?
I DON'T KNOW.
(BOX SNAPS SHUT)
♪♪
MILES:
HELLO!
THERE YOU ARE.
I THOUGHT YOU RAN AWAY.
HUNTER:
I TRIED. BUT DAD SAID MOVING
IN WITH HIM
VIOLATES THE TERMS OF HIS
SEPARATION AGREEMENT WITH MOM.
MILES:
WHY WOULD YOU WANNA LIVE
WITH THAT JERK?
HUNTER:
BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT THERE.
MILES:
OKAY, WHAT IS YOUR PROBLEM?
HUNTER:
YOU. BUT YOU WON'T BE
MUCH LONGER.
WOW, HUNTER. THIS IS WEIRD.
EVEN FOR YOU.
HUNTER:
TAKE THE KENDO STICK.
WE'RE GONNA DUEL.
AND IF I WIN,
YOU NEVER TALK TO ME AGAIN.
OKAY. FINE.
BUT IF I WIN, YOU HAVE TO SMILE
ONCE A DAY FOR THE NEXT MONTH.
(LOUD SMACK)
(STICK SMACKS)
(LOUD SMACKS)
OW!
YA!
(LOUD SMACK,
STICK CLATTERS)
GO AHEAD.
I DESERVE IT.
HUNTER:
NO. I'M NOT YOU.
I'M NOT A BULLY.
MILES:
NEITHER AM I.
HUNTER:
ARE YOU KIDDING?
YOU MAKE FUN OF EVERYTHING
I DO.
YOU PUSH ME TO DO THINGS
I DON'T WANT TO DO.
PLUS, YOU WALK AROUND WITH A
BIG, STUPID GRIN ON YOUR FACE
WHEN YOU MAKE ME MISERABLE!
I HATE YOU!
MILES:
SO YOU'D RATHER LIVE WITH HIM?
HUNTER:
AT LEAST HE USED
TO RUN INTERFERENCE.
I KNOW HE WASN'T PERFECT.
BUT I MISS HIM.
THAT'S MY DAD.
MILES:
I GET THAT THINGS HAVE BEEN
WEIRD FOR YOU SINCE HE LEFT,
BUT I WANT TO MAKE IT BETTER.
HUNTER:
FIND ME A DIFFERENT BROTHER.
MILES:
MAYBE I COULD BE ONE.
I KNOW I CAN'T TAKE DAD'S
PLACE, BUT I CAN TRY.
HUNTER:
OKAY.
ARE YOU HUGGING ME
RIGHT NOW?
MILES:
HEY, YOU WANTED ME
TO BE DIFFERENT.
NOW, CAN YOU PUT
THE SWORD DOWN?
(SWORD CLATTERS)
JENNA:
OH... WHERE IS THE BOAT?
DALLAS:
SHOULD BE HERE ANY MINUTE!
I HAVE A PROGRAM
TO KEEP YOU BUSY?
ALLI:
SERIOUSLY? I'M ABOUT TO HAVE
200 PEOPLE WHO'VE BOUGHT
TICKETS,
TUXES AND DRESSES,
BREATHING DOWN MY NECK
AND YOU'RE TELLING ME
THERE'S NO BOAT?
THIS COULD BE PEOPLE'S
LAST NIGHT TOGETHER!
AND THEY'VE INVESTED A LOT
TO MAKE SURE IT'S PERFECT!
HOW CAN YOU NOT HAVE
OUR BOOKING?
YES, I'LL HOLD.
YOU HAVE THE BOAT BOOKING.
RIGHT?
DALLAS:
YEAH. I HAVE AN EMAIL!
I KNOW HOW IMPORTANT THIS
IS FOR YOU. FOR US.
ALLI:
SEE, I HAVE THE CONFIRMATION
EMAIL FROM YOU RIGHT HERE.
IT SAYS JUNE 27TH ...
OF NEXT YEAR.
DALLAS:
WHAT?!
ALLI:
AND THERE'S NOTHING YOU CAN DO?
PERFECT.
YOU MESSED UP THE YEAR?!
HOW COULD YOU MESS UP THE YEAR?!
DALLAS:
WHY WOULD THEY LET PEOPLE
BOOK MORE THAN A YEAR OUT!
CLARE:
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
JENNA:
YEAH, WHERE'S THE BOAT?
MY SEA LEGS ARE READY!
CONNOR:
AND SOME OF US ARE HUNGRY.
DALLAS:
I AM SO SORRY.
ALLI:
FOR RUINING THE MOST IMPORTANT
NIGHT OF OUR LIVES!
DALLAS:
LET ME MAKE THIS UP TO YOU.
JUST TELL ME WHAT TO DO.
ALLI:
YOU CAN EVERYONE
THAT YOU RUINED PROM!
(HUFFS)
(SIGHS)
THERE'S NO FREAKIN' BOAT!
BECKY:
OKAY. WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
HOME... TO EAT A FEW PIZZAS!
COME ON, CRAZY PANTS.
PROM IS SUPPOSED TO BE THE MOST
MAGICAL NIGHT OF OUT LIFE.
EXCEPT THERE IS NO BOAT!
SO WE CAN STILL MAKE OUR OWN
MEMORIES.
LET'S ALL GO SKINNY DIPPING
OR STREAKING?
WAIT? HOW COME EVERYTHING
THEY DO IN TEEN MOVIES
INVOLVES GETTING NAKED?
YEAH. I DON'T REALLY FEEL LIKE
DOING ANY OF THAT?
HEY SAD SACK,
WHAT'S UP?
JACK AND I BROKE UP BECAUSE
OF PROM REMEMBER?
I'M PRETTY SURE THERE IS SOME
OTHER STUFF IN THERE TOO.
YEAH, BUT NOW THERE IS NO PROM
AND NO JACK.
WHAT IF WE WERE MEANT TO BE AND
I MESSED IT ALL UP FOR THIS.
OKAY, COME WITH ME.
ARE WE GONNA EAT PIZZA
BECAUSE FAIR WARNING,
I'M GETTING THE ONE WITH
THE FRENCH FRIES ON IT.
NO, WE'RE GOING TO JACKS HOUSE.
WHAT? WHY?
SO YOU CAN TELL HER
HOW YOU FEEL!
COME ON, MARINO, IF WE'RE NOT
GONNA SKINNY DIP OR STREAK,
THE NEST TEEN MOVIE THING
WE CAN DO
IS MARCH OVER TO THE EX'S HOUSE
AND PUT YOUR HEART ON THE LINE.
OKAY. LET'S DO THIS.
(BECKY CHUCKLES)
DUDE, I NEED YOUR HELP.
THE BOAT DIDN'T SHOW UP.
DREW:
(LAUGHS) I KNOW.
I KNOW.
I'M FOLLOWING IT ON FACERANGE.
LISTEN TO THIS,
THIS IS MY FAVOURITE.
THIS PROM REMINDS ME
OF A DEFLATED BALLOON.
(LAUGHS)
BUT I HAVE A QUESTION FOR YOU...
DID IT SINK?
PLEASE TELL ME THE BOAT SANK.
NO, I CONFIRMED IT
FOR THE WRONG YEAR.
(LAUGHS)
YOU HAVE TO HELP ME FIX THIS.
DREW:
OH, DO I?
DALLAS:
YOU'RE GONNA LET THE WHOLE
SCHOOL DOWN BECAUSE YOU'RE
MAD AT ME?
YOU'RE THE PRESIDENT.
YOU'RE THE KING OF GETTING
OUT OF STICKY SITUATIONS.
I CAN'T DO THIS WITHOUT YOU.
YEAH. NOT SO FUN WHEN YOUR
"BRO" WON'T HELP, IS IT?
OW! WHAT WAS THAT FOR?!
AUDRA:
HELP DALLAS!
HE'S LEAVING.
WELL, HE MADE IT PRETTY CLEAR
HE DOESN'T WANNA BE MY FRIEND.
YEAH, WELL, WITH THAT ATTITUDE,
I WOULDN'T WANT TO BE EITHER.
DO YOU REALLY WANT YOUR MEMORY
OF PROM NIGHT
TO BE BARBEQUE WITH YOUR MOM?
(SIGHS)
HEY, I MAY HAVE A PLAN.