VINCE:
OKAY BOYS, REMEMBER:
DO NOT TAKE MOSS STREET.
AND?
WALK IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE STREET,
DON'T LINGER,
DON'T LOOK LIKE A THREAT.
THIS IS DUMB!
DAMON'S GUYS ARE THREATENING
US AND WE'RE RUNNING SCARED!
I'M TRYING TO PROTECT YOU!
WE SHOULDN'T NEED PROTECTING,
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO SHOT HIM!
WATCH YOURSELF!
ZIG:
I'M SORRY, I'M JUST...
VINCE:
I GET IT, BUT WE ALL NEED
TO KEEP IT TOGETHER.
YOU DON'T THINK ALL THAT
CHATTER ONLINE'S JUST FRONTING?
VINCE:
MAYBE, MAYBE NOT.
WE NEED TO LAY LOW.
THEY'RE THREATENING MAYA!
OKAY, WE SHOULD BE
STEPPING UP TO THEM!
DON'T BE AN IDIOT!
YOU WANNA GET YOURSELF
IN EVEN MORE TROUBLE?!
TINY:
WHAT IF THEY TRY SOMETHING
AT SCHOOL?
I MEAN, WE GO TO CLASSES
WITH A BUNCH OF THESE GUYS.
VINCE:
WE JUST NEED TO BE COOL,
AND SEE HOW THIS PLAYS OUT,
CAN YOU DO THAT?
NOW GET GOING, YOU'RE GOING
TO BE LATE FOR CLASS.
I'LL SEE YOU AT THE MUSICAL
TONIGHT.
ZIG: YOU'RE COMING?
VINCE: DAMN STRAIGHT!
NO WAY I'M LETTING SOME PUNKS
AND THEIR THREATS
MAKE ME MISS MY BOY'S
BIG STAGE DEBUT!
WOW, THANKS.
REMEMBER,
KEEP YOURSELF IN CHECK.
GOT IT?
YEAH.
YEAH, I GOT IT.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Ohh... ohh... ohh... ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
DAMON:
YOU BACK HERE TO ACCUSE ME
OF ROBBING A BANK OR SOMETHING?
SO DID YOU EVER FIND OUT
WHO DID TAKE YOUR MONEY?
WHAT'S HE TALKING ABOUT?
NEVER MIND, IT'S NOTHING.
USUALLY IT'S THE PEOPLE
YOU TRUST THE MOST.
YOU KNOW, MOM, DAD.
THE BOYFRIEND.
NO, HE'S NOT MY BOYFRIEND.
DID SOMEBODY STEAL FROM YOU?
YES, AND IT WAS PROBABLY
JONAH, OKAY?
SO CONGRATULATIONS,
YOU WERE RIGHT,
MY BOYFRIEND'S A BIG LIAR!
NO, BECKY-
GET OUT OF MY FACE,
I DON'T WANNA TALK ABOUT IT.
YEAH, WHATEVER YOU WANT.
YOUR BOYFRIEND, HUH?
THAT'S ROUGH.
WHY WOULD ONE GUY BE GIVING
ANOTHER GUY MONEY
IN A NOT SO FRIENDLY SITUATION?
DAMON: DRUGS.
BECKY: BUT HE'S STRAIGHT EDGE!
SOMETIMES GOOD PEOPLE
GET IN BAD SPOTS.
THAT DOESN'T MEAN YOU SHOULD
GIVE UP ON THEM, RIGHT?
HMM... OH HEY,
DO YOU THINK YOU COULD DO ME
A FAVOUR?
YEAH, SURE.
DO YOU HAVE YOUR CELL PHONE?
I NEED YOU TO SEND
SOMEONE A MESSAGE.
YOU'RE TELLING ME A BUNCH
OF GANGSTERS ARE GONNA COME
AND SHOOT UP "CAPTAIN WHO?!"
NO, BUT WE DO NEED TO TAKE
SOME EXTRA PRECAUTIONS.
ESPECIALLY SINCE ONE OF THE
STUDENTS WE'RE CONCERNED ABOUT
IS INVOLVED IN THE MUSICAL.
IMOGEN:
OH MY GOD! I KNEW HUNTER
WAS WEIRD, BUT I DIDN'T-
NOT HUNTER, ZIG.
REMEMBER,
THESE ARE KIDS LIKE YOU.
THEY'VE JUST HAD A ROUGHER
GO OF THINGS.
BUT THE MUSICAL'S STILL
GONNA HAPPEN, RIGHT?
MS. PILL:
I HAVEN'T DECIDED YET.
TINY:
ZIG, DON'T,
REMEMBER WHAT VINCE SAID.
WE CAN'T CANCEL IT,
WE'VE WORKED SO HARD ON IT!
WE'LL INCREASE SECURITY,
AND THERE WILL BE
A POLICE PRESENCE.
I'M JUST GONNA TALK TO HIM,
ALL RIGHT?
SEE YOU IN THERE.
MS. PILL:
BUT WE DEFINITELY CAN'T PROCEED
IF IT'S GONNA PUT STUDENTS
IN DANGER.
YOU NEED TO BE VIGILANT,
AND COME TO ME
IF YOU HEAR ANYTHING.
YES, ABSOLUTELY.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
WE'LL CATCH HIM AFTER SCHOOL.
CAN I HELP YOU WITH SOMETHING?!
ZIG:
YOU NEED TO STAY AWAY.
FROM ME, FROM MAYA,
AND THE MUSICAL.
WE'RE JUST TRYING
TO LIVE OUR LIVES.
JASON:
OH YEAH, AND WHAT WAS DAMON
DOING WHEN YOUR BOY SHOT HIM?
HE WAS WASHING THE GODDAMN
DISHES!
DAMON WASN'T INNOCENT.
ALL RIGHT, YOU KNOW WHAT
HE DID TO TINY!
JASON:
AND I KNOW WHAT
I'M GONNA DO TO YOU!
AND THAT LITTLE BLONDE
OF YOURS.
YOU THINK YOU CAN JUST
THREATEN MY GIRLFRIEND,
AND THERE WON'T BE
ANY CONSEQUENCES?!
MAYA:
ZIG!
AW, LOOK AT THIS!
OUR BOY'S WHIPPED!
WELL, HOW ABOUT THIS,
GO UP ON STAGE TONIGHT,
DO YOUR SONG AND DANCE,
AND THEN WE CAN DEAL
WITH THIS AFTERWARDS.
(BELL RINGS)
WHAT WAS THAT?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
YOU SAID EVERYTHING
WAS UNDER CONTROL.
IT'S NOT!
DAMON'S GUYS
ARE COMING FOR US.
BECAUSE VINCE SHOT HIM?
WHY ARE YOU PROTECTING HIM?
I'M PROTECTING YOU TOO, MAYA!
I'M OUT OF OPTIONS!
YOU ALWAYS HAVE OPTIONS,
YOU COULD DO THE RIGHT THING.
YOU COULD GO TO THE COPS!
I ALREADY TOLD YOU, I CAN'T!
I THOUGHT YOU UNDERSTOOD THAT!
MAYA:
WHEN'S IT GONNA STOP, ZIG?
MAYA: WHEN YOU'RE ALL DEAD?!
ZIG: I CAN'T STEP DOWN!
MAYA:
THEN I CAN'T LISTEN
TO THIS ANYMORE!
♪♪
ZOE AND WINSTON:
♪ All my life ♪
♪ I've been searching
For someone like you ♪
♪ Show me who you are ♪
(SIGHS) I'M...
SIMON?
NO, NO, NO, NO!
(GROANS)
I CAN'T DO IT.
OKAY,
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?!
ARE YOU'RE WORRIED THAT YOU'LL
GET EXCITED, OR SOMETHING?
WHAT? NO!
I JUST CAN'T KISS SOMEONE
WHO ISN'T FRANKIE.
WELL, YOU DIDN'T SEEM TO HAVE
THAT PROBLEM WITH LOLA.
OH MY GOD,
DOES EVERYONE KNOW?
YES. ANYWAY, THIS IS DIFFERENT,
IT'S PROFESSIONAL.
BUT I DON'T WANNA DO THIS
IF IT'S NOT WITH FRANKIE.
EVEN THOUGH I'M TOTALLY ANNOYED
AT HER FOR BAILING LAST MINUTE.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD GO
A LITTLE EASY ON HER.
WHY, SHE'S BEING CRAZY!
IT'S REALLY HARD WATCHING
YOUR PARENTS SPLIT UP.
DO I REALLY HAVE
TO EXPLAIN EVERYTHING?!
WINSTON:
YES.
SHE TRUSTED HER DAD,
AND HE BETRAYED THEIR
ENTIRE FAMILY,
SHE'S WORRIED THAT
IF SHE TRUSTS YOU AGAIN,
SHE'LL GET HURT AGAIN.
BUT I'M NOTHING LIKE
THAT GARBAGE DUDE!
THEN YOU NEED TO FIND
A WAY TO SHOW HER THAT.
OR ELSE YOU'LL BE STUCK
KISSING ME.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(PLAYING SLOW,
MELODIOUS SONG)
I SAW YOU, I SAW YOU GIVE
ZIG THAT MONEY!
THE MONEY YOU STOLE FROM ME!
I WAS REALLY HOPING YOU'D START
DENYING IT RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
WELL, I CAN'T,
BECAUSE IT'S TRUE.
YOU STOLE FROM ME?!
I OWED SOMEONE MONEY,
AND I WAS SCARED
OF WHAT THEY'D DO
IF I DIDN'T PAY.
THEY WERE STARTING
TO THREATEN ME.
OWED THEM MONEY FOR DRUGS?
TELL ME THE TRUTH!
YES.
BUT YOU'RE STRAIGHT EDGE.
I AM NOW, OKAY?
IT'S AN OLD DEBT,
FROM WHEN I WAS MESSED UP,
BEFORE I EVER MET YOU.
WHY DIDN'T YOU JUST ASK ME?
I WOULD'VE LENT YOU THE MONEY!
I DIDN'T WANT YOU TO SEE
THAT SIDE OF ME.
(SIGHS)
(ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS)
FRANKS, IT'S ME.
THIS ISN'T SOMETHING
I CAN REALLY TEXT, SO...
(SIGHS)
I TRIED TO KISS ZOE
BUT I COULDN'T,
BECAUSE I WROTE
"CAPTAIN WHO" FOR YOU,
AND THERE'S NO POINT IN THIS
MUSICAL EVEN HAPPENING
IF YOU'RE NOT IN IT.
I'M SORRY, OKAY,
FOR ALL THE WAYS IN WHICH
I DISAPPOINTED YOU,
BUT PLEASE COME BACK!
IF NOT FOR ME,
THEN FOR THE MUSICAL.
WE'VE WORKED SO HARD,
AND IF YOU'RE NOT ELLA,
THEN NONE OF IT
WILL BE WORTH IT.
I'M BEGGING YOU, FRANKIE.
PLEASE.
(ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS,
PHONE CUTS OFF)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
WHOA, NOVAK,
ARE YOU OKAY?
NOT EVEN A LITTLE.
WHAT'S WRONG?
EVERYTHING!
EVERYTHING IS WRONG,
AND NO MATTER WHAT I DO,
I JUST MAKE THINGS WORSE.
DAMON'S GUYS ARE STILL
AFTER YOU.
MAYA DOESN'T UNDERSTAND THAT
WE NEED TO STEP UP TO THEM.
LOOK, THEY'RE THREATENING HER,
AND EVERYONE IN THE MUSICAL.
LIKE, WHAT ELSE
AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?!
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
THAT'S WEIRD, A VIDEO TEXT
FROM BECKY BAKER?
THE ANNOYING BLONDE?
DAMON:
UM, THANKS TO MY HELPFUL
VOLUNTEER,
FOR SENDING YOU THIS MESSAGE.
ZIG, WE USED TO BE FRIENDS.
HOW DID WE GET CAUGHT UP
IN THIS STUPID CRAP?
REMEMBER WHEN WE USED TO RIDE
OUR BIKES DOWN TO THAT DINER,
AND EACH ORDER TWO
CHEESEBURGERS, NO ONIONS?
NOW WE'RE ON OPPOSITE SIDES
OF THIS STUPID WAR.
I GOT SHOT,
I COULD'VE DIED.
MAYBE NEXT TIME I WILL.
I SHOULD'VE LISTENED TO YOU
WHEN YOU TRIED TO WARN ME.
SO I GUESS NOW I'M WARNING YOU.
BE CAREFUL,
AND GET THE HELL OUT,
NO MATTER WHAT IT TAKES.
ANYWAY... BE GOOD, BROTHER.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
TO FIX THIS.
AND YOU'RE SURE IT WAS VINCENT
BELL WHO SHOT DAMON CARTER?
ZIG: YEAH.
DETECTIVE TAYLOR: AND DEON?
TINY HAD NOTHING
TO DO WITH IT.
OKAY.
AND YOU SAY VINCENT'S
COMING TO DEGRASSI TONIGHT?
UH, YEAH.
HE'S COMING TO SEE ME
IN THE MUSICAL.
LOOK, YOUR HELP IS GOING
TO GO A LONG WAY
TOWARDS KEEPING PEOPLE SAFE.
ZIG:
WHAT ABOUT THE OTHER GUYS?
THE ONES THREATENING US ONLINE?
I'M WORKING WITH YOUR PRINCIPAL
TO MAINTAIN A POLICE PRESENCE,
BUT USUALLY ONCE WE MAKE
ONE ARREST, THINGS DIE DOWN.
OKAY.
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN TO ME?
AM I GONNA GO TO JAIL?
I HOPE NOT. YOUR COOPERATION IS
GOING TO WORK IN YOUR FAVOUR,
I GOTTA PUT IN A GOOD
WORD FOR YOU,
BUT I CAN'T PROMISE ANYTHING.
(BELL RINGS)
I'M SURE YOU HAVE TO GO
GET READY FOR SHOW TIME.
I CAN STILL DO THAT?
WELL, WE DON'T WANNA RAISE
ANY SUSPICIONS.
IT'S VERY IMPORTANT YOU
DON'T TELL ANYONE WE SPOKE,
UNDERSTAND?
YEAH.
OKAY.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
(PREPARATORY EXHALE)
AND, LIGHTS!
♪♪
♪ Oh my god, could it be? ♪
♪ I don't believe it's true! ♪
♪ An incredible discovery ♪
♪ Eureka! ♪
♪ I've found it! ♪
♪ Ella! I've found it! ♪
♪ Ella! ♪
♪ You don't have to yell,
Simon! ♪
♪ I can hear you just fine! ♪
♪ You'll never believe it!
Eureka! ♪
♪ You found it? ♪
♪ I found it! ♪
WINSTON: YOU CAME!
FRANKIE: I CAME.
♪ An incredible discovery! ♪
MAYA, I AM SO SORRY.
OH, DON'T! YOU'RE HERE,
WE'RE TOGETHER.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
A LITTLE PRE-PERFORMANCE
ACTION!
I LIKE IT!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING BACK HERE?
T'S SAVING SEATS
IN THE FRONT ROW.
I JUST WANTED TO WISH
MY BOY GOOD LUCK.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THAT.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
THIS IS A SPECIAL OCCASION,
I'M PROUD OF YOU, ZIG.
VINCENT, I NEED YOU
TO COME WITH US, PLEASE.
NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN,
DETECTIVE TAYLOR.
BREAK A LEG OUT THERE.
I FEEL LIKE I'M GONNA THROW UP.
ZIG, YOU'RE ON!
♪ All my life... ♪
♪ I've been searching
For something like this ♪
♪ Ella Elliot, ♪
♪ I love you. ♪
WHAT DID YOU SAY, SIMON?
I, UH... LUCIUS!
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
♪ I'm the monster
Underneath your bed ♪
GIRL IN AUDIENCE:
WHOO!
♪ The creature lurking
in the dark ♪
♪ Better listen
to what your mama said ♪
♪ You know my bite is worse
Than my bark! ♪
♪ I'm the thing that goes bump
In the night ♪
♪ The thing that makes
your children cry ♪
♪ It's no use in putting
Up a fight ♪
♪ Say hello to the bad guy! ♪
♪ Say hello
To your biggest fear ♪
♪ Say hello to the bad guy! ♪
♪ You should believe
Everything you hear! ♪
FRANKIE:
HELP ME!
(AUDIENCE CLAPS AND CHEERS)
MAYA:
YEAH! WOO!
HEY, AREN'T YOU COMING
TO THE MUSICAL?
DREW: ARE YOU OKAY?
BECKY: NO.
DREW:
IT'S JONAH, ISN'T IT?
HE REALLY STEAL THAT MONEY
FROM YOU?
HE SAID IT WAS FOR
AN OLD DRUG DEBT.
DRUGS? REALLY?
I KNOW,
I WAS SO MAD,
I WAS READY TO BREAK UP
WITH HIM THEN AND THERE.
BUT THEN HE WAS STILL
THAT PERSON I CARE ABOUT.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
I DON'T KNOW, BECKY.
BUT YOU HATE JONAH,
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE LIKE,
"BREAK UP WITH HIM, ASAP!"
YEAH, THAT'S KINDA WHAT
I WANNA SAY, BUT...
THAT WOULDN'T MAKE ME
A VERY GOOD FRIEND.
SO YOU THINK I SHOULD GIVE
JONAH ANOTHER CHANCE?
(SIGHS)
I JUST WANT YOU
TO BE HAPPY.
THANKS, DREW.
YEAH, NO PROBLEM.
(SIGHS)
WINSTON: (GRUNTS)
ZIG: OOF!
(FIGHTING GRUNTS,
SHATTERING GLASS)
(PANTING)
(FIGHTING GRUNTS)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
WINSTON: HAAAA!
BECKY:
WERE YOU DOING DRUGS IN THERE?!
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
BECKY: DON'T SAY IT LIKE THAT!
JONAH: LIKE WHAT?
LIKE IT'S A CRAZY THING
FOR ME TO THINK!
BECKY, I AM NOT THAT GUY
ANYMORE, OKAY?
JONAH: I PROMISE.
BECKY: BUT HOW DO I KNOW THAT?
HOW DO I KNOW WHICH VERSION
OF YOU I CARE ABOUT,
AND WHICH VERSION STOLE
FROM ME, AND LIED ABOUT IT?
BECKY, I KNOW THAT
I AM FLAWED.
BUT I AM TRYING TO BE BETTER.
I NEED YOU.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
I'M SORRY.
JONAH: DON'T-
BECKY: I CAN'T.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(AUDIENCE CHEERS AND CLAPS)
MAYA:
YOU WERE SO AWESOME UP THERE!
YEAH, YEAH,
I KINDA WAS, WASN'T I?
I THINK EVERYTHING'S
GONNA BE OKAY.
YOU KNOW, I SAW COPS
INTERVIEWING PEOPLE,
AND SEARCHING LOCKERS.
THAT WAS THE HARDEST THING
I'VE EVER HAD TO DO.
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
TINY:
HOW COULD YOU DO THIS?
ZIG: TINY.
TINY: THEY ARRESTED VINCE,
YOU SNITCHED!
OKAY, LET'S TALK ABOUT THIS,
ALL RIGHT? BUT LET HER LEAVE.
SHE'S NOT GOING ANYWHERE!
ZIG:
LISTEN, EVERYTHING
IS GOING TO BE OKAY,
I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING
ABOUT YOU TO THE COPS,
THEY DON'T EVEN KNOW
YOU WERE THERE!
YOU DON'T GET IT!
VINCE IS GONE,
AND IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT!
MY DAD'S IN PRISON,
MY MOM'S SO HIGH
MOST OF THE TIME,
SHE BARELY REMEMBERS MY NAME!
VINCE WAS ALL I HAD.
HE TOOK CARE OF ME!
ZIG:
WELL...
YOU'RE NOT ALONE,
ALL RIGHT?
YOU'VE GOT ME.
THE GUY WHO RATTED
ON MY BROTHER!
BECAUSE HE SHOT A DUDE!
THE DUDE WHO STABBED ME!
ZIG:
AND NOW YOU'RE THE ONE
WITH THE KNIFE!
COME ON T,
YOU'RE NOT THIS PERSON.
MAYBE I AM BECAUSE NO MATTER
HOW HARD I TRY
TO GET AWAY FROM THIS MESS,
IT KEEPS FINDING ME!
AND HOW IS HURTING ME
OR MAYA GONNA FIX THAT?
I-I DON'T KNOW, I...
EXACTLY!
WE NEED TO STOP
THIS STUPID CYCLE.
AND WE CAN.
TOGETHER.
(TINY SOBS)
(CRYING)
♪ Once I know the real you ♪
♪ We can get out
of this place ♪
WINSTON AND FRANKIE:
♪ All my life... ♪
♪ I've been searching
For someone like you! ♪
♪ Show me who you are... ♪
I'M...
SIMON!
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO.
(LAUGHS)
(MUSIC SWELLS,
CROWD CHEERS, APPLAUSE)
YEAH, OKAY, BYE.
JOSE SAID THAT WE COULD
STAY WITH HIM FOR A WHILE.
SO WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN NOW?
HE'S GONNA DO SOME OF HIS
GANG-INTERVENING OR WHATEVER?
UH YEAH,
YEAH, I GUESS.
HE WANTS TO MAKE SURE THAT
WE FLY UNDER THE RADAR
WHILE WE COOPERATE
WITH THE COPS.
WAIT, YOU GUYS AREN'T
GETTING CHARGED, RIGHT?
WELL, THE DETECTIVE
SAID COOPERATING
WILL MAKE CUTTING
A DEAL EASIER, BUT...
BUT THERE ARE NO GUARANTEES.
IT WAS STILL THE RIGHT
THING TO DO.
WASN'T IT?
TINY:
YEAH.
IT WAS.
LISTEN MAN, I'M SORRY.
DON'T APOLOGIZE.
I GET IT.
LOOK BLONDIE, I-
I'LL BE OKAY, AS LONG
AS YOU GUYS WILL BE, TOO.
(SIGHS) YEAH.
WE WILL.
WE SHOULD HEAD TO JOSE'S.
YEAH... YEAH.
BUT I NEED TO STOP
SOMEWHERE FIRST.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDS AND CHEERS)
(LAUGHS)
THAT JOKE AT THE END
OF THE THIRD SCENE,
YOU GOT SO MANY LAUGHS!
WELL, THAT WAS NOTHING
COMPARED TO YOUR SOLO,
YOU TOTALLY KILLED IT!
HEY, UM...
THANKS FOR COMING THROUGH,
IT MEANT A LOT TO ME.
AND IF YOU WANT US TO GO
OUR SEPARATE WAYS, I-
WINSTON...
SHUT UP.
WHA-
(LAUGHS)
YOU GOT MY MESSAGE.
TWO CHEESEBURGERS, NO ONIONS.
(BOTH LAUGH)
WHAT, ARE YOU TRYING TO POISON
ME NOW, OR SOMETHING?
UH NO, I JUST THOUGHT
YOU MIGHT WANT-
I'M JUST MESSING WITH YOU.
(LAUGHS)
SO, UH...
THE COPS PICKED VINCE UP.
THEY THINK THE CHARGES'LL HOLD.
SO IT'S OVER?
FOR NOW.
WHAT, YOU GONNA MAKE ME
EAT BOTH OF THESE?
(LAUGHS)
THANKS FOR COMING.
YEAH.