BECKY:
AGH, ISN'T IT TOO LITTLE EARLY
FOR THAT?
IMOGEN:
NO! THERE ARE ONLY A FEW WEEKS
UNTIL GRADUATION!
JACK:
AND I HAVE TO SPEND THE REST OF
MY AFTER-SCHOOLS IN DETENTION.
BECKY:
GOOD!
I'M SORRY,
BUT YOU DESERVE IT.
YOU ALL DID OOMFCHAT
OUR BOOBS FOR MONEY.
IMOGEN:
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN, ANYWAY?
A WHOLE WEEK OFF
SO THEY COULD REPAIR THE SCHOOL
AFTER THE FIRE,
I DIDN'T SEE YOU ONCE!
JACK:
OH. I BET SHE WAS WITH JONAH.
YES, BUT WE WERE
JUST WRITING SONGS.
OKAY. MAYBE I HAVE
A GIANT CRUSH ON HIM,
BUT I'M NOT ACTING ON IT.
I JUST BROKE UP WITH DREW.
JONAH:
HEY.
JACK, IMOGEN:
HIIII JONAHHHHH.
(GIRLS GIGGLE)
BECKY:
WHAT THE HECK?
DREW:
CELL PHONES ARE NO LONGER
ALLOWED ON SCHOOL PROPERTY.
SO PLEASE PUT THEM IN THE BOX
AND YOU WILL GET THEM BACK
AT THE END OF THE DAY.
CLARE:
AND THEY'RE ALSO INSTALLING
SECURITY CAMERAS EVERYWHERE.
IT'S ALL PART OF THE NEW
PRINCIPAL'S CRACKDOWN.
BECKY: NEW PRINCIPAL?
JONAH: WHAT HAPPENED
TO SIMPSON?
CLARE:
I'M NOT SURE. SUSPENSION,
I THINK?
BUT HE'S OUT,
AND MS. PILL'S IN.
IMOGEN:
OH, SHUCKS.
I'M REALLY GONNA MISS THAT GUY.
MS. PILL:
AS YOUR NEW PRINCIPAL,
I AM COMMITTED TO MAKING
DEGRASSI A SAFE SPACE,
I'M ALSO INSTITUTING A BAN ON
PUBLIC DISPLAYS OF AFFECTION.
THIS INCLUDES HUGGING,
KISSING, AND HOLDING HANDS.
IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS
ABOUT THESE RULES
PLEASE SEE A TEACHER OR
A DESIGNATED HALL MONITOR.
YOU'LL KNOW WHO THEY ARE BASED
ON THEIR YELLOW CARDS ON THEIR
LANYARDS.
JACK:
THIS IS ALL VERY NINETEEN
EIGHTY-FOUR-BIG-BROTHER.
MS. PILL:
FINALLY, ALL EXTRA-CURRICULARS
HAVE TO BE APPROVED BY MYSELF
ALONG WITH STUDENT COUNCIL.
WE'LL BE HEARING THE FIRST SET
OF PROPOSALS TODAY AT LUNCH.
THANK YOU.
IMOGEN:
SO, WE'RE BASICALLY LIVING
UNDER A FASCIST REGIME
FOR THE LAST FEW WEEKS
OF HIGH SCHOOL. OH. GREAT.
BECKY:
RULES ARE IMPORTANT!
THEY KEEP US
FROM MAKING MISTAKES.
JACK:
HOW DO YOU THINK
THAT'S GONNA GO?
IMOGEN:
BECKY BAKER CAUGHT
BETWEEN TWO GUYS?
I HAVE NO EARTHLY IDEA.
♪ What ever it takes ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Oh-Oh-Oh... ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
MR. PERINO:
TAKE TIME TO FAMILIARIZE
YOURSELF
WITH THE NEW CODE OF CONDUCT,
PLEASE.
(BELL RINGS)
MAYA:
WHAT DO YOU THINK HAPPENED
TO MR. SIMPSON?
MILES:
MAYBE HE'S LYING
ON A BEACH SOMEWHERE.
TINY:
OR MAYBE THERE'S A RUBBER ROOM
FOR PRINCIPALS.
ZIG:
YEAH, WHERE THEY PUT YOU
IF YOUR STUDENTS
SEND NAKED PICTURES OR
TRY TO BURN THE SCHOOL DOWN.
WINSTON:
AND THIS NEW PRINCIPAL?
SHE'S A BITTER PILL TO SWALLOW,
AM I RIGHT?
TINY:
AW, THAT'S CUTE.
MILES' SIDEKICK IS TRYING
TO BE FUNNY.
WINSTON: HEY-
MILES: HE'S LOTS MORE
THAN MY SIDEKICK.
HE'S ALSO MY SISTER'S
BOYFRIEND, AND HE'S HILARIOUS.
ZIG:
AW, DID YOU HEAR THAT?
MILES' SISTER'S BOYFRIEND
IS HILARIOUS!
HEY, I'M JUST MESSING AROUND.
DON'T LET IT GET TO YOU.
WINSTON:
GET TO ME? NO WAY.
I LOVE BEING YOUR SIDEKICK.
BECKY:
WELL, WE'D LIKE TO HOST A
WEEKLY LUNCHTIME VARIETY SHOW
TO SHOWCASE ALL THE TALENT
AT THE SCHOOL.
MS. PILL:
ALL EXTRA-CURRICULARS NEED
A STAFF ADVISOR.
JONAH:
I ALREADY GOT ONE LINED UP.
BECKY:
WE THINK IT'S REALLY
IMPORTANT TO SHOWCASE
THE STUDENTS AT DEGRASSI
WHO ARE DOING THINGS RIGHT.
DREW:
AND IT WOULD BE JUST YOU TWO
DOING THE PLANNING TOGETHER?
JONAH:
YEAH. ABSOLUTELY.
WE'RE A TEAM.
DREW:
WHERE WOULD YOU DO
THIS PLANNING?
BECKY:
UM, PROBABLY MY HOUSE?
JONAH:
YEAH, WE DON'T REALLY WANNA
YOU KNOW,
LIKE GET ANYONE ELSE INVOLVED.
DREW: NOT EVEN YOUR GIRLFRIEND?
JONAH: I DON'T HAVE
A GIRLFRIEND.
MS. PILL:
AND I'M NOT SURE
THAT'S RELEVANT.
DREW:
I JUST NEED TO KNOW
IF JONAH IS EASILY DISTRACTED.
MS. PILL:
OKAY, LET'S MOVE ON
TO LOGISTICS.
BECKY:
UM, WE THOUGHT WE COULD HOLD IT
IN THE CAFETERIA,
THE SHOW WOULD START 15 MINUTES
AFTER LUNCH BEGINS
WHICH WOULD ALLOW ANY STUDENTS
WHO NEEDED TO GET FOOD
TO DO SO UM...
ZOE:
I TOOK ALL THE HEAT WITH
THE POLICE FOR OOMFCHAT,
AND NOW I HAVE A MILLION
LAWYER MEETINGS
WHILE I WAIT FOR SENTENCING.
TRISTAN:
WAIT, SENTENCING?
LIKE, YOU COULD GO TO JAIL?
AND THE REST OF THE GIRLS
ONLY GOT DETENTION?
HOW IS THAT FAIR?
ZOE:
I TOLD THE POLICE
I WAS THE RINGLEADER.
WHICH I WAS.
SO, LIKE I SAID,
I THINK I CAN HANDLE
A LITTLE DETENTION.
ZOE:
HEY LO!
LOOK ON THE BRIGHT SIDE.
WE COULD BE IN ACTUAL PRISON!
(CHUCKLES)
LOLA:
THEY TOOK AWAY OUR CELL PHONES.
IT'S LIKE MY BEST FRIEND DIED.
ZOE:
YOU'RE REALLY STILL MAD AT ME?
DAMON:
FOR THE RECORD,
I LOVED YOUR BUSINESS.
VERY ENTREPRENEURIAL.
ZOE:
CAN WE NOT? I'VE KINDA HAD
ENOUGH FOR ONE DAY.
DAMON:
AW, THE CHILD PORNOGRAPHER
DOESN'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT.
IT'S NOT-
NEVERMIND.
YOU'RE EVEN NOT WORTH IT.
(STUDENT CHUCKLES)
(SPITS, BOYS LAUGH)
BOY: NICE.
(BIRD CHIRPS, WATER SPLASHES)
WINSTON:
YOU THINK I'M FUNNY, RIGHT?
FRANKIE:
YOU'RE HILARIOUS.
NOW PLEASE KISS ME TO DISTRACT
ME FROM MY DUMB PARENTS
AND THEIR DUMB DIVORCE.
WINSTON:
LIKE LOUIS CK HILARIOUS,
OR CARROT TOP HILARIOUS?
FRANKIE:
HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
WINSTON:
THAT MS. PILL JOKE,
WHILE NOT MY FINEST WORK,
WAS AT LEAST WORTH A CHUCKLE.
FRANKIE:
THIS IS STILL ABOUT WHAT
HAPPENED IN CLASS THIS MORNING?
WINSTON:
LOOK, MILES IS THE HANDSOME
RICH KID,
ZIG IS THE REBEL WITHOUT
A CAUSE, AND I'M THE FUNNY GUY!
BUT NOT IF NO ONE LAUGHS
AT MY JOKES.
(SONG PLAYS)
♪ ...Flies through the night
wearing a disguise... ♪
FRANKIE: WHAT IS THIS?
WINSTON: NOTHING!
(GRUNTS)
JUST PUT ON SOME JOHN LEGEND
AND WE CAN GET BACK TO IT.
FRANKIE:
THIS IS YOU!
WHAT IS THIS?!
WINSTON:
THIS IS...
A SONG FROM THE FIRST ACT
OF MY MUSICAL
ABOUT A SHAPE-SHIFTING ASIAN
SUPERHERO NAMED CAPTAIN WHO.
CAN WE KISS NOW?
FRANKIE:
THIS IS AMAZING!
WE HAVE TO DO THIS AT SCHOOL!
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR SOMETHING
TO KEEP ME OUT OF THE HOUSE!
WINSTON:
I SAID I WANTED
TO BE THE FUNNY GUY.
NOT THE MUSICAL GUY.
FRANKIE:
OKAY THEN, MISTER,
WHAT'S YOUR PLAN TO CEMENT
YOUR POSITION
AS DEGRASSI'S RESIDENT
COMEDIAN?
WINSTON:
DON'T KNOW YET.
BUT I REFUSE TO BE
AN ANDREW LLOYD WANNABE.
THAT WAS A JOKE.
(BELL RINGS,
LOW HUM OF STUDENT CHATTER)
BECKY:
IS "LUNCHTIME VARIETY HOUR"
A DORKY A NAME?
JACK:
MAYBE SO DORKY,
IT'S NOT DORKY?
IMOGEN:
I GUESS YOU DIDN'T SEE
THE LIST.
BECKY:
OF THE APPROVED ACTIVITIES?!
IT'S UP?
AND WE'RE NOT ON IT?!
IMOGEN:
SORRY, BECKS.
BECKY:
WHAT GIVES?
OUR PITCH WAS SOLID!
OKAY.
JUST TELL ME!
DON'T DO THAT THING WHERE
YOU GUYS KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT THE OTHER IS SATING
BECAUSE YOU HAVE SECRET
LESBIAN TELEPATHY.
IMOGEN:
OH MY GOD,
WOULDN'T THAT BE AWESOME?
BECKY:
FOCUS!
JACK:
DREW DENIED YOUR REQUEST BECAUSE
HE'S JEALOUS OF YOU AND JONAH.
BECKY:
BUT THERE'S NOTHING
GOING ON BETWEEN US!
JACK:
DREW'S NOT BLIND.
HE CAN SEE THERE IS SEXINESS
BETWEEN YOU TWO.
IMOGEN:
AND FOR THE RECORD,
I FULLY SUPPORT IT -
BOY IS SUPER CUTE AND BONUS,
HE'S TOTALLY CHRISTIAN!
JACK:
DREW'S STILL INTO YOU.
SO GO ASK HIM TO APPROVE
YOUR IDEA,
AND THIS TIME...
BE A LITTLE NICER.
I ALREADY WAS REALLY NICE!
I'M ALWAYS REALLY NICE!
JACK:
OKAY.
NICER.
HM-HM?
BECKY:
OHHHH.
(CLOCK TICKS)
DAMON:
PSSST!
I SURE MISS SEEING THOSE
CHEERLEADING UNIFORMS
IN THE HALLS.
LOLA:
RIGHT? I LOOKED SO CUTE
IN MINE!
(DAMON SPITS, THEN CHUCKLES)
LOLA: UM, EW!
(CHAIR SCRAPES ON THE FLOOR)
ZOE:
OKAY, WE NEED TO DO SOMETHING
ABOUT THIS JOKER.
LEAVE US OUT OF THIS.
LAST TIME WE FOLLOWED YOU,
LOOK WHAT HAPPENED.
I FEEL HORRIBLE I'M THE REASON
YOU GUYS ARE IN HERE
GETTING BOTHERED
BY THAT CREEPO.
THEN FIND A WAY
TO MAKE IT UP TO US.
(BELL RINGS)
♪♪
♪ It's hot up here tonight,
girl, ♪
♪ Your honey is dipping
from your hive ♪
♪ I've got a sweet tooth ♪
♪ And the way you move
really wets my appetite ♪
BECKY:
HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
DREW:
MS. PILL'S WANTED ME
TO PUT UP THESE POSTERS
OF ALL THE NEW RULES.
BECKY:
LISTEN, I WANTED TO TALK
TO YOU
ABOUT WHY YOU DIDN'T APPROVE
MY VARIETY SHOW.
DREW:
YEAH. RIGHT. UM...
I DIDN'T THINK IT WAS
THE RIGHT FIT, OKAY?
BECKY:
LOOK, THIS ISN'T
ABOUT JONAH, IS IT?
DREW:
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO SAY,
BECKY?
ALL RIGHT. I JUST DON'T TRUST
A DUDE IN EYELINER.
BECKY:
LOOK, I THINK YOU HAVE THE
WRONG IDEA ABOUT ME AND JONAH.
DREW:
I DON'T CARE.
BECKY:
LOOK, WE'RE STRICTLY
MUSICAL PARTNERS. OKAY?
I MEAN, HONESTLY...
(WHISPERS)
HOW COULD HE EVER STACK UP
AGAINST DREW TORRES?
(SMALL LAUGHS)
YOUR HAIR SMELLS REALLY GOOD.
BECKY:
IF THERE'S ANY WAY YOU COULD
MAKE THE VARIETY SHOW HAPPEN,
IT WOULD MEAN SO MUCH TO ME.
DREW:
IT'S POSSIBLE I COULD HAVE
BEEN A LITTLE HASTY
IN MY DECISION MAKING.
BECKY:
BECAUSE I REALLY,
REALLY WANT IT.
DREW:
(GULPS)
YEAH,
I'LL SEE WHAT I CAN DO.
MAYBE WE CAN HANG OUT SOMETIME?
ABSOLUTELY!
YOU'RE MY HERO!
♪♪
(BELL RINGS,
LOW HUM OF STUDENT CHATTER)
IMOGEN:
I TAKE IT YOUR TALK
WITH DREW WENT WELL?
BECKY:
YES! I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW
MANY PEOPLE SIGNED UP!
DREW:
HEY BEAUTIFUL.
CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOU KICK ASS
ON STAGE, TODAY.
BECKY:
HEY... THANKS.
OKAY. WHAT NOW?!
I TALKED TO HIM NICELY
JUST LIKE YOU SAID!
I EVEN USED MY BOOBS
IMOGEN:
OKAY, WE TALKED LAST NIGHT
AND DECIDED THE ADVICE WE GAVE
YOU MAY HAVE BEEN A LITTLE...
JACK:
...ILL ADVISED.
BECKY:
OKAY, YOU GUYS REALLY NEED
TO TELL ME THESE THINGS.
IMOGEN:
IT'S JUST... YOU CAN'T PRETEND
TO LIKE DREW FOREVER!
BECKY:
WHY THE HECK NOT?!
I'VE ALWAYS DONE
THE RIGHT THING
AND WHERE HAS IT GOTTEN ME?
NOWHERE!
JACK:
I THOUGHT YOU SAID THAT "RULES
KEEP YOU FROM MAKING MISTAKES."
MAYBE! BUT APPARENTLY
THEY ALSO KEEP YOU
FROM ALL THE GOOD STUFF, TOO.
SO... SCREW THAT!
IMOGEN:
OH, YOU'RE CUTE
WHEN YOU'RE MAD.
BUT WATCH OUT -
BREAKING RULES TENDS
TO COME WITH CONSEQUENCES.
TRISTAN:
THERE YOU ARE.
ZOE:
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
I'VE BEEN IN DESPERATE NEED
OF YOUR SAGE ADVICE.
TRISTAN:
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
TO MEET IN THE GARDEN!
UGH, HOW DID PEOPLE DO ANYTHING
BEFORE CELL PHONES?
ZOE:
I HAVE NO IDEA.
OKAY, WHAT AM I GONNA DO
ABOUT THIS CREEP DAMON?
OKAY. SO YOU COULD CALL HIM
PRETENDING TO BE A DOCTOR
AND TELL HIM HE HAS HPV?
(LAUGHS)
GROSS, TRIS.
IT'S MY FAULT THE CHEERLEADERS
HAVE TO PUT UP WITH HIM.
AND I NEED TO FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO MAKE HIM STOP.
TRISTAN:
YOU'VE GOTTA EMBARRASS HIM
IN HIS OWN HOUSE.
I DON'T KNOW. I'VE MESSED UP
ENOUGH THIS YEAR.
AND I DON'T WANNA GET
INTO MORE TROUBLE
ESPECIALLY UNDER
THE NEW REGIME.
WELL, THEN YOU BETTER FIND
A WAY TO MAKE NICE
WITH YOUR NEW BUDDY, DAMON.
♪ We can bring back the light ♪
♪ If we find the right matches ♪
♪ If we strike them just so... ♪
WINSTON:
"WHAT'S THE DEAL WITH TEXT
MESSAGES, AM I RIGHT?"
FRANKIE:
OKAY. SO I DID SOME GOOGLING
LAST NIGHT
AND HERE ARE SOME COOL, FUNNY
PEOPLE WHO HAVE DONE MUSICALS:
JON HAMM, HUGH JACKMAN,
NEIL PATRICK HARRIS-
WINSTON:
I CAN'T TALK RIGHT NOW.
I'M ABOUT TO DO
MY STAND-UP ROUTINE.
FRANKIE:
WHAT? SINCE WHEN?
(STUDENTS APPLAUD)
BECKY: THANK YOU.
AND NOW FOR THE COMEDIC
STYLINGS OF WINSTON CHU.
WINSTON:
WISH ME LUCK.
DEGRASSI!
HOW ARE WE TODAY?
(APPLAUSE)
MANAGING OKAY WITHOUT
OUR CELL PHONES?
ALL:
BOO!
WINSTON:
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
I GUESS WE HAVE OUR TALENTED
POWER CHEER TEAM
TO THANK FOR THIS REGIME
CHANGE!
(LAUGHING)
THANKS A LOT, LADIES.
I MEAN, HOW ELSE AM I SUPPOSED
TO AVOID TALKING TO UGLY PEOPLE
IN THE HALLWAY?
I CAN'T PRETEND TO ANSWER
MY MATH TEXTBOOK.
(LAUGHING)
BUT SERIOUSLY, I'M REALLY
MISSING ALL THOSE TEXTS
FROM MY GIRLFRIEND.
"WHY DIDN'T YOU TEXT ME BACK?"
"I SAW YOU CHECKING OUT
THAT OTHER GIRL."
"DO I LOOK FAT IN THIS?!"
(STUDENTS LAUGHING)
NAW, I'M JUST PLAYING -
MY GIRLFRIEND'S A GODDESS.
AND GODDESSES DON'T SWEAT,
RIGHT? THEY GLISTEN.
WELL, MY GIRLFRIEND GLISTENS
ALL RIGHT.
SHE GLISTENS RIGHT THROUGH
HER SHIRT.
(STUDENTS LAUGHING)
THAT'S ALL FOR TODAY, FOLKS!
YOU'VE BEEN GREAT.
(CHEERING, APPLAUSE)
WINSTON:
WASN'T THAT AWESOME?!
FRANKIE:
HOW COULD YOU EMBARRASS ME
LIKE THAT?!
WINSTON:
WHAT? I NEVER SAID YOUR NAME!
FRANKIE:
I'M YOUR GIRLFRIEND!
EVERYONE JUST ASSUMED YOU
WERE TALKING ABOUT ME!
WINSTON:
I WAS DOING A CHARACTER.
ALL STAND-UPS DO IT.
BESIDES, THEY LOVED ME!
DIDN'T YOU HEAR
ALL THE LAUGHS I GOT?
FRANKIE:
THEY WERE ALL AT MY EXPENSE
AND YOU DON'T EVEN CARE!
WINSTON: WAIT, THAT'S NOT TRUE!
FRANKIE: YES IT IS!
YOU'D RATHER BE THE FUNNY GUY
THAN A GOOD BOYFRIEND.
WINSTON:
WHAT'S WRONG WITH WANTING
TO BE THE FUNNY GUY?
FRANKIE:
YOU HURT ME TO DO IT!
WHICH MAKES YOU "THE LOSER."
JONAH: ♪ The way you do ♪
BECKY: ♪ The way you do ♪
♪ I love the way you dance ♪
♪ The way you do ♪
(APPLAUSE AND CHEERING)
BECKY:
(CHUCKLES) THANK YOU.
THEY ACTUALLY LIKED US.
JONAH:
THEY LIKED YOU
BECAUSE YOU WERE AMAZING.
BECKY:
UM, WE... SHOULDN'T.
JONAH:
YEAH. WE WOULDN'T WANNA GET
IN TROUBLE WITH BIG BROTHER.
BECKY:
YEAH. WE WOULDN'T WANNA
UPSET ANYONE.
(SIGHS)
(WINSTON GROANS)
LOLA:
YOU LOOK LIKE I DID
WHEN MY HAMSTERS DIED.
THAT'S RIGHT.
BOTH OF THEM.
WINSTON:
I'M A TOTAL SCREW-UP.
FRANKIE HATED MY STAND-UP.
LOLA:
BUT YOU WERE HILARIOUS!
ESPECIALLY THAT PART ABOUT
PRETENDING TO BE ON THE PHONE!
I DO THAT ALL THE TIME!
WINSTON:
YEAH. I LIKE THAT ONE, TOO.
SHE DIDN'T EVEN UNDERSTAND
WHY I WANTED TO DO IT
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
LOLA:
YOU WANT PEOPLE TO THINK
YOU'RE THE FUNNY ONE.
WINSTON:
YEAH! EXACTLY!
LOLA:
JUST LIKE FRANKIE'S
THE SMART ONE,
SHAY'S THE CONFIDENT ONE,
AND I'M THE DUMB ONE.
IT'S OKAY.
IT'S JUST THE WAY IT IS.
WINSTON:
I'LL NEVER BE COOL LIKE MILES,
OR A BAD ASS LIKE ZIG,
SO IF I'M NOT EVEN
THE FUNNY GUY,
THEN MAYBE I AM THE LOSER.
LOLA:
NO WAY! YOU'RE WINSTON!
WHO IS TOTALLY THOUGHTFUL,
AND NICE,
AND EVEN THOUGH HE DOESN'T
THINK SO, HILARIOUS.
WINSTON:
REALLY?
LOLA:
NO ONE CAN MAKE ME LAUGH
LIKE YOU!
SO YOU DON'T THINK I'M A LOSER?
I THINK YOU'RE AWESOME,
AND SOMEDAY EVERYONE ELSE
WILL THINK SO TOO.
I KNOW IT!
OH MY GOD! OH MY GOD!
WHAT DID I DO?!
YOU KISSED ME!
WELL, BECAUSE YOU SAID
I WASN'T A LOSER.
I AM A LOSER.
I AM SUCH A LOSER!
LOLA:
WE HAVE TO TELL FRANKIE!
WINSTON:
NO! SHE CAN NEVER KNOW
ABOUT THIS!
(BELL RINGS)
PROMISE ME, PLEASE!
LOLA:
I-I HAVE TO GET TO DETENTION!
(BANGS HIS HEAD AGAINST LOCKER)
DAMON:
OH, COME ON, GIRL,
DON'T PLAY ME LIKE THAT.
LOLA:
I SAID, LEAVE ME ALONE.
DAMON:
SO I CAN'T PAY A HOTTIE
LIKE YOU A COMPLIMENT?
I'M JUST TRYING TO BE NICE.
(CHAIR SCRAPES)
WHAT THE HELL?!
ZOE:
OH NO! LOOKS LIKE YOU HAD
AN ACCIDENT.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD GO HOME
SO YOUR MOMMY CAN CLEAN YOU UP.
THESE WERE BRAND NEW PANTS!
ZOE:
WELL, MAYBE NOW YOU'LL STOP
WITH THE SPITBALLS.
DAMON:
YOU'RE A NIGHTMARE.
NO WONDER THESE GIRLS HATE YOU.
DREW:
HEY, GUYS, REMEMBER,
PDA IS AN ALLEGED ONE WAY
TICKET TO DETENTION, OKAY?
HEY! I NEVER GOT TO TELL YOU
HOW GREAT YOU SOUNDED.
BECKY:
THANKS. UM, LISTEN, I-
DREW:
I WAS THINKING MAYBE WE COULD
HANG OUT TONIGHT.
BECKY:
DREW-
DREW:
THERE ARE NO RULES ABOUT PDA
IN THE TORRES BASEMENT.
BECKY:
I CAN'T.
DREW:
LOOK, BECKY, I KNOW THINGS
GOT MESSY BETWEEN US,
I WOULD LOVE A CHANCE
TO MAKE THEM RIGHT.
BECKY:
LOOK, I DON'T LIKE YOU!
I MEAN, I DID!
BUT I DON'T ANYMORE.
I FLIRTED WITH YOU SO YOU'D
APPROVE THE VARIETY SHOW.
DREW:
(SCOFFS) I'M SORRY, WHAT?
BECKY:
I KNEW YOU SAID NO BECAUSE YOU
WERE JEALOUS OF ME AND JONAH.
DREW:
SO THERE IS SOMETHING GOING ON
BETWEEN YOU TWO.
BECKY:
THAT'S NOT THE POINT.
I FELT BAD ABOUT USING YOU.
AND THAT'S WHY I WANTED
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH.
DREW:
OH NOW YOU WANNA TELL ME
THE TRUTH?!
JONAH:
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
DREW: STAY OUT OF IT, GUYLINER.
JONAH: NO NEED TO BE INSULTING.
MS. PILL:
DREW! WHAT'S GOING ON
OVER THERE?
DREW:
I WAS TRYING TO ENFORCE
THE NEW RULES.
WHEN I CAUGHT THESE TWO MAKING
OUT ON THE STAIRWELL -
WHICH IS IN DIRECT
VIOLATION OF THE RULES
OUTLINED ON THESE FLYERS.
BECKY:
WHAT?! OKAY.
THAT IS NOT TRUE.
JONAH:
YEAH. HE'S LYING.
MS. PILL:
I'D LIKE TO SEE YOU BOTH
IN MY OFFICE, NOW.
(LOW HUM OF STUDENT CHATTER)
(WINSTON EXHALES)
FRANKIE:
WHAT'S THIS?
WINSTON:
IT'S THE SCRIPT
TO "CAPTAIN WHO."
YOU WERE RIGHT, MY STANDUP
WAS TOTALLY OFFENSIVE.
I WAS WORRIED ABOUT WHAT
EVERYONE ELSE THOUGHT,
WHEN REALLY, YOU'RE THE ONLY
PERSON WHOSE OPINION I CARE
ABOUT.
WE SHOULD TOTALLY
DO THE MUSICAL.
UNLESS YOU HATE ME NOW.
I'M SO, SO, SORRY.
FRANKIE:
I'M SORRY, TOO.
WINSTON:
FOR WHAT? YOU DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO BE SORRY ABOUT!
FRANKIE:
FOR CALLING YOU A LOSER.
YOU ARE THE FUNNY GUY.
YOU'RE MY FUNNY GUY.
(CHUCKLES)
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
WINSTON:
ABSOLUTELY.
TOTALLY.
NEVER BETTER.
BECKY:
THIS IS TOTAL CRAP!
DETENTION FOR A WEEK,
OUR VARIETY SHOW GOT CANCELED,
AND WE DIDN'T EVEN DO ANYTHING!
YOU'RE LUCKY THE SECURITY
CAMERAS AREN'T WORKING YET.
JONAH:
LOOK ON THE BRIGHT SIDE...
REALLY GREAT SONGS
GET WRITTEN IN PRISON.
BECKY:
OKAY, FINE, I LED DREW ON
WHEN I REALLY LIKED YOU,
BUT THEN I CAME CLEAN!
WHY IS IT THAT WHENEVER
I FOLLOW THE RULES,
THINGS JUST GET WORSE?!
WHAT?
YOU LIKE ME.
YES!
AND I DIDN'T KISS YOU
WHEN I WANTED TO
BECAUSE IT WASN'T FAIR TO DREW,
BUT LOOK WHERE THAT GOT US.
JONAH:
WHAT A RIP OFF.
I GET IN TROUBLE
FOR KISSING YOU
AND I DON'T EVEN GET
TO ACTUALLY DO IT?
(DEEP INHALE AND EXHALE)
WELL, THAT WOULD BE A RIP OFF,
WOULDN'T IT?
(SHARP EXHALE)
(SMALL LAUGH)
ZOE:
THAT'S A GOOD LOOK ON YOU.
MAYBE YOU'LL START A TREND.
DAMON:
IT'S TOO BAD YOU'RE SUCH
A BITCH,
BECAUSE YOU'RE TOTALLY HOT.
ZOE:
NO NEED TO GET NASTY.
DAMON:
I LIKED YOU BETTER
WHEN YOU WERE JUST BOOBS
THAT COULDN'T TALK.
ZOE:
OKAY. GET AWAY FROM ME, CREEP.
DAMON:
SO, YOU CAN DISH IT OUT,
BUT YOU CAN'T TAKE IT.
ZIG:
COME ON, MAN, ALL RIGHT,
YOU HEARD HER.
JUST BACK OFF.
YOU WANNA MAKE ME?
ZOE:
OKAY, ZIG, IT'S OKAY,
I CAN HANDLE HIM.
ZIG:
YEAH, BUT YOU SHOULDN'T
HAVE TO.
JUST GET OUT OF HERE, MAN.
OH, LOOK AT YOU ZIGGY BOY,
ACTING ALL TOUGH
WITH YOUR NEW FRIEND.
TINY:
HEY! NO ONE TOUCHES MY BOY.
ZOE:
GUYS! STOP IT!
GUYS STOP!
AGHHHH!
OH GOD!
OH MY GOD.
NO! WE NEED TO CALL FOR HELP!
(PAINED GRUNTS)
(LABOURED BREATHING)