(BLUE JAY CRIES,
BIRDS CHIRP)
(APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS)
TRISTAN:
HEY, HAVE ANY OF YOU SEEN ZOE?
GRACE:
NOT SINCE LAST NIGHT.
AFTER WE LOOKED AT THE STARS,
MR. BAIN GAVE HER A RIDE HOME.
TRISTAN:
YOU LET HER GO OFF, ALONE,
WITH HIM?
OKAY, SHE DIDN'T MEET ME TO
WALK TO SCHOOL THIS MORNING,
AND GIRLS ARE GOING MISSING.
GRACE:
YOU MEAN LIKE THAT
GLORIA GIRL?
SHAY:
I HEARD SHE ELOPED
WITH SOME GUY.
HUNTER:
I HEARD SHE WAS ABDUCTED
BY THE YAKUZA,
WHO HARVESTED HER ORGANS.
ZOE:
TRIS, OVER HERE!
(BOOK SNAPS SHUT)
TRISTAN:
(RELIEVED SIGHS)
WHERE WERE YOU?
ZOE:
SORRY ABOUT THIS MORNING.
I CAME EARLY TO HELP BAIN
SET UP.
THERE'S LIKE NO RECEPTION
OUT HERE.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
MR. BAIN: OKAY, EVERYBODY,
GATHER ROUND!
GET IN CLOSE!
OKAY, UH...
SCIENCE IS ABOUT OBSERVATION,
BUT BECAUSE WE HAVE BIASES,
OUR RESULTS CAN BECOME CLOUDED.
TODAY, WE'RE GOING
TO IDENTIFY AND CATALOGUE
EVERYTHING WE SEE.
OKAY, LET'S GO!
ALL THROUGH THE FOREST,
EVERY QUADRANT. OVER HERE.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT YOU AND BAIN
SPENDING TIME TOGETHER.
ZOE:
WE WENT STARGAZING,
AS A GROUP.
HE THINKS I'M SMART.
CHILL.
TRISTAN:
A TEACHER WORKING HARD TO MAKE
YOU FEEL GOOD ABOUT YOURSELF?
GIVING YOU AFTER-HOURS
ATTENTION?
TRYING TO HANG OUT ALONE?
SOUND FAMILIAR?
ZOE:
JUST BECAUSE ONE TEACHER
GOT FRISKY WITH YOU, TRIS,
DOESN'T MEAN THEY'RE ALL BAD.
HUNTER:
WHOA! I FOUND BONES!
GRACE:
BIG ONES.
LIKE HUMAN-SIZED.
(STUDENTS CHATTER ALL AROUND)
HUNTER:
NO, NO, NO.
I RECOGNIZE THESE.
DEER BONES.
ZOE:
OUR TEACHER IS NOT INTERESTED
IN ME LIKE THAT.
I'LL PROVE IT.
(FOLIAGE RUSTLES,
MR. BAIN GASPS)
(WOODPECKER PECKS
IN THE DISTANCE)
(CROW CAWS)
FRANKIE:
HIS NOSE WAS POINTIER.
EVEN POINTIER.
I KNOW IT DOESN'T SEEM
POSSIBLE, BUT TRUST ME.
DETECTIVE:
YOU'RE FREE TO GO, MISS.
FRANKIE:
ALREADY? YOU ONLY ASKED ME,
LIKE, FIVE QUESTIONS.
DETECTIVE:
AND WE GOT OUR ANSWERS.
THEY DON'T SEEM RELATED
TO THE MISSING GIRL.
FRANKIE:
MAYBE YOU DIDN'T HEAR ME.
A WEIRD GUY OFFERED ME A RIDE.
I TOOK IT ALL DOWN.
DON'T YOU WANT EVERY DETAIL?
I REMEMBER A LOT!
DETECTIVE:
NO, I'D LIKE TO SAY THANK YOU
FOR COMING IN.
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER,
PHONES RING)
(CHAIR SCRAPES BACK)
WINSTON:
ON THE BRIGHT SIDE,
YOU CAN STILL MAKE IT TO WORK.
MADAM.
FRANKIE: I JUST REALLY WANTED
TO HELP LOGAN.
YOU TRIED YOUR BEST.
NOW, YOU CAN FREE UP YOUR MIND
FOR TRIVIA NIGHT.
IT'D BE SWEET TO FINALLY
BRING HOME A VICTORY
FOR TEAM FRANKSTON.
DETECTIVE:
YEAH, IT'S ME. NO, THERE'S
NOTHING NEW ON THE TIP.
MY MONEY'S STILL ON
THE NEW GUY
HER PARENTS SAID
SHE WAS TALKING TO.
THE ONE THEY CALLED
"RUDE AND IRRITATING."
YEAH. LOOK, I THINK
IF WE FIND HIM, WE FIND HER.
ANOTHER GUY?!
SHOULD I TELL LOGAN?
WINSTON:
THAT HIS GIRL WAS INTO
SOMEONE ELSE?
WOULD YOU WANNA BE
TOLD THAT?
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh... ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
SO EVERYONE HAD
DIFFERENT THEORIES
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED
TO GLORIA.
ESPECIALLY MAYA.
POOR MAYA.
(LOUD THUNDERCLAP,
THUNDER RUMBLES)
MAYA:
SO EVERETT SERIOUSLY THINKS
THIS PLACE IS HAUNTED?
EVERETT:
IT IS.
LENA:
AND THAT THE GHOSTS TOOK GLORIA
OR SOMETHING.
THEY DID.
MAYA:
SO WE CAN USE THE OUIJA BOARD
TO MAKE THE GHOSTS OR...
WHATEVER,
TELL HIM THAT NEVER HAPPENED?
YUP, SHOULD WORK.
HEY, EV,
WANNA USE THE OUIJA BOARD?
MAYA:
COME ON. IT'LL BE FUN.
COME ON.
(SULKS)
OKAY... (CLEARS THROAT)
WHAT SHOULD WE ASK IT?
EVERETT:
ARE THERE ANY SPIRITS
WITH US TODAY?
(LOUD THUNDERCLAP)
MAYA:
YES. UM... OKAY.
UH, WHO ARE YOU, SPIRIT?
LENA: C...
MAYA: C...
LENA:
A...
M...
(LOUD THUNDERCLAP)
I...
L-L...
A.
OH, HEY, CAMILLA.
WHAT, YOU KNOW HER?
YEAH.
SHE DIED IN HERE.
MAYA: WHAT?
LENA: DID YOU TAKE GLORIA?
MAYA:
NO. SEE, EVERETT?
WE'RE FINE.
LENA: I... KNOW... WHO...
(PLANCHETTE MOVES QUICKLY)
MAYA: ARE YOU DOING THIS?
LENA: NO!
IT'S CAMILLA...
OR ONE OF THE OTHERS.
MAYA: OTHERS?
LENA: THIS USED TO BE
AN INSANE ASYLUM.
(LOUD THUNDERCLAP,
THUNDER RUMBLES)
LENA:
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
THEY CONVERTED IT INTO CONDOS
AFTER ALL THOSE PEOPLE
WERE BASICALLY TORTURED HERE.
BUT NOTHING WEIRD HAPPENS,
RIGHT?
NOT REALLY, EXCEPT...
SOMETIMES I HEAR
STRANGE NOISES IN THE NIGHT.
LENA:
AND ALL OF OUR NANNIES -
WHOO! WHEW! - DISAPPEAR.
MAYA:
COME ON.
YOU MEAN LIKE THEY QUIT.
BUT WAIT, SPIRIT, WE'RE LIKE...
SAFE IN HERE, RIGHT?
(PLANCHETTE SWIPES
ACROSS BOARD FURIOUSLY)
EVERETT:
SHE SAYS... "U R N-E-X-T."
(LOUD THUNDERCLAP,
THUNDER RUMBLES)
WHAT'S WRONG?
WHAT DOES THAT SPELL?
LENA: YOU'RE NEXT.
MAYA: (GASPS) OH MY GOSH!
(BELL RINGS,
STUDENT YELPS)
MR. BAIN:
WELL, I UH... WELL,
THAT'S LUNCHTIME, SCIENTISTS!
NOW, IF YOU EAT OUTSIDE,
DO SO IN YOUR CAR.
WHEN LIGHTNING STRIKES,
IT WILL ARC AROUND
THE METAL BODY,
UH, SPARING YOU.
FASCINATING?
(STUDENTS CHATTER,
IGNORING HIM)
MR. BAIN:
OH WELL.
(ZIPPER UNZIPS,
POWER FLICKERS)
ZOE:
(EXHALES HEAVILY,
SLIGHTLY SCARED)
(THUNDERCLAP,
THUNDER RUMBLES)
ZOE:
HI, MR. BAIN.
CAN I... ASK YOU SOMETHING?
MR. BAIN:
YES, OF COURSE.
AN INQUISITIVE MIND LIKE YOURS
CAN ASK ME ANYTHING.
IS THERE ANYTHING SCIENCE
CAN DO FOR...
MY TAN LINES?
MR. BAIN: WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
ZOE: WELL...
WOULDN'T THAT LOOK NICER
IF IT WAS ALL ONE COLOUR?
MR. BAIN:
I... I SUPPOSE, IF-IF ONE LIKED
AESTHETIC UNIFORMITY.
WELL, DO YOU?
MR. BAIN:
UH... HERE'S WHAT YOU DO.
YOU MIX BAKING SODA
WITH WATER.
SCRUB WITH THE MIXTURE
FOR TWO MINUTES.
IT WILL EXFOLIATE
THE DARKER LAYERS,
AND BLEND THE TWO TOGETHER.
THANKS, MR. BAIN.
I KNEW YOU'D COME THROUGH
FOR ME.
(THUNDER RUMBLES,
CREEPY MUSIC PLAYS)
(RUNNING FOOTSTEPS,
DOOR CLOSES HEAVILY)
I THINK IT'S BEST WE DON'T
SPEND ANY TIME ALONE TOGETHER.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
MR. BAIN:
I DIDN'T WANT TO PRE-JUDGE YOU
BECAUSE OF YOUR REPUTATION,
BUT HERE WE ARE.
I THINK IT'S BEST
FOR EVERYONE
IF YOU NO LONGER JOIN
THE AFTER-HOURS GROUP.
(GASPS)
(DOOR CREAKS OPEN,
STUDENTS CHATTER IN THE HALL)
(UPSET, SHAKY BREATH)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(LOUD THUNDERCLAP)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(PHONE RINGS SUDDENLY,
TRAY CRASHES)
IT'S JUST A PHONE.
DON'T FREAK.
(PHONE BEEPS ON)
HELLO?
(LOUD THUNDERCLAP)
HELLO...?
OKAY, WHO IS THIS?!
JORDYN:
WOW, MAYA. RELAX.
I HAD TO ANSWER A QUESTION
FOR THE BAND.
MAYA:
OH, HI, JORDYN.
UM, THE KIDS ARE IN BED,
LIKE YOU ASKED.
ARE YOU CLOSE?
JORDYN:
ACTUALLY, I'M MAKING SOME MAGIC
IN THE STUDIO TONIGHT.
I NEED YOU TO STAY
A COUPLE EXTRA HOURS.
MAYA:
(FRUSTRATED SIGH)
UM, WELL, HOW MANY?
BECAUSE I'M SUPPOSED TO-
JORDYN:
YOU REALLY WANT ME TO TELL
THE BAND TO PACK IT IN?
MAYA:
NO. NO, IT'S FINE.
IT'S COOL.
UM... I'LL SEE YOU
IN A COUPLE OF HOURS.
(PHONE BEEPS OFF)
(LOUD CLATTERING THUMP,
THUNDER RUMBLES)
(SLOW, CREEPY MUSIC PLAYS)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(LOUD THUNDERCLAP,
THUNDER RUMBLES)
(MAYA RATTLES THE DOORKNOB,
AND OPENS THE DOOR)
ZIG: SURPRISE!
MAYA: (GASPS) ZIG!
(LAUGHS) WHAT?
I GOT OFF MY SHIFT EARLY.
I THOUGHT I'D COME
PICK YOU UP.
YEAH, WELL,
I CAN'T COME OUT ANYMORE.
ZIG:
OH? SO YOU WANNA HAVE
THE DATE HERE.
I SEE WHERE YOUR HEAD'S AT...
MAYA: (LAUGHS) NO...
YOU CAN'T STAY, OKAY?
I'M TRYING TO BE
THE PERFECT NANNY,
SO THAT JORDYN WILL THINK
I'M A HARD WORKER
AND HIRE ME TO WORK
AT HER STUDIO.
SO THEN WHY'D YOU
PULL ME IN?
I NEED YOU TO CHECK
FOR GHOSTS.
(SNORTS) O-OKAY.
UM... CHECKED. DONE.
THERE'S NO SUCH THING
AS GHOSTS.
PLEASE! ZIG, JUST CHECK.
HUMOUR ME!
(SLIGHTLY AMUSED)
FINE.
(LOUD THUNDERCLAP)
(BASKET LID CLICKS)
NO GHOST HERE.
(ZIG SIGHS,
SIREN WAILS IN THE DISTANCE)
(ZIG FAKE GASPS,
MAYA GASPS)
STILL NO GHOSTS.
(BASKET LID THUMPS)
NOTHING. SEE?
AM I YOUR HERO?
MAYA:
MMM...
DISTORTED VOICE: YOU'RE NEXT!
ZIG AND MAYA: (SCARED GASPS)
(THUNDER RUMBLES,
SCREECHING VIOLINS PLAY)
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
HEY! ABE SAID
WE COULD KICK IT.
I'M SORRY.
IF I KNEW THIS PROJECT MEANT
SO MANY LATE NIGHTS,
I NEVER WOULD HAVE
SUGGESTED IT.
NO, IT'S GOOD YOU DID.
IT'S A GREAT IDEA,
AND IT'S GONNA HELP
A LOT OF PEOPLE.
WE'RE GRABBING SUSHI.
DO YOU WANNA COME?
THANKS, BUT...
IT'S DATE NIGHT.
OKAY.
(RECEDING FOOTSTEPS)
GLORIA: (IN VIDEO)
TODAY'S S'MORES-INSPIRED
FROZEN TREAT RECIPE
COMES FROM SAMANTHA
IN NEW JERSEY.
THIS IS ONE SERIOUSLY
SWEET TREAT,
BUT NOT AS SWEET
AS MY SWEETIE.
HAPPY THREE MONTH ANNIVERSARY,
LOGIE! (BLOWS KISS)
LOGAN:
HEY. HOW'D IT GO
WITH THE POLICE?
THEY DON'T THINK MY THING
IS RELATED TO GLORIA.
I TRIED TO GET THEM TO LISTEN-
LOGAN: YEAH, THEY'RE IDIOTS.
I MEAN, THEY STILL THINK
SHE RAN AWAY.
WHICH IS... IS STUPID,
YOU KNOW?
EVERYTHING WAS PERFECT.
WHY WOULD SHE DO THAT?
THEY THINK SHE WAS TALKING
TO ANOTHER GUY.
SOMEONE HER PARENTS
DIDN'T LIKE.
THEY THINK
SHE'S WITH HIM.
NO. GLORIA WOULDN'T
DO THAT TO ME!
ALL RIGHT, I'M SORRY,
SMALL FRY. I...
LOOK, IF I'M BEING
COMPLETELY HONEST,
YEAH, MAYBE SHE WAS
PULLING AWAY.
I-I DON'T REALLY KNOW.
IT'S ALL SO CONFUSING...
OKAY, YOU PROBABLY
GOTTA GO.
YOU'RE NOT GOING
FOR SUSHI?
NO, I'M JUST GONNA GET
SOME WORK DONE.
NO. YOU SHOULDN'T BE ALONE
TONIGHT.
YOU'RE COMING WITH ME.
AND YOUR BOYFRIEND?
I DON'T REALLY WANNA BE
AROUND PEOPLE RIGHT NOW.
IS THAT ALL I AM TO YOU?
"PEOPLE"?
THERE'S THAT SMILE.
NOW, COME ON.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
(SNIFFS)
(RECEDING FOOTSTEPS,
THUNDER RUMBLES)
(LOUD THUNDERCLAP)
DISTORTED VOICE:
YOU'RE NEXT...
MAYA:
IT'S COMING
FROM OVER THERE.
DOES THAT LOOK LIKE
A TORTURE CHAMBER TO YOU?
ZIG: YEAH...
MAYA: ZIG, YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE THE ONE THAT SAYS,
"IT JUST LOOKS LIKE
A PANTRY."
DISTORTED VOICE:
YOU'RE NEXT!
MAYA: (SHAKY EXHALE)
ZIG: IT'S DEFINITELY
GETTING LOUDER.
(DOOR CREAKS OPEN)
DISTORTED VOICE:
YOU'RE NEXT!
MAYA:
OH, IT'S COMING
FROM DOWN THERE.
DISTORTED VOICE:
YOU'RE NEXT!
MAYA:
(SHARP EXHALE)
IT'S A TOY?!
BOTH: (RELIEVED LAUGHTER)
MAYA: OH, CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?!
ZIG:
UH, YES. BECAUSE I TOLD YOU,
THERE'S NO SUCH THING AS GHOSTS.
MAYA:
AS IF YOU WEREN'T SCARED, TOO!
ZIG:
NOT FOR A SECOND.
(DOOR BANGS SHUT,
LIGHTS CLICK OFF)
MAYA:
(RATTLES DOORKNOB)
IT WON'T OPEN.
ZIG:
WHAT'S GOING ON?
PRETTY SURE IT'S "LOVE."
FRANKIE: PRETTY SURE?
WINSTON: 90 PERCENT.
FRANKIE:
OKAY, BECAUSE WE NEED THIS.
WE'RE ONLY DOWN 500 POINTS.
WINSTON: UGH.
LOGAN: THE MOST SUCCESSFUL
BEACH BOYS' ALBUM
ISN'T "LOVE SOUNDS."
IT'S "PET SOUNDS."
WINSTON:
OH, YEAH, AND ALL THE SONGS
ARE CALLED "WOOF-WOOF"
AND "MEOW-MEOW QUACK"?
FRANKIE: WHO HAS A PET DUCK?
LOGAN: IT'S YOUR TEAM, MAN.
I'M JUST A PINCH HITTER.
FRANKIE:
OKAY, GUYS,
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
WINSTON:
IT'S "LOVE."
LOCK IT IN.
(TRIVIA TEAMS CHEER NEARBY)
WINSTON: UGH.
WINSTON:
OH, DO YOU HAVE TO GO
MEET UP WITH YOUR FRIENDS?
THAT'S TOO BAD.
LOGAN:
NO, ACTUALLY, I WAS JUST GONNA
GO GET ANOTHER DRINK.
YOU GUYS WANT ANYTHING?
WINSTON: I CAN BUY
MY OWN DRINKS, THANKS.
FRANKIE: TWO BANANA-MANGO
SMOOTHIES, PLEASE.
LOGAN:
'KAY. GOT IT.
FRANKIE:
WHY ARE YOU BEING
SO MEAN TO HIM?
WINSTON:
OH, TO THE HANDSOME OLDER GUY
YOU BROUGHT ON OUR DATE?
FRANKIE:
HE'S MY FRIEND,
AND HIS GIRLFRIEND IS MISSING.
CAN YOU EVEN IMAGINE?
WHAT IF IT WERE ME?
WE'LL STILL HAVE A CHANCE
FOR SOME ALONE TIME.
I'LL LET YOU WALK ME HOME -
THE LONG WAY.
JUST PLAY NICE... FOR ME?
WINSTON:
OKAY, BUT HE'D BETTER KNOW...
"WHO WAS THE FIRST ACTOR
TO PLAY THE JOKER ON SCREEN?"
CESAR ROMERO.
FRANKIE:
SEE? THERE IS PLENTY OF ROOM
ON THIS TEAM FOR THREE.
(LAUGHS DRYLY)
(MAYA SIGHS,
FOOTSTEPS THUMP IN KITCHEN)
MAYA:
THERE'S SOMEONE OUT THERE.
ZIG: MAYBE IT'S THE KIDS?
MAYA: IT DOESN'T SOUND
LIKE THEM.
OH, I HOPE THEY'RE OKAY.
(BANGING ON DOOR)
GOD, I'M THE WORST NANNY EVER.
(DOOR BURSTS OPEN,
MAYA GASPS)
I'M SO HAPPY TO SEE YOU.
ARE THE KIDS OKAY?
JORDYN:
YEAH, EVERYONE'S FINE.
MAYA? WHO'S THIS?
AND WHAT IS HE DOING
IN MY PANTRY?
MAYA:
OH, NO, NO, NO.
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
I THOUGHT I HEARD A NOISE,
AND ZIG POPPED OVER TO SAY HI
FOR LIKE ONE MINUTE...
IT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
IT'S JUST WITH GLORIA
BEING MISSING...
AND THE FACT THAT THIS PLACE
USED TO BE AN INSANE ASYLUM-
JORDYN:
IT USED TO BE
A PENCIL FACTORY.
INSANE ASYLUM?
WHO TOLD YOU THAT?
(SIGHS) WHATEVER,
I'M STARVING.
WE'LL TALK
ABOUT THIS TOMORROW.
MAYA: SO THIS WHOLE THING
WAS A PRANK?
LENA: WHAT WHOLE THING?
MAYA:
HOW COULD YOU EMBARRASS ME
LIKE THAT IN FRONT OF YOUR MOM?
LENA:
BECAUSE YOU MAKE IT SO EASY.
(CAMERA BEEPS ON)
THE PRESSURE WAS MOUNTING.
NO ONE WAS SAFE...
NOT EVEN ME.
(HORROR MUSIC)
NO, PLEASE. DON'T.
LOOK, THESE COST A FORTUNE,
AND I STILL HAVE A FEW USES
TO WRING OUT OF THEM
BEFORE LABOUR DAY.
THANKS TO YOU,
MR. BAIN BANNED ME
FROM THE SCIENCE GROUP.
TRISTAN:
SO YOU DON'T HAVE TO HANG OUT
WITH A PREDATOR? N B D.
ZOE:
HE'S NOT-
HE ACTUALLY THINKS I'M SMART.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
I KIND OF LIKED DOING
THE EXTRA CREDIT STUFF
WITH GRACE AND THE SMART KIDS,
BUT NOW-
YOU HAVE MORE TIME
TO HANG OUT WITH ME
AND FIGURE OUT WHAT
WE'RE GONNA DO FOR THIS VLOG!
THAT'S IT!
YOU'RE JEALOUS.
TRISTAN:
OF WHAT? SCIENCE?
(GASPS)
OKAY, WE-WE PARTNERED UP
WITH HUNTER AND GRACE
SO YOU AND I COULD HAVE
MORE TIME TO HANG OUT, REMEMBER?
HEY, I'M JUST AS SURPRISED
AS YOU
THAT GRACE AND I EVEN HAVE
ONE THING IN COMMON.
BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER NOW,
BECAUSE YOU WRECKED IT.
TRISTAN: (SIGHS HEAVILY)
ZOE: I'LL SPARE YOUR
PRECIOUS PANTS...
BUT DON'T TALK TO ME...
FOR THE REST OF THE SUMMER.
TRISTAN:
OKAY, YOU DON'T MEAN THAT.
(APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS)
GRACE! GRACE, UM... TAKE THIS.
IT'S MY HALF
OF TODAY'S ASSIGNMENT.
YOU COULD'VE DONE THAT
IN CLASS.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
ZOE:
I... CAN'T GO BACK IN.
EVER.
OKAY, NOW YOU'RE NOT
MAKING SENSE.
(RUSHED FOOTSTEPS)
ZOE:
I EMBARRASSED MYSELF
WITH BAIN.
HE THINKS I WAS COMING ON
TO HIM.
GRACE:
(LAUGHS) WHY WOULD
HE THINK THAT?
ZOE:
BECAUSE I... KIND OF WAS?
I GUESS EVERYONE'S
GOT A TYPE.
ZOE:
NO, IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
I WAS JUST TESTING HIM
BECAUSE...
TRISTAN THOUGHT
HE WAS TRYING TO PERV ON ME.
GRACE:
JUST TELL HIM WHAT HAPPENED.
HE'S A WEIRD DUDE.
HE'LL GET IT IF YOU EXPLAIN
YOU WERE JUST BEING WEIRD.
I'LL COME WITH YOU,
IF YOU WANT.
YOU'D DO THAT?
GRACE:
I'D NEVER LAST A WHOLE SUMMER
WITHOUT YOU.
YOU'RE THE ONLY REMOTELY
BEARABLE PERSON IN THAT CLASS.
(CHUCKLES) THANKS.
I THINK.
(MARIACHI MUSIC PLAYS)
ZIG: (CLEARS HIS THROAT)
MAYA: WHAT?
YOU ORDERED THE SAUSAGE, RIGHT?
GOD, I'M SUCH A FAILURE.
NO, NO,
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
NO ONE CAN STAY MAD
AT BACON.
MAYA:
IT'S NOT THE BACON.
I'M JUST FAILING AT EVERYTHING,
ESPECIALLY THE JOB.
TINY:
I THOUGHT
IT WAS YOUR DREAM JOB.
MAYA:
WELL, IT'S TURNING
INTO A NIGHTMARE.
I MEAN, I CAN HANDLE
THE SMALL PAYCHECKS
AND JORDYN CHANGING
THE HOURS ON THE FLY,
WITHOUT ANY NOTICE.
BUT THE KIDS,
THEY JUST DON'T LIKE ME.
TINY: WHO CARES
IF THE KIDS LIKE YOU?
ZIG: DUDE!
TINY: LOOK, CHILDREN
ARE LIKE DOGS.
ZIG: SOLID START.
YOU CAN PLAY WITH THEM
ALL YOU WANT,
BUT IF YOU DON'T SHOW
THEM YOU'RE IN CONTROL
WHEN YOU'RE DONE PLAYING
WITH THEM,
THEY JUST GET ANXIOUS
AND EAT YOUR SLIPPERS.
MAYA:
SO WHAT DO I HAVE TO DO?
TINY:
BE FIRM.
SHOW THEM YOU'RE IN CHARGE
AND THEY'LL FOLLOW YOU FOREVER.
LIKE HOW ZIG
FOLLOWS YOU AROUND.
ZIG:
HEY!
(POP SONG PLAYS QUIETLY,
PHONE RINGS)
LOGAN:
UH, I NEED YOUR CONTACT FROM
THAT BUILDING SUPPLY COMPANY
TO ORDER LUMBER
FOR THE GARDENS.
WAIT. ISN'T THIS YOUR FAVOURITE
SONG, "MEOW MEOW QUACK"?
FRANKIE:
UGH! IT'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
GETS ME EVERY TIME.
THANKS.
(POP SONG CONTINUES)
CAT:
YOU TWO SEEM
TO REALLY GET ALONG.
FRANKIE:
OH. HE'S PRETTY AMAZING,
AND SMART,
AND FUN TO HANG OUT WITH-
CAT: YOU SHOULD STOP.
FRANKIE: WHY? WE'RE FRIENDS.
CAT: "AMAZING" FRIENDS?
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
I HAVE A BOYFRIEND
AND HE HAS A GIRLFRIEND -
WHO I'M SURE IS
GONNA BE OKAY.
CAT:
'KAY, MONOGAMOUS RELATIONSHIPS
ARE JUST ARTIFICIAL CONSTRUCTS.
IF TWO HUMANS LIKE EACH OTHER,
A TITLE ISN'T A WALL
THAT'S GONNA KEEP THEM APART.
I'M NOT GONNA STOP
HANGING OUT WITH LOGAN
JUST BECAUSE YOU DON'T THINK
GUYS AND GIRLS CAN BE FRIENDS.
CAT:
THEY CAN BE FRIENDS,
JUST NOT IF THERE ARE FEELINGS.
(INTERNS CHATTER,
PHONES RING)
LOGAN: HEY. WHOA.
FRANKIE: (GASPS)
JUST WONDERING IF YOU WANTED ME
TO WALK YOU HOME?
UM... WHY- UH,
WHY WOULD I WANT THAT?
WITH GLORIA MISSING AND ALL,
YOU SHOULDN'T WALK HOME ALONE.
I'M SURE I'LL BE OKAY.
LOGAN:
COME ON, SMALL FRY,
DON'T MAKE ME WORRY ABOUT
SOMEONE ELSE I CARE ABOUT.
(RECEDING FOOTSTEPS)
(TRAFFIC RUMBLES)
MAYA:
LENA. EVERETT. CAN YOU GUYS
COME HERE FOR A SEC?
SO... THINGS ARE GONNA CHANGE
AROUND HERE, OKAY?
EVERETT: OKAY.
LENA: CAN I GO BACK TO WATCHING
REAL HOUSEWIVES, NOW?
MAYA:
OKAY, BUT I'M SERIOUS.
FROM NOW ON, YOU TWO
ARE GONNA TREAT ME BETTER.
OKAY, YOU'RE GOING
TO BE NICE TO ME,
YOU'RE GOING TO LISTEN,
AND NO MORE PRANKS, OKAY?
LENA: OKAY, SURE, WHATEVER.
MAYA: GREAT.
I'M GLAD WE HAD THIS CHAT.
(CHAIR SCRAPES ACROSS FLOOR)
HEY! I THOUGHT WE SAID
NO MORE PRANKS.
LENA:
THAT WASN'T ME.
(CHANDELIER RATTLES)
KIDS: (FRIGHTENED GASPS)
MAYA: JUST STOP IT, OKAY?
LENA: I'M NOT! EVERETT...
IS THIS YOU?
EVERETT: WHAT DO WE DO?
MAYA:
JUST BACK OUT, SLOWLY...
AND THEN...
BOW DOWN TO YOUR MASTER
'CAUSE I GOT YOU GUYS!
ZIG: ♪ Say hello
to the bad guy! ♪
EVERETT AND LENA: (GIGGLE)
I WAS SO SCARED.
LENA: NOT ME.
MAYA: YEAH RIGHT.
OKAY, BUT CAN WE AGREE NOW -
WE'RE EVEN, NO MORE PRANKS?
EVERETT:
OKAY, NO MORE PRANKS.
MAYA:
AND YOU HAVE TO ADMIT TO ME
THAT THAT WAS AWESOME.
LENA:
OKAY... IT WAS MILDLY AWESOME...
ESPECIALLY SINCE
IT INVOLVED ZIG.
I THINK SHE FINALLY LIKES ME.
ZIG:
ACTUALLY, I KINDA THINK
SHE LIKES ME. (LAUGHS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
ZOE: EVERYONE'S GONE?
GRACE: EVERYONE BUT BAIN.
APOLOGIZING TO HIM CAN'T
POSSIBLY BE MORE EMBARRASSING
THAN WHEN YOU ACTUALLY
FLIRTED WITH HIM.
ZOE: (LAUGHS DRYLY)
GRACE: (CHUCKLES)
UH, I THOUGHT YOU SAID
HE WAS IN HERE.
MAYBE HE'S IN
HIS OFFICE.
(KNOCKING)
(DOOR CREAKS OPEN)
ZOE:
OH MY GOD.
IT'S GLORIA CHIN.
GRACE:
THE MISSING GIRL?
WHY WOULD HE HAVE THAT?
BECAUSE TRISTAN
WAS RIGHT...
(LAUGHS) DID YOU HEAR THAT?
"TRISTAN WAS RIGHT."
BUT IF THEY HAD ONLY
LISTENED TO ME,
WHAT HAPPENED NEXT
COULD'VE BEEN AVOIDED...