(CAMERA BEEPS ON)
TRISTAN: WELCOME BACK.
SO THIS IS WHERE THE STORY
GETS REALLY FREAKING CREEPY.
YOU SEE, ZOE AND GRACE WERE
CONVINCED OUR SCIENCE TEACHER
WAS RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE MISSING GIRL
AND WILLING TO DO ANYTHING
TO PROVE IT.
I JUST REALLY WISH
THEY HADN'T DONE THIS...
ZOE:
(EXHALES NERVOUSLY)
THIS IS A BAD IDEA.
MAYBE WE SHOULD LEAVE
THE DETECTIVE WORK
TO THE POLICE.
GRACE:
THE COPS GET A THOUSAND TIPS
A DAY.
THEY NEED EVIDENCE
TO FOLLOW UP.
YOU'RE NOT SCARED,
ARE YOU?
THAT OUR WEIRDO TEACHER
WILL CATCH US BREAKING
INTO HIS TRUCK?
YES.
AND YOU SHOULD BE, TOO.
WE NEED TO KNOW
IF HE'S THE PERV TAKING GIRLS.
OKAY, JUST HURRY UP!
I'M DOING MY BEST.
THIS IS HARDER
THAN IT LOOKS ONLINE.
WAIT, YOU'VE NEVER
DONE THIS BEFORE?
WAIT, YOU HAVE?
I AUDITIONED
FOR FAST & FURIOUS SIX.
THE DIRECTOR WENT
A DIFFERENT DIRECTION.
HMPH.
BIG MISTAKE.
GRACE: HUGE.
(WINDOW HISSES OPEN)
SOMEONE SHOULD GIVE
HOARDERS A CALL.
(GRACE AND ZOE GRUNT
AS THEY CLIMB IN)
AGH!
(FRIGHTENED GASP)
GRACE:
AW! THE LITTLE GUY'S
MORE SCARED OF YOU.
ZOE:
YEAH, I SERIOUSLY DOUBT THAT.
(PAPERS FALL FROM FOLDER)
OH MY GOD.
OH MY GOD. OH MY GOD.
THESE... (SOMEONE WHISTLES
NEARBY)
THESE ARE ALL MISSING GIRLS.
(WHISTLING)
BOTH: (GASP)
ZOE: IT'S BAIN.
(BLANKET RUSTLES)
(FLIES BUZZ)
(WINDOW BANGS SHUT)
(KEYS JINGLE,
BAIN RESUMES WHISTLING)
(DOOR OPENS,
BAIN WHISTLES)
ZOE:
WHAT'RE WE GONNA DO?
(ENGINE STARTS)
GRACE:
(HUSHED) GET COMFORTABLE.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh... ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
LENA:
I'D RATHER DIE!
MAYA:
YOU WILL,
FROM SKIN CANCER,
IF YOU DON'T PUT ON
THIS RASH GUARD.
LENA: BUT MY FRIENDS'LL
MAKE FUN OF ME.
MAYA: THEN THEY'RE NOT REALLY
YOUR FRIENDS, ARE THEY?
OH NO,
WHEN DID I BECOME MY MOTHER?
WHAT'S WRONG?
ZIG:
(GROWLS MENACINGLY)
MAYA: IT'S NOT FUNNY. UGH!
ZIG, EVERETT AND LENA: (LAUGH)
ZIG:
MY AUDIENCE DISAGREES.
SORRY. I'M JUST SO EXCITED
FOR THE ZOMBIE WALK.
THAT'S THIS WEEKEND,
RIGHT?
YEAH.
OH, DON'T TELL ME
YOU HAVE TO WORK.
NOT YET.
BUT MY BOSS IS SO BUSY.
(SIGHS) AND I KNOW THAT
YOU WANNA IMPRESS HER
BY BEING SUPER-NANNY,
BUT...
I BARELY EVER SEE YOU
ANYMORE.
WELL, YOU'RE SEEING ME
RIGHT NOW.
YES, BUT ALONE...
WHERE I CAN DO THIS.
(KISS)
EVERETT: EW!
ZIG: WITHOUT THAT.
LENA: HI, ZIG!
(SIGHS) I KNOW,
I MISS YOU TOO.
SO YOU'LL TALK YOUR BOSS
ABOUT SATURDAY?
OKAY. AS LONG AS YOUR BICEPS
TALK TO LENA ABOUT SUN SAFETY.
FRANKIE:
OKAY, WHAT ABOUT THIS ONE?
LOGAN:
MISSING SINCE FEBRUARY...
TAKEN FROM SCHOOL,
DURING LUNCH HOUR...
HEY, IT'S COOL OF YOU
TO SPEND YOUR LUNCH HOUR
LOOKING THROUGH THESE MISSING
PERSONS REPORTS WITH ME.
UH... WHAT ABOUT THIS ONE?
IT'S... MISSING ONLY A MONTH.
NEARBY.
COULD BE RELATED.
(LOGAN'S PHONE BUZZES)
FRANKIE: WHAT IS IT?
LOGAN: A TEXT FROM GLORIA.
GLORIA: (ON VIDEO)
THEY HAVE ME HERE... (SOBS)
AND THEY WON'T LET ME GO...
UNLESS SOMEONE GIVES THEM
TEN THOUSAND DOLLARS.
IF YOU TELL ANYONE
THEY SENT THIS,
THEY'LL HURT ME...
HONEY, I'M SO SCARED...
WE NEED TO CALL
THE POLICE.
WELL, NO, WE CA- WE CAN'T.
THEY'LL HURT HER.
OKAY, THEN WHAT DO WE DO?
I... I DON'T KNOW.
GET TEN THOUSAND DOLLARS?
WHAT, LIKE FROM THE BANK?
SURE, I'LL JUST TAKE IT
OUT OF MY TRUST FUND.
UM... SORRY.
I'M... FREAKING OUT RIGHT HERE.
WELL, MAYBE YOU COULD ASK
GLORIA'S PARENTS FOR HELP?
NO, THEY'D THINK
I'M TRYING TO SCAM THEM.
THEY NEVER THOUGHT I WAS
GOOD ENOUGH FOR THEIR GIRL.
WELL,
MAYBE THEY'RE RIGHT.
WHAT? HOW CAN YOU
SAY THAT?
'CAUSE MY GIRLFRIEND'S
IN TROUBLE, AND...
I'M FALLING FOR SOMEONE ELSE.
(GLASS CLATTERS
AND SPILLS)
FRANKIE:
I AM SO SORRY.
UH, NO, IT'S...
IT'S MY FAULT.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE SAID ANYTHING.
I KNOW YOU HAVE A BOYFRIEND.
YEAH, I DO
AND HIS NAME IS... WINSTON.
HIS NAME'S WINSTON.
HERE. HERE. TAKE THESE.
UM... WHAT IF I ASKED MY DAD
FOR HELP?
MAYOR HOLLINGSWORTH?
NO, HE'D CALL THE COPS.
YOU CAN'T TELL HIM.
YOU HAVE TO PROMISE ME.
FINE, I PROMISE,
BUT... WHAT CAN I DO?
LOGAN:
JUST... DO WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
JUST BE HERE.
(TRUCK RUMBLES TO A HALT)
(GEARSHIFT CLUNKS)
ZOE:
WE'RE STOPPING.
WHERE DO YOU THINK WE ARE?
GRACE:
HIS HOUSE, PROBABLY.
ZOE:
GREAT. WE FOLLOWED THE PREDATOR
BACK TO HIS LAIR.
I WONDER WHICH ONE OF US
HE'S GONNA KILL FIRST.
PROBABLY ME,
NO OFFENSE.
GRACE:
NONE TAKEN.
WE'RE GOING TO GET OUT OF HERE,
WE JUST NEED TO WAIT
UNTIL HE GETS INTO THE HOUSE.
(BAIN WHISTLES TUNELESSLY)
(DOOR CLOSES,
WINDOW POPS OPEN)
ZOE: ARE WE GOOD:
GRACE: YEAH.
LET'S GO.
ZOE AND GRACE:
(GRUNTING WITH EFFORT)
OH! MY BRACELET!
IT SAYS MY NAME ON IT.
IF IT'S IN THE VAN,
HE'LL FIND IT.
NOT IF THE POLICE
FIND HIM FIRST.
(DIALING BEEPS, RINGING)
911 OPERATOR:
NINE-ONE-ONE,
WHAT'S YOUR EMERGENCY?
ZOE:
I THINK I HAVE SOME INFORMATION
ON THAT MISSING GIRL.
(DOOR CLOSES,
APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS)
(GASPS AWAKE)
WHAT?
JORDYN:
I SAID I'D BE HOME BY TEN,
DIDN'T I?
MAYA:
UM, YOU SAID EIGHT,
ACTUALLY.
JORDYN: OH, CRAP.
MAYA: (CHUCKLES)
I HOPE YOU DIDN'T HAVE PLANS.
MAYA:
JUST A MOVIE DATE
WITH MY BOYFRIEND,
BUT WE CAN RESCHEDULE.
I GIVE THEM
A GORGEOUS RECORD
AND THEY COME BACK AND TELL ME
THERE ISN'T A SINGLE.
MM. OH, I HOPE YOU CAN TAKE
A SHORT BREAK SATURDAY.
JORDYN: WHAT'S SATURDAY?
MAYA: UH, THE ZOMBIE WALK.
MY BOYFRIEND REALLY WANTS TO GO
AND I'VE BARELY SEEN HIM
ALL SUMMER
BECAUSE I'VE BEEN WORKING
TWENTY-FOUR-SEVEN.
I DIDN'T REALIZE YOU FOUND
THIS JOB TOO DEMANDING.
MAYA:
OH, NO, NO, NO.
NOT AT ALL.
UM, NO, I LOVE THE JOB.
THE KIDS ARE GREAT,
AND I'M LEARNING
SO MUCH FROM YOU.
GOOD.
'CAUSE I KNOW YOU WANNA WORK
IN MUSIC ONE DAY.
MAYA:
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
JORDYN:
SACRIFICE IS PART OF THE GAME,
YOU KNOW?
STUFF HAPPENS.
WHICH IS WHY I NEED
DEPENDABLE PEOPLE.
I AM DEPENDABLE PEOPLE.
BUT NOT SATURDAY.
I'LL... I'LL TELL ZIG
I CAN'T MAKE IT.
BEAUTIFUL.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
ZOE:
LOOKS LIKE BAIN IS A NO-SHOW.
GRACE:
SO, SHOULD WE TELL THE OFFICE
WE NEED A NEW SCIENCE TEACHER?
OR WE COULD GO TO THE BEACH
AND PLAY?
TOGETHER?
I MEAN, ONLY IF... YOU WANT.
RACE YOU TO THE DOOR?
(DOOR OPENS)
MR. BAIN:
NOT SO FAST, YOUNG SCIENTISTS.
ZOE: OH NO.
TRISTAN: OH YES.
MR. BAIN:
EXCUSE MY TARDINESS.
FOR SOME REASON, THE POLICE
WANTED TO QUESTION ME
ABOUT THE DISAPPEARANCE
OF GLORIA CHIN.
THE FROZEN TREAT
PRINCESS?
MR. BAIN:
SOMEONE THOUGHT THAT...
I WAS RESPONSIBLE.
BUT, LUCKILY, THE POLICE
DIDN'T FIND ANY REASON
TO PURSUE THEIR INVESTIGATION.
(VIDEO GAME MUSIC PLAYS,
CHARACTERS SHOUT AND SCREAM)
SUCK IT, NEWB!
(CHARACTER GRUNTS WITH EFFORT,
VIDEO GAME BYSTANDERS SHOUT)
(TV SHUTS OFF)
WHA- WHAT?!
(ANGRY BREATHS)
(FRIGHTENED GASP)
SERIOUSLY?
I TRIED CALLING YOUR NAME.
YOU DIDN'T RESPOND.
YEAH, BECAUSE I WAS IN
THE MIDDLE OF A GAME.
FRANKIE:
OKAY, THAT HAS A LOT
OF CAFFEINE IN IT
AND LONG TERM EXPOSURE COULD
DEFINITELY CAUSE KIDNEY DAMAGE.
WELL, LUCKILY I HAVE A TWIN
THAT WILL BE THE PERFECT MATCH.
AND I WOULD SAY YES
IN A HEARTBEAT.
YOU KNOW THAT, RIGHT?
(SNORTS) WHAT DO YOU WANT,
FRANKS?
I NEED TO BORROW YOUR BIRTHDAY
MONEY FROM GRANDPA.
HUNTER: YOU ALREADY SPENT
YOURS?
FRANKIE: NO, I NEED MORE.
YOU NEED
TEN THOUSAND DOLLARS?
PLEASE, HUNTER? I WOULDN'T ASK
IF I HAD OTHER OPTIONS.
OH MY GOD,
YOU-YOU'RE PREGNANT!
THIS IS WHY YOU'VE BEEN
IGNORING WINSTON ALL SUMMER!
(AMUSED) NO!
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
AND... I HAVEN'T BEEN
IGNORING HIM.
I'VE JUST BEEN BUSY
WITH WORK.
THEN WHY DO YOU NEED
THE MONEY?
FRANKIE:
SOMEONE'S IN TROUBLE.
SOMEONE I CARE ABOUT,
AND I NEED TO HELP.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU WANT ME TO SAY.
FRANKIE:
YES.
HUNTER:
(SIGHS)
♪♪
(NERVOUS, SHAKY BREATHS)
AGH! OH!
GRACE, GET OFF!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
(STRUGGLING GRUNTS)
GRACE: (LAUGHING)
YOU SAID YOU WANTED ME
TO TEACH YOU SELF DEFENSE.
ZOE:
I DO, BUT IT'S POINTLESS.
YOU'RE WAY STRONGER THAN ME
AND SO IS BAIN.
IF THE COPS CLEARED HIM,
HE'S PROBABLY NOT THE ONE
TAKING THE GIRLS.
SOMEONE IS,
AND HE'S OUT THERE.
GRACE:
WHICH IS WHY YOU SHOULD LEARN
TO PROTECT YOURSELF.
DO YOU THINK I WAS BORN
THIS WAY?
OKAY. LET'S TRY THIS
ONE MORE TIME.
♪ I'm letting go
so lose control... ♪
GRACE: READY?
ZOE: (SIGHS) SURE.
OH!
(STRUGGLING GRUNTS)
GRACE:
NICE ONE.
(STRUGGLING GRUNT)
ZOE AND GRACE:
(LAUGHING)
ZOMBIE WALKERS:
(GROWLING AND MOANING)
MAYA:
AAARGH!
MAYA: (LAUGHS) HI.
ZIG: OH HO-HO-HO.
WOW, DEAD LOOKS GOOD
ON YOU.
TECHNICALLY,
ZOMBIES ARE UNDEAD.
ZIG:
OH, WELL, YOU CAN BE
WHATEVER YOU WANT
AS LONG AS I HAVE YOU
TO MYSELF TODAY.
(KISSING)
EVERETT: EW!
LENA: HI, ZIG!
(SIGHS) ABOUT THAT...
(SIGHS) YOU DIDN'T ASK
FOR THE DAY OFF?
I DID, IT'S JUST...
JORDYN NEEDED ME.
(SNORTS, UPSET)
TRY TO BE UNDERSTANDING.
YEAH, I HAVE BEEN, MAYA.
ALL SUMMER.
BUT TODAY WAS IMPORTANT.
WE MADE PLANS.
WELL, YOU THINK I WANNA
SPEND TWENTY-FOUR-SEVEN
WITH THESE KIDS?
NO. I WOULD WAY RATHER
BE WITH YOU.
BUT YOU CARE TOO MUCH
ABOUT IMPRESSING YOUR BOSS.
COME ON,
DON'T BE MAD.
WE CAN STILL HAVE
LOADS OF FUN TODAY.
I'M NOT MAD.
I'M JUST... DISAPPOINTED.
WELL, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
ZIG: (SIGHS)
ZOMBIE WALKERS: (GROWLING)
IT'S MY DAY OFF, TOO.
I DON'T WANNA SPEND IT
LOOKING AFTER
SOMEONE ELSE'S KIDS.
WHERE'S YOUR SISTER?
(ZOMBIE WALKERS GROWL)
WAITING FOR ME?
DON'T WORRY. I'M NOT THE ONE
WHO GOES MISSING THIS SUMMER.
(GASPS) OOPS!
I'M GETTING AHEAD OF MYSELF.
NOW, WHERE WAS I?
OH, RIGHT.
THE SUMMER WAS GETTING HOTTER
AND HOTTER...
(LAUGHS)
♪ I put the needle
in the groove ♪
♪ To a song
that fits the mood ♪
(RECORD SCRATCHES)
OH, AND ZOE WAS GETTING CLOSER
TO GRACE.
♪ Bright red chords
on jet-black vinyl... ♪
(GIGGLING)
GRACE: HELSINKI.
ZOE:
I SAID ANYWHERE
IN THE WORLD.
GRACE:
FINNS ARE SELF-SUFFICIENT,
STRAIGHTFORWARD,
AND VALUE PRIVACY.
ZOE:
SO YOU THINK
YOU'RE BETTER OFF ALONE?
WOW, YOU'RE LIKE
SERIOUSLY DAMAGED.
MUST BE LIKE
LOOKING IN A MIRROR.
ZOE:
(LAUGHS)
♪ Primal... ♪
♪ It hits my hips
before my mind ♪
ZOE:
WANT ANOTHER?
ZOE: ME TOO.
GRACE AND ZOE: (LAUGH)
GRACE:
I'LL GET THIS ONE.
♪ Shoes slapping
on the floor ♪
♪ Come on,
let's rock some more ♪
ZOE: DON'T... DO THAT.
MILES: HEY.
(LAUGHING)
OH, I THOUGHT WE WERE
GONNA HANG THIS SUMMER.
ZOE: I'VE BEEN BUSY.
MILES: BECOMING BFFS
WITH THE QUEEN OF DARKNESS?
GRACE IS
MY SCIENCE PARTNER.
SHE'S ALSO HOPELESSLY
IN LOVE WITH YOU.
GRACE ISN'T GAY.
(LAUGHS)
SHE DOESN'T DRESS LIKE THAT
TO IMPRESS GUYS.
WELL, EVEN IF SHE IS,
SHE KNOWS I'M NOT.
MILES:
MM. YOU DON'T PICK
WHO YOU FALL FOR.
BESIDES, I'VE BEEN
WATCHING YOU TWO.
SHE HANGS ON EVERY WORD
YOU SAY.
FIRST, STALKER MUCH?
SECOND, SO DO YOU.
I KNOW, WHICH IS WHY
YOU SHOULD CALL ME.
(LAUGHING)
♪ Primal... ♪
♪ Oh oh-oh-oh-oh yeah! ♪
GRACE:
SO WHAT DID MILES
HAVE TO SAY?
♪ You know you feel it... ♪
♪♪
(BIRDS CHIRP,
FOUNTAIN WATER FLOWS)
FRANKIE:
ANY LUCK WITH THE BANK?
LOGAN:
WHEN I ASKED FOR A LOAN,
THEY LAUGHED IN MY FACE.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S WHY
I WANTED TO GO INTO POLITICS.
SO I COULD MAKE A DIFFERENCE
FOR THE OTHER 99 PERCENT.
WOW.
I RESPECT THAT
AND I RESPECT YOU,
WHICH IS WHY... HERE.
WHAT'S THIS?
IT'S TEN THOUSAND
DOLLARS.
THIS ISN'T FROM YOUR DAD,
IS IT?
I SAID I WOULDN'T TELL
AND I DIDN'T.
WELL, THIS FEELS WEIRD.
ME TAKING MONEY FROM YOU,
FOR HER.
WHERE ELSE ARE YOU
GONNA GET IT?
I GUESS,
BUT I'M GONNA PAY YOU BACK.
YOU KNOW THAT, RIGHT?
UH, EVERY CENT.
UM... I DON'T KNOW HOW,
BUT I WILL.
JUST BE SAFE, AND TEXT ME
WHEN YOU GET HOME.
LOGAN:
YEAH. FRANKIE...
MMM...
YOU'RE THE BEST GIRL
IN THE WORLD.
YOU KNOW THAT, RIGHT?
MAYA: LENA! LENA?
EVERETT: YOU LOST MY SISTER.
MAYA:
I DIDN'T LOSE HER, OKAY?
I JUST MISPLACED HER.
THINK, MAYA.
IF I WERE A TEN-YEAR-OLD,
WHERE WOULD I BE?
EVERETT: ICE CREAM!
MAYA: NOT NOW, EVERETT.
(ZOMBIE WALKERS MOAN
AND GROWL)
MAYA:
(RELIEVED SIGH)
THANK YOU.
I AM SO HAPPY YOU'RE OKAY,
AND YOU ARE SO GROUNDED!
LENA:
YOU WANTED TO SPEND THE DAY
WITH ZIG.
I DON'T SEE WHY
YOU'RE SO UPSET.
MAYA:
BECAUSE YOU COULD'VE
GOTTEN HURT!
LENA:
AND THEN MY MOM WOULDN'T
HELP YOU WITH YOUR MUSIC.
I KNOW THAT'S THE ONLY REASON
YOU TOOK THIS JOB.
THAT'S NOT TRUE!
OKAY,
IT'S A LITTLE TRUE.
LENA:
I GET IT, OKAY? NOBODY WANTS
TO HANG OUT WITH ME.
NOT YOU.
NOT MY MOM.
SHE'S JUST REALLY BUSY
WITH THIS RECORD RIGHT NOW.
BUT ONCE THAT'S DONE...
THERE'LL BE ANOTHER ONE,
AND ANOTHER ONE.
YOUR MOM LOVES YOU.
I KNOW THAT.
THEN SHE SURE SUCKS
AT SHOWING IT.
MR. BAIN:
WHO CAN KNOW THE DISTANCE
OF AN OBJECT FAR AWAY?
WE ALL CAN. HOW?
GRACE:
BY USING THE FOCAL LENGTH
OF OUR CAMERAS.
MR. BAIN:
YES, AND BY FOLLOWING
THE FORMULA ON THIS CHALK
BOARD.
NOW, IT'S TIME TO START PUTTING
THE THEORY INTO PRACTICE.
GRACE: WHAT?
ZOE: NOTHING.
MR. BAIN:
WE'LL START BY MEASURING
YOUR PARTNER'S HEIGHT.
COME HERE.
GRACE:
OKAY, YOU'VE BEEN ACTING
LIKE A WEIRDO SINCE YESTERDAY.
WHAT GIVES?
IT'S MILES... HE UH...
HAS THIS CRAZY THEORY
THAT YOU'RE IN LOVE
WITH ME.
WOW.
THIS IS EMBARRASSING.
I WOULD'VE SAID
SOMETHING BUT-
OH MY GOD.
IT'S TOTAL BS.
SOUNDS LIKE MILES
HAS THE HOTS FOR YOU.
YEAH, HE KEEPS
ASKING ME OUT.
GRACE: DO YOU LIKE HIM?
ZOE: HE LOOKS GOOD
IN A BATHING SUIT.
SOUNDS LIKE TRUE LOVE.
BOTH: (LAUGH)
ZOE: YEAH, AND WHAT DO YOU
KNOW ABOUT THAT?
GRACE:
YOU KNOW THAT FEELING YOU GET
ON A ROLLER COASTER,
RIGHT BEFORE
YOU GO OVER THE HILL?
YOUR HEART'S
IN YOUR THROAT.
YOU'RE EXCITED,
BUT ALSO TERRIFIED...
GRACE: AND THEN, WHOOSH!
ZOE: PURE JOY...
UNTIL YOU GET TO THE BOTTOM
AND THEN ALL YOU WANT
IS MORE.
GRACE:
ONCE YOU'VE FELT THAT WAY,
EVERYTHING ELSE IS POINTLESS.
YEAH, WELL... MILES AND I BARELY
KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT EACH OTHER.
WE HAVEN'T BEEN FRIENDS
THAT LONG.
GRACE:
NEITHER HAVE WE AND I KNOW
ALL SORTS OF THINGS ABOUT YOU.
WELL, THAT'S DIFFERENT.
BECAUSE I HAVE OVARIES?
NO. BECAUSE...
I FEEL LIKE
I'VE KNOWN YOU FOREVER.
BETTER WATCH OUT,
DRAMA.
MAYBE YOU'RE THE ONE
IN LOVE WITH ME.
(BUS RUMBLES)
JORDYN:
♪ SUMMER'S HOT,
SO ARE YOU... ♪
♪ BUT THAT DOESN'T GIVE YOU
THE RIGHT ♪
♪ TO STEP ALL OVER MY HEART... ♪
♪ MY HEART... ♪
HEY. IS THAT
THE NEW SINGLE?
JORDYN:
YEAH. IT'S NOT QUITE THERE YET,
BUT IT'S HEADED
IN THE RIGHT DIRECTION.
MAYA:
COOL. SO UM...
I GUESS THAT MEANS
YOU HAVE A MINUTE?
JORDYN:
UH... EXACTLY ONE.
THEN A CONFERENCE CALL
WITH THE STUDIO.
WHAT'S UP?
OKAY. UM... WOW.
I THINK YOU NEED TO SPEND
MORE TIME WITH YOUR KIDS.
JORDYN: WHAT?
MAYA: SORRY.
I WAS GONNA EASE INTO THAT
AND THEN THE TIME LIMIT
MADE ME PANIC.
OH, CAN I JUST START OVER?
OR BETTER YET,
CAN YOU JUST FORGET
WHAT I JUST SAID?
(PHONE BUZZES)
JORDYN:
GIVE ME FIVE.
YOU PICKED AN AMAZING TIME
TO TELL ME HOW TO PARENT.
NO, NO, NO. THAT'S NOT
WHAT I MEANT TO DO.
UH... EXCEPT, I GUESS,
IT KIND OF WAS.
OKAY, UM... I GUESS
WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY IS...
I UNDERSTAND THAT
IN ORDER TO BE SUCCESSFUL,
YOU NEED TO MAKE SACRIFICES,
BUT YOUR KIDS DON'T...
(TO HERSELF)
NEITHER DOES ZIG.
SO WHAT'S YOUR ANSWER?
I STOP WORKING ON THIS ALBUM?
I LET SOMEONE ELSE
TAKE IT OVER?
MAYA: I DON'T KNOW.
JORDYN: NO, YOU DON'T.
'CAUSE YOU'RE A 16-YEAR-OLD
GIRL WHO HAS NO IDEA
ABOUT THE REAL WORLD.
OKAY, WELL, I DO KNOW
THAT YOUR KIDS ARE HURTING.
YOU DON'T THINK
THAT'S ON MY MIND
ALL THE TIME?
WELL... MAYBE WE COULD COME UP
WITH A SOLUTION TOGETHER.
OR MAYBE YOU COULD GO.
MAYA:
OKAY. I'M SORRY.
UM... I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
JORDYN:
NO, YOU WON'T.
WE'RE DONE HERE.
(ACTION MOVIE MUSIC PLAYS)
♪♪
WINSTON:
DON'T GO IN THE WAREHOUSE
ALONE!
(GIRL IN MOVIE SCREAMS)
WINSTON:
WHY DO PEOPLE IN THRILLERS
ALWAYS PUT THEMSELVES
IN DANGEROUS SITUATIONS?
SOMETIMES THEY HAVE
NO OTHER OPTION.
WINSTON:
YOU ALWAYS HAVE ANOTHER OPTION.
CALL THE POLICE.
CAN WE JUST SHUT UP
AND WATCH THE MOVIE?
WHOA! SOMEONE DIDN'T TAKE
THEIR HAPPY PILLS TODAY.
FRANKIE:
FORGET THIS STUPID MOVIE.
(RECEDING FOOTSTEPS,
DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
HUNTER:
OKAY, OBVIOUSLY YOU'RE
STRESSED OUT ABOUT SOMETHING,
BUT... YOU CAN'T TAKE IT OUT
ON WINSTON.
FRANKIE:
I KNOW. I'LL TRY TO BE NICER.
OR YOU COULD JUST TELL HIM
WHAT'S WRONG,
INSTEAD OF LEAVING HIM
HANGING.
I CAN'T.
BECAUSE THERE'S
ANOTHER GUY INVOLVED?
THAT'S THE "FRIEND"
YOU BORROWED THE MONEY FOR?
HIS NAME IS LOGAN AND...
HE NEEDED THE MONEY
FOR HIS GIRLFRIEND.
DO YOU KNOW HOW MESSED UP
THAT SOUNDS?
IT WAS THE ONLY WAY
TO KEEP HER SAFE.
WHAT WERE WE SUPPOSED
TO DO?
WINSTON:
LIKE I SAID...
YOU ALWAYS GO TO THE COPS...
UNLESS YOU'VE GOT SOMETHING
TO HIDE.
GRACE:
THERE'S A FOOD TRUCK
FESTIVAL TONIGHT.
WANNA CHECK IT OUT?
ZOE:
CAN'T. MADE PLANS.
GRACE: WITH WHO?
MILES: GREETINGS, NERDS.
ZOE:
SEE YOU TOMORROW?
(DOOR CLICKS OPEN)
MILES:
SO WHAT FINALLY GOT YOU
TO CALL ME?
ZOE:
I HAVE A HYPOTHESIS
TO TEST.
(KISS)
HAPPY TO BE YOUR LAB RAT.
(STUDENTS CHATTER,
DOOR BANGS SHUT)
(MARIACHI MUSIC PLAYS)
ZIG:
WELL, WE COULD BOYCOTT
HER ALBUM.
MAYA:
BUT IT'S GONNA BE
SO, SO GOOD.
ZIG:
THEN WE'LL ONLY DOWNLOAD IT
ILLEGALLY.
MAYA:
(MOANS)
COME ON,
LOOK AT THE BRIGHT SIDE, HUH?
NOW YOU GET TO SPEND ALL YOUR
TIME AT THE BEACH WITH ME.
THAT'S TRUE.
ZIG:
NOPE! NOT UNTIL I FIND
A BREATH MINT THOUGH.
MY LUNCH WAS PRETTY GARLICKY.
MAYA: AS IF I CARE.
(KISS)
YEAH, YOU SHOULD DEAL
WITH THAT.
ZIG:
OKAY.
MAYA:
(LAUGHS) UGH.
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER,
DISHES CLINK)
ZIG:
SO MY BREATH MUST'VE BEEN
PRETTY BAD, HUH?
WHAT'S WRONG? YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU JUST SAW A GHOST.
IT WASN'T A GHOST.
IT WAS GLORIA.
THAT'S RIGHT.
SHE'S BAAA-AAACK.