(ALARMS BLARE AND RING)
(QUIET BUZZ OF CHATTER
BECOMES PANICKED CHATTER)
(COUGHING,
PANICKED SCREAMS)
MILES: FRANKIE!
MAYA: FRANKIE!
MILES:
FRANKIE! (COUGHING)
HEY, HAVE EITHER OF YOU
SEEN FRANKIE?
UGH! (COUGHS)
WHERE'S FRANKIE?
BOY:
GO! NICE!
BECKY:
HI! POWER CHEER TRYOUTS?
AWESOME!
POWER CHEER?
♪ One, two, three, four!
Oh-oh-oh oh-oh! ♪
HAVE YOU SEEN FRANKIE?
(CHUCKLES)
WHO'S FRANKIE?
HOLLINGSWORTH.
DREW: OH, RIGHT, RIGHT.
BECKY: RIGHT.
OKAY, I HEARD
SHE'S AN ACE TUMBLER.
I NEED HER FOR THIS.
DEGRASSI'S ALREADY GOT
A CHEERLEADING TEAM.
NO. IT'S NOT CHEERLEADING.
IT'S POWER CHEER.
VERY DIFFERENT.
IT'S A SPORT.
WELL, THEN I AM A 100 PERCENT
BEHIND YOU.
IF YOU GET YOUR TEAM TOGETHER
IN TIME,
YOU CAN EVEN PERFORM
AT THE GIANT CHEQUE CEREMONY.
OOH YAY.
(KISS)
IMOGEN:
OOH! NEW COUPLE ALERT!
I GUESS IT WASN'T
JUST THE GAS.
(LAUGHING)
BECKY:
DO YOU WANT TO TRY OUT
FOR POWER CHEER?
ZOE:
OH! COUNT ME IN!
I'LL LOOK TOTALLY HOT
IN A CHEERLEADING UNIFORM.
TRISTAN:
THAT MAKES TWO OF US.
UM... SORRY, TRISTAN,
GIRLS ONLY.
DALLAS:
IT'S OUR LAST TERM IN HIGH
SCHOOL, LETS IT MAKE COUNT!
ALLI:
HEY, HAVE YOU GUYS
SEEN CLARE?
DREW:
UH, NO. SHE WAS SUPPOSED TO SHOW
UP THIS MORNING TO HELP ME.
ALLI: I SHOULD GO FIND HER.
(BELL RINGS)
DREW:
HEY, DON'T WORRY. I'M SURE
CLARE DOESN'T CARE ABOUT US.
NO, THAT'S NOT IT.
POWER CHEER IS SUPPOSED
TO BE MY FRESH START.
IF ZOE'S ON THE TEAM,
IT'LL CONSTANTLY REMIND ME
OF ALL THE DRAMA
THAT HAPPENED LAST TERM.
DREW:
DON'T LET HER ON THE TEAM.
'CAUSE AS PRESIDENT
I DECREE THAT OUR FINAL TERM
WILL BE... AWESOME.
BECKY:
MM-HMM? (CHUCKLES)
I JUST HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
WHERE THE HECK MY VEEP IS!
(WATER RUNNING,
CLARE SIGHS)
(WATER SHUTS OFF)
(BREATHING HARD)
ALLI: CLARE!
CLARE: YEAH, I...
OH!
(DOOR LOCKS)
(VOMITING) OH...
ALLI:
OH, THAT IS NASTY!
DO YOU HAVE THE FLU?
BECAUSE YOU SHOULD REALLY
GO HOME IF YOU HAVE THE FLU.
(TOILET FLUSHES,
DOOR UNLOCKS)
CLARE:
NO, UH... NO FLU.
JUST UM...
BAD BREAKFAST BURRITO.
BUT IT'S PASSED.
I'M FINE NOW.
WELL, NOBODY GETS OVER
FOOD POISONING THAT QUICKLY.
YOU SURE IT'S NOT
MORNING SICKNESS?
(AWKWARD SILENCE)
THAT WAS A JOKE!
I DON'T WANT TO TALK
ABOUT IT.
CLARE, YOU'RE PREGNANT?!
I DON'T. WANT.
TO TALK ABOUT IT.
BUT YOU SAID YOU AND ELI
DIDN'T HOOK UP
WHEN YOU WENT TO NEW YORK!
WE DIDN'T. IT-
DREW WAS THE LAST...
NEVER MIND,
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
YEAH, CLARE,
IT KINDA MATTERS.
NO, IT DOESN'T.
A WEEK FROM NOW,
THIS NIGHTMARE WILL BE OVER.
I'VE ALREADY DECIDED.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
'DECIDED'?
(DIALING BEEPS,
RINGING)
HI, IS THIS THE WOMEN'S
CARE HEALTH CLINIC?
YEAH, I'D... I'D LIKE TO BOOK
AN APPOINTMENT
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh... ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
ZOE:
I'M SO EXCITED
FOR A NEW TERM!
TRISTAN:
EVEN THE SCHOOL PART?
ZOE:
EVERYTHING.
I FINALLY FEEL LIKE ALL
THE TRIAL STUFF IS BEHIND ME.
PLUS, I ALREADY HAVE
MY NEW THING
THAT'S GOING TO MAKE THIS
THE BEST TERM EVER!
TRISTAN:
OKAY, CAN YOU EVEN DO
A CARTWHEEL?
ZOE:
UH, HELLO? I WAS THE FOURTH
MAIN GIRL
IN THE TWELFTH
"BRING IT ON" MOVIE!
RIGHT. I MUST HAVE
MISSED THAT ONE.
ZOE:
THE PRODUCERS MADE US
TRAIN A TON.
SO I'M PROBABLY A BETTER
TUMBLER THAN MOST GIRLS HERE.
CHEERLEADING?
SERIOUSLY?
TRISTAN: SHUT UP, ZIG.
ZOE: HI, ZIG!
AND MAYA.
(SMIRKS,
LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
(PHONE DINGS)
STUDENTS:
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
I'M OUT.
SKIPPING ON THE FIRST DAY?
THAT ONLY MEANS ONE THING.
MAYA:
YEAH, THAT TRISTAN'S
TRYING TO AVOID ME.
SECRET LOVER.
WELL, I DON'T KISS
AND TELL. AND YES.
ZIG:
(CLEARS THROAT) SO...
I NEVER WOULD HAVE PEGGED YOU
FOR A POM-POM GIRL.
POWER CHEER IS A SPORT.
IF YOU SAY SO.
BUT, YOU KNOW,
IF YOU MAKE THE TEAM,
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
LESS TIME FOR ME.
ZOE:
PROBABLY.
YOU'LL JUST HAVE TO...
PINE AFTER ME FROM AFAR...
WHILE I'M IN MY SHORT
CHEERLEADING SKIRT.
(BELL RINGS)
MR. PERINO:
WELCOME TO YOUR FIRST
ECONOMICS CLASS.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE THINKING:
BORING.
BUT YOU'D BE WRONG,
(CLARE'S PHONE BUZZES)
AND LET ME TELL YOU WHY.
(PHONE BUZZING)
I'M SORRY, MISS EDWARDS,
IS MY LECTURE KEEPING YOU
FROM YOUR VERY IMPORTANT CALL?
BOY: (GIGGLES)
GIRL: (WHISPERS) BUSTED!
I'LL BE BACK IN MINUTE.
I'M SORRY.
HELLO?
THANK YOU FOR CALLING ME BACK.
NO, NO, I-I DON'T NEED
A CONSULTATION.
WELL, CAN I BOOK A PROCEDURE
AND A CONSULTATION
FOR THE SAME TIME?
WHY NOT? I CAN'T SIT AROUND
AND DO NOTHING.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY I HAVE TO WAIT.
DREW:
WAIT FOR WHAT?
(PHONE BEEPS OFF)
SHOULDN'T YOU BE
IN CLASS?
I HAVE A SPARE.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
CLARE: NOTHING.
DREW: NOTHING? REALLY?
WELL, I FIGURED
YOU MUST BE SUPER BUSY
TO IGNORE ALL MY TEXTS,
CALLS, AND E-MAILS
FOR THE ENTIRE
SPRING BREAK.
THAT'S WHY THEY CALL IT
A BREAK, DREW.
BECAUSE YOU TAKE
A BREAK.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, SIMPSON WANTS
THE RENEWAL PROJECT LAUNCH
CEREMONY
TO BE A SUCCESS, OKAY?
HOLLINGSWORTH
IS DONATING BIG MONEY
AND HE'S BRINGING
REPORTERS.
I DON'T CARE.
YOU DON'T CARE.
CLARE, THIS IS
YOUR SCHOOL, TOO.
YOU'RE THE VICE-PRESIDENT.
YOU CAN'T JUST DO
NOTHING!
FINE. FINE.
WHAT HAS TO BE DONE?
THE STUDENT COUNCIL OFFICE
IS A MESS.
I'LL CLEAN IT
AT LUNCH.
THERE'S LOTS
TO BE DONE.
I'VE GOT IT, OKAY?
(FRUSTRATED SIGH)
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
(PASSIONATE KISSING)
TRISTAN:
WE MISSED OUR FIRST
CHEMISTRY CLASS.
I DON'T THINK WE HAVE
ANY TROUBLE WITH CHEMISTRY.
ARE WE EVER GONNA TALK
ABOUT THIS?
YEAH, SURE.
LET'S TALK.
TRISTAN:
OKAY, WELL, I'M FINE
WITH THIS BEING A SECRET.
ACTUALLY,
I PREFER IT THAT WAY.
I JUST WANT TO KNOW
THAT ALL THIS KISSING...
ISN'T ALL ABOUT MAYA.
UH, LOOK, TRISTAN,
YOU KNOW I DON'T CARE
ABOUT MY STUPID
EX-GIRLFRIEND'S OPINION.
OKAY, WELL,
WHAT ABOUT YOUR DAD'S?
MILES:
(SIGHS) OH, MOOD KILLER.
TRISTAN: I'M SERIOUS!
MILES: 'KAY, DON'T WORRY.
THINGS AT HOME
HAVE BEEN FINE.
HEY, YOU KNOW I EVEN AGREED
TO DO THIS
CAMPAIGN PHOTO SESSION
WITH MY PARENTS.
MY DAD WAS PRETTY HAPPY
I SAID YES.
OH. AND WHEN DOES THAT
HAPPEN?
UH...
15 MINUTES FROM NOW.
CRAP, I'M LATE!
OH, WELL, I... OKAY.
♪ Hey now, make it loud,
I'm gonna be a wild child ♪
♪♪
♪ Today I'm living life,
Living like I don't give a... ♪
♪ De-damn-a-lam ♪
♪ Hey now, make it loud,
I'm gonna be a wild child ♪
♪♪
♪ De-damn-a-lam ♪
BECKY:
POWER CHEER IS A SPORT, GIRLS,
I NEED FINELY TUNED ATHLETES,
WHO AREN'T AFRAID TO TOSS,
TUMBLE,
AND PUSH THROUGH PAIN
TO GET TO THE CHAMPIONSHIPS.
YOU MEAN LIKE THIS?
(TUMBLING THUMPS)
GIRL:
(GASPS) WOW!
LOLA:
WOW, I'M NEVER MAKING
THE TEAM NOW.
GIRLS:
(CHEERING AND CLAPPING)
BECKY:
YOU UH... YOU KNOW A LOT
ABOUT CHEERLEADING, ZOE?
A SMIDGE.
(GIGGLES)
OKAY, WELL, THANKS TO EVERYONE
WHO TRIED OUT.
I'LL LET YOU KNOW
BY THE END OF THE DAY.
OH! AND THINK ABOUT SOME
AWESOME FUNDRAISING IDEAS
IN CASE YOU'RE SELECTED.
LIKE... HOLDING A BAKE SALE-
ZOE:
WELL, IN "BRING IT ON" TWELVE,
THE CASH-STRAPPED TEAM
RAISED MONEY
BY HOLDING A CHEERLEADER
AUCTION.
WELL, THAT'LL BE UP TO
WHOEVER'S PICKED FOR THE TEAM
TO DECIDE.
(BELL RINGS)
♪♪
♪ De-damn-a-lam ♪
(MILES SIGHS,
CLOCK CHIMES)
MILES:
I KNOW, I KNOW, I'M LATE.
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH:
I TEXTED AND CALLED.
WE WERE WORRIED.
MILES: I'M SO SORRY.
FRANKIE: YOU SHOULD BE.
I MISSED POWER CHEER TRYOUTS
TO BE HERE.
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH:
THAT'S ENOUGH, FRANKIE...
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
COME HERE.
FRANKIE:
MOM, SERIOUSLY?
HE ALWAYS DOES THIS.
MILES:
LOOK, ALL I WANTED TO DO
WAS TO MAKE YOU GUYS HAPPY.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
OKAY, THEN DON'T DO THINGS
YOU HAVE TO APOLOGIZE FOR.
JUST TAKE THE PHOTO,
OKAY?
NO, JUST FIRST EXPLAIN
TO ME WHY YOU WERE LATE.
I WAS BUSY.
DOING WHAT?
LET ME GUESS.
CUTTING CLASS?
SMOKING DOPE?
YOU HITTING ON
SOME GIRL?
MILES: NEVER MIND.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH: NO, MILES.
I WANT YOU TO EXPLAIN TO ME
WHAT YOU WERE SO BUSY DOING
THAT YOU COULDN'T BE
TO MY PHOTO SHOOT ON TIME?
MAKING OUT
WITH MY BOYFRIEND!
(EVERYONE GOES QUIET,
BIRDS CHIRP OUTSIDE)
(CLACKING FOOTSTEPS)
(HARD THUMP)
(BOX RIPS,
ITEMS CRASH)
(SIGHS) GREAT.
DREW:
NEED SOME HELP?
CLARE:
ALL GOOD. THANKS.
DREW:
CAN YOU PLEASE TELL ME
WHAT'S STUCK UP YOUR BUTT?
EXCUSE ME?
YOU IGNORE ME
ALL SPRING BREAK
AND THEN WHEN I FINALLY
SEE YOU,
YOU'RE ACTING LIKE
A COMPLETE AND TOTAL...
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
NEVER MIND.
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE.
DREW:
THAT'S NOT GOING TO WORK,
CLARE.
WE RUN STUDENT COUNCIL
TOGETHER.
WE'RE IN EACH OTHER'S LIVES
EVERY SINGLE DAY.
PLEASE DON'T
REMIND ME!
DREW:
LOOK, IS THIS BECAUSE BECKY
AND I ARE A COUPLE NOW?
'CAUSE WE'LL TRY AND KEEP
THE PDA TO A MINIMUM
WHEN YOU'RE AROUND.
CLARE:
I COULD CARE LESS
WHO YOU KISS.
TELL ME WHAT THE PROBLEM IS
SO I CAN FIX IT.
YOU CAN'T FIX IT!
WHAT THE HELL DID I EVER
DO TO YOU, CLARE?
(CHAIR THUDS)
YOU GOT ME PREGNANT!
DREW:
WE USED A CONDOM.
COULD'VE BEEN EXPIRED.
DREW: IT WASN'T.
CLARE: PUT IT ON WRONG?
DREW:
I DIDN'T PUT IT ON WRONG.
THEN WE ARE THAT
TINY PERCENTAGE
FOR WHOM THEY PROVE
INEFFECTIVE.
(EMOTIONAL SIGH)
HOW AM I GOING TO TELL BECKY?
OR-OR MY MOM?
CLARE:
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TELL ANYONE
ANYTHING
BECAUSE I'M GETTING
AN ABORTION.
I'M JUST GLAD
YOU HAVE A PLAN.
IS THERE ANYTHING
I CAN DO?
JUST KEEP IT A SECRET.
CLARE:
(SHAKY BREATH)
DREW:
(FOUNTAIN WATER SPLASHES)
(PHONE CHIMES)
BECKY THINKS I HAVE WHAT
IT TAKES TO BE ON POWER CHEER.
(SQUEALS EXCITEDLY)
FRANKIE: (LAUGHS EXCITEDLY)
HUNTER: NO BRAINS?
MILES:
GOOD MORNING, FAMILY.
EVERYONE EXCITED ABOUT
THE "DEGRASSI RENEWAL
LAUNCH PROJECT" TODAY?
I KNOW I AM!
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
STOP IT.
AM I DOING SOMETHING WRONG?
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH:
WE WANT TO TALK ABOUT
THIS BOYFRIEND OF YOURS.
BECAUSE IT'S RIDICULOUS.
(LAUGHS)
MILES:
KISSING SOMEONE IS RIDICULOUS?
WELL, THEN I GUESS ALL OF US
ARE RIDICULOUS - EXCEPT HUNTER.
HUNTER:
SUCK IT.
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH:
YOU'RE NOT GAY, MILES.
NEVER SAID I WAS.
FRANKIE:
AND YET YOU'RE KISSING TRISTAN
ON A REGULAR BASIS?!
I LIKE HIM.
WHY NOT?
FRANKIE: ARE YOU GUYS
A COUPLE?
MILES: MAYBE.
FRANKIE: SO YOU'RE GAY?
MILES: NO.
FRANKIE: BI?
FRANKIE: EXPERIMENTING
WITH FLUID SEXUALITY?
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
ENOUGH. YOU WERE DATING GIRLS
A FEW WEEKS AGO.
YOU'RE KISSING BOYS NOW?
IT'S UH... IT'S NOT RIGHT.
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH: HONEY...
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH: NO, NO,
WELL, SERIOUSLY THOUGH,
IT ISN'T.
'CAUSE OUR SON IS NOT GAY.
HE'S JUST A SPOILED BRAT
HELL BENT ON RUINING THE LAST
CRUCIAL WEEKS OF MY CAMPAIGN.
I'M NOT GONNA LET YOU.
WELL, IT'S NOT ALWAYS ALL ABOUT
YOU AND THIS STUPID ELECTION.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
IS THAT WHAT YOU TOLD
YOUR BOYFRIEND?
AH, THIS IS... WHAT A JOKE.
SCREW YOU.
MM.
ZIG:
NAH, HE GOES TO A DIFFERENT
SCHOOL NOW.
MAYA:
WELL, THAT'S GOOD.
ZOE:
BIG NEWS!
YOU'RE LOOKING AT DEGRASSI'S
NEWEST POWER CHEERLEADER!
MAYA:
CONGRATS. BUT THE POM-POMS
KIND OF TIPPED US OFF.
ZIG:
AND WHERE IS THAT SKIRT
THAT YOU PROMISED?
ZOE:
SHUSH! (CHUCKLES)
BECKY:
UH... HEY, ZOE,
CAN I TALK TO YOU?
ABSOLUTELY, CAPTAIN.
ABSOLUTELY.
BECKY:
LISTEN, YOU'RE A SPECTACULAR
TUMBLER
AND YOU HAVE GREAT
FUNDRAISING IDEAS,
BUT YOU DIDN'T MAKE
THE TEAM.
(STUNNED)
HUH?
THE GIRLS SAID
I WAS AWESOME.
AFTER EVERYTHING
YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH,
I MEAN WITH THE TRIAL
AND ALL...
THAT HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH CHEERLEADING.
STILL. I FEEL THE...
THE TEAM FEELS,
TO HAVE YOU OUT THERE
REPRESENTING THIS SCHOOL,
WITH ALL YOUR BAGGAGE...
MY BAGGAGE?
DO I NEED TO REMIND YOU
WHO'S RESPONSIBLE FOR THAT,
BECKY BAKER?
OF COURSE NOT.
BUT HAVING ZOE RIVAS
ON THE SQUAD
TAKES AWAY
FROM THE REST OF THE TEAM.
YOU'RE A DISTRACTION.
I'M REALLY SORRY.
WOW.
OKAY, SCREW HER.
ZIG:
YEAH, FORGET ABOUT
THAT STUPID TEAM.
IT'S NOT STUPID TO ME.
(BELL RINGS)
TEACHER:
ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE,
SETTLE DOWN. SETTLE DOWN.
I WANT YOU TO START READING
FROM THE TOP OF CHAPTER THREE
BEFORE WE REVIEW.
(CLARE'S PHONE BUZZES)
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
CLARE:
I GOT IN.
(LAUGHING)
ALLI: TO COLUMBIA?
CLARE: YES! YES!
ALLI:
FINALLY, SOME GOOD NEWS!
(LAUGHING)
(LAUGHING EXCITEDLY)
DALLAS:
(CLEARS THROAT)
CLARE'S BUM!
ALLI: HUH?
DALLAS: CLARE'S BUM!
CLARE: WHAT?
ALLI: (GASPS)
ALLI: CLARE!
CLARE: WHAT?
ALLI:
OH MY GOSH,
COME WITH ME.
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
DALLAS:
WHY DO I HAVE TO BE THE GUY
WHO NOTICES EVERYTHING?
CLARE:
SO A NEW YORK HOSPITAL
AND A HOME PREGNANCY TEST
WERE WRONG?
ALLI:
PERIOD EQUALS NOT PREGNANT.
NO BABY DREW TORRES,
AND THAT IS A GOOD THING.
I DON'T THINK
IT'S MY PERIOD.
I THINK SOMETHING'S WRONG
WITH THE BABY.
WHAT DO I DO?
GO SEE A DOCTOR.
COME WITH ME?
DO YOU WANT ME TO GET DREW?
I MEAN HE IS THE FATHER.
NO.
COME ON.
(STALL DOOR OPENS)
(STUNNED EXHALE)
(SIREN WAILS IN THE DISTANCE)
(PHONE RINGS,
LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
(EXHALES)
DOCTOR:
HOW'S THE CRAMPING?
IT'S BASICALLY GONE,
AND THE SPOTTING'S STOPPED.
GOOD. UM... DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHEN YOU CONCEIVED?
A BIT MORE
THAN A MONTH AGO.
DOCTOR:
OKAY, WELL, BASED ON THAT IT'S
TOO EARLY FOR AN ULTRASOUND,
SO WE'RE JUST GOING TO LET
NATURE ITS COURSE FOR A WHILE.
CLARE, IT'S PRETTY SURPRISING
YOU'RE PREGNANT AT ALL
CONSIDERING WHAT YOUR BODY
WENT THROUGH WITH THE CHEMO.
IT'S A MIRACLE.
DOCTOR:
WELL, SOME WOMEN NEVER CONCEIVE
AFTER CANCER.
BUT IT IS POSSIBLE?
YOU'RE LIVING PROOF.
IF THE CRAMPING
OR THE SPOTTING STARTS AGAIN,
I WANT YOU TO COME BACK.
OTHERWISE, MAKE AN APPOINTMENT
WITH THE NURSE
FOR YOUR NEXT PRENATAL EXAM.
I'M GONNA WRITE YOU OUT
A PRESCRIPTION FOR FOLIC ACID
'CAUSE EVEN THOUGH YOUR BABY'S
JUST THE SIZE OF A PEA,
CRUCIAL DEVELOPMENT HAS BEGUN.
THERE'S A BABY
INSIDE ME.
DOCTOR:
MM-HMM. IN A FEW WEEKS,
YOU SHOULD START
TO FEEL MOVEMENT.
JUST FLUTTERING, AT FIRST.
AND THEN, A FEW KICKS.
(BUZZ OF EXCITED CHATTER,
BAND TUNES UP)
(CAMERA SHUTTER SNAPS)
(BUZZ OF EXCITED CHATTER,
BAND TUNES UP)
MILES:
HEY, LET'S DITCH.
YOU WANNA SKIP
THE GIANT CHEQUE CEREMONY?
MILES:
YEAH, WELL, MY DAD
AND HIS CAMPAIGN STOOGES
WILL BE HERE ANY SECOND
AND I REALLY
DON'T WANNA BE, SO...
TRISTAN:
WELL, UH...
OKAY, I GUESS I'M NOT MEETING
THE PARENTS.
JENNIFER:
MILES HOLLINGSWORTH?
MISSED YOU AFTER THE PHOTO OP.
CAN I GET A QUOTE?
AFTER ALL, THIS IS YOUR SCHOOL.
MILES:
I'M BUSY.
JENNIFER:
OKAY, REAL QUICK THEN.
YOUR FATHER IS MAKING
A VERY GENEROUS DONATION
TO THE SCHOOL.
HE MUST BE YOUR HERO
AFTER EVERYTHING HE DOES
FOR THE COMMUNITY.
PERHAPS YOU CAN SHARE
SOME OF HIS WORDS OF WISDOM?
MILES:
WORDS OF WISDOM, HMM?
YEAH, I THINK WE CAN COME UP
WITH SOMETHING.
HEY, TRIS,
CAN YOU JUST GIVE ME A SECOND?
TRISTAN:
SURE.
GREAT! UM... OKAY,
SO WHAT IS THE LAST PIECE OF
ADVICE YOUR DAD GAVE TO YOU?
OH, THAT'S EASY.
BEING GAY IS RIDICULOUS.
(MICROPHONE SQUEALS)
SIMPSON:
OKAY, LADIES AND GENTS,
THEY SAY YOU CAN'T KEEP
A GOOD SCHOOL DOWN!
WELCOME ONE AND ALL
TO THE LAUNCH
OF THE DEGRASSI
RENEWAL PROJECT!
(CHEERING AND CLAPPING,
MARCHING BAND MUSIC PLAYS)
♪♪
ZOE:
BECKY! BECKY!
BECKY:
CAN'T TALK RIGHT NOW.
WE'RE WAITING FOR OUR CUE.
ZOE:
I JUST WANTED TO SAY
NO HARD FEELINGS.
THANKS, ZOE.
ZOE:
BUT I WISH YOU'D REALIZE
THAT...
EVERYONE HAS BAGGAGE
THAT COULD BE DISTRACTING.
EVEN YOU.
WHAT'RE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WHAT'S THAT CALLED
WHEN YOUR BOYFRIEND...
GETS HIS BEST GIRL FRIEND
KNOCKED UP?
OH...
I THINK IT'S CALLED BAGGAGE.
(MARCHING BAND MUSIC PLAYS)
(BAND BEGINS INTRO
TO ROUTINE)
BECKY:
READY, GIRLS?
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT!
(BAND PLAYS,
STUDENTS CHEER)
♪♪
(CROWD CHEERS AND WHISTLES)
OH MY GOODNESS.
(INSTRUMENTS BLOW WILDLY,
CROWD GASPS)
SIMPSON:
OH! OH! UH...
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
UGH!
YOU SHOULD BE HAPPY
YOU DIDN'T MAKE THAT TEAM.
ACTUALLY, I THINK A SPOT
JUST OPENED UP.
♪ Hey now, make it loud,
I'm gonna be a wild child ♪
(MARCHING BAND DRUMMING,
WHISTLE BLASTS)
♪ Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! ♪
♪ You hear the whistle blow,
hear the whistle blow, ho! ♪
APPARENTLY I AM A DISTRACTION.
♪ Hear-Hear the whistle blow,
hear the whistle blow, ho! ♪
hear the whistle blow ♪
♪ Hear-hear the whistle blow ♪
CLARE:
BUT WHAT IF THIS
IS MY ONLY CHANCE?
WHEN THAT DOCTOR SAID THE BABY
WAS GOING TO BE OKAY,
I WAS HAPPY. WHY?
ALLI:
CLARE, THE FROM THE FIRST DAY
I MET YOU,
YOU'VE HAD YOUR ENTIRE FUTURE
PLANNED OUT.
CLARE:
BUT WHAT IF THAT PLAN
IS WRONG?
SOMETIMES PLANS DON'T WORK OUT
LIKE THEY'RE SUPPOSED TO,
BUT THEY'RE BETTER
THAN YOU COULD HAVE IMAGINED.
I DON'T KNOW, MAYBE I'M
SUPPOSED TO HAVE THIS BABY?!
WHAT DO I DO?
I CAN'T TELL YOU,
SWEETIE.
I WISH YOU COULD.
PLEASE JUST GIVE ME
THE ANSWER.
ALLI:
OKAY...
THE ANSWER IS TO DO WHATEVER
CLARE EDWARDS WOULD DO,
BECAUSE SHE ALWAYS DOES
THE RIGHT THING.
(KNOCKING)
DREW: HEY.
CLARE: HEY.
(RECEDING FOOTSTEPS)
DREW:
SO... EVERYTHING'S OKAY?
YOU GOT YOUR PERIOD?
NO. IT WAS JUST
SOME SPOTTING.
IT'S NORMAL
WHEN YOU'RE PREGNANT,
SO... STILL PREGNANT.
OH. WELL, UM...
(CLEARS THROAT)
WHEN YOU GO FOR THE THING -
THE-THE PROCEDURE -
I CAN-
I CAN DRIVE YOU THERE
OR COOK SPAGHETTI FOR YOU
AFTERWARDS...
WHATEVER YOU NEED, CLARE,
I'M THERE.
DREW, I DON'T THINK I CAN
GO THROUGH WITH AN ABORTION.
IN MY HEAD, IT MAKES SENSE,
BUT IN MY HEART...
THERE'S A LITTLE PERSON
INSIDE ME -
PERSON THAT WE MADE.
OH MY GOD.
I NEED TO KEEP THE BABY.