♪♪
ALLI:
READY FOR SCHOOL?
ELI SAID HE WAS SENDING ME
A SURPRISE THIS MORNING,
FOR GETTING INTO COLUMBIA.
WELL, THAT'S SWEET!
EVEN AFTER YOU TOLD HIM
ABOUT YOUR SURPRISE?
I ACTUALLY HAVEN'T
TOLD HIM, YET.
CLARE!
I NEED TO FIND
THE PERFECT WORDS.
HOW ABOUT, "ELI, I'M PREGNANT
WITH DREW'S BABY?"
NOT ELEGANT ENOUGH?
WELL, WHAT'D YOU TELL
YOUR MOTHER?
I HAVEN'T ACTUALLY
DONE THAT YET EITHER.
CLARE!
I NEED TO DO THIS ALL
VERY CAREFULLY,
SO I CAN KEEP MY LIFE
ON TRACK.
BECAUSE YOU THINK YOU CAN
STILL GO TO NEW YORK,
AND BE WITH ELI?
I DON'T KNOW, MAYBE.
ELI AND I HAVE BEEN
THROUGH SO MUCH,
MAYBE WE CAN GET
THROUGH THIS, TOO.
(SIGHS)
ELI:
CLARE!
OH NO, WHAT DO I DO?
YOU FIND THE PERFECT WORDS,
BEFORE HE HEARS 'EM
FROM SOMEONE ELSE!
ELI:
SURPRISE!
I'M DONE MY EXAMS,
SO THE SUMMER JOB HUNT BEGINS!
S-SO YOU'RE JUST BACK?
THAT'S EXCITING,
RIGHT?
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
ELI:
YOU KNOW, WHAT I'M MOST
EXCITED ABOUT IS...
MAYBE CONTINUING THAT TALK
ABOUT OUR FUTURE?
CLARE:
YEAH, YEAH.
WE SHOULD DEFINITELY TALK
ABOUT OUR FUTURE.
TONIGHT, AFTER SCHOOL?
ELI:
I CAN'T WAIT.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Ooh-ohh-ohh... ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
WINSTON:
CHOMPY CHICKEN FOR THE WIN!
I'M SO GLAD YOUR DAD
GAVE YOU THE WHEELS!
HEY, HAVE YOU NOTICED FRANKIE'S
JUST BEEN A BIT WEIRD LATELY?
UM... I DON'T KNOW, MAN,
SHE'S A 14-YEAR-OLD GIRL,
SHE'S ALWAYS WEIRD.
(BELL RINGS)
MS. WOLFE:
AHEM. NOW, HELIUM WALKS
INTO A RESTAURANT,
AND THE WAITER SAYS,
"I'M SORRY, WE DON'T SERVE
NOBLE GASSES HERE."
HELIUM DOESN'T REACT.
AH, AND NEITHER DO MY STUDENTS.
OKAY, EVERYBODY,
TAKE A SEAT, SIT!
(WHISTLES)
TRISTAN:
(SCOFFS) NO WAY, I CALL DIBS!
WINSTON: HUH?
TRISTAN: BOYFRIEND DIBS.
THAT'S NOT A THING.
SURE IT IS.
(BAG UNZIPS)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
DITCHED BY MILES?
HM. BEEN THERE.
DON'T WORRY,
HE GETS BORED QUICKLY.
MS. WOLFE:
NOW, LOOK TO THE PERSON
BESIDE YOU,
THAT'S YOUR LAB PARTNER
FOR THE SEMESTER.
NOW, COME GRAB A LAB SHEET.
THANK YOU!
ZIG:
COME ON, MAYA,
I BELIEVE IN YOU!
I CAN'T...
HEY, NO FAIR!
THINK OF IT LIKE
TRAINING WHEELS!
OH!
AH! NO!
ZIG:
OHHHH!
ALL PRAISE THE VICTOR!
I HOPE I DIDN'T HURT YOU,
BLONDIE.
SERIOUS QUESTION,
ARE YOU ON STEROIDS?!
ALL RIGHT, GRACE.
LET ME SHOW YOU
HOW IT'S DONE.
OOOH!
(CHUCKLES)
AH, GOOD IDEA, TINY!
MAKE SURE TO RECORD
THIS EPIC SMACK DOWN
FOR POSTERITY.
OKAY, THREE...
TWO, ONE, GO!
TINY:
WHAT?!
COME ON MAN, ARE YOU GONNA LET
A GIRL SHOW YOU UP?
(TINY LAUGHS)
OH! OH MY GOSH, LOOK!
OH! OH! OH!
(LAUGHS)
OKAY, STOP MAN,
YOU'RE DISTRACTING ME!
ALL: OHHHH!
TINY: SNAP!
BOW DOWN, NOVAK.
THAT DOESN'T COUNT,
HE BROKE MY CONCENTRATION!
MAYA:
A LIKELY STORY!
(ALL LAUGH)
MS. GRELL:
SORRY, PHOTOCOPIER JAMMED!
SO STOP WHATEVER YOU'RE DOING
THAT YOU WEREN'T SUPPOSED
TO BE DOING!
WE'VE GOT A LOT TO COVER TODAY.
TODAY, WE'RE GONNA WORK
ON INTERPERSONAL SKILLS-
DON'T WORRY, SWEETHEART,
MAYBE YOUR BRA STRAP
GOT IN THE WAY. (CHUCKLES)
(BELL RINGS)
SO FIRST, I FIND A GIRL,
OR GUY, THAT MILES
CAN'T SAY NO TO,
THEN, I CONVENIENTLY
BRING TRISTAN
TO CATCH MILES IN THE ACT,
AND BOOM, BROKEN UP!
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I THINK WE SHOULD BE DONE
THIS ASSIGNMENT BY NOW!
WELL, I'M WORKING ON IT!
MORE IMPORTANT, WILL THAT BREAK
MILES AND TRISTAN UP?
MILES IS HAPPY.
SO? I'M NOT!
AWW, YOU LIKE MILES!
I KNEW IT!
FOR THE LAST TIME, NOT GAY!
OR HOMOPHOBIC.
I'M JUST...
MISSING MY BEST BRO.
THEN TALK TO HIM,
TELL HIM HOW YOU FEEL.
AND HOW DO I START
A CONVERSATION LIKE THAT?
MARCH UP AND BLURT
SOME FEELINGS.
LIKE, "I THINK YOUR SHIRT
IS UGLY."
HEY, I SAVED UP FOR THIS!
SEE?
CONVERSATION STARTED.
NOW, CAN WE FINISH
THIS ASSIGNMENT?
(SIGHS)
(CAR RUMBLES)
CLARE:
WHICH BRINGS US TO WHEN
WE WERE BROKEN UP,
AND...A THING HAPPENED.
(PHONE RINGS)
A-A TINY, ONE-TIME THING.
WITH DREW.
A MISTAKE.
BUT, SOMETIMES WHEN YOU DO
THAT THING,
OTHER THINGS HAPPEN,
AND-AND ONE OF THOSE
THINGS DID HAPPEN,
AND IS STILL HAPPENING
CURRENTLY,
AM I MAKING ANY SENSE?
NO, NO, I AM NOT!
COME ON, CLARE!
(CELL PHONE BUZZES)
(APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS)
HELEN:
CLARE, HONEY,
CAN I TALK TO YOU?
CAN WE DO IT LATER?
ELI'S ON HIS WAY OVER.
THAT WAS AUDRA TORRES
ON THE PHONE.
OH?
SHE AND DREW
ARE COMING OVER.
OH...
(DOORBELL RINGS)
CLARE:
THAT WOULD BE ELI.
I'LL TELL HIM
YOU'RE FEELING SICK.
YOU WOULDN'T BE WRONG.
(BELL RINGS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
(ZOE, LOLA, AND SHAY GIGGLE)
ZOE, LOLA, SHAY:
WE LOVE YOUR GIF, ZIG!
NO BRAINS OR BRAWN?
YOU REALLY DODGED
A BULLET THERE, ZO.
ZIG:
WHAT WERE THEY TALKING ABOUT?
GRACE:
THIS, PROBABLY.
WHAT THE HELL, MAN?!
WHO SAID IT WAS ME?
YOU WERE THE ONE FILMING!
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
IT WAS ME.
IT'S BEEN RETWEETED
A HUNDRED TIMES!
I NEVER GET MORE THAN LIKE,
SIX RETWEETS.
MAYBE YOU SHOULDN'TVE LET
A GIRL KICK YOUR BUTT.
WHOA!
NOVAK, CALM DOWN!
TINY WAS JUST MESSING AROUND,
OKAY?
THEN HE WON'T MIND DELETING IT!
MAYA:
GUYS, TEACHER!
LOOKS LIKE YOU TWO'LL BE
DISCUSSING THIS IN DETENTION.
(SIGHS)
HELEN:
HOW DID MY SMART,
TALENTED DAUGHTER
GET PREGNANT AT SEVENTEEN?!
CLARE:
BAD LUCK?
HELEN:
I WISH I KNEW WHAT TO SAY,
BUT I NEVER IN A MILLION YEARS
EXPECTED TO BE HAVING
THIS CONVERSATION.
WHEN WERE YOU GOING TO TELL ME?
ONCE I FIGURED OUT WHAT TO DO.
ON YOUR OWN?!
YOU'RE STILL A KID!
YOU CAN'T HANDLE THIS
ON YOUR OWN,
I DON'T WANT YOU TO HANDLE
THIS ON YOUR OWN!
HONEY, I'M HERE FOR YOU,
ALWAYS.
WE'LL FIGURE THIS OUT
AS A FAMILY, OKAY?
OH...I DON'T WANT
THIS LIFE FOR YOU.
MOM, THIS CHANGES NOTHING.
I CAN STILL HAVE ALL
THE SAME THINGS.
I'M STILL THE SAME PERSON!
I'M CLARE EDWARDS!
CLARE EDWARDS ALWAYS
HAS A PLAN.
TRUST ME.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
AREN'T YOU GONNA APOLOGIZE
FOR GETTING ME DETENTION?
THAT'S WHAT THE POUTINE IS FOR.
TINY:
HMM!
THEN, APOLOGY ACCEPTED.
(ZIG LAUGHS)
SO WHAT DO YOU SAY, GRACE?
REMATCH?
WHY WOULD I RISK MY TITLE?
BECAUSE OUR LITTLE ZIGMUND
IS FEELING EMASCULATED.
HE WANTS ANOTHER CHANCE TO
PROVE WHAT A MAN HE REALLY IS.
I WANT TINY TO TAKE DOWN
THAT GIF.
THEN YOU NEED TO PROVE
YOU'RE NOT A WUSS.
HOW AM I GONNA DO THAT IF SHE
WON'T AGREE TO ROUND TWO?
GRACE:
I'VE GOT AN IDEA.
UNLESS YOU'RE SCARED.
OF WHAT?
GRACE:
I THINK I'LL KEEP IT
A SURPRISE.
IT'S MORE FUN LIKE THAT.
(MAYA AND GRACE LAUGH)
AUDRA: HOW MANY WEEKS ARE YOU?
CLARE: NINE.
AUDRA:
OKAY, SO WE STILL HAVE OPTIONS.
CLARE:
I'VE ALREADY CONSIDERED
MY OPTIONS,
I'M KEEPING THE BABY.
SO, YOU'RE GONNA RUIN
YOUR LIFE AND DREW'S?
WATCH YOUR TONE.
THIS IS MY DAUGHTER
YOU'RE TALKING TO.
I JUST THINK SHE SHOULD
CONSIDER WHAT SHE'S GIVING UP!
HOW IS SHE POSSIBLY
GONNA MANAGE UNIVERSITY?
I'LL HELP HER OUT.
CLARE:
ACTUALLY, I'M GONNA BE
IN NEW YORK.
THEY HAVE FAMILY HOUSING,
GREAT DAYCARE,
I'VE LOOKED INTO IT.
SO YOU'RE GONNA HAVE THIS BABY,
AND THEN MOVE IT
OUT OF THE COUNTRY?!
DID YOU KNOW THIS?
IT'S WHAT SHE WANTS.
HELEN:
IT'S AN IVY LEAGUE SCHOOL!
IT'LL BE HARD ENOUGH
WITHOUT A BABY,
YOU NEED YOUR FAMILY
AROUND YOU.
I'M SURE ELI CAN HELP.
AUDRA:
UH, WHO'S ELI?
HER EX-BOYFRIEND.
UM... DID WE HAVE A PATERNITY
TEST HERE?
SERIOUSLY,
I'M NOT SUBSIDIZING
THIS DELUSIONAL
GIRL'S EDUCATION,
IF IT'S NOT EVEN MY GRANDKID!
I AM NOT DELUSIONAL!
A COUPLE MONTHS AGO,
I THOUGHT I MIGHT NEVER
GET TO HAVE CHILDREN.
AND THE CANCER MIGHT STILL
COME BACK.
THIS MIGHT BE MY ONLY CHANCE,
I AM KEEPING THE BABY!
FINE,
BUT WE NEED A NEW PLAN.
BASED HERE IN TORONTO,
WHERE YOU HAVE SUPPORT.
OBVIOUSLY, DREW WILL HELP
AS MUCH AS HE CAN.
WE'LL MAKE A ROOM IN OUR HOME
FOR THE BABY.
HELEN:
JAKE'S ROOM'S FREE,
I THOUGHT THAT COULD BE
THE NURSERY.
AUDRA:
YEAH, OKAY,
A REAL ROOM SOUNDS GOOD.
HELEN:
CLARE, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?!
WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE
OF A DISCUSSION!
CLARE:
ACTUALLY IT SEEMS LIKE YOU TWO
HAVE IT ALL FIGURED OUT SO I'M-
(DOOR SLAMS)
DREW:
CLARE!
SLOW DOWN!
HEY. WHERE ARE YOU EVEN GOING?
CLARE:
TO TALK TO ALLI, SOMEONE WHO
ACTUALLY SUPPORTS ME!
YOU DIDN'T EVEN DEFEND ME
IN THERE!
YOU BLINDSIDED ME!
I BLINDSIDED YOU?!
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO TOLD YOUR MOM!
SHE CAUGHT ME RESEARCHING
CRIBS, IT JUST ALL CAME OUT!
ALL RIGHT, I TRIED TO CALL YOU,
YOU DIDN'T ANSWER!
BECAUSE I WAS GETTING READY
TO TELL ELI!
WHAT DID YOU THINK?
WE WERE GONNA MOVE IN TOGETHER,
GET A STATION WAGON?
YEAH, KINDA.
NOTHING HAS TO CHANGE!
THIS ONLY DISRUPTS OUR LIVES
IF WE LET IT.
DALLAS SAYS THAT A BABY
CHANGES EVERYTHING.
VANESSA'S LIFE WAS NEVER
THE SAME!
THEN I'M GLAD I'M NOT HER,
BECAUSE I PLAN ON GOING TO
SCHOOL AND BEING WITH ELI,
AND YOU CAN DO WHATEVER IT IS
YOU'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO DO!
CLARE, I CAN'T GO BACK
TO YOUR HOUSE WITHOUT YOU!
MY MOM'LL KILL ME!
CLARE!
ZIG:
(PREPARATORY BREATHS)
ALL RIGHT, GRACE,
WHAT'S IT GONNA BE?
PUSH UP COMPETITION?
'CAUSE I CAN DO TWENTY THREE
AND A HALF PUSHUPS,
NO PROBLEM! AH!
REAL MEN KNOW
HOW TO GET HOME-TATTOOED.
TINY:
WHAAAAT?!
ALL RIGHT, VERY FUNNY, GRACE.
MAYA:
I THINK SHE'S SERIOUS, ZIG.
GRACE:
DEAD.
I GOT THIS WHEN I WAS FOURTEEN,
IN A GUY'S LIVING ROOM.
MAYA: WHOA!
ZIG: THAT DOESN'T MEAN
IT WAS A GOOD IDEA!
TINY:
DUDE, YOU HAVE TO DO IT,
YOU CAN'T LET HER
SHOW YOU UP AGAIN.
WILL YOU TAKE DOWN THE GIF?
OH, DEAL!
ZIG:
OKAY, LET'S EVERYONE JUST
SLOW DOWN FOR A SECOND, OKAY?
DO YOU EVEN KNOW HOW?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
SO?
MILES:
GUY ON YOUR LEFT,
GUY ON YOUR LEFT!
WINSTON:
GOT HIM!
SO UM, YOU AND TRISTAN
HAVE BEEN SPENDING
A LOT OF TIME TOGETHER LATELY.
MILES:
YEAH. GOT HIM!
SO, ARE YOU GUYS
GONNA HANG OUT MORE?
PROBABLY.
I JUST FEEL LIKE-
MILES:
I'M GONNA GO AFTER THIS JERK,
COVER ME.
(GROANS)
I THINK YOUR SHIRT IS UGLY!
HELLO!
ARE YOU DEAF?
I'VE BEEN KNOCKING FOR,
LIKE, TEN MINUTES, SO.
WHAT'S HE DOING HERE?!
OH, I INVITED HIM.
SORRY, TRIS, THE GAME
GOT A BIT INTENSE.
DO YOU LIKE THIS SHIRT?
TOTES, IT'S CUTE.
(BOTH LAUGH, KISS)
WINSTON:
WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE
OF SOMETHING!
TRISTAN:
YEAH, A SHOOTING GAME.
PLEASE TELL ME YOU HAVE
"JUST DANCE?"
WE'RE NOT PLAYING
"JUST DANCE-"
YEAH, I COULD PLAY
"JUST DANCE."
(TRISTAN CLAPS)
HEY!
I'M JUST KIDDING, HERE.
AND IF YOU WANT
EVEN MORE DESSERT,
WE COULD GO BACK TO MY PLACE,
EVERYONE'S OUT...
ALLI:
HI?
CLARE:
CAN YOU PLEASE TELL DREW
THAT IF WE PUT OUR MINDS TO IT,
THERE'S A WAY I CAN HAVE
THIS BABY AND GO TO COLUMBIA!
CAN YOU PLEASE TELL CLARE
THAT WE CAN'T EVEN BEGIN
TO KNOW WHAT HAVING A BABY
WILL BE LIKE,
UNTIL WE ACTUALLY HAVE ONE!
CHEQUE PLEASE?
YEAH, I WOULD NEVER GET
IN THE WAY OF CLARE
AND ONE OF HER DREAMS,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
THAT'S NOT AN ANSWER.
OH! IS THAT COFFEE?
DREW:
YOU CAN'T DRINK THAT!
YOU'RE POLICING MY LIQUID
INTAKE NOW, TOO?
THERE'S CAFFEINE IN IT!
IT'S NOT GOOD FOR THE BABY,
ALL RIGHT? I'LL GET YOU
A WATER.
I CAN DO IT MYSELF!
SORRY, ARE WE INTERRUPTING
SOMETHING?
NOW, LIE DOWN ON THE COUCH WITH
YOUR ARM EASILY ACCESSIBLE.
WHY LYING DOWN?
GRACE:
OH, IN CASE YOU FAINT.
MAYA:
YOU'RE NOT GONNA FAINT.
GRACE:
HE MIGHT.
TINY:
OH YEAH, THAT WOULD REALLY
PROVE YOU'RE TOUGH.
GRACE:
SO WE'RE JUST DOING A "Z"
ON YOUR ARM?
NO FLAMING DRAGONS?
UH, YEAH, AND NOT TOO BIG.
AND MAKE SURE MY SLEEVE
CAN COVER IT.
TINY:
YOU DON'T WEAR SLEEVES.
ZING! HAH!
WHAT'S THAT FOR?
TO MAKE SURE THE NEEDLE
IS TOTALLY DISINFECTED.
OKAY WITH YOU?
♪♪
OKAY, NO, IT'S NOT OKAY
WITH ME, ALL RIGHT?!
GETTING A HOME TATTOO
TO PROVE THAT YOU'RE TOUGH,
IT'S STUPID!
LOOKS WHO'S FINALLY GOT
HIMSELF SOME BALLS!
WAIT, WHAT?
YOU AGREE WITH ME?
HELL YEAH!
AND GOOD ON YOU
FOR GETTING OUT NOW,
BECAUSE I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT I'M DOING.
(MAYA, TINY, AND GRACE LAUGH)
EXCUSE ME,
COULD I GET A WATER?
DO YOU WANNA TRY?
MAYBE YOU CAN GET HIS ATTENTION
WITH YOUR CLEAVAGE.
HEY, IT WAS A DATE!
HERE YOU GO.
ARE YOU SURE?
BECCA:
YEAH, I ALWAYS HAVE
A FEW EXTRA.
YOU NEVER KNOW WHEN YOU'RE
GONNA FORGET TO HYDRATE.
(BABY COOS)
IS IT REALLY THAT CRAZY?
WHAT?
THAT YOU FORGET TO DRINK WATER?
BECCA:
YEAH, SOMETIMES.
IF HE'S SICK,
OR HAS AN APPOINTMENT,
ANYTHING THAT THROWS HIM
OFF SCHEDULE,
AND I'M JUST SCRAMBLING.
I'LL LOOK UP, IT'S TWELVE AND
I HAVEN'T EVEN EATEN. (LAUGHS)
IT SOUNDS TERRIBLE.
OH, NO!
NO, NO, NO.
I MEAN, YEAH,
I GUESS I'M...
A SLEEPLESS CREATURE WHO LIVES
TO SERVE HIS EVERY WHIM,
BUT LUCKILY, HE'S A PRETTY
COOL OVERLORD,
MOST OF THE TIME.
YOU WANNA HOLD HIM?
SURE!
BECCA:
WHO'S THIS?
YOU CAN SAY HI!
HI, MISTER!
(BECCA LAUGHS)
CLARE!
I THOUGHT YOU WERE SICK.
(BABY COUGHS)
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
ELI... (SIGHS)
I'M PREGNANT.
♪♪
TRISTAN:
RIGHT, LEFT, RIGHT,
LEFT, RIGHT, LEFT, RIGHT.
THAT'S PERFECT.
♪♪
HELLO WINSTON, SUPASTAR,
OKAY, YOU'RE TOTALLY
LOVING THIS.
(PUNCH, TRISTAN GASPS)
OKAY, MAYBE WE SHOULD
SPREAD OUT.
WINSTON:
YEAH.
(PUNCH)
HEY, THAT WAS ON PURPOSE!
MILES:
NOT SO FUN, IS IT?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
MILES: DON'T PLAY DUMB, CHEWY.
WINSTON: I'M NOT DOING
ANYTHING!
MILES: EXCEPT BEING A JERK.
WINSTON: I'M THE JERK?!
I'M NOT THE ONE WHO INVITED
MY BOYFRIEND OVER
ON OUR BRO-DATE!
TRISTAN:
OKAY, WHY DON'T WE JUST
ALL CALM DOWN!
CAN IT, TRISTAN!
EVERYTHING WAS SO MUCH BETTER
BEFORE YOU GOT HERE!
(SCOFFS)
(SIGHS)
(GROANS)
ARE YOU SERIOUSLY
THIS THREATENED BY TRISTAN?
(SIGH)
YES!
OKAY, YOU USED TO HAVE MY BACK.
WE USED TO BE BROS!
WE ARE BROS.
SINCE WHEN?
LATELY IT'S ALL BEEN:
"TRISTAN, LET'S DO
SCIENCE TOGETHER,
AND PLAY SILLY DANCE GAMES!
ARE YOU SURE THAT'S
WHAT THIS IS ABOUT?
WHAT?
NOT THAT HE'S...
A HE?
WELL, THAT'S WEIRD, TOO.
I MEAN, YOU WERE
A HUNDRED PERCENT
PUPPY DOG WITH MAYA
FOR MONTHS.
AND NOW YOU'RE SLOBBERING
ALL OVER TRISTAN?
LOOK, MAYA DUMPED ME, MAN.
HARD.
AND YOU SPENT ALL SPRING BREAK
ATTACHED AT THE HIP
TO MY SISTER.
WINSTON: SO?
MILES: SO, I NEEDED SOMEONE.
AND I LIKE HANGING OUT
WITH TRISTAN.
BUT WHAT ABOUT THE KISSING?
WELL, I LIKE THAT, TOO.
OKAY, DON'T WORRY, THERE'S
ENOUGH MILES TO GO AROUND.
(SIGHS)
HEY.
NO ONE IS REPLACING YOU.
YEAH.
ESPECIALLY NOT AT VIDEO GAMES.
YEAH, TRIS IS PRETTY BAD.
COME ON.
WINSTON:
OH! OH, OKAY.
MILES: OKAY.
WINSTON: OH! OKAY, YEAH.
(LAUGHS AWKWARDLY)
ELI:
WE HAD SO MANY PLANS!
I'M NOT READY TO GIVE THEM UP!
COLUMBIA, LIVING IN NEW YORK-
CLARE: ELI-
ELI: IN OUR APARTMENT!
THERE'S A GUY
IN MY ITALIAN CINEMA CLASS
WHO MIGHT GIVE UP
A STUDIO IN THE VILLAGE.
I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE PERFECT!
CLARE: ELI-
ELI:
THIS AFFECTS EVERYTHING,
HOW COULD YOU NOT TELL ME?
BECAUSE IT'S DREW'S.
YOU...
YOU HAD SEX WITH DREW?!
I'M SORRY.
I WAS SO MESSED UP,
AND I DIDN'T TELL YOU
ABOUT THE BABY SOONER
BECAUSE I WANTED TO TELL YOU
IN PERSON THAT WE'RE-
THAT I'M KEEPING IT.
YOU SAID "WE," CLARE!
CLARE: I JUST MEANT-
SO YOU AND DREW,
YOU'RE WHAT?!
YOU GONNA RAISE
A FAMILY TOGETHER?
GET MARRIED?
BUY A HOUSE?
NO, I LOVE YOU, ELI!
NOTHING'S CHANGED!
HOW CAN YOU SAY THAT?!
EVERYTHING HAS CHANGED!
BUT-BUT I CAN'T IMAGINE
A LIFE WITHOUT YOU!
I DON'T CARE.
(SOBS)
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M SURE OUR MOMS WILL
HAVE AN IDEA OR TWO.