HUNTER:
'KAY, A BROKEN CENTER LINE
ON A ROAD MEANS...?
MILES:
YOU CAN PASS AFTER VERIFYING
THAT THERE'S NO ONCOMING
TRAFFIC AND THE WAY IS CLEAR.
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH:
IF ONLY YOU WORKED THIS HARD
AT YOUR ENGLISH GRADE.
MILES:
WELL, I'M GONNA ACE
MY ROAD TEST TODAY!
FRANKIE:
AS IF DAD'S GONNA
LET YOU TAKE IT.
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH:
YOU SPOKE WITH A REPORTER?
FRANKIE:
AND MADE DAD LOOK LIKE
A BATMAN VILLAIN
WHO HATES HIS GAY SON.
MILES:
WELL, IT'S TRUE.
(APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS)
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
MILES, A WORD.
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH:
OKAY, PEANUTS, LET'S GET YOU
TO SCHOOL ON TIME FOR ONCE.
(DISGUSTED SIGH)
PEANUTS? SERIOUSLY, MOM?
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH:
YOU TOO, FRANKIE.
FRANKIE:
BUT THIS IS GONNA BE GOOD.
MILES:
I WOULD ALSO LIKE TO GO
TO SCHOOL, AS WELL.
NOT TODAY.
SO, ANYWAY, I UH...
WANT YOU TO TRY THESE OUT
AND SEE IF THEY'RE
THE RIGHT HEIGHT FOR YOU.
(DISBELIEVING LAUGH)
YOU WANNA GO GOLFING?
YES, I DO.
I HAVE THE DAY OFF
AND I KNOW I DON'T HAVE
TO CONVINCE YOU TO SKIP SCHOOL.
I'LL EVEN LET YOU DRIVE.
YEAH, BUT I HAVEN'T PASSED
MY ROAD TEST, YET.
YEAH, YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
IF YOU DON'T SQUEEZE IN
A LITTLE PRACTICE.
SO... WE'RE NOT GONNA TALK
ABOUT THE ARTICLE?
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
MILES, I'M NOT PROUD
OF THE WAY I REACTED
TO THE NEWS ABOUT YOU
AND THIS TRISTAN.
GAY, STRAIGHT,
WHATEVER YOU ARE,
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT I ACCEPT YOU.
WELL, JUST SO YOU KNOW,
I'LL PROBABLY BE CRANKING
THEM OFF THE TEE WITH THESE.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
(LAUGHING) I EXPECT NOTHING
LESS FROM MY SON.
THERE YOU GO.
(KEYS CLANK, MILES LAUGHS)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh...♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
BECKY: (OVER P.A. SYSTEM):
WANT TO HELP A CHILD IN NEED?
DONATE!
SEE BECKY BAKER FOR DETAILS.
(LIGHT SWAT)
ZOE:
NICE BUM, CHUM.
ZIG:
(CLEARS THROAT)
WELL, I DO WORK OUT.
OH! SOMEONE'S REALLY EMBRACING
BEING A CHEERLEADER.
A POOR CHEERLEADER.
DID YOU KNOW RENTING A BUS
COSTS $200 DOLLARS?
ONE BUS!
WE NEED FUNDRAISING IDEAS, FAST.
(PHONE CHIMES)
WELL, I'M SURE YOU'LL THINK
OF SOMETHING G-R-E-A-T!
MM!
(SHARP INHALE)
ZOE:
WHAT PICTURE IS TINY OOMF
CHATTING YOU NOW?
ZIG: UH, COME ON NOW. HONEST-
ZOE: JUST...
UM...
WHO'S SENDING YOU BOOBS?!
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU DON'T KNOW?
IT'S PROBABLY JUST
SOME DUMB NINER.
ZOE:
LOTS OF DUMB NINERS...
ZIG:
COME ON, SO? I...
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
HALF THOSE GIRLS.
THEN WHY ARE THEY SENDING YOU
NUDES?
BECAUSE THEY WANT
TO GET TO KNOW ME?
EXACTLY.
(BELL RINGS, ZIG SIGHS)
SIMPSON:
FIRE SAFETY SAVES LIVES.
TAKE A MOMENT TO MEMORIZE
YOUR FIRE EXITS.
(CHAIR SCRAPES BACK)
DALLAS:
YOU COMING TO MATH CLASS?
DREW:
TELL ARMSTRONG I'M SICK.
YOU'RE HOLED UP
IN YOUR ROOM ALL WEEKEND.
YOU'VE BEEN IGNORING BECKY,
WHO BROKE HER ANKLE BY THE WAY.
TALK TO ME.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
CLARE'S PREGNANT.
DALLAS:
(LAUGHS) GOOD ONE.
(PANICKED, EMOTIONAL GASPS)
SHUT THE FRONT DOOR!
DREW: (EMOTIONAL)
EVERY TIME I THINK ABOUT IT...
I FEEL LIKE I'M GONNA HURL.
WHAT DID CLARE SAY?
SHE WANTED TO GET RID OF IT,
AT FIRST,
BUT NOW SHE'S THINKING
OF KEEPING IT.
(SIGHS) DID SHE ASK YOU
WHAT YOU THOUGHT?
WHY WOULD SHE CARE
WHAT I THINK?
BECAUSE THAT BABY'S
FIFTY PERCENT YOU.
YOU GUYS SHOULD DISCUSS
ALL YOUR OPTIONS.
(LAUGHING)
MILES:
DAD, DO YOU REMEMBER MY...
MY FIRST PAIR OF JUNIOR CLUBS?
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
(LAUGHING) YEAH.
HOW ARE YOU?
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH: UM... WELL...
MILES: THEY WERE SPIDER-MAN.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
YES, AND I ALSO REMEMBER
THOSE CLUBS
GOING THROUGH
THE POOLHOUSE WINDOW.
THAT'S-THAT'S WHAT I REMEMBER.
WELL, I WAS PLAYING SPIDER-MAN,
AND I WAS SEVEN, SO...
LOOK, OKAY, SO...
WHAT'S THIS ABOUT?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I HUMILIATED YOU
IN THE NEWSPAPER,
I CALLED YOU A HOMOPHOBE,
AND YOU BRING ME OUT GOLFING
AND LET ME THE DRIVE
THE BEEMER. WHY?
YOU ARE MY ELDEST SON,
AND JUST SOMETIMES I FEEL
I KNOW NOTHING ABOUT YOU.
THAT'S BECAUSE
WE'RE ALWAYS FIGHTING!
YEAH. WE BOTH HAVE
TO WORK ON THAT, HUH?
MILES: YEAH.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
COME HERE, YOU.
(SIGHS)
AH, YOU'RE A GOOD KID, HMM?
(CAMERA SHUTTERS SNAP)
(SIGHS)
MILES:
WHAT THE HELL?
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
LOOKS LIKE THE PRESS FOUND US.
OH, COME ON!
YOU GUYS, THIS IS SUPPOSED
TO BE MY DAY OFF.
SORRY, BUT IT'S A RARE
OPPORTUNITY
TO CATCH A GENUINE MOMENT
WITH YOUR ELDEST.
CARE TO COMMENT?
WELL... I MEAN ALL I CAN SAY
IS THAT...
WHEN YOUR CHILD COMES
OUT OF THE CLOSET...
DAD?!
IT'S A VERY DIFFICULT TIME
FOR EVERYONE.
BUT THE IMPORTANT THING TO
REMEMBER IS THAT YOU JUST...
YOU JUST KEEP COMMUNICATING,
AND YOU JUST KEEP LOVING THEM,
NO MATTER WHAT.
BUT I DO HOPE
THE LGBT COMMUNITY
JUST UNDERSTANDS THAT
I'M UH... I'M LEARNING...
I'M GROWING AS A PERSON
AND AS A FATHER.
HEY, MILES?
(CAMERA SHUTTERS SNAP)
THANKS.
DID YOU GET THAT, GUYS?
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
DREW:
DO YOU KNOW THAT DAUGHTERS
OF TEEN MOMS
ARE THREE TIMES MORE LIKELY
TO BECOME TEEN MOMS THEMSELVES?
I DO.
AND THAT SONS OF TEEN MOMS
ARE TWICE AS LIKELY
TO END UP IN PRISON!
CLARE:
WOW. SOMEONE'S DONE
THEIR RESEARCH.
DREW:
YEAH! HAVE YOU? CLARE, WE ARE
STILL IN HIGH SCHOOL.
DREW: WE CAN'T HAVE A BABY!
CLARE: SHH! NOT SO LOUD.
DREW:
CLARE, YOU NEED TO CONSIDER
ALL THE OPTIONS HERE.
I HAVE.
I'M NOT HAVING AN ABORTION.
IT DOESN'T FEEL RIGHT.
OKAY. WE'RE TELLING OUR FOLKS
ABOUT THE BABY?
WE CAN WAIT A WEEK OR TWO.
CLARE, I'M NOT JUST TALKING
ABOUT THE BABY, ALL RIGHT?
WE'RE ALSO GONNA HAVE TO TELL
THEM THAT WE'RE GETTING MARRIED.
CLARE: WHAT?
DREW: I'M SORRY,
DO YOU THINK THAT MY MOM'S
GONNA LET BE A DEADBEAT DAD?
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
TO MOVE IN TOGETHER.
I'M GONNA HAVE
TO GET A JOB.
(SIGHS)
DO YOU THINK THE CELL PHONE
KIOSK WILL TAKE ME BACK?
MAYBE THEY'LL TAKE
PITY ON ME
IF I TELL THEM
I'M HAVING A BABY.
CLARE:
WHOA! OKAY, STOP SAYING BABY!
THIS IS NOT THE 1950S.
WE'RE NOT GETTING MARRIED.
ALL RIGHT,
SO WHAT'S THE PLAN, CLARE?
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO DECIDED TO
KEEP THE - BEAN ALL ON YOUR OWN.
CLARE:
IT'S MY CHOICE!
AND YOU'RE RIDICULOUS.
YES! EXACTLY!
I AM RIDICULOUS.
I'M DREW TORRES, THE PERSON
YOU ARE CHOOSING TO HAVE...
A-A BEAN WITH,
ALL RIGHT?
I CAN BARELY
TAKE CARE MYSELF.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO BE INVOLVED.
WE CAN DRAW UP PAPERS
OR SOMETHING.
AFTER GRADUATION, WE DON'T EVER
HAVE TO SEE EACH OTHER AGAIN.
(SIGHS)
ARE YOU SURE?
(BELL RINGS)
YEAH. I'M LETTING YOU
OFF THE HOOK.
(RECEDING FOOTSTEPS)
(ANGRY EXHALE)
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
YOU MADE A MOCKERY OF ME
BACK AT THE COURSE.
MILES:
ME?!
YOU ACTED LIKE YOU WANTED
TO SPEND TIME WITH ME,
BUT YOU CALLED THE PRESS?
ALL YOU EVER DO IS MANIPULATE
EVERYTHING!
I... I CAN'T BELIEVE
I FELL FOR THIS!
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
MILES, HANG ON.
WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING?!
MILES: BACK TO SCHOOL,
WHERE AT LEAST ONE PERSON
GIVES A CRAP ABOUT ME!
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
NO. NOT UNTIL WE FINISH TALKING!
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH: NO, NO.
MILES: I'M DONE!
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
YOU DO NOT WALK AWAY FROM ME
WHEN I AM TALKING!
(HARD THUD)
OH GOD, OH GOD... OH GOD, THAT
WAS- THAT WAS AN ACCIDENT!
I'M FINE. NOW CAN I-
NOW CAN I GO?
YEAH, YEAH.
♪♪
ZIG:
IT'S JUST THAT ZOE HAS NO RIGHT
TO BE MAD, YOU KNOW?
WE'RE NOT EVEN DATING.
GRACE:
BUT YOU WANT TO BE, RIGHT?
THEN YOU NEED TO APOLOGIZE.
FOR WHAT?
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING WRONG.
EVERYONE OOMF CHATS.
(SNORTS)
I DON'T.
YEAH, WELL EVERYONE ELSE.
SO WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
GRACE:
THE PROBLEM IS THAT RIGHT NOW
ZOE THINKS THAT
YOU'RE THE TYPE OF GUY WHO
WANTS SEXY PICS FROM GIRLS.
ZIG:
SHE WOULDN'T BE WRONG.
SO, SHE PROBABLY FEELS LIKE SHE
SHOULD SEND YOU SOME SEXY PICS.
I'M STILL NOT SEEING
THE PROBLEM.
EVEN THOUGH, LAST TERM,
GUYS SENT SEXY PICTURES OF HER
AROUND THE SCHOOL
WITHOUT HER CONSENT.
OH JEEZ.
SO WHAT DO I DO
TO MAKE IT BETTER?
APOLOGIZE. PREFERABLY WITH A
HUGE TOKEN OF YOUR AFFECTION.
OKAY, DOABLE.
GRACE:
OH, AND DELETE THE APP.
(LAPTOP KEYS CLACK)
(SIGHS) FINE.
FINE, I'LL DELETE IT.
(PHONE CHIMES)
OH! 'KAY, UM...
MILES:
HEY, WHERE'S TRISTAN?
ZOE:
MILES HOLLINGSWORTH!
LITTLE BOY BLUE
SUDDENLY LIKES DUDES?
HMM. JUST ONE.
HAVE YOU SEEN HIM?
ZOE:
YEAH, BUT HE DOESN'T WANT
TO SEE YOU
AFTER YOU OUTED YOUR
RELATIONSHIP IN THE NEWSPAPER.
EVERYONE'S TEASING HIM.
WHAT? WHY?
TRISTAN:
BECAUSE THEY THINK YOU'RE
USING ME TO PISS OFF YOUR DAD.
YOU PROMISED ME TO KEEP
OUR RELATIONSHIP A SECRET
UNTIL WE FIGURED THINGS OUT.
MILES: OKAY, TRISTAN,
JUST LET ME EXPLAIN.
TRISTAN: NO, I DON'T WANNA
TALK TO YOU.
MILES: PLEASE!
I THOUGHT YOU
ACTUALLY LIKED ME.
MILES: I-I DO LIKE YOU.
TRISTAN: NO, YOU DON'T.
YOU MANIPULATED ME.
(BELL RINGS)
MILES:
NO, NO, I DIDN'T.
I DIDN'T DO IT. DON'T SAY THAT.
TRISTAN, I NEED...
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU, OKAY?
(STUDENTS CHATTER IN THE HALL)
MAYA:
OH! MILES?
NOT NOW, MAYA.
MAYA:
WHAT, MY EX STARTS MAKING OUT
WITH MY EX BEST FRIEND -
I DON'T EVEN DESERVE
A CONVERSATION?
MILES:
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE.
(DOOR BANGS OPEN,
BOOKS CRASH ON THE FLOOR)
(DOOR CLICKS SHUT)
(SHAKY BREATH,
DOOR OPENS)
YOU KNOW THIS IS THE BOYS
LOCKER ROOM.
MAYA:
LIKE I CARE.
DID YOU DO THIS
TO HURT ME?
YOU REALLY THINK
A LOT OF YOURSELF.
MAYA:
WELL, THEN TELL ME WHAT'S
GOING ON? I'M JUST CONFUSED.
MILES:
YOU'RE CONFUSED?!
(SNIFFS)
MAYA:
MILES, TALK TO ME.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
MILES:
I'M HAPPENING, MAYA.
THE GREAT TORNADO THAT IS
MILES HOLLINGSWORTH THE THIRD
IS SCREWING UP HIS LIFE AGAIN.
MAYA:
YOU HAD ANOTHER FIGHT
WITH YOUR DAD?
MILES:
I SHOULD FIND TRISTAN.
MAYA:
MILES, IF SOMETHING'S
GOING ON AT HOME,
YOU NEED TO TALK TO SOMEONE.
HEY, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO TALK TO ME... BUT SOMEONE.
WHEN YOU DON'T TELL PEOPLE
WHAT'S INSIDE YOUR HEAD,
IT ONLY GETS WORSE.
(GYM WHISTLE BLOWS NEARBY)
(HALL BUZZES WITH CHATTER)
DREW:
(WHISTLES)
(LAUGHS) DID I FORGET
OUR ANNIVERSARY AGAIN?
DREW:
NO, NO, IT'S FOR BECKY.
I GOTTA MAKE UP FOR BEING
SUCH A CRAPPY BOYFRIEND
THESE LAST FEW DAYS.
THAT'S QUITE A TURNAROUND
FROM THIS MORNING.
DREW:
YEAH.
SO HAS YOUR BABY MOMMA DECIDED
TO RECONSIDER HER OPTIONS?
NO, NO, CLARE'S A BRICK WALL
ONCE SHE'S DECIDED SOMETHING.
BUT WE TALKED AND SHE SAID
I'M OFF THE HOOK.
DALLAS:
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
DREW:
THAT WE'RE SIGNING PAPERS
OR SOMETHING.
WE DECIDED THE BABY'S GONNA
BE BETTER OFF WITHOUT ME.
WHAT'S CLARE GONNA
TELL THE KID
WHEN THEY ASK
ABOUT THEIR FATHER?
DREW:
I'M SURE SHE'LL FIGURE IT OUT.
HOW'S THAT KID GONNA FEEL
ON FATHER'S DAY?
NOT GREAT, I GUESS.
BUT A LOT OF KIDS GROW UP
WITHOUT THEIR DAD AROUND.
SO WHAT HAPPENS, AT SOME POINT,
WHEN YOU DECIDE
YOU WANNA FIND THE LITTLE PIECE
OF YOU IN THE WORLD,
BUT THE KID ISN'T INTERESTED
IN HIS JERK OF A DAD
WHO DESERTED HIM IN UTERO?
WHY CAN'T YOU JUST BE HAPPY
FOR ME?
I GOT EVERYTHING I WANTED!
BECAUSE I TRIED IT YOUR WAY.
IT DOESN'T WORK.
I CAN'T BE A DAD, DALLAS.
I JUST CAN'T.
OH, YOU'RE STILL GONNA BE
A DAD - JUST A CRAP ONE.
BECKY'S GONNA FREAK.
AT LEAST YOU GOT
A SHIELD.
ZOE:
SO YOU'RE GOING TO REPORT TO ME
EVERY MORNING
AND THAT'S WHEN I WILL GIVE YOU
YOUR ENERGY DRINK
THAT I MAKE AT HOME
WITH TWO SHOTS OF ESPRESSO.
YOU'LL BE BOUNCING OFF
THE WALLS.
IT'S SO FABULOUS.
LIKE YOU'RE GOING-
ZIG:
UH, ZOE? UM...
CAN WE TALK ABOUT THAT PICTURE
THAT YOU SENT ME EARLIER?
ZOE:
IF YOU WANT ANOTHER,
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS ASK.
UH, NO, I... I DON'T WANT
ANY SEXY PICTURES FROM YOU.
BUT YOU WANT THEM
FROM DUMB NINERS?
LOLA:
HEY. WHO ARE YOU CALLING DUMB?
ZOE:
GUESS I TOTALLY MISREAD
WHAT WAS GOING ON BETWEEN US.
AWESOME.
ZIG:
NO, YOU DIDN'T.
IT'S JUST THAT...
AFTER EVERYTHING THAT
YOU WENT THROUGH LAST TERM,
YOU SHOULDN'T FEEL LIKE
YOU HAVE TO SEND
PICTURES LIKE THAT TO GUYS.
I WANTED TO.
OR YOU FELT PRESSURED?
OKAY, MOM.
I'M JUST TRYING
TO LOOK OUT FOR YOU, ZO.
NO! YOU'RE JUDGING ME.
EVERYONE THINKS
I SHOULD BE SHUTTERED AWAY
SOMEWHERE FOREVER,
INCLUDING YOU.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
BECKY:
(STRUGGLING GRUNTS,
PAINED WINCES)
OH- OH!
(NOTEBOOK CRASHES)
DREW:
IT'S OKAY, I GOT IT.
HOW'S THE ANKLE?
IT'S A PAIN IN THE BUTT.
(CHUCKLES)
THAT'S FUNNY.
STOP ACTING LIKE
EVERYTHING'S OKAY.
LOOK, I'M SORRY
I BLEW YOU OFF.
I-I JUST HAD SOMETHING
I HAD TO DEAL WITH.
OH YEAH, WHAT'S THAT?
LET'S TALK ABOUT IT, TONIGHT.
I'LL COME TO YOUR PLACE.
CLARE DOESN'T NEED YOU?
WHO TOLD YOU CLARE'S PREGNANT?
BECKY: IT'S TRUE?!
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
BECKY: (CRINGES)
IS SHE KEEPING THE BABY?
DREW: YES.
YOU TWO ARE GONNA BE TOGETHER?
NO. NO, NO.
SO YOU AND I CAN STAY TOGETHER.
BUT THERE'S STILL GONNA BE
A BABY OUT THERE, DREW - YOURS.
I KNOW, I KNOW. ALL RIGHT?
BUT WE CAN MAKE IT WORK.
OKAY,
WE HAVE TO MAKE IT WORK.
BECKY, YOU ARE
THE ONLY GOOD THING
THAT I HAVE IN MY LIFE,
RIGHT NOW.
AND I KNOW THAT THIS SITUATION
IS MESSY, BUT YOU AND I...
WE CAN GET THROUGH THIS
TOGETHER.
(EMOTIONAL)
NO.
I'M SORRY, DREW.
I WISH THINGS WERE DIFFERENT.
(SIGHS) ME, TOO.
(BECKY'S CRUTCHES CREAK
AS SHE LEAVES)
ZOE:
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU LANDED THAT
TUMBLE, SHAY! YOU WERE SUBLIME.
LOLA:
DON'T LISTEN TO HER SHAY,
YOU'RE GREAT.
(GIRLS LAUGH)
ZOE:
GIRLS, THAT'S NOT NICE.
NO GIGGLING,
EVEN WHEN ONE
OF OUR TEAM MEMBERS
IS BEING A TOTAL DUMBASS.
UH... ZO, I THINK
YOU HAVE A VISITOR.
(STUDENTS CHUCKLE)
(GASPS)
I MESSED UP.
CAN I HAVE A SECOND CHANCE?
ZOE: NO.
STUDENT: (GASPS) OH...
LOLA: WHAT?
ZIG:
WHAT?!
I'M DONE BEING JUDGED, ZIG.
I'M DONE WITH BOYS.
I'M DONE WITH YOU.
(SNAPS FINGERS)
(BELL RINGS)
(CROW CAWS)
HUNTER:
WHICH PLANET HAS
A ROCKY SURFACE?
FRANKIE:
I DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE HERE.
CAN WE JUST MOVE ON
TO THE NEXT ONE?
HUNTER: OKAY, UM...
MILES: WHERE'S MOM?
I NEED TO TALK TO HER.
HUNTER:
I DUNNO, BUT, UH, DAD
LOCKED HIMSELF IN THE STUDY.
WHAT HAPPENED THIS TIME?
MILES:
WELL, THAT'S WHAT I WANT
TO TALK TO MOM ABOUT.
LET ME GUESS.
YOU GUYS HAD ANOTHER FIGHT?
YEAH, A BIG ONE.
HUNTER:
OH, DIDN'T LIKE THE COURSE
HE TOOK YOU TO?
MILES:
WELL, YOU KNOW IT WAS JUST
A TOTAL JOKE, HUNTER.
HE DIDN'T TAKE ME
ON SOME BONDING EXPEDITION,
NO, HE TOOK ME
FOR A PHOTO OP.
FRANKIE:
MILES, YOU ONLY LOOK ON
THE WORST SIDE OF THINGS.
DAD CARES ABOUT YOU,
AND YOU CARE ABOUT HIM.
MILES:
NO, I DON'T.
SO WHY DO YOU SPEND ALL
YOUR TIME TRYING TO GET
HIS ATTENTION?
OKAY, ARE YOU TWO LIVING IN
SOME ALTERNATE UNIVERSE HERE?
DAD IS ALWAYS YELLING AT ME!
HUNTER:
YEAH, AND MOST OF THE TIME,
YOU'RE YELLING BACK.
OR YOU STARTED IT.
YOU TWO ARE PRETTY MUCH
EXACTLY ALIKE.
NO, I-I AM NOTHING LIKE HIM.
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
MILES:
READY? MY ROAD TEST
IS IN 20 MINUTES.
FIRST, WHAT HAPPENED
AT THE GOLF COURSE?
WHAT ALWAYS HAPPENS -
WE FOUGHT.
WELL, HE SAID YOU MADE A SCENE
IN FRONT OF THE PRESS.
(DOOR OPENS)
AH! AT THE VERY LEAST,
YOU NEED TO APOLOGIZE
TO YOUR FATHER.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
NO, HE DOESN'T.
WE HAVE TO DEAL WITH
THIS SITUATION, DEAR.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
THE STRESS OF THIS CAMPAIGN
IT'S JUST REALLY TAKING
ITS TOLL.
WE NEED TO... WE NEED TO FIND
A WAY TO START FRESH.
CAN WE FIND A WAY
TO DO THAT, MILES?
MILES:
I DON'T KNOW.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
OKAY, OKAY.
EASIER QUESTION, THEN.
BLACK OR SILVER?
MILES:
WHAT?
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
(LAUGHS) BLACK OR SILVER?
I UH, I DON'T THINK YOUR MOTHER
WILL LET YOU HAVE BOTH,
SO JUST PICK UH... PICK ONE
TO TAKE ON YOUR ROAD TEST!
♪♪
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
WHAT HAPPENED?
DREW:
BECKY KNOWS ABOUT THE BABY.
WELL, YOU TOLD HER YOU'RE NOT
GONNA BE INVOLVED, RIGHT?
(SIGHS)
I'VE CHANGED MY MIND.
LOOK... I-I WANT TO BE INVOLVED
IN THIS BABY'S LIFE.
YOU CAN'T JUST CHANGE
YOUR MIND.
YOU DID. I MEAN, FIRST,
YOU WANTED TO HAVE AN ABORTION,
AND NOW YOU WANNA KEEP IT.
IT'S MY CHOICE, DREW.
DREW:
FAIR ENOUGH, OKAY,
BUT I GET A SAY.
MAYBE NOT IN WHAT YOU DO,
BUT IN WHAT I DO.
I MEAN I ALWAYS TRY AND TAKE
THE EASY WAY OUT OF EVERYTHING.
NOT BECAUSE I'M A BAD GUY,
JUST BECAUSE I DON'T WANNA
SEE PEOPLE TO GET HURT.
THIS TIME I'M GONNA TRY
SOMETHING NEW.
I'M GONNA TAKE
THE HARD WAY OUT.
I'M GONNA TRY
AND BE A DAD.
WHO KNOWS,
MAYBE IT'LL WORK OUT.
DREW...
DREW: THIS IS MY CHOICE, CLARE.
CLARE: OKAY! OKAY.
I AM REALLY SCARED.
ME, TOO.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
(RUMBLES LOUDLY)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
♪ A fading hope,
Throughout the street ♪
♪ The dying smoke... ♪
ZOE:
WHOA! HOT WHEELS.
MY REWARD FOR PASSING
MY ROAD TEST!
YOUR DAD BOUGHT YOU A CAR?
HE AND I ARE IN A...
BETTER PLACE NOW.
HE WANTS TO HAVE MY BOYFRIEND
OVER FOR DINNER.
THAT IS IF I STILL HAVE ONE.
THAT DEPENDS.
WILL A RIDE BE PROVIDED
IN THIS CAR?
IF THAT'S WHAT IT TAKES.
(KISS)
DOES THAT MEAN
I'M FORGIVEN?
I'M HAPPY YOU WORKED THINGS OUT
WITH YOUR DAD.
ARE YOU JUST GONNA
LEAVE IT THERE?
MILES.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
MAKING THINGS BETTER, MAYA.
♪ What you can't get back ♪