ALLI:
IMAGINE YOU'RE UNDER A CANOPY
OF GLITTERING STARS...
JENNA:
OOH. PRETTY.
ALLI:
THERE ARE BISTRO TABLES,
SCRUMPTIOUS FOOD,
AND ALL OF YOUR CLOSEST
FRIENDS.
YOU ARE AT YOUR PROM.
INSPIRED BY VAN GOGH'S
"THE STARRY NIGHT".
AND BROUGHT TO YOU
BY YOURS TRULY.
IT'S SOPHISTICATED,
STYLISH AND SUPER ROMANTIC.
DALLAS: IT IS.
ALLI: QUESTIONS?
DREW:
YEAH. ISN'T PROM SUPPOSED
TO BE... FUN?
ANYONE ELSE?
I'M PRESENTING TO PILL
TOMORROW.
SO IF NO ONE
HAS ANY BETTER IDEAS-
DREW: WHAT ABOUT A BOAT?
ALLI: LIKE A CANOE?
DREW:
NO, ALLI, LIKE ONE OF THOSE
HARBOR CRUISES.
DALLAS:
THAT'D BE AWESOME!
IF MY GIRLFRIEND DIDN'T
ALREADY PITCHED A MUCH,
MUCH BETTER IDEA.
ALLI:
THAT CLARE AND I HAVE BEEN
WORKING ON SINCE GRADE 9.
YEAH, WHO OBVIOUSLY DOESN'T CARE
ENOUGH TO SHOW HER SUPPORT.
JENNA:
YEAH, WHERE IS MOMMA CLARE?
DREW:
SHE'S PROBABLY MAKING OUT
WITH HER BABY-DADDY SOMEWHERE?
ALLI:
YOU DON'T KNOW THAT.
CONNOR:
SHOULDN'T YOU? I THOUGHT BEST
FRIENDS TELL EACH OTHER
EVERYTHING.
ALLI: WE DO.
DREW: TIME'S UP.
ALL RIGHT. ALL IN FAVOUR
OF A SUPER AWESOME -
POSSIBLY PIRATE-THEMED -
BOAT PROM, SAY ARRR!
DREW, CONNOR, JENNA:
ARRRR!
THE CREW HAS SPOKEN.
I'LL LEAVE THE DETAILS
UP TO YOU.
(SIGHS)
THANK YOU.
(CHAIRS SCRAPE ON THE FLOOR)
I JUST WANTED OUR LAST NIGHT
TOGETHER TO BE PERFECT.
DALLAS:
IT WILL BE... AS LONG AS
WE'RE ALL TOGETHER.
ALLI:
YEAH, IF WE'RE ALL TOGETHER.
MAYBE I CAN FIND A BOAT
WITH A PLANK.
DALLAS:
HMM. YOU WARMING UP
TO THE PIRATE THEME?
ALLI:
NO. I WANT DREW TO WALK IT.
(DALLAS CHUCKLES)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Oh oh oh... ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(ZIG LAUGHING)
JOSE:
SHE'S A CUTE GIRL AND ALL, ZIG,
BUT YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
YOU HAVE IT GOOD HERE,
AND YOU JUST HAD TO KISS HER?
ZIG: I'M IN LOVE WITH HER.
JOSE: OH, IN LOVE. RIGHT, RIGHT.
ZIG:
BESIDES I'VE-I HAVE CAUSED
MAYA AND HER FAMILY
ENOUGH STRESS ALREADY.
JOSE:
'CAUSE YOUR MOM, SHE'S NOT TOO
ENTHUSIASTIC ABOUT YOU COMING
BACK.
ZIG:
YOU TALKED TO HER?
I... I THOUGHT WE WERE
MAKING PROGRESS.
JOSE:
WE WERE...
UNTIL SHE HEARD YOU WERE THERE
WHEN TINY GOT STABBED.
ANYWHERE ELSE YOU CAN GO?
ZIG:
TINY'S PLACE, I GUESS.
JOSE:
YOU SURE THAT'S A GREAT IDEA?
HIS BROTHER, VINCE,
DID A STINT IN JAIL.
AND HE'S PRETTY DEEP
INTO THE LIFESTYLE.
ZIG:
BUT TINY'S NOT.
AND WE CAN KEEP EACH OTHER
IN CHECK. I'LL BE FINE.
JOSE:
ALL RIGHT,
I CAN'T MAKE YOU DO ANYTHING,
SO I'LL KEEP WORKING
ON YOUR MOM,
AND YOU JUST KEEP DOING
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
HEAD DOWN. FOCUS ON SCHOOL.
THAT MUSICAL.
ZIG:
YEAH.
MAYA:
HE'S ONE OF THE LEADS,
DID HE TELL YOU THAT?
JOSE:
HE'S DOING REAL WELL,
OUR ZIG.
LET'S KEEP IT THAT WAY.
GOOD LUCK.
AND REMEMBER, MY ADVICE
IS ONLY A PHONE CALL AWAY.
MRS. MATLIN:
THANK YOU.
MAYA:
YOU SURE YOU'LL BE
SAFE AT TINY'S?
ZIG:
WHAT? YEAH, YEAH.
FOR SURE.
MAYA:
BUT YOU'D TELL ME THOUGH, RIGHT?
ZIG:
LOOK MAYA, YOU DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO WORRY, ALL RIGHT.
ZOE:
I KNOW IT'S NOT FAIR.
TRISTAN:
WHAT HAPPENS IF YOU HAVE TO
TEXT YOUR MOM OR SOMETHING?
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO CALL.
MILES:
HEY, ANYONE WANNA GO CHECK OUT
KENDRICK LAMAR
AT THE OPERA HOUSE
TOMORROW NIGHT?
TRISTAN:
YOUR PEACE OFFERINGS
ARE NO GOOD HERE.
MILES:
WELL, LET ME KNOW
IF YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND.
ZOE:
WHAT GIVES?
HE'S JUST TRYING TO BE NICE.
WOULD IT BE THE WORST
IF WE WENT?
TRISTAN:
HE'S JUST GOING OUT
OF HIS WAY TO BE CIVIL
SO HE WON'T FEEL BAD
ABOUT MOVING ON.
ZOE:
HE MOVED ON?
WITH WHO?
TRISTAN:
DON'T KNOW.
BUT HE'S GOT A SMILE ON HIS
FACE, A SKIP IN HIS STEP,
WHICH ONLY MEANS ONE THING -
NEW CRUSH.
PLEASE DON'T LET IT BE A BOY.
ZOE:
WELL, MAYBE YOU SHOULD MOVE ON,
TOO.
WELL, THERE'S NOT EXACTLY A
STRING OF HOTTIES LINING UP
FOR ME.
ZOE:
MAYBE NOT AT SCHOOL.
BUT WHAT ABOUT
IN YOUR TEENDR APP?
TRISTAN:
OH YEAH, THERE REALLY
ARE TONS OF
"HOT SINGLE GUYS IN YOUR AREA."
THOUGH, SO FAR, NONE OF THEM
WANT TO BE IN MY SPECIFIC AREA.
ZOE:
LET ME SEE YOUR PROFILE.
MAYBE YOU AREN'T PUTTING OUT
THE RIGHT VIBES.
LOOKS PRETTY GOOD TO ME.
GRACE:
YEAH, IF YOU WANT TO DIE ALONE.
(SCOFFS)
"LOOKING FOR MASCULINE GUYS."
"STRAIGHT-ACTING."
"BUFF GUYS."
SEE THE PATTERN?
TRISTAN:
YEAH, IT SAYS:
IF I WANT A BOYFRIEND,
I HAVE TO HIT THE GYM.
GRACE: BULLSEYE.
ZOE:
NOT YOU, YOUR PROFILE.
TRISTAN:
OKAY. SO, YOU'RE SAYING
THE ONLY THING STANDING
BETWEEN ME AND TRUE LOVE
IS A PROFILE MAKEOVER?
ZOE:
LET'S DO IT.
GRACE:
IT'LL HAVE TO WAIT.
BELL'S ABOUT TO RING.
AND IF YOU WANT TO STASH
YOUR PHONES, I NEED A DOLLAR.
(SIGHS)
ALLI:
THERE ARE OVER A HUNDRED
BOAT COMPANIES IN THE CITY.
I FIGURED YOU COULD
CALL HALF OF THEM.
CLARE:
YOU KNOW I GET SEA SICK.
ALLI:
WELL, THEN YOU BETTER BUCKLE UP
BECAUSE PROM'S GONNA
BE ROUGH NIGHT.
FOUR YEARS.
FOUR YEARS WE'VE BEEN PLANNING
OUR "STARRY NIGHT"
AND IT GOT DEFEATED
IN ONE MINUTE.
THE VOTE WAS THIS MORNING.
I TOTALLY FORGOT.
I'M SO, SO SORRY.
WELL, I HOPE YOU HAVE
A GOOD EXCUSE.
I HAD TO TALK TO ELI.
ALLI:
BABY STUFF?
CLARE:
YEAH. SORT OF.
ALLI:
PROM IS OUR LAST NIGHT
TOGETHER.
AND THAT'S WHY WE AGREED
TO ORGANIZE IT, TOGETHER.
CLARE:
I KNOW.
ALLI:
BUT IF THIS WHOLE PREGNANCY
THING IS TOO MUCH,
I CAN FIND ANOTHER CO-CHAIR-
CLARE:
DON'T. I'LL DO IT.
ALLI:
DON'T SOUND SO ENTHUSIASTIC.
CLARE:
I'M SAYING YES, AREN'T I?
NOW I HAVE TO BRING POMPOMS?
JUST TELL ME HOW I CAN HELP.
ALLI:
YOU CAN START BY CALLING
THESE BOATS.
WE'RE AUDITIONING MUSIC ACTS
IN THE MORNING.
AND WE NEED TO PICK ONE
BEFORE WE PRESENT TO PILL.
CLARE:
GREAT. I'LL BRING THE COFFEE.
ALLI:
GREAT.
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
ZOE:
OMG, YOU LOOK SO TOUGH.
GRACE:
AND FAKE.
TRISTAN:
AND... UPLOADED!
ZOE:
AND PERFECT.
"INTERESTS INCLUDE:
LIFTING, DRINKING PROTEIN
SHAKES, AND ROCK-CLIMBING."
NICE TOUCH.
TRISTAN: THANKS.
(PHONE CHIMES)
SWEET MERCIFUL GAGA,
I ALREADY GOT A MATCH!
ZOE:
SEE?
TRISTAN:
GAGE. LOOKS LIKE A GREEK GOD.
AND HE WANTS TO GO OUT
WITH ME!
ZOE:
WAIT. WHAT'S WRONG?
TRISTAN:
WELL... HE WANTS TO GO HIKING...
WHICH MEANS NOW I HAVE
TO BE THIS GUY - IN PERSON.
GRACE:
SEE?
(UNSURE EXHALE)
ALLI:
IS THIS THE CELEBRATION CAKE?
YUP! YOU ARE LOOKING AT THE
NEWEST MEMBER OF THE NIPPON
PAPER CRANES.
JAPAN HERE I COME!
PAPER CRANES?
YOU'RE SURE THIS IS A REAL
PROFESSIONAL HOCKEY TEAM?
DALLAS:
OH YEAH. A REAL HOCKEY TEAM.
IN A REAL LEAGUE.
AND THEY'RE PAYING ME REAL
MONEY TO PLAY NEXT YEAR.
LIKE, BIG MONEY.
BABE, WE KNEW IT MOST LIKELY
BE LONG-DISTANCE.
WE CAN MAKE IT WORK.
ALLI:
I KNOW WE CAN.
AND I AM SO EXCITED FOR YOU.
BUT IT'S NOT THAT.
DALLAS:
YOUR HEART-TO-HEART WITH CLARE
DIDN'T GO SO WELL?
ALLI:
I ASKED HER TO HELP WITH PROM,
AND YOU'D THINK I'D INVITED HER
TO HER OWN EXECUTION OR
SOMETHING.
I THINK SHE'S MOVED ON.
DALLAS: FROM HIGH SCHOOL?
ALLI: FROM ME.
YOU KNOW SHE DITCHED ME THIS
MORNING TO HANG OUT WITH HER
BOYFRIEND!
HER AND ELI SHOULD
JUST GET MARRIED
AND MOVE TO SOME DESERTED
ISLAND
WHERE THEY CAN READ EACH OTHER
PRETENTIOUS POETRY.
ELI:
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE A BIT
MORE UNDERSTANDING.
ALLI:
ABOUT THE BABY?
CLARE'S NOT THE FIRST GIRL
IN THE WORLD TO BE PREGNANT,
YOU KNOW.
ELI: SHE ISN'T.
ALLI: WHAT?!
ELI:
WE LOST THE BABY.
DALLAS:
WHOA, DUDE.
I'M SO SORRY.
ELI:
I CAN'T BELIEVE
SHE DIDN'T TELL YOU.
ME NEITHER.
(BIRDS CHIRP)
(FOLIAGE CRUNCHES UNDERFOOT)
GAGE:
YOU DO THIS A LOT?
TRISTAN:
OH YEAH, BRO.
ALL THE TIME.
GAGE:
RAD. SO, YOU'RE GOOD FOR
THE LOOKOUT POINT TRAIL THEN?
TRISTAN:
YEAH, I DON'T ACTUALLY
HIKE HERE, THOUGH.
GAGE:
MORE OF A BLUE MOUNTAIN MAN?
TRISTAN: BIG TIME.
GAGE: KILLER!
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR SOMEONE
TO DO THOSE TRAILS WITH ME.
TRISTAN:
WELL, I'M YOUR MAN.
GAGE:
WHOA, LET'S NOT MOVE TOO FAST
NOW.
I MEAN, THE CLIMBING'S
GOOD UP THERE,
BUT WHAT I'M INTO
IS THE MOUNTAIN BIKING.
I MEAN, HOW IS IT THAT
WE HAVE SO MUCH IN COMMON,
YOU'RE LIKE A FIVE-MINUTE BIKE
RIDE AWAY FROM ME,
AND YET WE'VE NEVER MET?
TRISTAN:
I KNOW, IT'S CRAZY.
GAGE:
YEAH, BUT NOT AS CRAZY AS THIS
HIKE'S ABOUT TO GET.
I KNOW YOU'RE UP
FOR A TOUGH CLIMB?
SO, LET'S DO THIS.
WOO!
(PANTS)
TINY:
UH, BATHROOM'S THERE.
TV'S FIRST COME, FIRST SERVE,
AND BACK ROOM'S YOURS.
VINCE:
ZIGGY, COME CHECK
THIS GAME OUT.
ZIG:
IT'S ALL RIGHT, MAN, I GOT AN
EARLY REHEARSAL, TOMORROW.
VINCE:
ALL RIGHT THEN,
ENJOY THAT BREAD SANDWICH.
(CHUCKLING)
TINY:
YOU REMEMBER, RIGHT?
LAST WEEK AT CHOMPY C?
OH, RIGHT.
YOU WERE AT REHEARSAL.
WELL, WE REALIZED EVERYTHING
ON THE MENU HAD SOME BIRD IN IT,
WHICH MEANT THE ONLY THING
A VEGETARIAN COULD HAVE
WAS A BREAD SANDWICH.
ZIG:
BUT I'M NOT A VEGETARIAN.
VINCE:
IT MEANS YOU'RE MISSING OUT
ON THE BEST PARTS OF LIFE!
TINY:
IT'S ALL GOOD, ZIG.
GO CRASH.
VINCE:
DON'T BLAME US WHEN YOU
DON'T KNOW WHAT'S WHAT.
(GAME SOUNDS, GUNFIRE)
MAN: MOVE BACK!
MAN 2: I NEED TO RELOAD.
ATTA BOY.
TINY:
BET YOU COULDN'T DO THIS
AT YOUR GIRLFRIEND'S HOUSE.
ZIG:
YOU'D BE RIGHT.
(GAME SOUNDS, GUNFIRE)
MAN 3: TAKE HIM OUT!
LOOK OUT! LOOK OUT!
(EXHALES)
BECKY, JONAH:
♪ ...We've been waiting
all this time ♪
♪ To get where we belong ♪
I THINK THIS IS THE PERFECT SONG
TO PLAY DURING THE SLIDE SHOW.
DREW:
UH, I DON'T LIKE IT.
ALLI:
WELL, WE STILL HAVE
FIVE MUSICAL ACTS TO HEAR
UNTIL WE MAKE OUR VOTE.
JENNA:
SPEAKING OF VOTING,
WHERE'S CLARE?
ALLI:
OH!
CLARE:
I'M SO SORRY, I'M LATE.
THE LINE AT THE DOT WAS EPIC.
YOU'D THINK A BARISTA'S
GIRLFRIEND COULD SKIP AHEAD.
ALLI:
LET ME TAKE THOSE.
AND DON'T FEEL THE NEED
TO STAY.
I'VE GOT EVERYTHING
UNDER CONTROL.
SO YOU DON'T
WANT ME INVOLVED?
BECAUSE I MISSED
A COUPLE MEETINGS?
NO! NO, NO, NO.
I'M JUST TRYING TO BE
AN UNDERSTANDING FRIEND.
ELI TOLD YOU.
HE THOUGHT I KNEW.
I DIDN'T WANT PEOPLE TREATING
ME DIFFERENTLY.
THIS IS WHY I DIDN'T
TELL ANYONE.
SO I'M JUST ANYONE NOW?
AND HOW WOULD I KNOW
WHAT YOU WANT?
YOU DON'T TELL ME ANYTHING!
I FEEL LIKE I DON'T EVEN KNOW
CLARE EDWARDS ANYMORE.
WELL, I'M SORRY FOR BEING
SUCH A HUGE DISAPPOINTMENT.
COME ON, THAT'S NOT
WHAT I MEANT.
CAN WE JUST GO SOMEWHERE
AND TALK.
I'M GOOD. THANKS.
(RETREATING FOOTSTEPS)
IMOGEN:
OKAY, FRANKIE, CROSSES
STAGE RIGHT AND THEN SINGS-
FRANKIE:
♪ Show me who you are... ♪
WINSTON:
♪ I'm... ♪
IMOGEN:
AND LUCIUS GERONIMO ENTERS,
STAGE LEFT.
WINSTON:
THAT'S WEIRD.
HAS ANYONE SEEN ZIG?
ZIG:
SORRY, SORRY.
I SLEPT IN.
WINSTON:
WE NOTICED.
ZIG:
JUST CAN IT, GLASSES.
SORRY.
I'M JUST REALLY BAGGED.
IMOGEN:
OKAY. GO GET SOME COFFEES.
ZIG:
LOOK, THIS, THIS WILL NEVER
HAPPEN AGAIN. I PROMISE.
OKAY. I NEED EVERYONE TO BE
100 PERCENT COMMITTED TO THIS.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I'M CRASHING AT A FRIEND'S
AND THEY GO TO BED AT LIKE...
I DON'T KNOW.
I HEARD MORNING BIRDS.
IMOGEN:
YOU NEED TO TELL YOUR ROOMMATES
YOU NEED YOUR BEAUTY SLEEP.
ZIG:
LIKE THAT'S GONNA WORK.
DIDN'T YOU JOIN THE MUSICAL
SO YOU COULD STAY OUT OF
TROUBLE?
ZIG:
LOOK, ME AND THESE GUYS,
IT'S A DIFFERENT WORLD, IMOGEN.
I CAN'T JUST PISS THEM OFF
AND THEN EXPECT THEM TO HAVE
MY BACK WHEN I NEED IT.
IMOGEN:
SOUNDS TO ME LIKE YOU'VE GOT
TO START HAVING YOUR OWN BACK,
KNOW WHERE TO DRAW THE LINE.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO DO THAT?
I MEAN, THESE ARE MY BOYS.
IF THEY'RE REALLY "YOUR BOYS,"
THEY'LL UNDERSTAND.
(FRUSTRATED EXHALE)
ZOE:
I TAKE IT YOUR DATE
WENT POORLY.
NO! IT WENT GREAT ACTUALLY.
(WINCES) AGH!
AND GAGE EVEN WANTS TO GO OUT,
AGAIN.
ZOE:
REALLY?
THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
YEAH. EXCEPT HE DOESN'T WANT
TO GO OUT WITH THE REAL ME,
HE WANTS TO GO OUT
WITH FICTIONAL ME.
IT'S ALREADY DOOMED.
WHICH SUCKS BECAUSE
HE'S A SWEETHEART,
AND I THINK I COULD
REALLY LIKE HIM.
ZOE:
OKAY, WELL...
WHY NOT GO OUT WITH HIM AGAIN,
BUT THIS TIME BE YOURSELF?
SO HE CAN DUMP ME FASTER THAN HE
CAN MOUNTAIN BIKE DOWN A HILL?
YOU SHOULD AT LEAST TRY.
HE OBVIOUSLY LIKES PARTS OF YOU.
SO HE MIGHT LIKE THE REAL YOU.
BUT WHAT IF HE DOESN'T?
THEN I'VE THROWN AWAY MY ONE
SHOT AT ROMANCE SINCE MILES.
IS THAT REALLY
WHAT YOU WANT?
LOOK AT YOU.
YOU'RE IN CLASS,
LITERALLY DRESSING YOUR WOUNDS.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY,
LOVE HURTS.
(SIGHS)
ALLI:
AND THIS, APPARENTLY,
IS WHERE WE'D LIKE
TO HOST OUR PROM.
MS. PILL:
A BOAT?
ALLI:
WELL, YOU KNOW THAT OLD SAYING,
"THE BEST SHIP
IS THE FRIENDSHIP"?
MS. PILL:
I THINK PROM ON A BOAT
SOUNDS... INCREDIBLE.
ALLI:
YOU DO?
MS. PILL:
I'M A SUCKER
FOR A BEAUTIFUL PROM.
AND YOUR PRESENTATION
WAS VERY IMPRESSIVE.
DID YOU HAVE HELP?
I WAS SUPPOSED TO.
HMM. YOUR CO-CHAIR
WAS CLARE EDWARDS?
SHE'S BEEN THROUGH
A LOT THIS YEAR.
(BELL RINGS)
SO EVERYTHING IS APPROVED,
THEN?
MS. PILL:
YES. I THINK YOU'VE GUARANTEED
YOURSELF THE PERFECT PROM NIGHT.
(SIGHS) ACTUALLY, I HAVE ONE
LAST DETAIL TO IRON OUT.
GAGE:
HEY.
TRISTAN:
DIDN'T TAKE YOU
FOR A TEA DRINKER.
GAGE:
KOMBUCHA.
IF YOU GO HARD LIKE WE DO,
THIS IS THE PERFECT DRINK
BEFORE YOU HIT THE TRAILS.
YEAH. I DON'T.
GAGE:
YOU DON'T WHAT?
TRISTAN:
"GO HARD LIKE WE DO."
I LIED ON MY PROFILE.
PLEASE DON'T HATE ME.
YOU SEEM LIKE A GREAT GUY.
AND I WISH I LIKED
THE SAME THINGS YOU DO,
BUT... I DON'T.
GAGE:
I DON'T ALWAYS, EITHER.
WHAT?
GAGE:
I LOVE BEING PHYSICAL.
BUT I LIKE OTHER THINGS, TOO.
TRISTAN:
LIKE WHAT?
GAGE:
MUSIC. COOKING SHOWS.
I DUNNO.
IT'S JUST THAT THIS WHOLE
ONLINE DATING THING
MAKES YOU FEEL LIKE YOU HAVE
TO PUT YOURSELF INSIDE A BOX -
THAT YOU AREN'T ALLOWED
OUT OF...
YEAH, IT'S REALLY HARD.
ONLINE DATING?
HOW LONG HAVE YOU DONE IT?
GAGE:
NOT JUST ONLINE DATING.
BEING OUT. AT SEVENTEEN.
THERE'S SO FEW OF US.
SOMETIMES I FEEL
LIKE A UNICORN.
GAGE:
RIGHT?
IT'S LIKE, I MEET GUYS
I HAVE LOTS IN COMMON WITH
AND THEN THEY'RE STRAIGHT.
AND THEN MY FRIENDS TRY
TO SET ME UP WITH SOMEONE
JUST BECAUSE THEY'RE GAY,
AND WE HAVE NOTHING IN COMMON.
TRISTAN:
SO YOU FEEL LIKE YOU'LL BE
ALONE, FOREVER?
GAGE:
EXACTLY.
TRISTAN:
WELL, YOU AREN'T ALONE
IN FEELING THAT, TRUST ME.
GAGE:
THAT'S NICE TO HEAR.
TRISTAN:
OKAY, I ADMIT IT-
I DON'T WANT TO GO
MOUNTAIN BIKING,
UM, BUT I DON'T HAVE TO BE
HOME FOR A COUPLE HOURS.
DO YOU WANNA MAYBE,
GO SOMEWHERE AND TALK?
ABOUT WHAT?
WELL, DID YOU WATCH THE LAST
EPISODE OF CHOPPED?
WITH THE SUNCHOKES?
DUDE!
YOU KNOW, I HADN'T EVEN
HEARD OF THEM!
GAGE:
THEY'RE THE BEST.
YOU KNOW I DID THAT RECIPE?
TRISTAN: REALLY? WAS IT EASY?
GAGE: YEAH.
(DOOR OPENS)
TINY:
AH, SWEET, YOU'RE HOME.
LET'S GO GET SOME DINNER.
I'M FEELING... SUSHI?
ZIG:
UH, I CAN'T, MAN,
I GOTTA PRACTICE.
YOU KNOW, FOR THE MUSICAL.
VINCE:
BAD ENOUGH THIS NERD'S
ALWAYS DOING HOMEWORK,
BUT YOU'RE STILL
SINGING SONGS?
TELL ME YOU'RE JOKING.
ZIG:
DOES THIS LOOK LIKE
MY JOKING FACE?
I DUNNO, YOUR FACE KINDA
ALWAYS LOOKS THE SAME.
ZIG:
WELL, RIGHT NOW THIS FACE
IS SERIOUS ABOUT THE MUSICAL.
ALL RIGHT?
I LIKE DOING IT.
VINCE:
YOU ANY GOOD?
TINY:
HE'S LEGIT.
I'VE HEARD HIM SING.
VINCE:
I'LL BE THE JUDGE OF THAT.
WHAT? YOU MEAN,
LIKE RIGHT NOW?
WHAT HAPPENED TO SUSHI?
TINY:
WE'LL ORDER IN. COME ON,
SHOW VINCE WHAT YOU'VE GOT.
ZIG:
ALL RIGHT.
BUT, IF I'M GONNA PUT ON A
SHOW, THEN YOU ARE GONNA HELP.
I PLAY LUCIUS GERONIMO,
AND YOU CAN PLAY THE CAPTAIN.
TINY: CAPTAIN WHO?
ZIG: EXACTLY.
TRISTAN:
NO, I DON'T USE SALT
THAT MUCH IN COOKING,
BUT I'M ACTUALLY
GOING TO START...
GAGE:
ALL RIGHT.
TRISTAN:
I BETTER GET GOING.
GAGE:
SO, BLUE MOUNTAIN NEXT TIME?
TRISTAN:
OKAY. MAYBE A COOKING CLASS?
GAGE:
SOUNDS GOOD.
I'LL SEE YOU AROUND.
WELL... HE'S EASY ON THE EYES.
YOU GONNA SEE HIM AGAIN?
POSSIBLY. I'M IN NO RUSH
TO SETTLE DOWN.
BUT YOU'RE OVER MILES?
TRISTAN:
OH, BIG TIME.
THERE ARE SO MANY BETTER GUYS
OUT THERE.
I JUST HAVE TO GET
TO KNOW THEM.
ANYWAYS, GOTTA TINKLE.
ZOE: HEY.
MILES: HEY.
UM, YOU STILL GONNA
SEE KENDRICK LAMAR?
YEAH. BUT I FOUND SOMEONE
TO GO WITH.
OH. UM, WHO?
MILES:
YOU. THAT'S WHAT YOU
WERE ASKING, RIGHT?
I GUESS THERE ARE WORSE WAYS
TO SPEND THE NIGHT.
(SMALL LAUGH)
MAN, MY EGO IS IN NO DANGER
OF BLOWING UP AROUND YOU,
IS IT?
ZOE: NO.
(BOTH LAUGH)
(DOOR OPENS AND SLAMS SHUTS)
CLARE:
YOU BOUGHT ME FLOWERS?
ALLI:
THE GUY AT FLOWER SHOP SAID,
YELLOW ROSES REPRESENT
FRIENDSHIP.
A THEME I HOPE
IS STILL RELEVANT.
CLARE, ALLI:
I'M SORRY.
ALLI:
I SHOULDN'T HAVE EXCLUDED YOU
FROM PROM PLANNING.
CLARE:
I DON'T BLAME YOU.
I HAVEN'T EXACTLY BEEN
DEBBIE DEPENDABLE, LATELY.
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME
ABOUT THE BABY?
CLARE:
BECAUSE IT'S HARD FOR ME
TO BE AROUND YOU RIGHT NOW.
ALLI:
WHY? WHAT DID I DO WRONG?
CLARE:
NOTHING. YOU...
YOU DID EVERYTHING RIGHT.
YOU HAVE EVERYTHING
SO TOGETHER.
ARE WE TALKING
ABOUT THE SAME ME HERE?
YOU'RE PLANNING PROM
ALL BY YOURSELF.
YOU HAVE A PERFECT BOYFRIEND.
YOU'RE GOING TO CAMBRIDGE
UNIVERSITY OR M.I.T.
OR SOMEWHERE EVEN MORE AWESOME.
AND... AND ME?
I HAVE NOTHING!
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
(SCOFFS)
YOU HAVE ME.
AND YOU'LL ALWAYS HAVE ME.
(SIGHS)
BUT ONLY IF WE TALK
BECAUSE NEXT YEAR,
TALKING'S ALL WE'LL HAVE.
BUT FIRST PROM.
AND WE'LL MAKE IT AWESOME.
I SWEAR,
A NIGHT TO REMEMBER.
ALLI:
IF PROM PLANNING IS TOO MUCH
FOR YOU RIGHT NOW-
CLARE:
IT'S NOT.
SOME REGULAR TEEN GIRL STUFF
IS EXACTLY WHAT I NEED.
ESPECIALLY IF IT'S WITH YOU.
OKAY. WELL...
WE BETTER GET TO WORK.
♪♪
ZIG:
♪ I'm the thing that goes
bump in the night ♪
♪ The thing that makes
your children cry ♪
♪ It's no use
in putting up a fight ♪
♪ Say hello to the bad guy! ♪
TINY
NICE.
VINCE:
NAILED IT!
(CLAPS) BRAVO!
(PHONE BUZZES)
ZIG: OH.
AH, IT'S THE GIRLFRIEND.
BETTER TAKE THIS,
OR SHE'LL BE WORRIED.
LUCIUS GERONIMO,
AT YOUR SERVICE.
MAYA:
AM I INTERRUPTING
SOMETHING?
TINY:
YEAH, DON'T YOU KNOW
MY MAN'S GOTTA PRACTICE?
ZIG:
HEY, I CAN ALWAYS SQUEEZE IN
A MINUTE FOR MISS MAYA MATLIN.
MAYA:
YOU LOOKED OFF THIS MORNING,
BUT NOW YOU SEEM ALL SHINY
AND HAPPY.
LIFE IS GOOD.
GANG GUY: (BANGING ON DOOR)
POLICE! OPEN UP!
ZIG:
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW?
MAYA:
CAN'T WAIT.
AND ZIG...?
I'M PROUD OF YOU.
(BANGING ON THE DOOR)
(DOOR CLICKS OPEN)
(LAUGHING)
(ZIPPER OPENS, BAG RUSTLES)
GANG GUY:
JUST WHAT THE DOCTOR ORDERED.
VINCE:
YO, T, GET US A COUPLE BEERS?
THIS IS SOME PREMIUM MOLLY.
WE BETTER GET TO WORK.
(EXHALES)
YOU MAY AS WELL HELP US OUT,
YOU KNOW,
SINCE YOU'RE FREELOADING.
(BAGGIES RUSTLE)