(MONITOR BEEPS)
(APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS)
ZIG:
YOU KNOW, YOU'D THINK
THEY'D FEED SOMEONE
WHO JUST GOT STABBED
SOMETHING BETTER
THAN SOME RUBBER EGGS.
MAYA:
WHICH IS WHY
WE BROUGHT YOU... DONUTS!
TINY: OH, YES.
ZIG: ZOE PAID FOR HALF.
SHE FEELS HORRIBLE
FOR WHAT HAPPENED.
TINY:
WHY? SHE DIDN'T STAB ME.
OH! HOW'D YOU KNOW
CHOCOLATE DIP IS MY FAVOURITE?
MAYA:
I THINK WE GOT YOU
IN TROUBLE.
TINY:
AH, DON'T PLAY ME LIKE THAT,
RHONDA.
YOU KNOW YOU LOVE ME!
(LAUGHS THEN GRUNTS IN PAIN)
HOW YOU FEELING, MAN?
SORE.
BUT THE DOC SAYS I'LL BE GOOD
TO GO HOME IN A COUPLE DAYS.
MAYA:
AND WHY CAN'T WE JUST
TELL THE COPS IT WAS DAMON
SO THEY CAN ARREST HIM?
TINY:
'CAUSE SNITCHES GET STITCHES,
BLONDIE.
I THOUGHT HE WAS YOUR FRIEND.
BUT THEN HIS FAMILY MOVED
TO ANOTHER BLOCK AND...
HE GOT CAUGHT UP
WITH SOME BAD DUDES.
I CAN'T TALK.
ONLY MAKE THINGS WORSE.
MAYA:
SO YOU TOLD THE COPS
YOU GOT JUMPED BY SOME RANDOM?
TINY:
EXACTLY.
ZIG:
ANY OF YOUR GUYS
TALKING PAYBACK?
TINY:
NO NEED TO CONCERN YOURSELF
WITH ANY OF THAT.
MAYA:
(SIGHS) WE SHOULD
GET TO SCHOOL.
DON'T WANNA BE LATE
OR SCARY MS. PILL
WILL NAIL US WITH DETENTION.
TINY: AGH! BE GENTLE.
MAYA: RIGHT.
(TINY AND MAYA CHUCKLE)
NOVAK, MY MAN.
YOU GOTTA CHILL.
EVERYTHING'S GONNA BE FINE.
YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh... ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
ELI:
OKAY. A LARGE NON FAT LATTE AND
A DECAF CAPPUCCINO ON THE HOUSE.
WELL, THIS IS A PERK
I CAN GET USED TO.
I'LL TEXT YOU LATER
ABOUT THIS AFTERNOON.
MM. NO CELL PHONES,
REMEMBER?
SO HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO MAKE PLANS?
THE OLD FASHIONED WAY:
I'LL STOP BY AFTER YOUR SHIFT.
AND I HAVE A SPARE
LAST PERIOD ANYWAY.
ELI: CAN'T WAIT.
WE'RE GONNA ROCK THIS.
CLARE: MM-HMM!
HIGH-FIVING
OVER A DATE?
YOU TWO HAVE ALWAYS BEEN
THE WEIRDEST COUPLE.
CLARE:
NOT A DATE.
BIRTHING CLASS.
AND WE HIGH-FIVED BECAUSE
THAT'S WHAT STRICTLY PLATONIC
CO-PARENTS DO.
CLARE, I LOVE YOU,
BUT YOU'RE DELUSIONAL.
HOW SO?!
BECAUSE YOU AND ELI
WILL NEVER BE FRIENDS.
IT'S JUST NOT POSSIBLE.
THANKS FOR YOUR SUPPORT.
ALLI:
WELL, IF HISTORY IS ANY
INDICATION,
YOU TWO ARE LIKE MAGNETS.
YOU GET IN
EACH OTHERS' ORBITS AND...
SMASH.
IT'S INEVITABLE.
WELL, IT CAN'T BE.
NOT THIS TIME.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
MAYA:
HEY, DID YOU REMEMBER
TO SET THE DVR
TO RECORD THE NEW
"GAME OF THRONES?"
ZIG:
UH, I DON'T KNOW.
MAYA:
DAENERYS BETTER GET
TO KING'S LANDING, THIS WEEK.
IT'S TAKING FOREVER.
ZIG:
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
WHAT'S UP?
YOU'RE ALL FAR AWAY.
I FEEL LIKE IT'S MY FAULT.
WHAT? TINY?
ZIG, THAT'S CRAZY.
BUT HE JUMPED IN
TO HELP ME.
MAYA:
DAMON WAS BEING A CREEP!
YOU WERE DEFENDING ZOE!
HOW WERE YOU SUPPOSED
TO KNOW THAT HE HAD A KNIFE?
I'M PISSED, OKAY?
I... I WANNA DO SOMETHING.
I WANNA GET BACK
AT THOSE GUYS.
YOU CAN'T, RIGHT?
YOU KNOW THAT.
IT'S JUST NOT FAIR.
TINY STILL LIVES IN A
NEIGHBORHOOD WHERE ANYTHING
CAN HAPPEN.
MEANWHILE,
I GET TO LIVE WITH YOU
AND BASICALLY BE A PART
OF YOUR FAMILY.
AND TINY WOULDN'T WANT YOU
TO JEOPARDIZE THAT
BY DOING SOMETHING STUPID.
THIS SUCKS.
MAYA:
MAYBE YOU NEED SOMETHING ELSE
DURING THE WEEK.
YOU COULD ALWAYS AUDITION
FOR THE SCHOOL MUSICAL.
THAT'S NOT GONNA MAKE TINY
UN-STABBED.
I KNOW, BUT...
IT'S WORTH A TRY.
(BELL RINGS)
(MUSIC FROM CAPITAN WHO" PLAYS)
WINSTON:
I'M JUST A LAB TECH, ELLA.
I CAN'T STOP THE EVIL MAYOR
LUCIUS GERONIMO
FROM DESTROYING THE CITY.
LOLA:
IF ONLY I KNEW WHO
CAPTAIN WHO REALLY WAS!
(MUSIC STARTS)
♪ Whenever you are close to me ♪
♪ I want to...
Kiss your lips ♪
♪ But until I know
The real you ♪
♪ I have to resist ♪
♪ Can you ever love the guy
who hides behind the mask ♪
♪ Show me who you are ♪
FRANKIE:
THAT WAS GREAT!
SUPER CUTE.
BUT LET'S TRY IT AGAIN!
THIS SCENE IS SUPPOSED TO
CRACKLE WITH ROMANTIC TENSION!
REMEMBER, ELLA ELLIOT IS
IN LOVE WITH CAPTAIN WHO,
HAVING NO IDEA THAT
HE'S ACTUALLY HER BEST FRIEND,
SIMON HU!
LOLA:
SO... LIKE THIS?
WINSTON:
(LAUGHS AWKWARDLY)
NO PDA, REMEMBER?
IMOGEN:
I THINK, IN THIS CONTEXT,
IT'S TOTALLY FINE.
FRANKIE:
STRAIGHT FROM THE MOUTH
OF OUR WISE STUDENT ADVISOR!
WINSTON:
OH, I THINK WE HAVE A PRETTY
GOOD IDEA OF WHAT LOLA CAN DO.
FRANKIE:
THEN THAT'S A WRAP
ON GIRLS' AUDITIONS.
TOMORROW, IT'S THE GUYS.
IMOGEN:
I AM MIGHTY IMPRESSED
YOU WROTE THE WHOLE MUSICAL
BY YOURSELF.
LOLA:
SO?! HOW WAS I?!
FRANKIE:
WE'LL MAKE OUR DECISIONS, SOON.
BUT BETWEEN YOU AND ME,
YOU'RE A SHOO-IN.
WINSTON:
OKAY, LET'S NOT GO
WRITING CHEQUES
OUR BUTTS CAN'T CASH,
FRANKIE.
FRANKIE:
ALL RIGHT.
LET ME SHOW YOU THIS.
IMOGEN:
(CLEARS HER THROAT)
WHY ARE YOU BEING SO WEIRD?
LOLA WAS AWESOME.
CAN YOU KEEP A SECRET?
WHEN I WANT TO.
I KISSED LOLA.
OR SHE KISSED ME.
IT'S ALL A BLUR.
ALL I KNOW IS THAT
IT WAS A GIANT MISTAKE.
(LAUGHING)
IT'S NOT FUNNY!
YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
I KNOW!
WHAT DO I DO?!
OH JEEZ.
I HAVE NO IDEA.
SORRY.
(SIGHS)
(BELL RINGS)
DID YOUR BOY GET
MY GET WELL FLOWERS?
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?!
GO ON.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF YOU THE WAY
I TOOK CARE OF YOUR BOY.
COME ON!
(SNORTS)
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
(BREATHING HARD)
(HARD PUNCH)
MILES:
AUDITIONING FOR THE MUSICAL?
GOOD LUCK WITH THAT.
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
EXACTLY WHAT IT
SOUNDS LIKE.
BUT, IF YOU GET THE PART,
I GUESS YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO CUT ALL THE SLEEVES OFF
YOUR COSTUMES.
WATCH YOUR MOUTH,
RICH BOY!
WHAT'S YOUR DAMAGE?
ZIG:
YOU ARE!
(LOUD CRASH)
GRACE:
NOVAK! STOP!
GET OUTTA HERE.
GRACE: WHAT WAS THAT ALL ABOUT?
ZIG: I LOST MY TEMPER!
IS THIS BECAUSE OF TINY?
YEAH. YEAH, I GUESS.
BECAUSE MONEYBAGS ISN'T
THE ONE WHO STABBED HIM.
ZIG:
YEAH, I KNOW THAT!
BUT I CAN'T DO ANYTHING
ABOUT THE GUY WHO DID DO IT.
YOU GOTTA SORT YOURSELF OUT,
NOVAK.
THAT KIND OF ANGER
IS POISONOUS.
IT JUST LEADS TO MORE ANGER.
YOU GOTTA FIND A WAY
TO BREAK THE CYCLE.
(SOFT MEDITATION MUSIC PLAYS)
CLARE:
WE ARE TOTALLY GONNA GET AN 'A'.
ELI:
I DON'T THINK
THAT'S HOW THIS WORKS.
INSTRUCTOR:
PREGNANT GODDESSES.
I'M HONOURED TO BE A GUIDE
FOR YOU AND YOUR PARTNERS
AS YOU MOVE THROUGH
YOUR PREGNANCY
TOWARDS A PEACEFUL, POWERFUL,
AND BEAUTIFUL BIRTHING
EXPERIENCE.
WELCOME.
CLARE:
OH NO. I THINK I SIGNED US UP
FOR A BIRTHING CLASS IN '60S.
ELI:
I'M INTO IT.
WHERE ARE MY CRYSTALS?
INSTRUCTOR:
I LIKE TO BEGIN EACH CLASS
WITH AN AFFIRMATION.
BIRTHING PARTNERS, TURN TO
THE MOTHER OF YOUR CHILD,
AND AFFIRM TO HER YOUR LOVE
AND YOUR BELIEF
IN HER CAPABILITY
TO UNDERTAKE THIS CHALLENGE
AHEAD.
IT'S OKAY,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
CLARE, I'M NOT GONNA
BE RESPONSIBLE
FOR YOUR FIRST FAILING GRADE.
(SIGHS)
CLARE EDWARDS.
YOU ARE THE MOST INCREDIBLE
PERSON I'VE EVER MET.
AND I KNOW THIS ISN'T HOW
YOU PLANNED FOR THINGS TO GO,
AND I KNOW IT'S SCARY,
BUT...
I FEEL REALLY LUCKY TO BE PART
OF THIS JOURNEY WITH YOU.
I LOVE YOU AND I'LL...
I'LL ALWAYS BE HERE FOR YOU
NO MATTER WHAT.
NAMASTE.
RECORDING OF LOLA:
♪ But until I know
the real you, I have... ♪
(LAPTOP KEY CLICKS,
SONG STOPS)
FRANKIE:
OKAY, I DEFINITELY THINK
LOLA'S THE RIGHT CHOICE
FOR ELLA ELLIOT.
WINSTON:
I DON'T KNOW.
SHE SOUNDED A LITTLE PITCHY.
YEAH,
ISN'T SHE A LITTLE PITCHY?
(KEY CLICKS)
LOLA: ♪ I have to resist... ♪
SHE SOUNDS PRETTY GREAT TO ME.
I JUST THINK THERE WERE
STRONGER CHOICES.
LIKE SHAY.
WERE WE WATCHING
THE SAME AUDITIONS?
I LOVE SHAY,
BUT THE GIRL IS TONE DEAF.
I JUST THINK LOLA'S...
TOO SHORT.
I KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON HERE.
YOU DON'T LIKE LOLA.
YEAH, SOMETHING
ABOUT HER JUST...
RUBS ME THE WRONG WAY.
FRANKIE:
BUT SHE'S MY FRIEND,
AND IT'S IMPORTANT TO ME
THAT YOU LIKE MY FRIENDS,
AND THAT YOU WANT TO CAST THEM
IN OUR MUSICAL.
SORRY, FRANKS.
LOLA'S JUST... THE WORST.
SHE'S SO... YOU KNOW...
THE WORST.
BUT YOU HAVEN'T EVEN
GIVEN HER A CHANCE.
I KNOW WHAT NEEDS
TO HAPPEN.
WHY DO I FEEL LIKE
YOU'RE GONNA SAY
WE ALL NEED TO HANG OUT
TOGETHER?
FRANKIE:
BECAUSE WE ALL NEED
TO HANG OUT TOGETHER!
AS SOON AS YOU SEE
HOW AWESOME LOLA IS,
YOU'LL TOTALLY BE DOWN WITH
CASTING HER IN CAPTAIN WHO.
(CHUCKLES WEAKLY)
ZIG:
HEY, MILES?
MILES:
FIND SOMEONE ELSE
TO GO POSTAL ON.
I'M NOT REALLY IN THE MOOD.
LOOK, I'M...
I'M SORRY, OKAY?
I SHOULDN'T HAVE FREAKED OUT
AT YOU LIKE THAT.
I'M GOING THROUGH
SOME STUFF RIGHT NOW
AND I TOOK IT OUT ON YOU.
SO WE'RE COOL?
(CLEARS HIS THROAT)
WELL, I DON'T THINK WE'LL BE
GETTING LUNCH ANYTIME SOON,
BUT YEAH, WE'RE COOL.
(RELIEVED SIGH)
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER
IN THE HALLWAY)
GRACE:
NOVAK! THIS IS BAD.
ZIG:
WHAT'RE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
GRACE:
PEOPLE ARE CHIRPING ONLINE,
SAYING THERE'S GONNA BE
SOME SORT OF RETALIATION
TOMORROW NIGHT
FOR WHAT HAPPENED TO TINY.
AT THAT BASKETBALL COURT
BEHIND SAINT FRANCIS.
BUT TINY SAID HIS GUYS
WERE CHILL.
BELIEVE ME WHEN I SAY
THEY ARE NOT.
HOW DO YOU EVEN KNOW THIS
WITH THE CELL PHONE BAN?
I HAVE MY WAYS, AND THAT'S ALL
YOU'RE GETTING OUT OF ME.
IT SOUNDS SERIOUS.
YOU HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
WHAT, ME?
I... CAN-CAN'T!
WHY NOT?
I CAN'T RISK
GETTING INVOLVED.
AND BESIDES, WHAT ABOUT
ALL THAT CRAP YOU SAID
ABOUT STOPPING THE CYCLE
OF VIOLENCE AND ANGER.
FORGET WHAT I SAID.
ZIG, IF YOU DON'T DO SOMETHING,
SOMEONE COULD GET KILLED.
(SWALLOWS AUDIBLY)
(BIRDS CHIRP, CAR RUMBLES,
CEREAL RATTLES IN BOWL)
MRS. MATLIN:
GOOD LUCK WITH
YOUR MUSICAL AUDITION TODAY.
ZIG:
THANKS.
YOU DON'T THINK ME AUDITIONING
FOR THE MUSICAL
IS THE DUMBEST IDEA
YOU'VE EVER HEARD, RIGHT?
NO WAY! I THINK IT'S THE PERFECT
THING TO KEEP YOURSELF BUSY.
WHAT'S UP WITH YOU?
YOU'RE BEING WEIRD.
(SIGHS)
IT JUST DOESN'T FEEL RIGHT
WITH ALL THIS STUFF GOING ON.
MAYA:
ZIG, TINY'S GONNA BE OKAY,
YOU'RE GONNA ROCK
YOUR AUDITION,
AND EVERYTHING'S
GONNA BE FINE.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THANK YOU.
FOR WHAT?
(CHUCKLES)
I DUNNO, EVERYTHING?
HOUSING ME? KEEPING ME OUT
OF TROUBLE? NOT GIVING UP ON ME?
NEVER GONNA HAPPEN.
I WISH TINY HAD A MAYA.
HE'D HAVE TO GET HIS OWN,
BUT... YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
YEAH, WELL, HE HAS YOU.
YOU'RE NOT SO BAD.
♪ But they day
don't sleep at all ♪
FRANKIE:
YOUR HAIR MATCHES LIKE
EVERYTHING YOU'RE WEARING.
LOLA:
I KNOW!
ISN'T THAT AWESOME?
FRANKIE: IT'S PRETTY GREAT!
LOLA: I KNOW.
LOLA:
(GASPS) CRANBERRY MUFFIN?!
I COULD KISS YOU!
FRANKIE:
ISN'T HE THE BEST?
LOLA:
WITHOUT CHEER BOSS ZOE
TO KEEP ME HONEST,
I CAN KISS MY NO-CARB DIET
GOODBYE.
(WINSTON COUGHS)
DID YOU FORGET MY COFFEE?
SORRY!
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
NO, I'LL GO.
YOU TWO STAY AND CHAT.
WINSTON:
STOP SAYING KISS!
LOLA:
I'M SORRY! IT JUST KEEPS COMING
OUT OF MY LIPS!
AND STOP SAYING LIPS!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
WE'RE SCREWED.
NEITHER OF US IS DISCREET
ENOUGH TO PULL THIS OFF,
AND SHE TOTALLY WANTS
TO CAST YOU IN THE MUSICAL!
I KNOW,
ISN'T THAT AWESOME?!
WINSTON:
FOCUS! DO YOU REALLY THINK
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA -
US SPENDING THAT MUCH TIME
TOGETHER?
KISSING ON STAGE?
EXACTLY.
(SIGHS) HOW COULD I HAVE
BEEN SUCH AN IDIOT?
MAYBE WE SHOULD
JUST COME CLEAN!
NO, THAT IS NOT AN OPTION.
I CAN'T LOSE FRANKIE!
BESIDES, DO YOU WANT TO HURT
YOUR FRIEND LIKE THAT?
NO! I LOVE HER!
THAT'D BE AWFUL!
OKAY. WE JUST NEED
A GOOD ENOUGH REASON
NOT TO CAST YOU
IN CAPTAIN WHO.
(SIGHS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER NEARBY)
DAMON...
WE NEED TO TALK.
DAMON:
WE SHOULDN'T BE SEEN TOGETHER.
YOU KNOW SCHOOL'S
A NEUTRAL TERRITORY.
ZIG:
YEAH, I DON'T CARE.
I JUST WANT TO SHUT THIS DOWN
BEFORE ANYONE ELSE GETS HURT.
DAMON:
SO YOUR BOY GETS A PAPER CUT
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN
YOU WANNA HOLD PEACE TALKS?
ZIG:
"A PAPER CUT?!"
YOU PUT HIM IN THE HOSPITAL!
DAMON:
HE HAD IT COMING.
BOY WAS BEEN PISSING ME OFF.
ZIG:
LISTEN, MAN. I'VE BEEN HEARING
RUMBLINGS, ALL RIGHT?
THE GUYS FROM MY BLOCK,
THEY'RE NOT HAPPY.
THEY'RE TALKING RETALIATION.
(SNORTS)
IS THAT SUPPOSED TO SCARE ME?
YEAH, IT SHOULD.
YOU KNOW THAT BASKETBALL COURT
BEHIND SAINT FRANCIS
WHERE YOU GUYS PLAY?
DAMON: YEAH?
ZIG: I WOULDN'T SHOW UP THERE
TONIGHT IF I WERE YOU.
LOOK, MAN, SOMEONE STEPS TO ME,
I GOTTA STEP BACK.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M SICK OF THAT CRAP.
AND I'M NOT PLAYING
BY YOUR STUPID RULES ANYMORE.
ARE YOU THREATENING ME?
NO, I'M WARNING YOU
THERE'S A TRAP.
(BELL RINGS)
JUST DON'T SHOW UP.
OR ELSE WHO KNOWS
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN.
(SIGHS)
(BEAKERS CLINK)
SO, HOW WAS BIRTHING CLASS
WITH YOUR TOTALLY PLATONIC
CO-PARENT?
WATCH ANY UPSETTING VIDEOS?
ELI TOLD ME
HE'D ALWAYS BE THERE FOR ME.
AND THAT'S A PROBLEM WHY?
BECAUSE WHEN HE SAID THAT
I WANTED TO KISS HIM.
NOW I DON'T WANT TO SAY
I TOLD YOU SO...
NO, ALLI, THIS IS REALLY BAD.
WE CAN'T GET BACK TOGETHER.
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE IT'S NOT JUST GONNA
BE US IN THE PICTURE ANYMORE!
BUT YOU LOVE HIM.
YOU CAN'T JUST TAKE THAT
OUT OF THE EQUATION.
AND THIS IS COMING
FROM SOMEONE
THAT DOESN'T EVEN LIKE THE GUY
ALL THAT MUCH.
I NEED TO SET
SOME BOUNDARIES,
SO WE DON'T SLIP
INTO OLD HABITS.
SO WHAT, YOU'RE JUST GONNA
TELL HIM NOT TO DO ANYTHING
THAT MAKES YOU WANNA
KISS HIM?
YEAH, IF I HAVE TO!
OKAY.
♪ I'm the monster
Underneath your bed ♪
♪ The creature lurking
In the dark ♪
♪ Better listen
To what your mama said ♪
♪ You know my bite is worse
Than my bark ♪
♪ I'm the thing that goes bump
In the night ♪
♪ The thing that makes
Your children cry ♪
♪ It's no use in
Putting up a fight ♪
♪ Say hello to the bad guy ♪
♪ Say hello
to your biggest fear ♪
♪ Say hello to the bad guy ♪
♪ You should believe
Everything you hear! ♪
(CHEERING AND CLAPPING)
IMOGEN: THAT WAS AMAZEBALLS!
MAYA:
YOU EVEN HIT THE HIGH NOTE!
ZIG:
WELL, I UH...
I HAD A GREAT COACH.
SO, HOW DO YOU FEEL?
UH... LIKE THIS MIGHT
ACTUALLY WORK.
MAYA: COME ON.
ZIG: WHERE ARE WE GOING?
MAYA:
TO THE PAY PHONES
SO WE CAN CALL MY MOM!
WHEN SHE HEARS HOW WELL
YOUR AUDITION WENT,
SHE'S TOTALLY GONNA TAKE US
FOR CHINESE BUFFET!
AH! WHO KNEW JAMES DEAN
COULD SING?
FRANKIE:
ZIG? YEAH, HE WAS AWESOME,
BUT THERE'S STILL NO ONE BETTER
THAN LOLA FOR ELLA ELLIOT.
I STILL DON'T THINK
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
FRANKIE:
WELL, YOU REALLY HATE LOLA SO
MUCH YOU WON'T EVEN CONSIDER IT?
I DON'T HATE LOLA,
I SWEAR!
THEN WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
I WANT YOU TO PLAY
ELLA ELLIOT.
ME? WHY?
I DON'T WANT TO KISS
ANYONE ELSE.
BUT IT'S JUST ACTING!
WELL, IT DOESN'T MATTER.
BESIDES, YOU WERE THE
INSPIRATION FOR THE CHARACTER
ALL ALONG.
YOU CAN TOTALLY DO IT.
THAT'S SWEET,
BUT I'M DIRECTING.
SOMEONE ELSE CAN DIRECT.
SOMEONE... LIKE IMOGEN.
FRANKIE:
WELL, I DON'T REALLY HAVE
ANY EXPERIENCE.
SO WHAT?
I KNOW YOU CAN SING.
WHAT DO YOU THINK,
IMOGEN?
IMOGEN:
UM... I CAN'T PROMISE
I'M NOT GONNA MAKE
SOME REALLY WEIRD CHOICES.
WINSTON: DEAL!
IMOGEN: OKAY.
FRANKIE:
THIS IS GONNA BE AWESOME!
MAYBE MY DREAM OF PERFORMING
WITH N.P.H. AT THE TONY'S
ISN'T SO CRAZY AFTER ALL!
(CHUCKLING)
(KNOCK AT THE DOOR)
ELI: HEY, WHAT'S UP?
CLARE: THANKS FOR COMING.
ELI:
YOU OKAY?
CLARE:
WE NEED SOME RULES HERE.
ELI:
I DON'T FOLLOW.
WE NEED TO SET SOME BOUNDARIES.
ELI:
OH. I THOUGHT WE WERE DOING
PRETTY WELL!
BIRTHING CLASS WAS AWESOME.
EXACTLY! TOO AWESOME!
ELI:
CLARE.
CLARE:
RULE ONE:
NO TELLING ME YOU LOVE ME
OR HOW AMAZING YOU THINK I AM
OR HOW MUCH YOU SUPPORT ME.
BUT I DO.
THAT'S NEVER GONNA CHANGE.
TWO: NO LOOKING AT ME
THAT WAY YOU DO
THAT TURNS ME
INTO A PILE OF MUSH.
ELI:
WHAT, SO I CAN'T EVEN
LOOK AT YOU NOW?
THAT'S GONNA MAKE THINGS
PRETTY DIFFICULT.
THREE: NO SAYING THE EXACT
THING I NEED TO HEAR
AT THE EXACT MOMENT
I NEED TO HEAR IT,
AND FOUR: NO PHYSICAL CONTACT
OF ANY KIND.
CLARE, I'LL OBEY ANY RULE
YOU WANT.
BUT WHAT ARE YOU
SO SCARED OF?
♪♪
CLARE:
THAT.
♪♪
MRS. MATLIN, MAYA AND ZIG:
(LAUGHING)
ZIG:
THANKS FOR DINNER,
MRS. MATLIN.
MRS. MATLIN:
MY PLEASURE.
I AM SO PROUD OF YOU, ZIG.
MAYA:
EVEN THOUGH HE GOT CAST
AS THE EVIL LUCIUS GERONIMO?
ZIG:
I WILL HAVE YOU KNOW THAT
HE HAS THE THIRD BIGGEST PART
IN THE SCHOOL MUSICAL.
MAYA: OH, I'M SO FULL.
(ZIG'S PHONE CHIRPS)
I SHOULDN'T HAVE EATEN
THAT ENTIRE CREME BRULEE.
ZIG:
(LAUGHS) YEAH,
AND HALF OF MY TIRAMISU.
MAYA: (GROANS)
MRS. MATLIN: MAYA!
(RUNNING FOOTSTEPS)
MAYA: OH MY GOD!
MRS. MATLIN: ZIG, CALL 9-1-1.
CLARE AND ELI:
(CHUCKLING)
CLARE:
THAT'S NOT HOW I PLANNED
FOR THAT TO GO.
DO YOU REGRET IT?
CLARE: NO.
WE CAN'T JUST PRETEND
THAT THINGS HAVEN'T HAPPENED.
EVERYTHING'S CHANGED.
(SIGHS)
I HURT YOU,
I KNOW THAT.
DO YOU REMEMBER THE LAST TIME
WE WERE HAPPY TOGETHER?
I'M HAPPY RIGHT NOW.
AREN'T YOU?
THINGS HAVEN'T BEEN PERFECT,
AND THEY NEVER WILL BE.
BUT I DON'T KNOW ANY OTHER WAY
TO BE, OTHER THAN WITH YOU.
I WANT US TO SPEND THE REST
OF OUR LIVES TOGETHER.
HEY, WHERE ARE YOU?
WITH YOU.
I'M RIGHT HERE.
(KISS)
(CAMERA SHUTTER SNAPS)
(MRS. MATLIN SIGHS)
MRS. MATLIN:
DETECTIVE ROBBINS JUST NEEDS
TO ASK YOU BOTH
A COUPLE OF QUESTIONS.
ZIG: BUT I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
DETECTIVE ROBBINS: WE'RE NOT
SAYING YOU DO.
WE JUST WANT TO FIND
WHOEVER DID THIS.
MAYA:
WE WERE OUT FOR DINNER.
WHEN WE GOT HOME,
IT WAS JUST LIKE THIS.
DETECTIVE ROBBINS:
AND WAS ANYTHING TAKEN?
MRS. MATLIN:
OTHER THAN THE TV,
I... UM, I DON'T KNOW.
I HAVEN'T HAD A CHANCE
TO CHECK.
DETECTIVE ROBBINS:
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE A STANDARD
BREAK AND ENTER.
UNLESS YOU CAN THINK OF ANY
REASON SOMEONE WOULD DO THIS?
MAYA:
NO. NOT AT ALL.
DETECTIVE ROBBINS:
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, GET IN TOUCH
IF YOU FIND ANYTHING TAKEN,
OR IF YOU THINK OF ANYTHING
WE SHOULD KNOW.
(SIREN WAILS IN THE DISTANCE,
RECEDING FOOTSTEPS)
(DOOR CLICKS OPEN THEN SHUT)
(NERVOUS, SHAKY BREATHS)