TINY:
AND HERE WE FIND A HORMONAL ZIG
ATTEMPTING ITS RARE
MATING RITUAL.
YOU GUYS ARE KILLING ME.
GRACE:
THEN GET A ROOM.
THIS IS WHAT WE CALL
A PUBLIC PLACE.
YEAH. WELL, WHERE ELSE
ARE WE SUPPOSED TO GO?
WE CAN'T DO IT AT MAYA'S HOUSE,
WE CAN'T DO IT AT SCHOOL,
OBVIOUSLY!
PEOPLE WON'T GIVE US PRIVACY.
TINY:
NOT KNOWN FOR ITS MIND,
ONE WONDERS IF THE ZIG WILL
CONSIDER THE OBVIOUS ANSWER:
TAKE ITS MATE TO ITS NEST.
WOULD YOU PLEASE STOP
WATCHING ANIMAL PLANET?!
THAT'S ACTUALLY A GREAT IDEA.
WHY DON'T I COME OVER TONIGHT?
OH, NO, YOU DON'T WANT
TO COME OVER.
WHY, WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOUR PLACE?
UH...
(BELL RINGS)
FINE, DINNER TONIGHT,
MY PLACE.
MAYA: YAY!
GRACE: ADORBS.
NOW, LET'S GO BEFORE PILL
CHOPS OFF OUR HANDS
FOR BEING LATE.
DUDE,
MAYA CAN'T COME OVER!
RELAX, OUR APARTMENT
IS FINE.
YEAH, FOR US, SURE!
BUT, WHAT IF SHE FINDS LIKE,
VINCE'S DRUGS, OR SOMETHING?
THAT KIND OF THING IS A DEAL
BREAKER FOR GIRLS LIKE MAYA.
AND SO, THE ZIG WORRIES,
WILL A VISIT TO ITS NEST
PROVIDE A VENUE FOR MATING,
OR AN END TO THE DATING?
(TINY CHUCKLES)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Ooh... ooh... ooh... ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
TWO WEEKS, AND I CAN PUT
THIS WHOLE YEAR BEHIND ME.
AND CELEBRATE WITH PROM!
CONNOR:
MS. PILL WOULD LIKE TO TALK
TO THE THREE OF US.
ALLI:
OKAY.
MS. PILL:
CONGRATULATIONS, YOU THREE
HAVE BEEN SHORTLISTED
FOR VALEDICTORIAN.
GET READY TO EAT MY DUST,
CONNOR.
YOU'LL GIVE SPEECHES VIA
THE VIDEO MONITORS,
TOMORROW AFTERNOON,
AFTER THAT YOUR PEERS WILL VOTE
FOR THE VALEDICTORIAN
OF THEIR CHOICE.
THANKS MS. PILL,
BUT I'LL PASS.
ACTUALLY, CLARE,
I'D LIKE TO CHAT WITH YOU.
ALLI, CONNOR, I LOOK FORWARD
TO YOUR SPEECHES.
(AWKWARD LAUGH)
YOU'D MAKE A GREAT
VALEDICTORIAN.
I'D RATHER JUST FOCUS
ON MY EXAMS.
I CAN SEE WHY
YOU'D SAY THAT,
BUT YOU CAN'T LET TRAGEDY
CONTROL YOU.
HOW DO YOU KNOW
I LOST THE BABY?
OUR CAMERAS AREN'T
JUST PREVENTIVE,
WITH THEM, I CAN HELP
STUDENTS WHO NEED IT.
STUDENTS LIKE YOU.
YOU'RE LISTENING TO OUR
PRIVATE CONVERSATIONS?!
WHETHER YOU LIKE IT OR NOT,
RUNNING FOR VALEDICTORIAN
WILL BE POSITIVE.
AND RIGHT NOW, YOU DESERVE
SOMETHING GOOD HAPPEN TO YOU.
NO, WHAT I DESERVE
IS BASIC PRIVACY!
(SIGHS ANGRILY)
FRANKIE:
♪ I wanna know the truth ♪
♪ But I'm too afraid to ask ♪
♪ Take off your mask ♪
♪ Let me see your face ♪
KEEP CLIMBING, FRANKIE!
♪ Once I know the real you ♪
♪ We can get out
Of this place ♪
FRANKIE AND WINSTON:
♪ All my life... ♪
♪ I've been waiting
For someone like you... ♪
YOU'RE NOT GOING FAST ENOUGH,
I'M GONNA CATCH YOU TOO SOON!
I'VE GOT THIS, WINSTON!
WHOA- (LOUD THUD)
IMOGEN:
OKAY, CUT!
WE'LL GO FROM THE TOP.
OR, BOTTOM, I GUESS.
MAYBE WE SHOULD SIMPLIFY
THE CLIMBING,
SO YOU DON'T HAVE TO SING
AND BE PHYSICAL
AT THE SAME TIME.
I CAN DO TWO THINGS
AT ONCE, THANKS.
SO WHAT, THE SET WAS JUST
TOO SLIPPERY, THEN?
IMOGEN:
CALL OFF THE NUCLEAR STRIKE,
GUYS!
FRANKIE:
KINDA LIKE HOW YOU WERE SLIPPERY
WHEN YOU KISSED LOLA, RIGHT?
I MADE A MISTAKE,
I SAID I WAS SORRY
LIKE, A MILLION TIMES!
WHAT MORE DO YOU WANT FROM ME?!
I WANT YOU TO GO TO HELL!
IMOGEN:
OKAY... THAT'S A WRAP
ON REHEARSAL FOR TODAY, KIDDOS!
EVERYONE GO HOME, AND RELAX.
ESPECIALLY YOU, FRANKIE.
(SIGHS)
HE JUST GETS UNDER MY SKIN.
I GET IT,
BREAKUPS SUCK.
BUT THIS IS AFFECTING
REHEARSAL WAY TOO OFTEN,
YOU HAVE TO TRY
AND WORK WITH HIM.
I DON'T KNOW IF I CAN.
WELL, LET ME KNOW
IF YOU FIGURE IT OUT.
IF NOT...
I NEED A NEW ELLA.
(TRASH BAG RUSTLES)
VINCE:
WHOA, WHAT'S WITH
SALLY HOMEMAKER?
ZIG'S GIRL'S COMING OVER.
HE WANTS US GONE, TONIGHT.
AH, SOMEONE'S GETTING LAID!
(ZIG LAUGHS)
UH, YEAH, YEAH SURE,
TOTALLY.
YOU HAVE CONDOMS, RIGHT?
WHY ARE WE EVEN TALKING
ABOUT THIS?
ZIG, DO YOU STILL HAVE
YOUR V-CARD?
OH, THAT'S RIDICULOUS,
MY BOY'S A LADY SLAYER,
RIGHT, ZIG?
YOU'RE A VIRGIN?!
SO? WHATEVER.
I JUST WANNA GET
THROUGH TONIGHT
WITHOUT MAYA FREAKING OUT,
OKAY?
VINCE:
ALL RIGHT, VIRGIN,
DON'T GET ALL WEEPY ON US.
YOUR NIGHT'S GONNA BE GREAT.
PROMISE.
COME ON, TINY, LET'S GO.
TINY:
ALL RIGHT.
(DOOR CLICK OPEN)
HUNTER:
DIABETES ONE,
FRANKIE, ZERO.
FRANKIE:
SHUT UP, EATING MY FEELINGS
IS LIKE,
THE ONLY HOBBY I HAVE
LEFT NOW.
HUNTER: YOU QUIT CAPTAIN WHO?
FRANKIE: STRONGLY CONSIDERING IT
I CAN'T BE AROUND
WINSTON ANYMORE.
HUNTER:
WINSTON WROTE IT,
BUT WITHOUT YOU,
IT'D BE SITTING ON A SHELF.
FRANKIE:
SO?
SO THAT PLAY'S JUST AS
MUCH YOURS AS IT IS HIS,
AND YOU'RE JUST GONNA LET
IT GO WITHOUT A FIGHT?
IT'S NOT THAT SIMPLE.
HUNTER: ACTUALLY,
IT KIND OF IS.
(DOOR CLICKS SHUT)
YOU'VE GOT THE JUNK FOOD,
I'VE GOT THE ROM COMS,
GIRLS' NIGHT IS ON!
MOM, AREN'T YOU GOING
TO THAT CHARITY THING?
OH, I WAS, BUT YOUR FATHER'S
GONNA BE THERE.
YOU'RE RIGHT, HUNTER.
WORDS I DON'T HEAR
OFTEN ENOUGH.
(RETREATING FOOTSTEPS)
SO, WHY WERE YOU SO WORRIED
ABOUT ME COMING OVER?
I MEAN, IT'S NOT HOGWART'S,
BUT WHAT IS, RIGHT?
BUT IS IT GOOD
ENOUGH FOR YOU?
VINCE:
OHHHH! YOU MUST BE
THE FAMOUS MAYA!
UM, HI.
VINCE:
I'M VINCE.
ZIG'S... LANDLORD.
ZIG: COME ON, LET'S JUST JET.
WAIT, HOLD ON,
I ACTUALLY WOULDN'T MIND
GETTING TO KNOW SOME
OF YOUR FRIENDS.
VINCE:
SPEAKING OF FRIENDS,
YOU KNOW WHO YOU HAVEN'T MET?
MY FRIEND MOLLY.
WHAT IS THIS, THE FIRST HALF
OF AN AFTER SCHOOL SPECIAL?!
FIRST TIMER, HUH?
DON'T WORRY,
ZIG'S NEVER DONE IT, EITHER.
LOOK, SHE'S NOT THAT KIND
OF GIRL!
MAYA:
WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT'S IT LIKE?
COLOURS GET BRIGHTER,
SOUNDS GET SHARPER.
YOU FEEL MORE CONNECTED
TO EVERYTHING YOU LOVE.
THAT'S WHY THEY CALL IT
"THE LOVE DRUG."
WHAT IF WE BOTH DID IT?
WOULDN'T IT BE GREAT
IF OUR FIRST TIME WAS TOGETHER?
MAYA, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO PROVE ANYTHING.
I'M KNOW,
BUT I'M CURIOUS.
♪ Molly molly molly molly
blow away ♪
♪♪
WAIT, WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"EVERYTHING?"
PILL KNOWS EVERY SINGLE
THING WE'VE DONE
SINCE THE CAMERAS WENT UP.
WE SHOULD BOTH PULL OUT
OF THE VALEDICTORIAN RACE.
ELI:
IT'S WEIRD THAT SHE KNEW
ABOUT THE BABY,
BUT RUNNING FOR VALEDICTORIAN
WOULD BE GOOD FOR YOU, RIGHT?
I WANTED TO WAIT
UNTIL AFTER GRADUATION
TO TELL EVERYONE
I LOST THE BABY,
ON MY OWN TERMS,
SO NO ONE MADE SCHOOL WEIRD!
LOOK, I GET THAT YOU'RE
FEELING VIOLATED,
BUT HONESTLY, SCREW PILL!
DON'T MAKE THIS ABOUT HER.
SHE'S BEEN HERE FOR WHAT,
FIVE MINUTES?
YOU'VE BEEN HERE
FOR FOUR YEARS.
DON'T YOU WANNA SAY
GOODBYE TO DEGRASSI?
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THIS IS MY CHANCE
TO SAY GOODBYE.
(PARTYGOERS LAUGH AND CHATTER)
♪ Freakin' goin' her way
can't stand her blazin' ♪
♪ We style with flash advantage
Get 'em up ♪
♪ Now we be ready
get it in ♪
♪ I ain't scared, look at me,
that's right the wolf,
the big bad ♪
♪ You know I try to bring
danger, danger ♪
♪ Bring it on
I'll bring you mines too ♪
♪ You can take it to the ring
to the streets... ♪
MMM!
OKAY, WHAT IS YOUR OBSESSION
WITH MY FACE?
IT'S SO SOFT!
(GIGGLES)
HERE, FEEL THIS.
MAYA:
OH MY GOD!
I- THIS COUCH IS AWESOME!
THIS HOUSE IS AWESOME!
YOUR FRIENDS!
I'M HAVING THE BEST TIME!
(BOTH GIGGLE)
I MEAN, I'M SERIOUS,
I'M-I'M SERIOUS, THOUGH.
YOU ARE SO FREAKING COOL
RIGHT NOW.
JUST RIGHT NOW?
YOU KNOW, I WAS SO WORRIED
THAT YOU'D HATE THIS HOUSE,
OR THAT YOU'D LOOK
AT ME DIFFERENTLY,
AND THE GUYS
WERE BOTHERING ME,
YOU KNOW, ABOUT DOING
"THE SEX" WITH YOU,
I DON'T WANNA BE
THAT GUY WHO'S-
WAIT, HOLD ON.
ARE YOU SAYING YOU DON'T WANT
TO DO "THE SEX" WITH ME?
NO, NO,
I DO I WANT TO,
I JUST- I DIDN'T
WANNA PRESSURE YOU.
HEY, IT'S NO PRESSURE.
♪♪
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
JUST SO I'M CLEAR,
YOU'RE SAYING...
WHICH ROOM IS YOURS?
♪♪
♪ Settle down ♪
(SEWING MACHINE RUMBLES)
OKAY, THANK YOU.
OKAY, I'M NOT LEAVING
THE MUSICAL.
GREAT NEWS.
BUT FROM NOW ON, WINSTON AND I
HAVE TO REHEARSE SEPARATELY.
LESS GREAT NEWS,
WE DON'T REALLY HAVE TIME
FOR TWO SETS OF REHEARSALS!
FRANKIE:
BUT HE'S THE JERK, WHY SHOULD I
HAVE TO FEEL UNCOMFORTABLE?
SO YOU ARE LEAVING?
I JUST DON'T WANNA WIND UP
LIKE MY MOM.
IS THIS LIKE A METAPHORICAL
MOM, OR?
MY PARENTS SPLIT UP,
AND NOW MY MOM DOESN'T DO
ANY OF THE STUFF SHE USED TO.
OH, LITERAL MOM.
SHE SKIPS CHARITY FUNDRAISERS,
AVOIDS THE COUNTRY CLUB,
SHE'S DOESN'T EVEN SHOP
IN YORKVILLE,
BECAUSE SHE'S WORRIED
IT'S ALL DAD'S TERRITORY.
BUT THAT'S CRAP, WE SHOULDN'T
HAVE TO GIVE UP STUFF WE LOVE,
JUST BECAUSE OF A BREAK UP!
OF COURSE NOT,
BUT THE PROBLEM
ISN'T YOUR BREAK UP,
IT'S THAT YOU'RE LETTING
YOUR ATTITUDE GET IN THE WAY
OF REHEARSAL.
BECAUSE WINSTON KEEPS
GETTING IN MY HEAD!
I SWEAR, IF I COULD REHEARSE
WITHOUT HIM, I COULD BE GREAT!
OKAY, I ALSO JUST WENT
THROUGH A BREAK UP.
AFTER JACK AND I AGREED
TO DO
OUR BIG FINAL ART
PROJECT TOGETHER.
IT WAS BRUTAL HAVING
TO BE SO CLOSE TO HER
I CAN SMELL HER,
ALL THE MEMORIES.
BUT, WE GOT AN "A."
AND I'M STRONGER NOW.
IF YOU REALLY DON'T
WANNA GIVE UP THE MUSICAL,
GIVE UP SOME ANGER INSTEAD.
IT'LL MAKE YOU FEEL BETTER.
MAYA:
SO THAT'S COSINE.
GRACE:
YEP, SINE, AND THEN
THE OTHER ONE'S TANGENT.
I NEED TO WRITE "TAN?"
YEAH, JUST "TAN" FOR SHORT,
ON THE CALCULATOR, AND...
HEY, UH, YOU LEFT THIS
AT MY PLACE.
THANKS.
WHAT THE BALLS HAPPENED
LAST NIGHT?!
MAYA:
WHAT? NOTHING!
GOING NOW.
ROUGH NIGHT?
(BELL RINGS)
WE... WE DID THE DEED.
YOU GUYS HAD SEX?!
SHHH!
YES, AND WE WERE HIGH
WHEN WE DID IT.
JUST HOW EVERY GIRL IMAGINES
HER FIRST TIME, NOVAK.
EACH CANDIDATE WILL BE GIVEN
TWO MINUTES TO MAKE A CASE
FOR WHY THEY SHOULD BE
YOUR VALEDICTORIAN.
AFTER ALL THREE CANDIDATES HAVE
HAD THEIR CHANCE TO SPEAK,
YOU WILL BE ALLOWED TO VOTE.
I'M HAPPY YOU'RE HERE.
YOU'RE STILL GONNA LOSE,
BUT I'M GLAD YOU'RE RUNNING.
LIKE YOU SAID,
SCREW PILL, RIGHT?
MS. PILL:
AND THAT'S ABOUT IT.
FIRST UP, CLARE EDWARDS.
I'M GLAD YOU REALIZED HOW
POSITIVE THIS WILL BE FOR YOU.
(CLARE SIGHS)
(SIGHS TEARFULLY)
CLARE:
AS MY TIME AT DEGRASSI
COMES TO AN END,
I HAVE A SIMPLE QUESTION
FOR YOU:
DO YOU DESERVE PRIVACY?
MS. PILL DOESN'T THINK SO.
SHE'S USING THE SCHOOL'S
CAMERAS TO SPY ON YOU.
SURE, SHE'LL SAY THAT SHE'S
WATCHING SO THAT SHE CAN HELP,
BUT SHE CAN'T DO ANYTHING
TO HELP!
WE NEED TO BE ABLE TO GO
THROUGH THINGS IN PRIVATE,
WITHOUT CAMERAS,
AND PRINCIPALS WATCHING US.
WE NEED TO STAND UP
AND TELL MS. PILL TO GO-
STUDENTS:
(SHOCKED MURMURS)
♪♪
I'M GLAD I DON'T HAVE
TO FOLLOW THAT.
♪♪
SO THIS "NO PHONE" RULE
IS THE WORST, HUH?
I MEAN, HOW DID PEOPLE
EVER FIND EACH OTHER
BEFORE CELL PHONES?
ZIG: SO LISTEN,
I DIDN'T MEAN FOR-
MAYA: I'M SORRY I-
(CHUCKLES)
YOU GO.
WHAT HAPPENED YESTERDAY...
I DIDN'T MEAN FOR THINGS
TO GO THAT FAR.
YEAH, ME NEITHER.
I SORTA WISH MY FIRST TIME
WASN'T HIGH, YOU KNOW?
YEAH.
MAYBE I SHOULDN'TVE
COME OVER YESTERDAY.
IT'S MY FAULT.
NO, NO, NO,
THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT.
NO, BUT IT'S TRUE!
I MEAN... I MEAN,
IF YOU WEREN'T WITH ME,
THEN NONE OF THIS
WOULD'VE HAPPENED.
I THINK IT'S BEST
IF YOU JUST...
STAY AWAY FROM ME
FROM NOW ON.
WAIT... THIS IS A JOKE,
RIGHT?
LIKE, HA HA?
I'M TRYING TO PROTECT YOU.
MAYA: FROM WHAT?!
FROM ME!
OKAY? I'M A BAD GUY!
I-I LET YOU TAKE
THOSE DRUGS!
WAIT, YOU LET ME?!
WHAT, I CAN'T MAKE
DECISIONS FOR MYSELF?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
YOU'RE BETTER OFF WITHOUT ME.
OKAY?
YEAH. WELL,
THAT'S PRETTY CLEAR!
(FENCE RATTLES)
FRANKIE:
♪ We don't have much time ♪
♪ Because danger is near ♪
♪ Is there a hero who hides
Behind that mask? ♪
IMOGEN:
ATTA GIRL!
FRANKIE:
YES! TAKE THAT, DUMB WALL!
OKAY WINSTON,
CHASE AFTER HER.
(WINSTON SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
(WINSTON GRUNTS)
OOF!
SERIOUSLY, WINSTON?!
WINSTON:
OKAY, I GET IT.
IT'S NOT AT EASY AS IT LOOKS.
NOPE, THAT CORNER'S A BEAST.
WINSTON: WELL, I'M SORRY THAT-
WAIT, ARE WE NOT FIGHTING
RIGHT NOW?
WANNA STICK AROUND
AFTER REHEARSAL,
AND PRACTICE THAT TRANSITION?
IMOGEN:
THIS IS THE PART
WHERE YOU SAY "YES."
UH, YES.
OF COURSE.
THANK YOU.
(SMALL SIGH)
ALLI:
SO MUCH FOR NOT ROCKING
THE BOAT!
UH, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
PREPARING FOR SUSPENSION.
MS. PILL:
WHO SUSPENDED YOU?
CLARE:
YOU, IN ABOUT TEN SECONDS?
ALLI, COULD WE HAVE
SOME PRIVACY?
YOU MAY HAVE A FUTURE
IN POLITICS,
BUT SUSPENSION, NO.
I DON'T WANT SPECIAL TREATMENT!
DESPITE WHAT YOU MAY BELIEVE,
THESE CAMERAS CREATE
A HEALTHY SCHOOL ENVIRONMENT.
REPORTABLE INCIDENTS
ARE DOWN BY 22 PERCENT,
CLARE, YOU'RE A BRIGHT YOUNG
WOMAN WITH A PROMISING FUTURE,
BUT I'M WORRIED
YOU'LL THROW IT ALL AWAY.
THAT IS NONE
OF YOUR BUSINESS!
IT'S NOT JUST ME.
YOUR FRIENDS ARE WORRIED TOO.
TALK TO THEM,
THEY WANNA HELP.
(ALLI SIGHS)
ALLI:
CLARE- STOP, THINK ABOUT
WHAT YOU'RE DOING!
(CLARE GRUNTS,
CAMERA CRASHES)
ALLI: FEEL BETTER?!
CLARE: STARTING TO!
(CRASHES)
VINCE:
THERE HE IS!
RUMOUR IS YOU'RE A MAN NOW,
ZIG! BRING IT IN.
ZIG:
YOU'RE LUCKY I DON'T
KICK YOUR ASS!
TINY:
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
RELAX! WHAT'S YOUR DEAL?
MY "DEAL" IS THAT THIS JERKWAD
PROMISED TO STAY AWAY
LAST NIGHT!
ACTUALLY, I PROMISED THAT
YOU'D HAVE A GREAT NIGHT,
AND YOU DID!
ZIG:
YOU THINK THAT'S HOW
I WANTED IT?!
SOMETHING HAPPEN BETWEEN
YOU AND MAYA?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?!
SORRY MAN,
SHE'S JUST A GIRL.
PLENTY OF FISH IN THE SEA,
RIGHT?
I DON'T WANT OTHER FISH!
WHEN I'M WITH MAYA,
OTHER GIRLS ARE JUST THAT-
OTHER GIRLS,
NONE OF THEM ARE HER!
HOW DON'T YOU GET THAT?!
YOU KNOW WHAT YOUR PROBLEM IS?
YOU ALWAYS TALK YOURSELF OUT
OF A GOOD THING,
LIKE YOU DON'T DESERVE IT.
MAYBE I DON'T.
VINCE: BULL!
SURE, THINGS DIDN'T GO
DOWN HOW YOU WANTED,
BUT IF MAYA MATTERS TO YOU,
YOU GOTTA FIGHT FOR HER.
GIVE HER A CALL,
WE'LL GO OVER THERE.
WE'VE JUST GOTTA MAKE
ONE STOP FIRST.
WHAT IF SHE DOESN'T ACCEPT
MY APOLOGY?
HEY MAN, IF SHE'S YOUR
RIDE-OR-DIE,
THAT'S A RISK
YOU GOTTA TAKE.
(ZIG SIGHS HEAVILY)
FRANKIE:
MOM? ARE YOU HOME?
GUESS WHAT HAPPENED
AT REHEARSAL!
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH:
OH! HI, PEANUT.
WAS THAT DAD?
NO, IT WAS THE NEWS.
REALLY, I'M FINE.
(MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH SNIFFS)
HEY, I WAS EATING THAT!
FRANKIE: NOT ANYMORE!
BUT-
FRANKIE: NO BUTS!
I REFUSED TO GIVE UP
THE MUSICAL
BECAUSE OF MY BREAK UP,
NOW IT'S YOUR TURN.
WE'RE TAKING BACK YORKVILLE!
NOW MOM, THE STORES WON'T STAY
OPEN ALL NIGHT!
OKAY...
LET ME GO GET CHANGED.
(MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH SIGHS)
(FOOD CLATTERS)
(CAR RUMBLES)
(GEAR SHIFTS,
SEAT BELT UNCLICKS)
WE'LL BE TWO MINUTES,
THEN, MAYA'S HOUSE.
(DOORS SLAM)
(SHUTS OFF ENGINE)
(CELL PHONE BUTTONS BEEP)
(PHONE RINGS)
ARE YOU OUTSIDE?
I THOUGHT YOU'D NEVER GET HERE.
UH NO, NO ACTUALLY,
I'M STILL WITH THE GUYS.
I CAN'T JUST LEAVE THEM HERE.
WE CAN JUST TALK AT SCHOOL,
I GUESS.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
WHAT WE DID WASN'T STUPID,
THE WAY WE DID IT WAS.
MAYA:
ZIG, I REALLY DON'T WANT-
NO MAYA, PLEASE,
I'VE GOTTA SAY THIS, ALL RIGHT?
WE WEREN'T OURSELVES
LAST NIGHT.
AND IF WE HAD BEEN, WE WOULD'VE
KNOWN THAT WE WEREN'T READY...
FOR WHAT WE DID...
FOR SEX.
MAYA:
(SIGHS) I FEEL THE SAME WAY.
AND I THINK THAT'S WHY TODAY
WAS SO AWKWARD,
BUT IT HAPPENED.
AND I DON'T WANT TO PRETEND
THAT IT DIDN'T, BECAUSE...
I'M GLAD THAT
IT WAS WITH YOU.
(SMALL LAUGH)
HELLO?
DID YOU HANG UP?
MAYA:
NO, I'M STILL HERE.
OH, THANK GOD!
MAYA:
ZIG...
I'M GLAD IT WAS WITH YOU, TOO.
ZIG:
YOU ARE?
OF COURSE, DUMMY!
SO DOES THAT MEAN
THAT WE'RE UH...
WE'RE STILL TOGETHER?
I GUESS SO.
OKAY!
UH...I WILL SEE YOU AT SCHOOL
TOMORROW, THEN.
MAYA:
DEFINITELY.
(PHONE BEEPS OFF)
(GUNSHOTS ECHO)
(CAR ALARM BLARES,
DOG BARKS IN THE DISTANCE)
(FOOTSTEPS RUNNING)
START THE CAR,
START THE CAR!
WHAT HAPPENED?
GO, GO!
COME ON!
(ENGINE STARTS)
(TIRES SCREECH)