FRANKIE:
MILES.
MILES!
(MILES GROANS)
FRANKIE: WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
HUNTER:
DAD SAYS YOU HAVE TO DRIVE US
TO SCHOOL.
MILES:
AH, GET OUT.
HUNTER:
NO NEED TO BE RUDE.
MILES:
GET OUT, PLEASE.
ARE YOU WALLOWING BECAUSE TRIS
IS STILL MAD AT YOU
FOR BLOWING OFF
YOUR HISTORY PROJECT?
OR ARE YOU HUNG OVER AGAIN?
MILES:
NEITHER. I'M SLEEPING.
AND DON'T WORRY
ABOUT TRISTAN AND ME.
I'LL SMOOTH IT OVER.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
A FINE EXAMPLE YOU'RE
SETTING FOR YOUR BROTHER
AND YOUR SISTER.
MILES:
DOES NO ONE KNOCK ANYMORE?
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
JUST TAKE A GOOD LOOK.
THIS IS EVERYTHING
YOU WANT TO AVOID BEING.
GET OUT OF BED,
CLEAN YOURSELF UP,
YOU DRIVE YOUR BROTHER
AND SISTER TO SCHOOL.
NO MORE SKIPPING,
OR ELSE!
(RELUCTANT EXHALE)
HUNTER:
HE'S PROBABLY JUST STRESSED OUT
ABOUT THE CAMPAIGN.
MILES:
IT'S OKAY, HUNTER.
I'VE COME TO ACCEPT THAT
I'M A PERPETUAL DISAPPOINTMENT.
MILES: WHERE THE HELL...?
FRANKIE: LOOKING FOR THIS?
MILES:
COME ON, FRANKENSTEIN,
GIVE IT BACK.
WHAT? CAN'T GO ONE DAY
WITHOUT GETTING HIGH?
MILES:
NOW.
FINE. BUT CAN YOU AT LEAST
WAIT TO SMOKE UP
UNTIL AFTER YOU'VE DRIVEN US
TO SCHOOL?
♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Ohh-Ohh-Ohh... ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
JACK:
WHO IS SENDING THESE
BLACKMAIL TEXTS?!
SHAY:
AND WHY DO THEY WANT YOU
OFF THE TEAM?
ZOE:
I DON'T KNOW!
WELL, I THOUGHT SHUTTING DOWN
DEGRASSI NUDES WOULD STOP IT,
BUT I GUESS THAT WASN'T ENOUGH.
BACK THE TRUCK UP.
WHOEVER THIS IS ALREADY
CONTACTED YOU?
YES. THEY WANTED ME TO QUIT,
BUT I COULDN'T, OKAY?
SHAY:
SO, YOU KEPT THIS FROM US?
I THOUGHT THE PROBLEM
WAS SOLVED!
JACK:
WELL, MAYBE WE SHOULD
LISTEN TO THEM.
SAYONARA, ZOE.
NICE KNOWING YA!
ZOE:
GUYS, SEMI-FINALS ARE TODAY.
IF WE STICK TOGETHER,
WE CAN GET THROUGH THIS.
JACK:
OR WE'RE GONNA HAVE BIGGER
PROBLEMS THAN SEMIS
IF WE GET EXPOSED.
SHAY:
WE COULD GET SUSPENDED.
OR EXPELLED.
JACK:
OR ARRESTED FOR DISTRIBUTION
OF CHILD PORNOGRAPHY.
WHAT?!
I WOULD NEVER DO THAT!
EXCEPT YOU DID.
WHEN YOU SENT PICTURES
OF YOUR BOOBS FOR MONEY.
WAIT, I'M THE CHILD
IN THIS SCENARIO?
ZOE:
STOP! WE'RE NOT GONNA
GET CAUGHT,
BECAUSE WE'RE GONNA TRACK
THIS PSYCHO DOWN AND STOP THEM.
I KNOW SOMEONE WHO MIGHT BE
ABLE TO TRACE DOWN THE NUMBER.
GREAT, LET'S GO.
LOLA:
OOH, GROUP TRIP!
ZOE:
WHOA. NO.
LISTEN, MISS SECRETS.
WE'RE ALL GETTING IN TROUBLE
IF THIS GETS OUT.
SO, WE'RE ALL COMING.
YOU SAID WE'LL ONLY WAY
WE'RE GETTING THROUGH THIS
IS IF WE STICK TOGETHER.
SO, WE'RE STICKING TOGETHER.
OKAY?
FINE.
LET'S GO.
JONAH AND BECKY:
♪ Even though it seems ♪
♪ Like the lights
Have gone out ♪
♪ Like the world
Has gone dark ♪
♪ Like there's nothing left
To sing about ♪
NO, THE PHRASING'S ALL
JACKED UP IN THAT LAST PART.
BECKY:
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU JUST
SWITCH THE FIRST TWO LINES?
WELL, I'M NOT GONNA
SING IT ON MY OWN.
HOW ELSE AM I SUPPOSED TO KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT?
LOOK, YOU'RE THE ONE WHO WANTED
TO BE IN A BAND SO BADLY.
(BECKY BREATHES IN DEEP
AND EXHALES)
♪ And even though it seems ♪
♪ Like the world
has gone dark ♪
♪ Like the lights
have gone out ♪
♪ Like we've lost
the old spark... ♪
JONAH:
(AMAZED EXHALE)
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE THAT'S DUMB.
IT'S NOT DUMB AT ALL.
WHAT ELSE HAVE YOU GOT?
AH, THEN I THOUGHT MAYBE
IT COULD GO LIKE...
♪ And if we find
The right matches ♪
♪ If we strike them
just so... ♪
JONAH:
NO, THAT'S DUMB.
YOU'RE MESSING WITH ME.
WELL, IT'S JUST SO EASY.
NO, YOU'RE ONTO SOMETHING.
TRY IT AGAIN.
♪ And if we find
The right matches ♪
♪ If we strike them just so ♪
♪ We can bring back the light ♪
BECKY AND JONAH:
DID WE JUST WRITE A SONG?
JONAH:
PART OF ONE.
WRITE ANOTHER VERSE AND THEN
WE'LL REHEARSE AT LUNCH
JONAH: AND THEN, AH...
BECKY: 'KAY.
MAYBE WE CAN EVEN PLAY ACOUSTIC
NIGHT AT THE DOT, TONIGHT.
(DISBELIEVING BREATH)
PRIVATE HOLLINGSWORTH,
REPORTING FOR DUTY.
I ASSUME I'M SUPPOSED
TO BE SO BLOWN AWAY BY
YOUR HANDSOMENESS
THAT I INSTANTLY
FORGIVE YOU?
YEAH, SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
TRISTAN, I'M SORRY
I BLEW OFF OUR PRESENTATION.
IT WASN'T FAIR.
YOU'RE RIGHT. IT WASN'T.
LOOK, I TALKED TO PERINO,
HE SAID HE'D GIVE US
ANOTHER CHANCE.
BUT THAT WOULD INVOLVE ME
GIVING YOU ANOTHER CHANCE,
WOULDN'T IT?
WHAT CAN I DO, TRISTAN?
I WANNA MAKE THIS RIGHT.
WEAR THAT CUTE UNIFORM
FOR THE REST OF THE DAY?
BUT, IF I'M GONNA LIVE DOWN
MY PRIOR HUMILIATION,
WE NEED TO BE STUNNING.
WHICH MEANS ONE MORE REHEARSAL
AT LUNCH?
MILES:
SIR, YES SIR!
JACK:
WHERE ARE YOU TAKING US?
LOLA:
I HEARD SOMEONE GOT SHIVVED
IN THIS HALLWAY.
ZOE:
WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
YEAH, YOU BROUGHT THE WHOLE
DAMN POM-POM SQUAD
INTO MY BUSINESS.
I DIDN'T HAVE A CHOICE.
WE'RE STILL GETTING
BLACKMAIL MESSAGES.
SO? WEBSITE'S DOWN.
I'M OUT.
ZOE:
YOU THINK YOU WON'T GET CAUGHT
IF THIS GETS OUT?
I DIDN'T FLASH MY TA-TAS.
BUT YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE WHO
CAN HELP US KILL THIS THING.
CAN'T YOU TRACE WHERE
A MESSAGE IS SENT FROM?
GIMME YOUR PHONE.
BE GENTLE WITH JULIO.
HE'S TESTY WITH NEW PEOPLE.
(BEEPING)
GRACE:
I'M JUST RUNNING CELLULAR
TRIANGULATION ON THE MESSAGE.
LOLA: WHAT?
GRACE: SEEING WHERE
IT WAS SENT FROM.
JACK:
YOU CAN DO THAT?
TELL ANYONE, AND I SHIV YOU.
SEE?!
GRACE:
MESSAGE WAS SENT
FROM THIS CELL TOWER.
LOLA:
LOOK AT THAT POOL.
THE HOLLINGSWORTHS.
FRANKIE.
WHAT? NO WAY.
SHE'S MY FRIEND!
BUT SHE HATES ME
FOR KICKING HER OFF THE TEAM.
EVEN SO, SHE'S A TOTAL
GOODY-TWO-SHOES.
SHE COULD NEVER DO THIS.
WHO ELSE, THEN?
MILES?
THIS DOESN'T SEEM
LIKE HIS STYLE.
JACK:
NO WAIT, ISN'T THERE ANOTHER
HOLLINGSWORTH KID?
WEIRD LITTLE LONER?
HUNTER!
JACK:
THAT'S THE ONE.
LET'S PAY THAT LITTLE CREEP
A VISIT.
GRACE:
PIECE OF ADVICE?
GET SOME EVIDENCE
BEFORE YOU ACCUSE SOMEONE
OF SOMETHING THIS CRAZY.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
(HEAVY SIGH)
HEY.
BECKY:
HI.
CAN YOU GIVE ME SOME WORDS
THAT RHYME WITH "WORKED"?
DREW:
(CLEARS THROAT)
IRKED.
AH, LURKED!
AH...
TWERKED!
(BECKY AND DREW LAUGH)
VERY FUNNY. BUT I HAVE
TO FINISH THESE LYRICS
SO JONAH AND I CAN PERFORM
TONIGHT.
WAIT, HOLD ON.
YOU'RE...
YOU'RE WRITING SONGS
WITH THIS GUY NOW?
I THOUGHT YOU GUYS WERE JUST
GONNA LIKE, SING OCCASIONALLY.
WE'RE WRITING ORIGINAL MUSIC!
JONAH SIGNED US UP FOR OPEN MIC
AT THE DOT TONIGHT.
DON'T LOOK SO SURPRISED.
IT'S FUN!
AND YOU'RE THE ONE WHO ALWAYS
SAYS I NEED TO HAVE MORE FUN.
BESIDES, JONAH SAYS I HAVE
SOME REALLY GOOD SONG IDEAS.
MM-HM.
I BET HE DOES.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
JUST SOUNDS LIKE JONAH WANTS
TO WORK ON MORE THAN A SONG.
WHY DO YOU ASSUME HE HAS
SOME ULTERIOR MOTIVE?
IS IT SO HARD TO BELIEVE THAT
I'M ACTUALLY GOOD AT THIS?
NO, NO, IT'S JUST
A CLASSIC MOVE, IS ALL.
"HEY BABY, YOU WANNA MAKE
SOME BEAUTIFUL MUSIC TOGETHER?"
WE'RE FRIENDS.
AND MUSICAL COLLABORATORS.
BECKY: THAT'S IT.
DREW: MM-HM.
AND I DON'T BUY IT.
GUYS CAN'T BE JUST FRIENDS
WITH GIRLS, BECKY.
DOESN'T WORK.
(SIGHS)
MILES:
YOU BROUGHT AN AUDIENCE.
GOOD CALL.
TRISTAN:
NO. ACTUALLY, UM,
WE WANTED TO TALK TO YOU.
MILES: ABOUT?
IT'S AN INTERVENTION, DUDE.
WE THINK YOU'RE ADDICTED
TO MARIJUANA.
OR AS YOU CALL IT,
"BREAKFAST."
OKAY, SO THAT'S WHY YOU WERE
BEING SO WEIRD THIS MORNING?
AND YOU?
YOU KNEW ABOUT THIS?
I WAS CONCERNED ABOUT YOU.
I MEAN, WE ALL ARE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'D
DO THIS TO ME.
FRANKIE:
YOU'RE DISPLAYING
CLASSIC SIGNS OF ADDICTION.
POOR PERFORMANCE
AT WORK OR SCHOOL.
WINSTON: CHECK.
FRANKIE: SUDDEN MOOD SWINGS,
IRRITABILITY,
OR ANGRY OUTBURSTS.
HUNTER:
DOUBLE CHECK.
FRANKIE:
DENIAL AND SECRECY TO THE POINT
THAT IT INTERFERES
WITH INTERPERSONAL
RELATIONSHIPS.
TRIPLE CHECK.
MILES:
OKAY, POT IS NOT MY PROBLEM!
YOU PEOPLE ARE.
FRANKIE:
HEY! DON'T BE SUCH A JERK!
OH, I'M SORRY.
DID I UPSET LITTLE FRANKIE?
LOOK, I KNOW YOU WANNA
PLAY WITH THE BIG KIDS,
BUT YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT
THE HELL YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT!
YOU DON'T MEAN THIS.
YOU'RE JUST UPSET.
AND YOU! YOU WENT BEHIND
MY BACK WHEN I THOUGHT
YOU WERE THE ONE PERSON
WHO UNDERSTOOD!
TRISTAN:
WELL, I DO UNDERSTAND!
MILES:
NO! YOU'RE PATHETIC,
YOU KNOW THAT?
TRISTAN, I TREAT YOU
LIKE ABSOLUTE GARBAGE,
AND YOU KEEP CRAWLING BACK
FOR MORE. WHY?
ARE YOU REALLY THAT DESPERATE
FOR SOMEBODY TO LOVE YOU?
SCREW THIS.
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
♪ Bright smiling girls
Always know ♪
♪ How to lose it ♪
♪ And never let it show ♪
(LAUGHS)
UM, I SHOULD GO!
AT LEAST LET ME SAY
SOME NICE THINGS TO YOU FIRST.
OH, YOU REALLY DON'T
HAVE TO DO THAT.
COME ON.
THIS SONG IS GREAT.
YOU'RE A NATURAL.
BECKY: YOU'RE SERIOUS?
JONAH: DEAD.
UM... I REALLY SHOULD GO.
JONAH:
OR, YOU COULD STAY AND RUN
THAT VERSE WITH ME AGAIN.
JUST SO I CAN GET
THE PHRASING RIGHT.
AH! JUST LOOK AT THE TIME!
I'VE SO MUCH TO DO!
IT WOULD REALLY
HELP ME OUT.
I HAVE A BOYFRIEND!
GOOD TO KNOW.
I HAVE A HOUSE PLANT.
I JUST... I FEEL LIKE
YOU'RE TRYING TO, YOU KNOW...
I JUST WANNA WRITE A SONG.
SO, YOU'RE NOT TRYING TO...
GET FRESH WITH ME?
NO.
EVEN IF I WAS,
IT'S A NON-STARTER.
LOOK, I DIDN'T ALWAYS
MAKE THE BEST CHOICES.
BUT I'VE RECOMMITTED TO GOD.
AND HE'S HELPING ME
STAY AWAY FROM THINGS
THAT USED TO TEMPT ME,
LIKE "GETTING FRESH."
WANNA RUN THAT VERSE
AGAIN?
(MURMUR OF STUDENT CHATTER)
(MILES' KEYS JINGLE,
CAR DOOR UNLOCKS)
(ENGINE ROARS)
(GIRL SHRIEKS)
BOY: OH!
GIRL: OH MY GOODNESS!
YOU OKAY?!
FANTASTIC.
MAYA:
THANKS FOR THE LIFT.
WELL, I GUESS MY DOCTOR
WILL BE WAITING.
HOPE IT'S NOT CONTAGIOUS.
I DON'T THINK CRAZY
IS CATCHING.
WHAT?
WHAT'RE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I SHOULDN'T
CALL MYSELF THAT.
DR. KEMP KEEPS TELLING ME
NOT TO CALL MYSELF CRAZY.
SOMETHING ABOUT STIGMA.
WHY DO YOU NEED THERAPY?
YOU'RE TOTALLY NORMAL.
OH WOW.
THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
I'M SEEING DR. KEMP
BECAUSE OF YOU.
AFTER WE BROKE UP, I...
I GOT REALLY WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
LIKE, REALLY WORRIED.
AND I COULDN'T THINK
ABOUT ANYTHING ELSE.
IT TOOK OVER EVERYTHING.
LOOK, I KNOW I'M NOT
THE EASIEST PERSON TO GET-
NO, IT'S OKAY. IT WASN'T
REALLY EVEN ABOUT YOU.
IT WASN'T EVEN ABOUT ME.
IT'S JUST THE ANXIETY.
BUT I'LL BE FINE.
I AM FINE.
AND LATE!
SEE YOU BACK AT SCHOOL.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
(LIGHTER FLICKS TWICE)
(SIRENS WAIL IN THE DISTANCE)
(KEYBOARD KEYS CLACK)
(LIGHTS CLICK OFF)
HUNTER: I DIDN'T-
ZOE:
SHUT UP, HUNTER.
WHY HAVE YOU BEEN SENDING US
MESSAGES?
HUNTER:
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT?
ZOE:
HOW DID YOU KNOW IT WAS US?
LOLA:
LOOK, HUNTER.
I LIKE YOU.
WE JUST NEED YOU TO TELL US
THE TRUTH. AND DON'T LIE!
OKAY, LOOK, I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU WEIRDOS THINK I DID-
ZOE:
WE'RE THE WEIRDOS?!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
ZOE: LOOKING FOR PROOF.
LOLA:
CAPTAIN COURAGE
VERSUS THE EVIL CHEER MONSTERS?
JACK:
WHAT'S THAT?
ZOE:
A COMIC WHERE HUNTER KILLS
THE ZOMBIE VERSIONS OF US.
HEY, THAT'S PRIVATE PROPERTY!
ZOE:
BE A SHAME IF SIMPSON SAW THEM.
JACK:
YEAH...
MIGHT MAKE HIS EXPULSION FINGER
TWITCHY.
YOU WOULDN'T.
AND WE WON'T.
AS LONG AS YOU PROMISE
TO STOP WITH THE MESSAGES.
ZOE:
TO: PRINCIPAL SIMPSON.
CC: DADDY HOLLINGSWORTH...
JACK:
AND THE COPS.
HUNTER:
OKAY, STOP! I WON'T SEND ANY OF
YOU ANY MORE... MESSAGES, OKAY?
(PHONE CAMERA CLICKS)
JUST IN CASE
YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND.
YOU CAN GO NOW.
OH, AND THANKS
FOR DRAWING ME CUTE!
ZOE:
AND JUST IN TIME TO CATCH
THE TEAM BUS FOR SEMIS.
LET'S DO THIS!
(HEAVY METAL ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
♪♪
MILES.
MILES!
UH...
YOU WAITED.
YEAH, I'D RATHER BE HERE
THAN AT SCHOOL.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS
THROUGH HEADPHONES)
YOU OKAY?
UH-HUH.
TOTALLY FINE.
(ENGINE REVS TO LIFE)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
♪ Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! ♪
♪ You hear the whistle blow ♪
♪ Hear the whistle blow! ♪
♪ Hear the whistle blow!
Hey! ♪
(LIVELY RAP-DANCE SONG PLAYS,
AUDIENCE CHEERS AND APPLAUDS)
♪♪
♪ You hear the whistle blow ♪
♪ Hear the whistle blow! ♪
♪ Hear the whistle blow!
Hey! ♪
(WILD CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
(EXCITED SQUEALS
FROM CHEER SQUAD)
DREW:
SO, HOW DID REHEARSAL
WITH ROMEO GO?
NOT GREAT, DREW.
WHY?
DID HE TRY SOMETHING?
NO! I MADE A COMPLETE FOOL
OF MYSELF
BECAUSE I KEPT THINKING
ABOUT WHAT YOU SAID.
NOW, IT'S GONNA BE SO AWKWARD
WHEN WE PLAY TOGETHER.
WAIT, ARE YOU STILL PLAYING
WITH HIM?
BAND IS LIKE THE ONLY THING
I HAVE GOING ON RIGHT NOW.
NO IT'S NOT.
YOU'VE GOT ME.
COME ON, LET ME TAKE YOU
OUT FOR ICE CREAM TONIGHT!
MY TREAT.
ACTUALLY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
CAN YOU SPOT ME A TWENTY?
YOU JUST DON'T WANT ME HANGING
OUT WITH HIM AT ALL, DO YOU?
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW,
ALL RIGHT. HE'S WEIRD.
WITH THAT FLOPPY HAIR.
AND... DOES HE WEAR EYE MAKE-UP?
I JUST DON'T TRUST HIM.
YOU'RE JEALOUS.
NO. NO, NO.
I AM DREW TORRES.
ALL RIGHT,
I DON'T GET JEALOUS.
EXACTLY. DREW TORRES.
MY BOYFRIEND.
IT SHOULDN'T MATTER
WHETHER OR NOT HE LIKES ME,
BECAUSE YOU'RE THE ONLY GUY
I LIKE.
BUT IF YOU DON'T TRUST ME
TO KEEP MY HANDS OFF JONAH
WHILE WE'RE ON STAGE TOGETHER,
I SUGGEST YOU STAY AWAY
FROM THE DOT TONIGHT.
ZOE:
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS,
I'M PROUD OF YOU, GIRLS.
BUT SERIOUSLY, IF WE GET
ANYTHING WORSE THAN FOURTH,
I'M SLASHING THE JUDGE'S TIRES.
(CHEER SQUAD TITTERS)
JACK:
9.2...
9.3...
9.6!
WE WON!
(WILD CHEERS AND APPLAUSE,
CHEER TEAM SQUEALS EXCITEDLY)
LOLA:
ZOE, WHAT'S WRONG?
WE WON!
I KNOW. THIS DAY COULD HAVE
GONE SO DIFFERENT.
BUT, IT DIDN'T.
BECAUSE WE STUCK TOGETHER.
THANKS.
YOU KNOW, AS A TEAM,
I THINK WE MIGHT BE ABLE
TO DO ANYTHING.
EVEN WIN FINALS?
BRING IT ON!
(LOLA, SHAY AND JACK LAUGH)
YOU'RE DRIVING REALLY SLOWLY.
YOU OKAY?
MILES:
WHAT? AH... ME?
YEAH, I'M TOTALLY FINE!
MAYA:
YOU'RE BEING WEIRD.
ARE YOU FREAKED OUT 'CAUSE
I'M SEEING A THERAPIST?
THINK I'M CRAZY NOW?
MILES:
NO, NO, YOU'RE NOT CRAZY!
I MEAN...
I MEAN,
WE'RE ALL A LITTLE CRAZY,
BUT YOU'RE NOT "CRAZY" CRAZY.
(SNORTED CHUCKLE)
MAYA:
YOU'RE HIGH!
NO I'M NOT.
OKAY, PULL OVER. YOU SHOULDN'T
BE DRIVING RIGHT NOW!
(ENGINE HUMS LOUDLY
AS MILES INCREASES SPEED)
SERIOUSLY!
PULL OVER, MILES.
MAYA: THIS ISN'T SAFE!
MILES: I'M FINE!
(GLASS SHATTERS, MAYA GASPS,
TIRES SQUEAL)
(ENGINE ROARS, TIRES SQUEAL)
MILES: YOU OKAY?
MAYA: (STUNNED BREATHS)
MAYA: I... UH...
MILES: ARE YOU OKAY?!
YES! I'M FINE!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WE HAVE TO GO BACK, MILES!
MILES: WE CAN'T!
WHAT IF WE HURT SOMEONE?!
OR WORSE?!
WE CAN'T JUST... JUST LEAVE!
WE CAN'T GO BACK!
IF WE GO BACK
AND I GET CAUGHT...
I HAVE POT IN MY BLOODSTREAM,
MAYA.
THAT MEANS A DUI.
RIGHT BEFORE THE ELECTION?
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT HE'D DO TO ME.
OKAY.
JUST DRIVE.
BECKY:
♪ Turns out the honest
truth is ♪
JONAH:
♪ A softer kind of science ♪
BECKY AND JONAH:
♪ If we find the right matches ♪
♪ If we strike them just so ♪
♪ We can bring back the light ♪
♪ And the bright
Smiling girls always know ♪
♪ How to lose it ♪
♪ And never let it show ♪
(APPLAUSE AND CHEERING)
ELI:
THAT WAS "PRODIGAL SPOON."
AND I'VE BEEN TOLD THAT WAS
THEIR VERY FIRST PERFORMANCE?
HARD TO BELIEVE.
LET'S GIVE 'EM SOME LOVE, GUYS.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDS AND CHEERS)
BECKY:
(LAUGHS HAPPILY)
WOW, WE ROCKED IT!
JONAH:
YEAH! YEAH.
YEAH, WE TOTALLY DID.
BECKY:
UM, I SHOULD GO SAY HI
TO MY FRIENDS.
JONAH:
WELL, JUST WAIT, WAIT.
LOOK, I WAS THINKING
ABOUT WHAT YOU SAID AND...
I MEAN, WE DO SOUND
REALLY GOOD TOGETHER.
(NERVOUS LAUGH)
DREW:
BABE! THAT WAS...
THAT WAS GREAT!
I'M SO SORRY FOR BEING
SUCH A DOOF, EARLIER.
NUT YOU GUYS ARE, LIKE,
A REAL BAND!
DREW: WHAT'S UP, I'M DREW.
JONAH: JONAH.
ANYWAYS,
YOU CAN PRACTICE OR PLAY,
OR WHATEVER,
ANYTIME YOU GUYS WANT,
I PROMISE
I WON'T GET JEALOUS.
AT LEAST NOT TOO JEALOUS.
YOU FORGIVE ME?
OF COURSE... YOU DOOF!
(BECKY GIGGLES)
IT WAS SOME SORT OF
INTERROGATION. SO STRANGE.
AND WHAT DID THOSE
CHEER WENCHES WANT?
I HONESTLY HAVE NO IDEA.
YOU KNOW, I JUST AGREED
WITH THEM TO SHUT THEM UP.
WELL, WHATEVER THEY HAVE
COMING, THEY DESERVE IT.
♪ Ooohh-ooohh-ooohhh... ♪