(CAMERA BEEPS ON)
HI, TRISTAN MILLIGAN, HERE.
EVERYONE'S TALKING ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED THIS SUMMER,
BUT I'M THE ONLY ONE
THAT KNOWS THE WHOLE TRUTH.
THAT'S WHY I'M RECORDING
THIS VLOG.
PLEASE, PAY CLOSE ATTENTION
SO THAT SOMETHING LIKE THIS
CAN NEVER, EVER, HAPPEN AGAIN.
OKAY, IT ALL TOOK PLACE DURING
THE HOTTEST SUMMER ON RECORD...
♪♪
♪ I'll burn the house down
and I'll leave it behind ♪
CANNONBALL!
(HUGE SPLASH)
OOPS. DID I WRECK
YOUR NEW OUTFIT?
FRANKIE:
IT'LL DRY. NOTHING CAN RUIN MY
FIRST DAY AT MY NEW SUMMER JOB!
MILES:
(LAUGHS) EASY.
IT'S AT CITY HALL WITH DAD,
NOT LIKE THE UN,
OR SOMETHING.
FRANKIE:
YEAH, BUT WE ARE WORKING TO
IMPROVE PRIORITY NEIGHBOURHOODS.
WE COULD MAKE A DIFFERENCE.
ESPECIALLY SINCE ALL
THE INTERNS ARE SUPER-SMART.
HMM. YOU WANT SMART?
DOING GRADE TEN SCIENCE
IN SUMMER SCHOOL
SO I CAN GRADUATE EARLY -
NOW THAT IS SMART.
NO. SMART WAS NOT
TAKING A JOB,
SO WE CAN FLOAT IN THE POOL
ALL SUMMER.
WINSTON:
(CHUCKLES) YOU COULD STILL
JOIN US GENIUSES...
"FRANKSTON: SUMMER OF ROMANCE."
FRANKIE:
THERE WILL STILL BE
PLENTY OF TIME FOR ROMANCE
AFTER WORK -
WHICH I SHOULD GET TO.
MILES:
DO YOU NEED A LIFT?
WE'VE LITERALLY GOT
NOTHING ELSE TO DO.
FRANKIE:
IN THE HOLLINGSWORTH-MOBILE?
I WANT THE INTERNS
TO SEE ME AS A PERSON,
NOT JUST A LAST NAME.
I'LL WALK.
ALONE? WHAT IF SOMETHING
HAPPENS TO YOU?
NOW YOU'RE JUST STALLING.
(KISS)
♪ ...By the end of the night ♪
My pocket's full of nothing
and it's keeping me light
♪ I need a- ♪
(SHOE HEEL SNAPS) OH!
GUY:
EXCUSE ME,
DO YOU NEED ANY HELP?
FRANKIE:
I'LL BE OKAY.
(SUCKS IN HER BREATH
AND SIGHS)
GUY:
UH... I'VE GOT SOME GLUE
IN THE BACK.
FRANKIE:
NO THANK YOU.
GUY:
YOU'RE SURE? I... I CAN GIVE YOU
A RIDE IF YOU'D LIKE.
FRANKIE:
LEAVE ME ALONE, OKAY?
GUY:
OH, I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO FRIGHTEN YOU!
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh... ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
ABE:
OKAY, SO WE'VE GOT CAT
AND LOGAN.
MATT AND... MATT.
ANYONE SEEN
FRANKIE HOLLINGSWORTH?
AS IN DAUGHTER OF
ONE MAYOR HOLLINGSWORTH?
SHE'S TEN MINUTES LATE.
(DOOR BANGS SHUT)
FRANKIE:
I AM SO, SO SORRY.
THERE WAS THIS WEIRD GUY
ON THE WAY TO WORK AND HE...
CAT:
(LAUGHS SMUGLY) WELL,
YOU HAVE TO GIVE HER POINTS
FOR SUCH A CREATIVE EXCUSE
ON DAY ONE.
HE KEPT TRYING TO OFFER ME HELP
AND HE WOULDN'T TAKE NO
FOR AN ANSWER.
FRANKIE:
FORGET IT.
WHAT'RE WE WORKING ON?
ABE:
LET'S BEGIN.
THIS SUMMER,
MY CITY HALL INTERNS,
WE'LL USE YOUR YOUNG,
NIMBLE BRAINS
AND NEXT-TO-FREE LABOUR
TO HELP TACKLE POVERTY
IN THIS CITY.
ANY IDEAS ON HOW WE CAN BOLSTER
OUR 12 PRIORITY NEIGHBOURHOODS?
FRANKIE:
WELL, THEY NEED MONEY, RIGHT?
SO LET'S START A CHARITY
AND HOLD A FUNDRAISER,
LIKE A SILENT AUCTION.
CAT:
YOU KNOW MOST CHARITIES LOSE
20% OF THEIR MONEY TO OVERHEAD.
LOGAN:
YEAH, NOT TO MENTION
ALLOW RICH PEOPLE
TO DISASSOCIATE
FROM THE ACTUAL CAUSE.
FRANKIE:
YEAH, BUT WHO ELSE IS GONNA BID
AT A SILENT AUCTION?
A PLUMBER?
CAT: MY DAD'S A PLUMBER.
LOGAN:
WOW. WHAT ARE THE ODDS?
ROUGH BREAK, SMALL FRY.
I'LL SHOW YOU
WHO'S A SMALL FRY.
ABE:
OKAY, ANY MORE IDEAS?
HOW'RE WE GETTING
OUR HANDS DIRTY, THIS SUMMER?
INTERN:
OKAY, WELL, HOW ABOUT THIS?
♪♪
ZOE:
TRISTAN!
MY SUMMER SCHOOL SAVIOUR!
WHAT? NO "HI ZOE.
AMAZING DRESS.
IT MATCHES YOUR SANDALS
PERFECTLY"?
SORRY, MY GOAL FOR THE SUMMER
IS TO BE INTERNET FAMOUS
AND I HAVE TO SCOPE OUT
MY COMPETITION.
HER NAME'S GLORIA.
SHE MAKES THESE CRAZY
FROZEN TREATS...
AND GETS LIKE
TWENTY THOUSAND VIEWS.
GLORIA:
YOU KNOW, I THINK I EVEN TASTE
A BIT OF WOODSY CAMPFIRE TOO.
THIS IS ONE SERIOUSLY
SWEET TREAT.
ZOE:
WELL, I'LL DO MY BEST TO HELP,
(BELL RINGS)
BUT MY FIRST PRIORITY
IS PASSING SCIENCE.
OH! LUCKY FOR YOU,
I HAVE A PLAN FOR THAT.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
PERFECT! A NINER,
HERE TO GET AHEAD.
A.K.A. MY LAB PARTNER.
ZOE: AH!
I THOUGHT WE'D BE PARTNERS.
WHO AM I SUPPOSED TO GO WITH?
TRISTAN:
BINGO. I KNOW FOR A FACT
SHE GOT AT LEAST A 'B.'
SHE'S HERE TO UPGRADE.
ZOE: YEAH, FACT NUMBER TWO:
SHE HATES MY GUTS.
TRISTAN:
OH, HATERS GONNA HATE.
(PUNK MUSIC BLARES
THROUGH HEADPHONES)
HEY!
ZOE:
SONG OF THE SUMMER?
(SIGHS) ONLY AN IDIOT STILL
THINKS THAT THERE'S SOME KIND
OF MONOCULTURE
THAT CAN BE DEFINED
BY A SINGLE SONG.
TOTALLY.
UM, I ACTUALLY WANTED TO ASK,
DO YOU MAYBE WANNA BE...
LAB PARTNERS?
IF I GET TO PICK THE MUSIC
FOR ALL STUDY SESSIONS.
SOUNDS GREAT.
(PUNK MUSIC BLARES)
TRISTAN: NICE WORK.
MR. BAIN: HELLO, CLASS!
OH MY! WELL, AREN'T YOU
THE EAGER STUDENT.
WELL, YOU'RE SO EAGER
YOU FORGOT TO EAT.
NOW STAND OVER THERE.
THERE WE ARE.
HELLO! I AM... AUGUSTUS BAIN,
YOUR SCIENCE TEACHER.
I'M SORRY FOR MY TARDINESS.
CAR TROUBLE.
LET'S. LEARN. SCIENCE.
(WAVES WASH ASHORE)
♪♪
MAYA:
SHE'S NOT MOVING!
WHAT DO WE DO?
ZIG:
CHECK TO SEE
IF SHE'S BREATHING!
IF NOT,
WE PERFORM CPR!
MAYA: OKAY.
TINY: DIBS ON
CHEST COMPRESSIONS.
ZIG:
YOU WOULD VOLUNTEER
FOR THAT.
ARE YOU TWO SERIOUSLY TALKING
ABOUT HER BOOBS RIGHT NOW?
GLORIA:
DYING OVER HERE, REMEMBER?
MAYA:
UM... WE'LL MOVE HER
AND GET HER COVERED UP.
(MAYA GRUNTS WITH EFFORT,
WHISTLE BLOWS)
LIFEGUARD INSTRUCTOR:
AND... TIME.
GREAT WORK, GUYS.
EXCEPT MAYA...
I HAVE TO FAIL YOU.
YOU DIDN'T CHECK FOR A SPINAL
INJURY BEFORE DRAGGING HER.
BUT... THERE WAS NO SIGN
OF TRAUMA.
ALL THESE GUYS DID
WAS OGLE HER.
GLORIA:
CAN YOU BLAME THEM?
(WAVES WASH ASHORE,
SEAGULLS CRY)
MAYA:
I BLAME YOU
FOR WEARING THAT BIKINI.
SHOULDN'T SHE FAIL? I MEAN...
THAT'S DEFINITELY NOT PROPER
LIFEGUARDING ATTIRE.
ZIG:
WELL, MAYBE YOU CAN TAKE
THE TEST AGAIN?
MAYA:
NO, IT'S COOL. I DON'T NEED IT
FOR THE JOB I WANT, ANYWAYS -
NANNY FOR JORDYN KINCAID'S
KIDS.
GLORIA: THE MUSIC PRODUCER?
MAYA: YEAH.
MAYBE IF I IMPRESS HER,
I'LL GET A JOB IN
THE INDUSTRY SOME DAY.
AND THAT IS SOMETHING YOUR
BOOBS CANNOT WRECK FOR ME!
ZIG: (CHUCKLES)
MAYA: COME ON.
(PUNK MUSIC BLARES)
ZOE:
QUESTION FOUR -
"WHAT FORCE CONTROLS
THE MOVEMENT OF THE PLANETS?"
GRACE:
I'M NOT GONNA ANSWER
EVERY QUESTION FOR YOU.
ZOE:
I KNOW THAT.
SO ANSWER ONE.
ANY QUESTION.
(SIGHS)
AS I SUSPECTED.
COOL.
WAIT. WELL WHAT-
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
LEARN SCIENCE.
BUT WHEN IT COMES TO THESE
BIG CONCEPTS,
I'M JUST... LOST.
LOST IN WHAT?
YOU DON'T EVEN TRY.
I ALREADY FAILED THIS CLASS
ONCE. I KNOW I DON'T GET IT.
OR YOU KNOW
IF YOU NEVER REALLY TRY,
YOU NEVER HAVE TO TRULY FIND
OUT IF YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
I JUST WANT TO PASS.
(LOUD THUMP, HARD CLUNK)
UM... WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
GRACE:
EVER HEARD OF TRANS-CRANIAL
DIRECT CURRENT STIMULATION?
SCIENTISTS HAVE FIGURED OUT
THAT APPLYING A SMALL CURRENT
TO THE BRAIN
CAN ACCELERATE LEARNING.
HOLD THESE TO YOUR TEMPLES...
AND I'M GOING TO ZAP YOU
WHILE YOU READ
THE NEXT CHAPTER.
WAIT!
BITE DOWN ON THIS.
'KAY.
(ZOE GRUNTS,
EXHALES NERVOUSLY)
TRISTAN:
YOU THINK THAT WAS SHOCKING,
BUT THAT'S NOTHING COMPARED
TO WHAT HAPPENED TO MAYA
AT HER INTERVIEW.
(CREEPY MUSIC PLAYS)
(FRIGHTENED GASP)
(APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS)
EVERETT: WHY DO YOU SCARE
ALL OF THEM?
LENA:
MOM'S SCARY.
I FIGURE...
THEY SHOULD BE WARMED UP.
(APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS)
JORDYN:
YOU HAVE A VERY IMPRESSIVE
RESUME.
SO NICE TO MEET YOU.
YOU'LL HEAR FROM ME
IN THE NEXT COUPLE DAYS.
GLORIA: MAYA?
MAYA: GLORIA?
JORDYN:
YOU TWO KNOW EACH OTHER?
GLORIA:
WE WERE IN THE SAME
LIFEGUARDING CLASS.
SHE DIDN'T EXACTLY PASS,
BUT I'M SURE
YOU'LL STILL LOVE HER.
JORDYN:
SMALL WORLD, HUH?
JORDYN KINCAID.
MAYA:
HI! MAYA MATLIN.
I'M A HUGE FAN.
HERE.
JORDYN: GREAT.
(ENVELOPE AND RESUME RUSTLE)
DID YOU REALLY FAIL
YOUR LIFEGUARDING CLASS?
UM... TECHNICALLY, YEAH.
TECHNICALLY? YOUR RESUME
SUGGESTS YOU PASSED.
RIGHT, WELL, I GUESS
I MADE THAT BEFORE I...
ACTUALLY FINISHED
THE COURSE.
BUT EVERYTHING ELSE
ON THERE IS TRUE.
I CAN COOK!
SORT OF.
♪♪
(INTERNS CHATTER)
WINSTON: COMING?
FRANKIE: HEY, WINSTON.
CAT'S INVITING EVERYONE
TO SOMETHING, TONIGHT.
DO YOU MIND
IF I SKIP THE BEACH?
WINSTON:
THE COOLER'S ALL READY TO GO.
ICE COLD CREAM SODA...
FRANKIE:
I JUST NEED TO SEE
WHERE THEY'RE GOING
AND PROVE I'M NOT JUST
SOME ANNOYING LITTLE GIRL.
(SIGHS)
OKAY, GO.
THANKS, WINSTON.
YOU'RE THE BEST.
CAT:
OKAY, LET'S GO CLEAN UP.
(INTERNS CHATTER,
PHONES RING)
HEY. UM...
WHAT WAS ALL THAT ABOUT?
OH, THAT. CAT'S HAVING
SOME BIRTHDAY THING.
OH. UM... LIKE, WHERE?
♪♪
♪ Oh the sound ♪
♪ Breaking through
just like it should ♪
♪ So you're so good ♪
MILES:
HEY! I HAVEN'T HEARD FROM YOU
SINCE SCHOOL GOT.
I THOUGHT WE WERE GONNA
HANG OUT THIS SUMMER.
MM. YOU CAN KEEP ON
THINKING THAT.
MILES: BUT ARE WE?
TRISTAN: I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU CHOSE SUMMER SCHOOL
OVER MILES.
(ZOE AND TRISTAN LAUGH)
(RECORD SCRATCHES,
DRINK THUDS)
MAYA: HEY! DRINK AT LOLA'S.
ZOE: OH MY GOD.
MAYA: THANKS.
TRISTAN AND ZOE: (LAUGHING)
MAYA:
WHAT? IT'S THE ONLY SUMMER JOB
I COULD GET.
I FAILED AT BEING A NANNY.
NO, IT'S UM...
A GREAT LOOK.
ZOE: MM-HMM.
TRISTAN: LETTUCE GET
A BETTER LOOK AT YOU.
MAYA:
WHATEVER, OKAY?
I'M LOOKING FOR ZIG.
HE'LL MAKE ME FEEL BETTER.
HE'S LIFEGUARDING.
HAVE YOU SEEN HIM?
OH...
GLORIA:
(GIGGLING)
OH MY GOSH...
OH MY GOD, MAYA.
HILARIOUS COSTUME.
MAYA:
DON'T "MAYA" ME.
GLORIA: WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
MAYA: YOU STOLE MY JOB.
AND NOW YOU'RE TRYING
TO STEAL MY BOYFRIEND!
OKAY, WHY DON'T YOU
JUST CHILL OUT?
MAYA:
FINE, I CAN CHILL.
BECAUSE KARMA'S GONNA GET YOU
FOR THIS
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
GIRLS LIKE YOU DESERVE IT.
LET'S GO.
(ZOE AND TRISTAN LAUGH)
(LOUD ROCK MUSIC BLARES,
GIRLS SCREAM AND LAUGH)
♪♪
"EAT ME"
OR "DRINK ME."
ARE THOSE DRUGS?
LOGAN:
OH, YEAH, HARD DRUGS.
COME ON,
IT'S COCKTAILS AND CANDY.
IT'S AN ALICE
IN WONDERLAND PARTY.
CAT:
MY FRIENDS CALL ME
CHESHIRE CAT.
IS THAT FOR ME?
FRANKIE:
OH, YEAH,
IS THERE A GIFT TABLE?
LOGAN:
YEAH, RIGHT NEXT TO THE CLOWN
MAKING BALLOON ANIMALS.
YOU SHOULD TAKE
THE JELLY BEANS.
THESE COCKTAILS GOT
A BIT OF A KICK.
FRANKIE:
WHATEVER. MY FRIENDS CALL ME
FRANK THE TANK.
LOGAN:
(AMUSED)
ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE REALLY GOING FOR THAT,
HUH?
(FRANKIE GRIMACES)
LOGAN: YOU GOOD?
(GIFT FALLS,
LOUD METALLIC CRASH)
OH...
SHOOT!
(FIRE IMPLEMENTS CLATTER)
(LIGHT CLICKS ON)
AGH!
MOM, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH:
WHY ARE YOU HOME SO LATE?
IT'S TWO HOURS PAST YOUR CURFEW.
FRANKIE:
I WAS OUT WITH WORK FRIENDS.
I THINK THEY LIKE ME NOW.
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH:
OKAY... AND HOW MANY DRINKS
DID THAT TAKE?
FRANKIE:
I SWEAR I ONLY HAD
A COUPLE OF SIPS.
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH: REALLY?
FRANKIE: (VOMITS)
UGH! UGH!
SORRY.
(MARIACHI MUSIC PLAYS)
LOLA:
...CON ESTE HILO MI HECHIZO
FIJO...
QUE MI DESEO SEA CONMIGO
MIENTRAS ESTE CONJURO DIGO...
DO YOU HAVE A LOCK
OF GLORIA'S HAIR?
MAYA:
NO. WHY WOULD I HAVE THAT?
FOR THE HECHIZO.
OKAY, WE'LL PRETEND.
WHAT KIND OF CURSE
DO YOU WANNA PUT ON HER?
WE COULD TAKE AWAY
HER BEAUTY... OR HER VOICE...
ALL I REALLY WANT IS THE JOB
THAT I RIGHTFULLY DESERVE.
THIS IS ALL ABOUT
A SUMMER JOB?
NOT ALL OF US HAVE PARENTS THAT
NAME THEIR RESTAURANT AFTER US.
LOLA:
OKAY, LET ME TRY SOMETHING.
(EXHALES) CON CADA PUNTO BORDO
ESTE ENCANTO,
QUE MI DESEO SEA CONMIGO
MIENTRAS ESTE...
(MAYA'S PHONE BUZZES)
CON CADA PUNTO BORDO
ESTE ENCANTO...
(PHONE BUZZES)
CON ESTE HILO
MI HECHIZO FIJO...
MAYA: HELLO?
JORDYN: MY REGULAR NANNY,
GLORIA, DIDN'T SHOW, TODAY.
I'M IN A BIND.
CAN YOU FILL IN?
OF COURSE!
UM, I'LL-I'LL BE RIGHT OVER!
THAT WAS AMAZING!
I'D ALSO LIKE A MILLION DOLLARS
AND A PRIVATE JET.
HUH?
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER,
PHONES RING)
ABE:
LOOK ALIVE, MINIONS.
WE'VE GOT A GUEST COMING.
APPARENTLY, SOMEONE WANTS YOU
FOR A SPECIAL ASSIGNMENT!
FUN TIMES, LAST NIGHT?
UH... A LITTLE TOO FUN.
ANY ADVICE ON HOW TO MAKE
THIS ROOM STOP SPINNING?
UH... GO BACK IN TIME
AND DRINK LESS?
CAT:
PICK A SPOT ON THE WALL
AND FOCUS.
(DOOR CLOSES NEARBY,
PHONES RING)
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
SO WHO IN HERE THOUGHT
IT WOULD BE A GOOD IDEA
TO GET MY TEENAGED DAUGHTER
DRUNK?!
FRANKIE:
DAD. WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
YOU DIDN'T THINK YOUR MOTHER
WAS GONNA TELL ME
YOU CAME HOME OBLITERATED?
FRANKIE: THESE ARE MY FRIENDS.
MR. H: YOUR "FRIENDS?"
YOUNG LADY, YOU HAVE TO LEARN
TO BE MORE CAREFUL
ABOUT WHO YOU CHOOSE
AS "FRIENDS."
PLEASE DON'T FIRE THEM.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
OH, I'M NOT FIRING THEM,
JUST GIVING YOU ALL
A VERY "SPECIAL" ASSIGNMENT.
(PHONE RINGS NEARBY)
MR. BAIN:
EXCELLENT WORK
ON THIS ASSIGNMENT.
ZOE:
(GASPS) I GOT AN A?
I GOT AN A! I GOT AN A!
SHAY:
HOW DID SHE DO BETTER
THAN ME?
TRISTAN:
OKAY, I KNOW YOU'RE
A TRAINED ACTRESS,
BUT YOU MIGHT BE
OVERSELLING IT A BIT.
ZOE:
NO, I DID THIS ONE
ON MY OWN.
TRISTAN:
UGH. SURE, YOU DID.
DON'T PRETEND YOU'RE NOT
JUST AS DUMB AS ME.
ZOE:
I'M NOT! NOT ANYMORE.
GRACE... ZAPPED MY BRAIN.
YOU SHOULD TRY IT.
TRISTAN:
YOU'RE TALKING CRAZY.
TELL HIM.
UH, TRANS CRANIAL...
DIRECT CURRENT STIMULATION.
HUNTER: BUT IT DOESN'T WORK.
GRACE: SHHH!
ZOE:
IT TOTALLY DOES.
LOOK.
HUNTER: (LAUGHS)
SHE ACT-SHE ACTUALLY BELIEVES
YOU. THAT'S HILARIOUS.
ZOE:
IT'S NOT FUNNY.
IT'S REAL.
MR. BAIN!
MR. BAIN: HMM?
ZOE:
CAN YOU TELL HUNTER
ABOUT TRANS-CRANIAL...
MR. BAIN:
DIRECT CURRENT STIMULATION.
YES.
THE MILITARY IS TOYING
WITH IT,
BUT UH... THE JURY'S STILL OUT
SCIENCE-WISE,
AND ANY HOME VERSION
WOULD BE A PLACEBO, AT BEST.
HUNTER: HA-HA!
MR. BAIN: NOW, ONTO TODAY'S
LESSON: "THE SUN."
DID YOU GUYS KNOW
THAT AT ONE TIME...
WAS THAT YOUR PLAN?
TO EMBARRASS ME IN FRONT
OF THE ENTIRE CLASS?
YOU DO REALIZE THIS ACTUALLY
MEANS YOU'RE SMART,
RIGHT, DUMMY?
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER,
ROLLERS SWIPE)
(INTERNS CHATTER,
(BIRDS CHIRP,
INTERNS CHATTER)
(CROW CAWS,
CIRCUS-LIKE MUSIC PLAYS)
CAT:
IT'S LIKE WE'RE IN
A HORROR MOVIE.
(ICE CREAM TRUCK RUMBLES UP)
LOGAN: WHAT THE HELL?
FRANKIE: SURPRISE!
I CALLED IT HERE AS AN
APOLOGY... FOR ALL OF THIS.
IT'S FREE ICE CREAM.
YAY!
(INTERNS MUTTER)
I'VE DONE EVERYTHING
TO MAKE YOU PEOPLE LIKE ME.
WHAT DID I EVER DO
THAT WAS SO WRONG?
YOU TOOK THIS INTERNSHIP.
THE REST OF US, WE HAD TO WORK
REALLY HARD TO GET HERE.
WE CARE ABOUT THE WORK.
FRANKIE: I CARE ABOUT THE WORK,
TOO.
AND YET, ALL YOU'VE DONE
IS DRINK TOO MUCH
AND GET US ALL IN TROUBLE.
I JUST DON'T KNOW
AS MUCH AS YOU.
I HAVEN'T BEEN TO UNIVERSITY,
SO I DON'T HAVE THE EXPERIENCE.
BUT... I'M SMART.
I WANNA LEARN.
PLEASE, TEACH ME.
MAYA:
AND DRUMROLL PLEASE...
(DRUMS HER HANDS)
BLUEBERRY SURPRISE!
LENA:
MORE LIKE BOOOOOO-BERRY.
EVERETT:
GLORIA MADE THEM
WITH THREE FLAVOURS.
MAYA:
YEAH, BUT I BET
THESE ARE WAY TASTIER.
LENA:
NOT EVEN!
GLORIA WAS THE BEST.
MAYA:
WAIT, YOU GUYS AREN'T SAYING
YOU ACTUALLY LIKE GLORIA CHIN?
SHE'S SO RUDE AND... AND FAKE.
SHE'S A MONSTER.
SHE'S THE BEST NANNY
WE'VE EVER HAD.
MAYA:
SHE DIDN'T EVEN SHOW UP TODAY!
LENA:
OH, (LAUGHS) I GET IT.
YOU'RE JEALOUS.
MAYA: OF GLORIA?
LENA: MM-HMM.
MAYA: NO WAY.
LENA: YOU CAN'T HANDLE THAT
SHE'S SMART AND PRETTY...
AND SWEET,
AND PEOPLE ACTUALLY LIKE HER.
EVERETT:
YEAH. MAYBE YOU'RE THE MONSTER.
TRISTAN:
OKAY, I'VE GOT A VLOG IDEA.
YOU AND ME TANNING...
WHILE REVIEWING ICED DRINKS.
HOT AND COLD,
TOGETHER AT LAST.
GRACE:
ZOE, WAIT UP.
ZOE: WHAT DO YOU WANT?
GRACE: SORRY ABOUT EARLIER,
OKAY?
MR. BAIN'S TAKING SOME OF US
TO GO SEE THE DELTA AQUARIDS
METEOR SHOWER.
COME.
ZOE:
SO YOU CAN FIND SOME NEW
AND CLEVER WAY TO MOCK ME?
BECAUSE I THINK
YOU'D BE INTERESTED.
MR. BAIN:
GUYS, TWENTY METEORS AN HOUR,
BURNING UP.
IT'S CRAZY.
JUST A 100 KILOMETRES ABOVE US!
COME ON!
(LAUGHS)
I KNOW YOU THINK
YOU'RE ALLERGIC TO SCIENCE,
BUT FOR A HOT MINUTE THERE,
YOU WERE GOOD AT IT.
YOU ACTUALLY CARED
HOW THE WORLD WORKED.
DON'T GIVE THAT UP.
OKAY, YOU CAN'T BE
CONSIDERING THIS.
I THINK I ACTUALLY WANNA USE
MY BRAIN FOR ONCE.
GRACE, WAIT UP!
TRISTAN: IF YOU REALLY WANTED
TO USE YOUR BRAIN,
YOU WOULDN'T FOLLOW A CREEPY
TEACHER OUT TO THE WOODS!
FRANKIE:
ARE WE SAFE HERE?
IT'S GONNA BE DARK SOON.
LOGAN:
THIS IS ONE OF THE
NEIGHBOURHOODS YOU SIGNED UP
TO HELP,
YOU'VE NEVER EVEN
BEEN HERE.
FRANKIE:
HAVE YOU?
LOGAN:
YEAH. I GREW UP IN AN APARTMENT
BUILDING OVER THERE.
NO YOU DIDN'T.
LOGAN:
YEAH, I DID.
NO SAFE PLACE TO PLAY,
NO FANCY COFFEE SHOPS.
I HADN'T EVEN HEARD
THE WORD "ESPRESSO"
TILL I GOT TO UNIVERSITY.
AND, WELL, TO GET THERE,
I HAD TO PAID MY OWN WAY -
ODD JOBS,
A LOT OF SAVINGS.
LOGAN, I HAD NO IDEA...
LOGAN:
SO THAT'S WHY
THIS IS SO IMPORTANT.
I WAS SUPPOSED TO EARN
SOME MONEY,
WHILE GIVING BACK
TO MY NEIGHBOURHOOD.
FRANKIE:
OKAY. I GET IT.
SO HOW DO WE HELP?
LOGAN:
SEE A LOT OF PEOPLE
AROUND HERE?
NO. WHY AREN'T THERE
MORE PEOPLE?
MAYBE THEY DON'T FEEL
SAFE EITHER.
IN THEIR OWN NEIGHBOURHOOD?
WHAT IF WE MADE IT
LOOK BETTER?
BUILD SOME COMMUNITY GARDENS...
WE COULD GET A CORPORATE
SPONSOR INVOLVED AND...
TRAIN YOUNG PEOPLE AROUND
THE NEIGHBOURHOOD TO HELP.
THEY COULD IMPROVE
THEIR NEIGHBOURHOOD
WHILE LEARNING
EMPLOYABLE SKILLS.
I'M IMPRESSED.
DO YOU THINK ABE
WILL GO FOR IT?
YEAH, IT'S DEFINITELY
A SOLID START.
OKAY. COME ON,
LET'S SEE MORE.
(PHONE BUZZES)
OH, SORRY.
WELL, WHAT'RE YOU
WAITING FOR?
LOGAN:
MY FRIEND JUST TEXTED ME.
MY GIRLFRIEND, GLORIA...
SHE'S MISSING.
FOR HOW LONG?
LOGAN:
TWENTY-FOUR HOURS,
AT LEAST.
I JUST THOUGHT SHE WAS IGNORING
ME 'CAUSE WE HAD FIGHT.
WHAT CAN I DO?
I'LL TELL THE POLICE
ABOUT THAT WEIRD GUY
WHO TRIED TO HELP ME.
MAYBE IT'S RELATED.
LOGAN:
ALL RIGHT. THANKS.
COME HERE.
LOOK, I'M SORRY I WAS SO HARD
ON YOU, YOU KNOW?
YOU'RE ONE OF THE GOOD ONES,
SMALL FRY.
(DOOR CLOSES)
MAYA:
HEY. THE KIDS ARE FINALLY
ASLEEP.
ZIG:
SO YOU'RE CALLING ME OVER
TO MAKE-OUT.
MAYA:
NO, I'M...
I'M CALLING YOU TO APOLOGIZE.
ZIG:
I ACCEPT. NOW, CAN I COME OVER
FOR A MAKEUP MAKE-OUT?
MAYA:
I'M SERIOUS, ZIG.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE SNAPPED
AT YOU. I WAS JUST JEALOUS
OF GLORIA.
APPARENTLY,
SHE'S ACTUALLY NICE.
ZIG:
I STILL LIKE YOU WAY BETTER.
MAYA:
I KNOW THAT. BUT, FOR THE REST
OF THE SUMMER,
I JUST WANNA FORGET SHE EVEN
EXISTS AND FOCUS ON THIS JOB.
ZIG:
SO... NO COMING OVER
FOR A MAKE-OUT?
MAYA:
NO. I'M JUST GONNA WATCH TV
AND TIDY THE PLACE UP.
MAYBE IF I KICK BUTT HERE,
(TURNS TV ON)
JORDYN WILL TAKE ME UNDER
HER WING IN THE MUSIC BIZ.
BYE, ZIGGY.
NEWS:...APPROXIMATELY 4 P.M.
DETECTIVE ON TV:
AFTER TEXTING HER PARENTS
YESTERDAY,
GLORIA CHIN VANISHED.
WE HAVE DECLARED HER
A MISSING PERSON.
ANYONE WITH INFORMATION,
CAN CALL THE POLICE DIRECTLY,
OR TO OUR ANONYMOUS TIP LINE.
WHAT HAPPENED TO GLORIA?
YOU'LL NEVER BELIEVE IT.
(CAMERA BEEPS OFF)