MAYA:
MILES?
(LIGHT APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS)
MILES.
MILES!
MILES, STOP!
MILES! NO!
(SCREAMS OUT)
(HEAVY BREATHING)
(DOOR CREAKS OPENS)
OH GOD...
ZIG: (YAWNS)
ANOTHER MILES NIGHTMARE?
MAYA:
THEY WON'T STOP.
I'M SO ANXIOUS,
I HAVEN'T SLEEP IN DAYS.
ZIG:
WELL, AH...
I COULD SING YOU A LULLABY?
OH, I'LL DO IT.
DON'T THINK I WON'T.
(MAYA CHUCKLES RELUCTANTLY)
♪ Twinkle, twinkle,
little star ♪
♪ How I wonder what you are ♪
MAYA:
OKAY, THANK YOU.
NOW I'M GONNA HAVE
NIGHTMARES ABOUT THAT.
ZIG:
WELL, THEN MY JOB HERE
IS DONE.
BUT SERIOUSLY, MAYA,
YOU NEED HELP.
NO, I JUST NEED TO GET
MY MIND OFF MILES.
WELL, THEN I CAN GIVE YOU
SOME KANYE?
I GOT HIS ENTIRE CATALOGUE
MEMORIZED.
SOMEHOW, I DON'T THINK
THAT'S GONNA CUT IT.
♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Oh-Oh-Oh... ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
MAYA:
HEY. CAN I BE A CHEERLEADER?
ZOE:
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
YOU HAVE ALL THE COORDINATION
OF A DRUNK HIPPO.
OH MY GOD,
YOU LOOK LIKE CRAP.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
MAYA:
I HAVEN'T BEEN SLEEPING.
SO YOU'RE SURE THERE'S NOTHING
I CAN DO FOR THE CHEER TEAM?
ZOE:
WELL, I DO NEED SOMEONE
TO CRAFT
SOME SWEET MASH-UP TRACKS.
MAYA:
THAT'D BE PERFECT!
MY GARAGE BAND SKILLS
ARE REALLY COMING ALONG.
ZOE:
THIS IS NOT SOMETHING
I HAND TO YOU LIGHTLY.
IF ANYTHING GOES WRONG,
WE COULD GET DISQUALIFIED.
ARE YOU UP TO SHOULDERING
THIS RESPONSIBILITY?
MAYA:
ABSOLUTELY.
YOU CAN COUNT ON ME.
ZOE:
GREAT. SO 30 SECONDS IN
I NEED A SOUND CUE FOR...
(BELL RINGS)
MAYA?
MAYA:
SORRY. MILES IS M.I.A.
WHERE DO YOU THINK HE IS?
ZOE:
OH, YOU KNOW,
PROBABLY OFF DOING SOMETHING
PREDICTABLY SELF DESTRUCTIVE.
MAYA:
HE'S BEEN MISSING CLASS
A LOT LATELY
AND ACTING REALLY WEIRD.
ZOE:
IF YOU SAY SO.
SO COME TO THE GYM AT LUNCH.
I'LL HAVE SOME OF THE GIRLS
RUN THE ROUTINE.
I NEED YOU TO KNOW THIS BABY
INSIDE AND OUT.
MATLIN!
DID YOU HEAR ME?
MAYA:
ABSOLUTELY!
INSIDE AND OUT!
IMOGEN:
SO YOU'RE TELLING ME,
YOU'VE NEVER ONCE JUST THOUGHT
EYEBALLS ARE SO WEIRD?
JACK:
NOT ONCE!
IMOGEN:
WHATEVER,
MAYBE I'M JUST A FREAK.
JACK:
AW, NO, I LOVE THAT
THESE ARE THE THINGS
THAT FILL YOUR WEIRD,
LITTLE MIND.
IMOGEN:
AND I LOVE YOU.
JACK:
WOW, UM... THANKS.
FRANKIE:
OKAY, I'M GONNA FINISH
THE CODING,
AND GUYS COVER DESIGN
AND ANALYSIS!
(THEY LAUGH)
WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
LOLA:
ARLENE'S FACE IN THIS PICTURE.
FRANKIE:
THAT'S NOT VERY NICE.
SHAY:
YEAH. OKAY, SAINT FRANKIE.
FRANKIE:
IF I DON'T GET AN 'A'
IN THIS CLASS,
IT WILL BRING DOWN MY WHOLE
AVERAGE.
(BELL RINGS)
WHICH MEANS WE'LL HAVE
TO FINISH AT LUNCH.
LOLA:
SORRY, FRANKS,
WE'VE GOT CHEER PRACTICE.
FRANKIE:
OF COURSE YOU DO.
LOLA:
IS THAT A TOUCHY SUBJECT
FOR YOU?
SINCE ZOE BOOTED YOU OFF
FOR BEING A PRUDE?
FRANKIE:
OKAY. I WASN'T KICKED OFF.
I QUIT.
AND I DON'T WANT
TO TALK ABOUT IT.
I JUST WANNA FOCUS ON GETTING
THIS WORK DONE?
SHAY:
YOUR FREAKY BROTHER'S
IN THIS CLASS.
GET THE ANSWERS FROM HIM.
LOLA:
YEAH, IT'S LIKE HIS TWIN DUTY.
FRANKIE:
OKAY. FIRST OF ALL,
THAT WOULD BE DISHONEST.
AND SECOND,
THERE'S NO WAY HE'D AGREE.
SHAY:
WELL, YOU BETTER FIND A WAY
IF YOU WANT THE GRADE.
♪♪
♪ I can make you laugh
I can be your best friend ♪
ZOE:
NICE.
LOCK THE KNEES.
TIGHTEN UP. TIGHTEN UP!
AND THIS IS WHERE WE NEED THE
45 SECOND BREAK FOR CHEERING.
IF WE DON'T HAVE ONE,
IT'S DISQUALIFICATION CITY.
MILES,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
MAYA: MILES! NO! (SCREAMS)
ZOE: EARTH TO MATLIN!
HUH?
ZOE:
CAN YOU PLEASE PAY ATTENTION?
I SWEAR, MAYA,
IF YOU MESS THIS UP FOR ME...
WELL, LET'S JUST SAY
IT WON'T BE PRETTY.
MAYA:
RIGHT. TOTALLY.
I'M ALL YOURS.
♪ I take care of my self ♪
♪ I'm very independent ♪
MAYA:
(SCREAMS) NO!
MILES, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
MILES! STOP! NO!
(SCREAMS)
♪ I might just blow your mind ♪
♪ I make you feel the best ♪
♪ You want a good time ♪
(SIGHS)
MAYA?
WHERE THE HELL DID SHE GO?!
(PANICKED BREATHS)
(SIGHS)
GRACE:
TOUGH DAY IN THE MINES,
BLONDIE?
ZIG:
SHE'S BEEN STRESSED OUT LATELY.
GRACE:
THEN YOU DEFINITELY
NEED TO COME WITH US.
MAYA:
WHERE YOU GOING?
GRACE:
TO, AH... RELAX.
YOU IN?
ZIG:
IT'LL HELP YOU FORGET
WHATEVER'S TROUBLING YOU.
(BELL RINGS)
MAYA: YEAH. SOUNDS PERFECT.
(LOW HUM OF STUDENT CHATTER)
HUNTER:
WHAT DO YOU WANT, FRANKENSTEIN?
FRANKIE:
A SISTER CAN'T HAVE LUNCH
WITH HER BELOVED BROTHER
WITHOUT SUSPICION?
HUNTER:
YOU HAVEN'T EATEN LUNCH WITH ME
SINCE MAY OF SIXTH GRADE.
JUST TELL ME WHAT YOU WANT.
FRANKIE:
YOUR COMPUTER SCIENCE HOMEWORK?
I USUALLY DO MY HOMEWORK
WITH SHAY AND LOLA,
BUT THEY'RE TOO BUSY
WITH CHEERLEADING.
HUNTER:
WHY ARE YOU STILL FRIENDS
WITH THEM?
AREN'T THEY THE REASON YOU GOT
KICKED OUT OF CHEERLEADING
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
FRANKIE:
IT WASN'T THEM, SPECIFICALLY.
HUNTER:
BUT THEY DIDN'T DEFEND YOU.
FRANKIE:
NO.
HUNTER:
I'D RATHER SPEND THE REST
OF MY LIFE ALONE,
THAN HAVE "FRIENDS" LIKE THEM.
FRANKIE:
OKAY. THANKS FOR THE PEP TALK.
I GUESS THAT'S A 'NO'
ON THE HOMEWORK ANSWERS?
HUNTER:
HOW CAN I SAY THIS
SO YOU'LL UNDERSTAND?
I WOULD SOONER SEE ALL THE
CHEERLEADERS DIE IN A FIRE
THAN HELP THEM.
WATCH MY STUFF.
I'M GETTING A CREAM SODA.
FRANKIE:
OKAY BROTHER,
WHERE THE SCHOOL WORK AT?
(KEYS CLACK)
A COMIC?
OH, MY GOD.
WOW, HUNTER REALLY DOES
HATE CHEERLEADERS.
(CAMERA CLICKS)
IMOGEN:
HI. UM, ABOUT WHAT I SAID
BEFORE...
I DIDN'T REALLY MEAN IT.
I MEAN,
I DID MEAN WHAT I SAID.
I JUST DIDN'T MEAN THAT
YOU SHOULD FEEL LIKE
YOU HAD TO SAY IT BACK.
UNLESS YOU FELT THAT TOO.
IN WHICH CASE IT WOULD BE VERY,
VERY NICE FOR YOU TO SAY IT
BACK,
BUT ONLY IF YOU MEAN IT,
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
JACK:
I THINK WE SHOULD BREAK UP.
IMOGEN:
VERY FUNNY, PHYLLIS DILLER.
WAIT, ARE YOU SERIOUS?
JACK:
IT'S NOT THAT I DON'T
LIKE BEING WITH YOU.
IMOGEN:
OKAY.
JACK:
I JUST DIDN'T EXPECT THIS TO
TURN INTO A MONOGAMOUS THING.
IMOGEN:
YOU DIDN'T?
JACK:
AND I'M WORRIED THAT YOU THINK
I'M INTO EXCLUSIVE
RELATIONSHIPS.
IMOGEN:
YOU'RE NOT?
JACK:
I'M JUST DON'T KNOW IF I BUY
INTO THIS HETERONORMATIVE IDEA
OF ROMANTIC LOVE.
JUST BECAUSE WE LIKE BEING
TOGETHER DOESN'T MEAN
WE OWN EACH OTHER.
I DON'T THINK I OWN YOU.
JACK:
I NEVER BROUGHT IT UP,
BECAUSE I DIDN'T KNOW
HOW YOU FELT ABOUT IT.
IMOGEN: ABOUT WHAT?
JACK: POLYAMORY...
NON-MONOGAMY.
IMOGEN:
OKAY. YOU MEAN
DATING OTHER PEOPLE,
WHILE WE'RE DATING EACH OTHER?
JACK:
I GET IT IF IT'S TOO MUCH
FOR YOU.
OKAY? I JUST WANTED
TO BE HONEST,
BEFORE THINGS WENT ANY FURTHER.
IMOGEN:
NO. NO-NO-NO.
I TOTALLY GET IT.
I ACTUALLY FEEL THE SAME WAY
ABOUT ALL THAT STUFF.
JACK:
OKAY. SO...
YEAH. THAT'S SOMETHING
YOU'RE GOOD WITH?
IMOGEN:
OH MY GOD, YEAH.
WHY DIDN'T YOU JUST SAY
SOMETHING BEFORE?
JACK:
COOL. YEAH. GREAT.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE WE JUST TAKE
THE NIGHT OFF?
POSTPONE OUR DATE?
OKAY. YEAH.
GREAT. BYE.
BYE.
(EXHALES)
AREN'T YOU EVEN TRY IT?
MAYA:
CAN'T BELIEVE THIS IS WHAT YOU
THOUGHT WOULD MAKE ME RELAX.
GRACE:
WHAT, DID YOU THINK WE WERE
GONNA GET YOU HIGH OR SOMETHING?
MAYA:
YEAH, KIND OF.
GRACE:
IT'S THE MIDDLE OF THE DAY.
WHO DO YOU THINK WE ARE?
ZIG:
(RELAXED EXHALE)
YOU KNOW, I FEEL LIKE
MY WHITE CRANE
IS WAY MORE FLUID
THAN IT WAS LAST WEEK.
MAYA:
YOU'RE SO WEIRD.
GRACE:
WE'RE WEIRD?
WHY IS SHE BEING
SUCH A DOWNER?
MAYA:
WHY DO YOU THINK MILES
WASN'T IN CLASS?
GRACE:
(SIGHS) NOT THIS AGAIN.
IF I CAN PROVE TO YOU HE'S FINE,
WILL YOU SHUT UP ABOUT IT?
MAYA:
MAYBE, BUT HOW ARE YOU GONNA
TO DO THAT?
GRACE:
POWER OF THE INTERNET.
JUST GOTTA GET INTO
HIS FACERANGE MESSAGES.
(KEYS CLACK)
SEE? HE'S AT HOME.
HE JUST MESSAGED TRISTAN
THIS MORNING.
MAYA:
OH MY GOD.
TRISTAN ASKED HIM HOW HE FEELS,
AND MILES RESPONDED
"I WANNA KILL MYSELF."
ZIG:
SO WHAT, MAYA?
I MEAN, PEOPLE SAY THAT
ALL THE TIME.
MAYA:
YEAH. AND SOMETIMES
THEY MEAN IT.
HEH. THIS HOUSE...
GRACE:
MAKES ME WANNA START THE
UPRISING OF THE PROLETARIAT.
MAYA:
COME ON, HURRY UP.
GRACE:
HEY! I'M MISSING MY TAI CHI
FOR THIS, SO BE NICE.
MAYA:
YOU GUYS STAND GUARD.
MILES.
MILES:
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING!?
MAYA:
CHECKING TO SEE
IF YOU'RE ALIVE!
MILES:
WHAT?!
MAYA:
TRISTAN ASKED YOU
HOW YOU WERE FEELING,
AND YOU SAID YOU WANTED
TO KILL YOURSELF!
MILES:
OKAY, BECAUSE I HAVE A HEAD
COLD AND I FEEL LIKE CRAP!
WAIT?
DID YOU HACK MY FACERANGE
ACCOUNT?!
I...
HAVE YOU TOTALLY LOST
YOUR MIND?
TRISTAN:
OH HELL NO.
BACK OFF MY B.F., BITCH.
MAYA:
THIS IS NOT WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE.
TRISTAN:
OH, REALLY? BECAUSE IT LOOKS
LIKE YOU'RE TRYING TO DIG
YOUR TRAMPY LITTLE TALONS
INTO MY MAN.
MAYA:
I WAS CHECKING ON HIM!
MILES:
LOOK, SHE'S CRAZY.
SHE HACKED FACERANGE.
TRISTAN:
WOW, YOU'VE GONE FULL GIRL
INTERRUPTED ON US HERE.
MAYA:
MILES, JUST TELL ME-JUST TELL
ME WHAT'S REALLY GOING ON!
MILES: GET OUT OF MY HOUSE!
ZIG: MAYA, COME ON!
MAYA:
JUST TALK TO ME!
MILES!
(SCOFFS)
(STUDENT CHATTER)
WINSTON:
HEY, ARE YOU FEELING OKAY?
YOU HAVEN'T SAID ANYTHING
IN OVER THREE MINUTES.
FRANKIE:
IS THAT UNUSUAL?
WINSTON:
HAVE YOU MET YOU?
NOT THAT I DON'T LOVE
YOUR LOQUACIOUSNESS.
WORD OF THE DAY CALENDAR.
FRANKIE:
OKAY. WHEN I SAY "HUNTER,"
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF?
WINSTON:
PSYCHO?
MAL-ADJUSTED WEIRDO?
FRANKIE:
OKAY, I'M GONNA SHOW YOU
SOMETHING,
BUT YOU HAVE TO PROMISE
YOU'RE NOT GONNA FREAK OUT.
WINSTON:
I PROMISE NOTHING.
OKAY, I'LL TRY MY BEST.
HOT NEW ONLINE COMIC?
FRANKIE:
NO! HUNTER DREW THIS.
WINSTON:
OH. OHHHH. YIKES.
THAT LOOKS LIKE HIM...
MURDERING A BUNCH OF PEOPLE
WHO LOOK A LOT LIKE-
FRANKIE:
CHEERLEADERS. EXACTLY.
WHAT DO I DO?
WINSTON:
CALL THE POLICE?
FRANKIE:
YOU'RE JOKING, RIGHT?
WINSTON:
50 PERCENT JOKING.
FRANKIE:
YOU DON'T THINK HUNTER WOULD
ACTUALLY HURT PEOPLE, DO YOU?
WINSTON:
WELL, HUNTER HAS ALWAYS
BEEN WEIRD,
BUT FRANKS,
THOSE ARE DARK.
FRANKIE:
BUT IF I TELL ON HIM, HE COULD
GET INTO A LOT OF TROUBLE.
I NEED TO MAKE SURE THERE'S
SOMETHING TO BE WORRIED ABOUT.
WINSTON:
WELL, YOU NEED MORE EVIDENCE.
FRANKIE:
I GUESS WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO DO SOME RECONNAISSANCE.
(BELL RINGS)
(DOOR CLICKS OPEN,
PATRONS CHATTER)
IMOGEN:
HOWDY, FRIEND.
ELI:
I HATE MY LIFE.
IMOGEN:
WOW. THAT CLARE/DREW SAGA HAS
REALLY DONE A NUMBER ON YOU.
ELI:
YOU THINK?
IMOGEN:
I KNOW WHAT WILL CHEER YOU UP -
GOING ON A DATE WITH ME?
ELI: I'M SORRY... WHAT?
IMOGEN: I'M POLYAMOROUS, NOW.
AND BESIDES JACK, YOU'RE THE
ONLY PERSON I LIKE ENOUGH
TO GO ON A DATE WITH,
EVEN THOUGH I HAVE NO DESIRE
TO BED YOU. SORRY.
ELI:
BACK IT UP A LITTLE?
IMOGEN:
I TOLD JACK I LOVED HER.
AND THEN SHE SAID THANKS.
AND THEN SHE WANTED TO BREAK UP,
BECAUSE SHE WANTS TO BE
POLYAMOROUS.
ELI:
WAIT, LIKE, DATE OTHER PEOPLE
AND EACH OTHER?
AND YOU AGREED?
IMOGEN:
WELL, ONLY BECAUSE
I DIDN'T WANT TO LOSE HER.
WHY? DO YOU THINK
IT WAS A BAD IDEA?
ELI:
THE WORST I'VE EVER HEARD.
LOOK, THE IDEA OF THE PERSON
I LOVE
RUNNING AROUND KISSING
AND WHATEVER-ING
WHOEVER THEY WANT?
NO THANK YOU.
IMOGEN:
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I DON'T WANT TO BE POLYAMOROUS!
I JUST WANT JACK AND
I JUST WANT HER TO WANT ME.
ELI:
UNFORTUNATELY, YOU CAN'T CONTROL
OTHER PEOPLE'S EMOTIONS.
BUT YOU CAN TELL HER
HOW YOU FEEL.
I TOLD HER I LOVED HER AND
LOOK HOW WELL THAT TURNED OUT.
ELI:
WELL, IN THAT CASE,
THERE'S PLENTY OF ROOM
IN MY PIT OF DESPAIR.
(SHOT GLASSES CLINK)
(SLURPING, CHOKES)
(PHONE CHIMES)
WHAT?!
SHE'S ON A DATE
WITH ANOTHER GIRL?!
THIS MAKES ME WANT TO BARF.
ELI:
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I NEED TO TELL HER HOW I FEEL
AND IF I DON'T I WON'T BE ABLE
TO LIVE WITH MYSELF.
ELI:
OR YOU COULD JUST GIVE UP.
IMOGEN:
NOT YET, GOLDSWORTHY.
NOT YET.
(GULP)
(READYING BREATH)
WINSTON:
I DON'T KNOW IF I CAN DO THIS.
FRANKIE:
I KNOW IT'S AN INVASION
OF PRIVACY, BUT I'M WORRIED!
WINSTON:
IT'S NOT THAT!
IT'S SCARY IN HERE!
FRANKIE:
WE JUST NEED A LITTLE
MORE INTEL.
BINGO!
IT'S THE REST OF THE COMIC.
WINSTON:
OKAY, SO THE MASKED AVENGER
SAVAGELY ATTACKS ALL THE EVIL
ZOMBIE CHEERLEADERS...
OKAY, STILL NOT GOOD.
SO HE CAN RESCUE THE PRINCESS
THEY'VE LOCKED
IN THEIR DUNGEON.
FRANKIE:
A PRINCESS WHO LOOKS
A LOT LIKE ARLENE.
WINSTON:
WHO?
FRANKIE:
WELL, SHE'S A GIRL
IN OUR GRADE...
WHO SHAY AND LOLA AND I
HAVEN'T BEEN THE NICEST TO.
HUNTER'S NOT A PSYCHO,
HE'S JUST IN LOVE!
FRANKIE:
SO, WHAT?
THIS IS NORMAL?
I WOULD SAY THIS IS AS CLOSE
TO NORMAL
AS HUNTER'S EVER GONNA GET.
THIS IS HIM WISHING
HE COULD GET UP THE NERVE
TO BE THIS GIRL'S HERO.
HUNTER:
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
DOING IN MY ROOM?
FRANKIE:
AH, I WAS JUST LOOKING
FOR YOUR COMPUTERS HOMEWORK!
HUNTER:
IF YOU'RE VIOLATING MY PRIVACY
TO STEAL HOMEWORK ANSWERS
FOR TWO IDIOTS
WHO AREN'T EVEN NICE TO YOU?!
FRANKIE:
YES?
HUNTER:
IT'S OKAY TO BE MAD AT PEOPLE!
ESPECIALLY WHEN
THEY SCREW YOU OVER! OKAY?
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYS)
JACK:
IMOGEN! I THOUGHT-
IMOGEN:
I DON'T WANNA TAKE
THE NIGHT OFF,
AND I DON'T WANT TO DO STUFF
WITH OTHER PEOPLE,
AND I DON'T WANT YOU
TO DO STUFF WITH OTHER PEOPLE.
AND I DON'T WANT YOU TO WANNA
DO STUFF WITH OTHER PEOPLE!
JACK:
CAN WE DO THIS SOMEWHERE ELSE-
IMOGEN:
I LOVE YOU, JACK JONES,
AND EVEN THOUGH
I BARELY UNDERSTOOD
ANT OF THAT HETERO-NOGAMY
STUFF,
I THINK YOU ONLY SAID IT
BECAUSE YOU'RE SCARED!
AND I GET IT,
COMMITMENT IS SCARY.
BUT I WANNA TAKE THAT LEAP.
AND IF WE BREAK EACH OTHER'S
HEARTS IN THE END,
THEN SO BE IT.
BUT I'M A ONE-WOMAN WOMAN.
IT'S JUST WHO I AM.
(EXHALES)
(GASPS)
(GIRLS GIGGLE)
I'M GONNA GO.
JACK:
THAT'S PROBABLY A GOOD IDEA.
(SIGHS)
(COMPUTER KEYS CLACK)
ZIG: MAYA, STOP.
MAYA: CAN'T!
ZIG:
MAYA, PLEASE.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE FREAKING ME OUT.
ZOE:
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?!
MAYA:
HE BLOCKED ME.
ZOE:
YOU BEG ME TO LET YOU
DO THE CHEER MUSIC,
AND THEN YOU TOTALLY
BAIL ON ME?!
MAYA:
WHY WOULD HE DO THAT?
ZOE:
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT,
BUT I'D REALLY LIKE
AN EXPLANATION.
MAYA:
I CAN'T LET IT HAPPEN AGAIN.
I CAN'T. I CAN'T. I CAN'T.
ZIG:
WHOA!
(PANICKED BREATHS)
ZIG:
MAYA?
(RAPID BREATHING)
OKAY, MAYA, DEEP BREATHS.
ALL RIGHT? WE'RE RIGHT HERE.
ZOE: IT'S OKAY. ZIG: OKAY?
(BREATHING RAPIDLY)
ELI:
GOOD NIGHT, GUYS.
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
IMOGEN:
(SIGHS)
JOINING YOU
IN YOUR WALLOWING.
ELI:
I TAKE IT THINGS
DIDN'T GO WELL WITH JACK?
IMOGEN:
IT LITERALLY COULD
NOT HAVE GONE WORSE.
ELI:
I'M SORRY, IMOGEN.
BUT IF I CAN BE REAL -
LOVE'S A LIE ANYWAY.
AND THE SOONER YOU ACCEPT THAT,
THE BETTER.
I HOPE YOU DON'T HAVE
ANY PLANS AFTER YOUR SHIFT.
I FEEL LIKE BINGE WATCHING
A TV SERIES
UNTIL MY EYEBALLS FALL OUT
OF MY HEAD.
ELI:
NOW YOU'RE SPEAKING
MY LANGUAGE.
(PHONE RINGS)
IMOGEN:
OH. ONE SEC.
HELLO.
JACK:
YOU WERE RIGHT.
IMOGEN:
WHAT?
ABOUT ME BEING SCARED.
OKAY. WE'VE ALWAYS MOVED
AROUND SO MUCH,
THAT JUST- I NEVER SAW
THE POINT IN GETTING CLOSE.
AND WHILE THERE ARE PARTS
OF WHAT I SAID I BELIEVE,
NONE OF IT IS WORTH
LOSING YOU OVER.
I WANNA TAKE THAT LEAP.
OKAY? I LOVE YOU,
IMOGEN MORENO.
ELI:
OKAY, FOR TOTAL MIND
OBLITERATION
I RECOMMEND BATTLE-
SORRY.
JACK:
IMOGEN? ARE YOU THERE?
IMOGEN:
UM... YEAH.
I-I CAN'T REALLY SPEAK
RIGHT NOW BUT UM...
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
I'LL BE THERE AS SOON
AS I CAN.
UM, THAT WAS MY MOM...
SHE HAS LIKE THE FLU...
SO...UM...
I'M GONNA COME SEE YOU,
TOMORROW! WITH PIZZA!
OKAY.
(LAUGHS)
MAYA:
MILES!
MILES?
NOOOOO!
(SCREAMS)
(PANICKED BREATHING)
NO NO NO NO NO NO...
(DOOR CREAKS OPEN)
ZIG:
AGAIN?
MAYA:
WHAT IF I HAVE THIS DREAM
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE?
MILES THINKS IT'S ME.
THAT HE'S FINE AND I'M THE ONE
WITH THE PROBLEM.
HE'S MESSED UP, ZIG!
I KNOW IT!
ZIG:
MAYA, THIS IS TAKING OVER
YOUR LIFE.
MAYA:
YOU THINK I'M CRAZY.
ZIG:
I THINK YOU NEED HELP.
MAYA:
I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M GONNA TALK TO MOM TOMORROW.
IS THERE ANYTHING I CAN DO?
LET'S TRY THAT LULLABY AGAIN.
(BELL RINGS, STUDENTS CHATTER)
SHAY:
HEY FRANKIE! BACK HERE!
FRANKIE:
SORRY, SHAY.
I'M GONNA SIT UP FRONT TODAY.
HEY, IS ANYONE SITTING HERE?
ARLENE:
UM, NO. GO AHEAD.
FRANKIE:
YOU HAVE A LITTLE SOMETHING
ON YOUR DESK.
ARLENE:
THANKS.
FRANKIE:
YOU'RE INTO COMICS?
ARLENE:
YEAH. I'M PRETTY MUCH OBSESSED.
FRANKIE:
ME, TOO!
THE NEW BLACK ORCHID
TOTALLY BLEW MY MIND.
YEAH.
BUT YOU KNOW WHO'S THE MOST
AMAZING COMIC ARTIST?
HUNTER.
ARLENE: REALLY?
FRANKIE: HM-HMM.
FRANKIE: HUNTER...
HUNTER: YEAH.
WHY DON'T YOU SWITCH SEATS
WITH ME
SO YOU CAN TELL ARLENE
ABOUT THAT NEW LINEWORK
TECHNIQUE YOU WERE SHOWING ME?
YEAH. OKAY.
HEY.
♪ I have fallen down ♪
IT THAT-
IS THAT YOUR LAPTOP?
YEAH.
DO YOU GAME?
ARLENE: HM-HMM.
♪ Don't know why
Don't know where ♪
♪ Don't care
Unless it's all the same ♪