(TIRES SCREECH,
CAR DOOR SLAMS)
DALLAS:
WHAT IF IT'S LOCKED?
DREW:
AH, THEN WE BREAK IN.
DALLAS:
LIKE, SMASH THE WINDOWS?
DREW:
NO, DUMMY, I'M THE PRESIDENT.
I KNOW THE SECURITY CODE.
DALLAS:
THIS IS CRAZY.
DREW:
NO, THIS IS THE KIND OF THING
FRIENDS DO FOR EACH OTHER.
DREW:
IT SHOULD BE IN HERE,
SOMEWHERE.
DALLAS:
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS FOR ME?
DREW:
WHO SAID I'M DOING IT
FOR YOU?
THERE'S A BOATLOAD OF PEOPLE
WHO ARE MISSING THEIR PROM,
RIGHT?
DALLAS:
LOOK, I DIDN'T HAVE YOUR BACK
WHEN YOU GOT BANNED FROM PROM,
THAT WAS WRONG. I KNOW THAT.
DREW:
YOU DID WHAT YOU HAD TO DO.
YOU HAVE A GIRLFRIEND.
YOU'RE BOTH GOING AWAY.
PROM IS IMPORTANT. I GET IT.
NOW, WE GOTTA HURRY UP
AND GET OUT OF HERE
BEFORE THE SECURITY GUARD
DOES HIS ROUNDS.
DALLAS:
WHAT CAN I DO TO MAKE THIS,
RIGHT?
DREW:
(SIGHS) ALLI IS PRETTY SAD,
RIGHT?
DALLAS:
DEVASTATED.
DREW:
EVERYBODY IS PISSED, TOO?
DALLAS:
OH YEAH. BIG TIME.
DREW:
SO, IF WE TURN THE NIGHT AROUND
FOR EVERYONE AND WE'RE HEROES,
ALL I WANT IS FOR YOU TO
REMEMBER THAT WE DID THIS.
YOU AND ME, TOGETHER.
DALLAS:
OF COURSE, BRO.
IF WE PULL THIS OFF,
I WILL NEVER FORGET IT.
DREW:
NEVER SAY NEVER...
EVEN THOUGH I JUST SAID IT
TWICE RIGHT THERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT? YOU KNOW
WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY.
LET'S JUST GET OUT OF HERE.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Ohh... ohh... ohh... ♪
♪ I know I can make it though ♪
(SIREN WAILS IN THE DISTANCE)
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER
AND TRAFFIC)
ALLI:
I CANNOT BELIEVE DALLAS MESSED
UP THE BOAT BOOKING!
JENNA:
IT'S NOT THE END
OF THE WORLD.
ALLI:
YEAH, BUT IT'S THE END
OF OUR WORLD!
THIS IS THE LAST NIGHT OUR
WHOLE CLASS WILL EVER BE
TOGETHER!
CLARE:
COME ON. THAT'S NOT TRUE.
YOU STILL SEE PEOPLE
FROM YOUR YEAR, RIGHT?
ELI:
NOT REALLY... IF YOU'RE NOT
IN THE SAME PLACE,
IT'S HARD TO STAY CLOSE.
ALLI:
WHEN I TOOK THE REINS
OF THE PROM COMMITTEE,
ALL I WANTED WAS FOR
THE GRADUATING CLASS
TO HAVE THE MOST AMAZING NIGHT
OF THEIR ENTIRE LIVES.
WAS THAT TOO MUCH TO ASK?
CONNOR:
MAYBE A LITTLE AMBITIOUS.
ALLI:
AND NOW, WE HAVE NO BOAT,
NO PROM,
AND OUR CLASS IS WANDERING
AROUND THE STREETS
LIKE A BUNCH OF TAFFETA-
AND TUX-WEARING ZOMBIES!
CLARE:
WE COULD TRY TO FIX IT.
ALLI:
HOW? ROUND EVERYONE UP
AND CRAM THEM INTO THIS LIMO?
JENNA:
WELL, MAYBE WE CAN'T GET
EVERYONE,
BUT WE COULD START WITH THE
PERSON WHO SHOULD BE HERE
WITH US.
ALLI: DALLAS?
JENNA: YEAH.
WE HAVEN'T SPOKEN SINCE
OUR FIGHT AT THE DOCK.
CONNOR:
I THINK HE'S AT THE DOT.
HAVE YOU FINALLY TRANSCENDED
FROM MERELY GIFTED TO FULLY
PSYCHIC?
CONNOR:
NO, HE TEXTED ME-
"I'M AT THE DOT. BRING ALLI.
DON'T TELL HER I TOLD YOU TO."
OH.
(JENNA CHUCKLES)
DALLAS:
YOU REALLY THINK
THIS WILL WORK?
DREW:
IF YOU BUILD IT,
THEY WILL COME.
DALLAS:
WHAT'S THAT FROM?
THE BIBLE?
DREW:
NO, SOME KEVIN COSTNER MOVIE.
(CAR HONKS)
WILL YOU EVER DOUBT KEVIN
AGAIN?
♪ Whoa... whoa... ♪
ALLI:
THIS IS BEAUTIFUL.
CLARE:
YOU GUYS DID THIS?
LIKE, ON YOUR OWN?
DREW:
YEAH. WE JUST PICKED UP A FEW
THINGS FROM THE SCHOOL.
REDIRECTED A CATERING TRUCK
OR TWO.
MADE A QUICK STOP AT THE
HARDWARE STORE TO PICK UP SOME
EXTRA LIGHTS.
PLUS, WE DID HAVE AN ARMY
OF FLYING MONKEYS HELPING US.
SERIOUSLY THOUGH,
THIS IS IMPRESSIVE.
DALLAS:
YOU WANNA SEE IMPRESSIVE?
(CURTAIN SCRAPES BACK)
ALLI:
(GASPS) MY STARRY NIGHT PROM!
DALLAS:
IS IT EVERYTHING YOU WANTED?
WHAT?
ALLI:
I JUST IMAGINED MORE PEOPLE.
DALLAS:
OH, YOU MEAN LIKE THEM...
AND THEM.
(ALLI AND DALLAS LAUGH)
SAY WHAT YOU WANT
ABOUT SOCIAL MEDIA,
BUT IT MAKES IT VERY EASY
TO SPREAD THE WORD.
DREW:
ALL RIGHT, GRADUATING CLASS,
WHO'S READY TO PARTY?!
(CHEERING)
WOOOO!
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYS)
♪♪
IMOGEN:
PROM'S BACK ON, AT THE DOT.
LET'S JUST SKIP THIS
AND GO THERE.
BECKY:
NO! CAUSE NOW YOU ACTUALLY HAVE
SOMETHING TO INVITE HER TO.
IMOGEN:
COME ON, I'LL STREAK IT
WITH YOU.
BECKY:
(CHUCKLES) GO GET 'EM, TIGER.
GO GO GO!
(DOOR CLICKS OPEN)
DO THIS NOW
OR REGRET IT FOREVER!
JACK:
IMOGEN?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
IMOGEN: AH...
BECKY: GO GO GO!
ARE YOUR PARENTS HOME?
NO...
THEN...
JACK: WHAT IS THAT?!?
IMOGEN: IT'S A HOT DOG.
I KNOW IT SHOULD BE FLOWERS,
BUT THIS IS THE ONLY THING
I CAN FIND ON THE WAY.
YOU LIKE MUSTARD, RIGHT?
I'M SORRY I PRESSURED YOU TO
COME OUT WHEN YOU'RE NOT READY.
JACK:
NO, NO, I'M...
I'M SORRY I WALKED AWAY
FROM US...
IMOGEN:
AND IF I NEVER ASK YOU THIS,
I'LL ALWAYS KICK MYSELF AND
WONDER WHAT COULD HAVE BEEN.
AND IF YOU'RE WORRIED
ABOUT YOUR PARENTS,
WE'LL MAKE SURE TO FLY
UNDER THE RADAR...
JACK:
ASK ME WHAT?
WILL YOU PLEASE COME WITH ME
TO WHATEVER WEIRD,
PROM-TYPE THING IS HAPPENING
AT THE DOT RIGHT NOW?
I'D LOVE TO.
HERE.
JUST LET ME GO GET CHANGED.
AND HI, BECKY!
BECKY:
HIIIII...
(HAPPY SQUEALS, CLAPS)
♪ Tonight we step it up ♪
♪ Step it up and fly away ♪
♪ Got our hands up
in the clouds ♪
JENNA:
OH CLARE! GET IN SOME SHOTS!
CLARE:
I CAN'T.
I HAVE TO FIND ELI.
ALLI:
SO YOU CAN PICK PAINT COLOURS
FOR YOUR LOVE NEST?
(JENNA BLOWS AIR KISSES)
ACTUALLY I TOLD HIM I CAN'T GO
TO NEW YORK WITH HIM.
NOW HE'S BEING WEIRD.
WHOA, SERIOUSLY?
I CAN'T JUST BE THE GIRL WHO
FOLLOWS HER BOYFRIEND, RIGHT?
WELL, WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO DO INSTEAD?
I'M NOT SURE.
MY STUPID GRAD CARD THING
IS STILL BLANK.
GRADE NINE CLARE VOWED THAT
SHE WOULDN'T MAKE HIGH SCHOOL
ABOUT BOYS.
UM...
CLARE:
YOU CAN SAY IT; I FAILED!
I'M NOT GONNA MAKE
THAT MISTAKE AGAIN.
I HAVE TO BE MATURE ABOUT THIS.
ALLI:
YOU DIDN'T FAIL.
YOU TURNED INTO THE AMAZINGLY
AWESOME WOMAN STANDING IN FRONT
OF ME.
JENNA: (SIGHS)
AND BESIDES, YOU'RE NOT THE
ONLY ONE WHO'S MADE MISTAKES
IN HIGH SCHOOL.
ALLI:
UM, SPEAK FOR YOURSELF.
(ALL CHUCKLE)
I'M GOING TO MISS YOU GUYS
SO MUCH WHEREVER I AM.
AND WHEREVER YOU ARE,
WE'LL SUPPORT YOU.
AND IF ELI DOESN'T, HE DOESN'T
DESERVE CLARE EDWARDS.
(SMALL LAUGHS)
JENNA:
SO WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO SAY TO HIM?
CLARE:
I AM NOT SURE.
JENNA:
WELL, YOU BETTER FIGURE IT OUT.
ELI:
DANCE WITH ME?
♪ Let me see your hands
Up in the sky ♪
♪ You gotta raise 'em up
You gotta raise 'em high ♪
DREW:
THIS IS A NIGHTMARE.
HOW IS A GUY SUPPOSED
TO CHOOSE?
BECKY:
YOU AND DALLAS SAVED PROM.
DREW:
YEAH. MIGHT BE THE LAST MEMORY
WE GET TO MAKE TOGETHER
SINCE HE'S TAKING OFF TO PLAY
HOCKEY IN JAPAN IN THE FALL.
WOW, I HAVE NEVER SEEN YOU
SO SAD AROUND FOOD.
(BECKY CHUCKLES)
DREW:
LOOK, I-I'M SORRY I ASKED YOU
TO PROM THE WAY I DID.
TO BE TOTALLY HONEST,
IT WAS KINDA...
SUPER EMBARRASSING...
DREW:
I ONLY DID IT BECAUSE EVERYONE'S
TAKING OFF TO DO COOL STUFF.
I MEAN, DALLAS, CONNOR... YOU.
I MEAN, I DIDN'T WANT
TO BE ALONE ON PROM NIGHT, TOO.
AND YET, HERE YOU ARE
TALKING TO YOURSELF.
DREW:
HEY, I AM TALKING
TO MY FRIENDS.
(BECKY CHUCKLES)
NO BUT... YOU'RE RIGHT.
I HAVE TO ACCEPT IT.
EVEN THOUGH DALLAS AND I
PULLED ALL THIS OFF,
HE'S STILL LEAVING.
AFTER TONIGHT, EVERYONE
IS GONNA MOVE ON
AND FORGET OL' DREW TORRES.
BECKY:
HEY, DON'T SAY THAT.
WE STILL HAVE GRAD TOMORROW.
BUT AFTER THAT...
(BOTH LAUGH)
I'M JOKING!
NO ONE COULD EVER FORGET
DREW TORRES.
I KNOW I WON'T.
♪♪
♪ Wanna make you feel good ♪
IMOGEN:
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
TWO HOURS AGO
THERE WAS NO PROM,
NOW I'M HERE AT PROM, WITH YOU!
IT IS LIKE MAGIC!
JACK:
YEAH! BUT DON'T YOU THINK THE
WHOLE IDEA OF PROM IS... WEIRD?
IMOGEN:
WHAT? WHY?
JACK:
I MEAN, YOU SPEND HUNDREDS
OF DOLLARS ON SOME DRESS
YOU'LL NEVER WEAR AGAIN
TO COME AND EAT UNDERCOOKED
CHICKEN
AND DANCE TO TERRIBLE MUSIC?
IMOGEN:
WELL, MY DRESS WASN'T
THAT EXPENSIVE.
JACK:
WELL, I DIDN'T MEAN YOU
SPECIFICALLY...
YEAH, JUST... THE WHOLE PROM
INDUSTRIAL COMPLEX, YOU KNOW.
OH. OH, YEAH.
YEAH, TOTALLY.
(TAPS ON GLASS)
GUYS, COME ON! COME ON!
IMOGEN:
A NOVELTY DANCE!
WE NEED TO GO.
JACK:
I...
YEAH, UM,
I THINK I'LL PASS.
BUT YOU SHOULD GO
IF YOU WANT TO, OKAY?
IMOGEN:
UH... NO, IT'S OKAY.
I WORKED SO HARD
TO GET YOU HERE,
I WANT TO SOAK UP EVERY
LAST MINUTE OF JACK-NESS.
JACK:
I REALLY MISSED YOU, MARINO.
IMOGEN:
YEAH. DITTO.
♪♪
♪ Slow down ♪
♪ Everyone's been
slowin' down ♪
♪ I've been up all night ♪
WE CAN TALK, YOU KNOW.
IT WAS HARD ENOUGH
THE FIRST TIME.
WHAT?
ELI:
LONG DISTANCE, CLARE.
WE BARELY MADE IT THROUGH
THIS YEAR.
I KNOW.
AND STILL YOU WON'T COME
TO NEW YORK WITH ME?
PLEASE BELIEVE ME WHEN I SAY,
"IT'S NOT ABOUT YOU."
WHAT'LL YOU DO, INSTEAD?
I DON'T KNOW.
ELI:
SO YOU'D LITERALLY DO ANYTHING
THAN BE WITH ME?
THAT'S NOT WHAT THIS IS ABOUT,
OKAY? I LOVE YOU...
ELI:
I LOVE YOU.
BUT IF YOU DON'T WANT
TO BE WITH ME...
THEN MAYBE THAT MEANS YOU
DON'T WANT TO BE WITH ME.
IT'S NOT THAT SIMPLE.
I NEED TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT I WANT.
ELI:
YEAH. YOU DO.
AND SO DO I...
GOODNIGHT, CLARE.
♪ Will you take my heart?
Can you promise me
an afterlife? ♪
♪ Oh, when we lose our time ♪
(LAUGHING)
ALLI:
LAST NIGHT WAS AMAZING.
YOU GUYS REALLY KNOW
HOW TO THROW A GOOD PARTY.
DREW:
WELL, YOU KNOW IT! DOUBLE D
PARTY PLANNING SAVES THE DAY.
HERE FOR MY GOWN.
UM, DREW TORRES?
MS. PILL:
THE YOUNG MAN WHO BROKE
INTO THE SCHOOL LAST NIGHT?
DREW:
WOULD YOU BELIEVE THAT
IT'S THE OTHER DREW TORRES?
YOU KNOW THE PASS-CODES
ARE PERSONALIZED, RIGHT?
THE ONLY THING
I CAN'T BE SURE OF
IS WHO YOUR ACCOMPLICES WERE.
SO YOU HAVE A CHOICE;
GIVE THEM UP,
AND I MAY GO EASY ON YOU,
OR TAKE THE FULL PUNISHMENT
YOURSELF.
I ACTED ALONE.
MS. PILL:
THEN YOU WON'T BE NEEDING
ONE OF THESE.
WAIT, WAIT...
SO I CAN'T GRADUATE?!
MS. PILL:
YOU'LL STILL GRADUATE,
YOU JUST WON'T CROSS THE STAGE
WITH YOUR CLASSMATES.
DALLAS:
MISS PILL, THAT'S NOT FAIR.
MS. PILL:
YOU'RE ALL GONE AFTER TODAY.
I STILL HAVE A SCHOOL TO RUN.
AND NEXT YEAR'S STUDENTS
NEED TO KNOW THAT MY RULES
ARE FOR REAL.
SIMPSON:
CLARE EDWARDS!
IT'S A BIG DAY, HUH?
READY TO BE A HIGH SCHOOL
GRADUATE?
CLARE: YOU'RE BACK?
SIMPSON: UM, NO.
I'M JUST HERE TO SEE YOU GUYS
GRADUATE.
COME ON, YOU MUST BE
SO PROUD OF YOURSELF?
CLARE:
YAY ME!
SIMPSON:
YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT?
OH. SORRY. OLD HABITS.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO IT'S-
MY CARD IS EMPTY!
I COULD GO TO NEW YORK
AND BE WITH ELI.
IT WOULD BE NICE.
REALLY, REALLY NICE.
BUT I THINK IF I DID THAT
A PART OF ME WOULD WONDER
WHAT ELSE IS OUT THERE.
BUT GOING FORWARD
WITHOUT A PLAN,
WITHOUT KNOWING
WHAT'S NEXT IT'S...
(DEEP INHALE)
IT'S TERRIFYING.
SIMPSON: EMBRACE IT.
CLARE: WHAT?
SIMPSON:
I ACTUALLY THOUGHT I'D WORK
HERE 'TIL I RETIRED
TO FLORIDA ON A NICE PENSION.
BUT WHEN I WAS PUT ON INDEFINITE
LEAVE, I WAS DEVASTATED.
CLARE:
YOU SEEM OKAY NOW.
WELL, I'M ACTUALLY HEADING
TO HAITI FOR THE SUMMER
TO OPEN A SCHOOL.
CLARE:
REALLY? THAT'S AMAZING.
SIMPSON:
YES. AND IT NEVER WOULD HAVE
HAPPENED UNLESS I'VE BEEN OPEN
TO NEW OPPORTUNITIES.
YOU HAVE TO LEARN TO SAY "YES."
EMBRACE THE CARD.
THAT WHITE SPACE ISN'T
EMPTINESS. IT'S OPPORTUNITY!
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOU GUYS
CROSS THAT STAGE.
(BECKY GIGGLES)
IMOGEN:
I AM SO HAPPY TO SEE YOU!
BECKY:
YOU LOOK SUPER-CUTE IN THIS.
IMOGEN:
YOU THINK? I CAN'T PUT MY CAP
ON OVER MY BUN.
BECKY:
WELL, HOW ABOUT A WHOLE NEW
HAIRDO FOR A WHOLE NEW CHAPTER.
(BOTH LAUGH)
SO HOW WAS LAST NIGHT
WITH JACK?
DID YOU GUYS RE-AFFIRM
YOUR LOVE FOR EACH OTHER
AND HAVE THE BEST TEEN-MOVIE
WORTHY PROM NIGHT EVER?
NO. IT WAS ACTUALLY KIND
OF THE WORST.
WHAT?! WHY?!
JACK DOESN'T REALLY LIKE
THE SAME THINGS AS ME.
I SPENT ALL NIGHT WITH HER
WISHING
I WAS SPENDING THE NIGHT
WITH MY FRIENDS.
I DIDN'T EVEN GET TO CONGA.
BECKY:
AW, IMMY.
I KNOW HOW MUCH YOU LOVE
NOVELTY DANCES. I'M SORRY.
IMOGEN:
DON'T APOLOGIZE!
JACK WAS IMPORTANT TO ME,
BUT THAT WASN'T THE BEST
RELATIONSHIP I HAD AT DEGRASSI.
IF SOMEONE WERE TO TELL ME MY
BEST FRIEND IN HIGH SCHOOL
WOULD BE AN IMPOSSIBLY SUNNY
BLONDE CHRISTIAN GIRL FROM
FLORIDA
I WOULD HAVE TOLD THEM
THEY'RE CRAZY.
BECKY:
DITTO,
EXCEPT CHANGE BLONDE-CHRISTIAN
TO WACKY-DRESSING LESBIAN.
(CHUCKLING TURN TO TEARS)
OH NOOOOO. MY MASCARA!
WE HAVEN'T EVEN STARTED
TAKING PICTURES YET!
IMOGEN:
NO DON'T START CRYING,
OR YOU'RE GONNA MAKE ME CRY...
LIKE BAWL.
DALLAS:
AM I INTERRUPTING?
DID YOU TWO FINALLY... ?
(LAUGHING)
I JUST ALWAYS THOUGHT-
NEVERMIND.
THE CEREMONY'S ABOUT TO START,
AND I NEED YOUR HELP WITH
SOMETHING.
IMOGEN:
OKAY.
(APPLAUSE)
WOOO!
CONNOR:
...SO, YOU SEE, I LEARNED
MANY THINGS AT DEGRASSI,
BUT NOT FROM THE CLASSES,
THEY WERE TOO EASY.
(THE CROWD CHUCKLES)
THEY SAY IT IS THE JOURNEY
AND NOT THE DESTINATION.
WELL, "THEY" ARE WRONG.
IT IS NOT OUR MISTAKES ALONG
THE JOURNEY THAT MATTER,
IT IS WHERE WE END UP
THAT COUNTS.
CARL SAGAN SAID, "SOMEWHERE,
SOMETHING INCREDIBLE
IS WAITING TO BE KNOWN."
AND I WISH YOU ALL GOOD LUCK
IN FINDING THE DESTINATION
IN WHICH YOU ENCOUNTER
THE INCREDIBLE.
THANK YOU.
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
MR. ARMSTRONG:
OUR FIRST GRADUATE,
BECKY BAKER,
WILL PURSUE A BIOLOGY DEGREE
AT THE UNIVERSITY OF VERMONT
NEXT YEAR.
ALLI BHANDARI, OFF TO CAMBRIDGE
UNIVERSITY TO STUDY BIO
SCIENCES.
MIKE DALLAS, WHO HEADS TO JAPAN
TO PLAY PROFESSIONAL HOCKEY
FOR THE NIPPON PAPER CRANES.
OUR VALEDICTORIAN,
CONNOR DELAURIER,
OFF TO CAL TECH FOR APPLIED
PHYSICS AND AEROSPACE.
CLARE EDWARDS...
OH...
MR. ARMSTRONG:
TAKING A GAP YEAR?
OR AS I PREFER TO THINK OF IT,
OPENING MYSELF UP
TO EVERYTHING.
(APPLAUSE)
MR. ARMSTRONG:
JENNA MIDDLETON,
OFF TO THE LOS ANGELES SCHOOL
OF RECORDING ARTS
FOR A DEGREE
IN SOUND ENGINEERING.
OFF TO OCAD'S FACULTY OF ART,
IMOGEN MORENO.
AND NOW, WE'D LIKE TO TAKE A
MOMENT TO REMEMBER A STUDENT
WHO WOULD HAVE GRADUATED
THIS YEAR, ADAM TORRES.
♪♪
♪ Let me go ♪
♪ I don't wanna be your hero ♪
I'M SORRY YOU DIDN'T GET TO SEE
AT LEAST ONE OF YOUR SONS
CROSS THAT STAGE.
I TRIED.
YOU DID. I'M PROUD OF YOU
FOR FINISHING SCHOOL,
STAGE OR NOT.
THANKS, MOM.
AND I SAW THE PICTURES YOU TOOK
OF THAT PROM YOU MADE.
TOTALLY WORTH IT.
DREW:
WHAT? HOW DID YOU-
AUDRA:
HEY, I'M ON FACERANGE!
(SMALL CHUCKLE)
MR. ARMSTRONG:
LET'S HAVE A BIG ROUND
OF APPLAUSE
FOR THIS YEAR'S GRADUATES
OF DEGRASSI!
(APPLAUSE, CHEERING)
I THINK THIS IS WHERE
YOU THROW YOUR HATS.
(GASPS)
DALLAS:
I DON'T, IT JUST FEELS
LIKE SOMETHING'S MISSING.
IF THERE'S ONE THING I'VE
LEARNED IN MY SHORT TIME HERE,
IT'S THAT THIS CLASS
SHOWS SOLIDARITY.
NOW OUR FINAL GRADUATE,
AND STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT,
DREW TORRES.
(CHEERING, APPLAUSE)
AUDRA: GO.
MR. ARMSTRONG:
CONGRATS.
CAN WE DO THIS NOW?
DREW:
YEAH. GUYS, YOU READY?
ALL: YEAH.
DREW: READY?
THREE, TWO, ONE!
ALL:
WOOOOO!
YEAH!
(APPLAUSE, CHEERING)
(LAUGHING, CAMERA CLICKS,
HUM OF EXCITED CHATTER)
DREW:
YOUR SON MADE YOU PROUD!
AUDRA:
SURE DID. BOTH OF THEM.
DREW:
HEY MAN, FOR REAL, YOU...
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO DO THAT.
DALLAS:
YOU HAD MY BACK YESTERDAY
AND I HAD YOURS TODAY.
AND THAT'S THE WAY
IT'LL ALWAYS BE.
NO, BUT YOU'RE GONNA FACETIME
ME EVERY DAY IN JAPAN,
YOU KNOW, RIGHT?
ALLI:
ONLY AFTER I GET MY FACETIME.
DREW:
OHHHH... FIIIIIIINE.
BECKY:
HEY IMMY, GRAB MY HIPS.
IMOGEN:
BECKY BAKER,
WAS DALLAS, RIGHT?
HAVE YOU BEEN IN LOVE
WITH ME THIS ENTIRE TIME!
BECKY:
JUST DO IT, GOOFBALL.
♪ BA-BA BA-BA BA-HEY! ♪
IMOGEN:
ARE YOU STARTING
A NOVELTY DANCE FOR ME?!
BECKY:
WELL... YEAH!
♪ BA-BA BA-BA BA-HEY! ♪
ANYONE EVER TELL YOU
YOU HAVE PRETTY EYES?
THAT FEELS LIKE FOREVER AGO.
KIND OF LIKE YESTERDAY.
ELI, I KNOW WHO I AM WITH YOU.
BUT IT'S BEEN SO LONG, I'M NOT
SO SURE WHO I AM ON MY OWN.
ELI: I KNOW.
CLARE:
AND I NEED TO TAKE TIME
TO FIGURE IT OUT,
OR ELSE I'LL REGRET IT.
ELI: I KNOW.
CLARE:
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE PLAN IS,
BUT I'M GIVING MYSELF A YEAR.
ELI: I GET IT.
CLARE: YOU DO?
ELI:
LOOK, I'LL MISS YOU,
BUT IF I LOVE YOU NOW,
IMAGINE HOW MUCH I'LL LOVE
THE PERSON YOU BECOME.
I THINK WE CAN MAKE LONG
DISTANCE WORK.
(DEEP EXHALE)
I KNOW WE CAN.
YOU WANT TO GO
WITH YOUR FRIENDS.
CLARE: WELL...
ELI: PLEASE, GO.
WE'LL ALWAYS FIND OUR WAY BACK
TO EACH OTHER.
CLARE:
OKAY, BUT FIRST.
♪♪
ALL GRADS:
♪ BA-BA BA-BA BA-HEY!
BA-BA BA-BA BA-HEY! ♪
ELI: ALL RIGHT. GO.
CLARE: (GIGGLES) OKAY.
WE'LL MISS YOU DEG-RASS-I!
WE'LL MISS YOU DEG-RASS-I...