(CHEER SQUADS CHEER
AND CLAP)
♪♪
CLARE:
RARRRRRRRR!
BETTER WATCH OUT.
GONNA BURN THIS WHOLE PLACE
DOWN.
ALLI:
IT IS NINE A.M. ON A SATURDAY.
HOW ARE YOU THIS CHIPPER
AT NINE A.M. ON A SATURDAY?
MY MOM AND I TALKED ABOUT ME
GOING TO SCHOOL NEXT YEAR,
IN TOWN, PART-TIME,
AFTER THE BABY COMES.
AREN'T YOU WORRIED ELI'S GONNA
FIND OUT HE'S THE BABY'S FATHER
AND BURST THROUGH THOSE DOORS
WITH SOME BIG GESTURE
TO TRY AND WIN YOU BACK?
ZOE:
I HAVE A HUGE SURPRISE!
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
CAN YOU GIRLS SMELL THAT?
LOLA:
OHMIGOSH,
DID I FORGET DEODORANT?
ZOE:
IT'S THE SMELL OF VICTORY!
WE ARE THIS CLOSE
TO WINNING REGIONALS.
WOOOOOO!
(CLAPS)
WHERE ARE YOUR "WOOOO"S,
LADIES?
SHAY:
DID YOU MAKE
THAT FACERANGE PAGE,
BLAMING FRANKIE
FOR DEGRASSI NUDES?
ZOE:
SAY THAT A LITTLE LOUDER, SHAY.
I'M SURE THE WHOLE SCHOOL
DIDN'T HEAR YOU
TALKING ABOUT THE SCANDAL
WE'RE TRYING TO KEEP
ON THE D-L.
SHAY:
SHE'S GONNA GET SUSPENDED.
MAYBE EXPELLED.
HOW COULD YOU DO THIS TO HER?
I HAD TO.
DO YOU WANT THE COPS
KNOCKING DOWN YOUR DOOR,
ASKING WHY YOU SOLD
NAKED PHOTOS?
WOULD YOUR MOM LIKE THAT?
SHAY: SHE WOULD NOT.
ZOE: NEITHER WOULD MINE.
AFTER WE WERE BLACKMAILED BY
THAT CREEP - ALMOST EXPOSED -
I DID WHAT I HAD TO DO
TO PROTECT US.
IT WAS THE ONLY WAY.
SHAY: AND WHAT ABOUT FRANKIE?
ZOE: SHE'S RICH, RIGHT?
SO HER DAD WILL
JUST BAIL HER OUT.
BUT NONE OF US
HAVE THAT LUXURY.
HERE'S THE SURPRISE...
BOUGHT WITH THE LAST
OF THE DEGRASSI NUDES CASH.
WE EARNED THESE.
JUST LIKE WE EARNED
THE RIGHT TO BE HERE TODAY.
NOW LET'S PUT THESE ON
AND WIN THIS CHAMPIONSHIP!
WHO'S WITH ME?!
♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes! ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh... ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(VIDEO GAME SOUND EFFECTS)
HUNTER:
HAVE YOU SEEN FRANKIE?
I THOUGHT SHE SLEPT
AT GRANDMA'S.
NO, SHE'S SUPPOSED TO BE BACK
THIS MORNING.
DAD'S ON THE WARPATH.
I KNOW, IT'S HILARIOUS.
HUNTER:
YOU THINK IT'S HILARIOUS THAT
SHE BASICALLY RUINED DAD'S
CHANCES OF BECOMING MAYOR?
WELL, HE WANTED HER
TO TAKE THE BLAME
FOR THE WHOLE CHEERLEADING
SCANDAL. SHE DIDN'T DO IT.
GUY'S A JERK.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
I'LL BE SURE TO LET HIM KNOW
YOU FEEL THAT WAY.
HAVE YOU SEEN FRANKIE?
SHE'S GOT TO DO THIS
PRESS CONFERENCE NOW.
'KAY, LOOK, THE POLLS OPEN
MONDAY, DAD.
IT'S ALREADY TOO LATE.
JUST LEAVE HER ALONE.
NO, MONTHS... MONTHS
I HAVE BEEN WORKING ON THIS.
YEARS. SHE WILL NOT
SCREW IT UP FOR ME.
YOU'D REALLY RATHER BE A MAYOR
THAN A GOOD FATHER?
WELL, YOU UNGRATEFUL...
I GIVE YOU KIDS EVERYTHING!
YOU GIVE US EVERYTHING
EXCEPT YOUR LOVE AND RESPECT,
OR EVEN COMMON DECENCY.
(GLASS SMASHES)
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
(PANTING) HUNTER, ARE YOU-?
HUNTER, I'M SO SORRY-
AS IF YOU CARE WHO YOU HURT!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I HAVE HAD JUST-
MILES: GET OUT OF MY FAC-
(HARD HIT)
I... DIDN'T MEAN TO DO THAT.
(SIGHS)
(PHONE BUZZES)
THIS IS CAMPAIGN HEADQUARTERS.
I... I HAVE TO TAKE THIS.
HEY, ARE YOU OKAY?
THAT CAN NEVER HAPPEN AGAIN.
(SHAKY BREATH)
I'M SO EXCITED
TO FINALLY WATCH JACK CHEER.
DO YOU WANNA COME?
IS CLARE GONNA BE THERE?
YES. SHE'S WORKING
THE CONCESSION TABLE.
THEN, NO.
BESIDES, I WORK 'TIL FIVE.
AND I REALLY WANNA FOCUS
ON MY LATTE ART.
WELL, IT'S GOOD THAT YOU HAVE
SOMETHING TO KEEP YOUR MIND
OFF THINGS.
RIGHT...
ALL RIGHT, HERE YOU GO!
(GASPS) OH!
IT'S A PERFECT SWAN.
ELI:
IT'S A TULIP.
OH...
WHY ARE YOU TREATING ME
LIKE I'M FRAGILE?
WELL, YOU JUST HAVE A LOT
GOING ON LATELY.
I DIDN'T WANNA UPSET YOU.
OH YEAH, I GOT A TON GOING ON.
FOUR CUSTOMERS.
MIGHT FIRE UP THE SANDWICH
MAKER LATER.
WHAT'RE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU DON'T KNOW.
KNOW WHAT?
OKAY. I OVERHEARD ALLI
AND JENNA TALKING AND UM...
CLARE WAS WRONG
ABOUT THE BABY.
DREW ISN'T THE DAD...
YOU ARE.
(WEAKLY) YAY.
(SIGHS)
(APRON CLATTERS ON COUNTER)
ELI?
(RUNNING FOOTSTEPS,
DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
OKAY, FIRST,
HE SMASHED A MUG ON HUNTER.
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH: ON PURPOSE?
MILES: YES, YES!
HE THREW IT AT THE WALL AND
IT SMASHED AND THEN IT HIT HIM!
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH:
OKAY, CALM DOWN.
YOU'RE NOT LISTENING TO ME,
MOM!
I AM JUST TRYING TO GET A CLEAR
PICTURE HERE OF WHAT HAPPENED.
OKAY, WHAT HAPPENED...
IS THAT HE HIT ME.
OUT OF THE BLUE?
THAT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
I MEAN... WAS THERE
AN ALTERCATION?
I MEAN MAYBE YOU DID SOMETHING
THAT MIGHT HAVE PROVOKED HIM?
MILES:
THAT SHOULDN'T MATTER!
I'M HIS SON.
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH:
YEAH, BUT THE TWO OF YOU HAVE
BEEN AT EACH OTHER, LATELY.
I JUST FIND IT HARD TO BELIEVE
THAT HE WOULD DELIBERATELY,
INTENTIONALLY HURT YOU.
BUT HE DOES.
HE DOES ALL THE TIME.
HE IS A BULLY, MOM!
H-HE BULLIES EVERYONE.
TELL HER.
HUNTER:
I... I-I-I DON'T KNOW.
MILES DID KINDA PUSH HIM FIRST.
MILES: SERIOUSLY?!
HUNTER: YOU DID!
AND YOU'VE BEEN REALLY ON HIM
FOR BEING A BAD DAD.
BECAUSE HE IS!
OPEN YOUR EYES!
OKAY, LOOK.
WHY DON'T WE TALK ABOUT THIS
WHEN YOU HAVE HAD SOME TIME
TO COOL OFF.
MILES:
OKAY... WHATEVER. JUST KEEP YOUR
HEADS IN THE SAND.
I'LL DEAL WITH IT MYSELF.
♪ Here we go! ♪
♪ Hey! We gonna rock it till
the wheels fall off this ship ♪
♪ And if it stops we'll gonna
still be on this first ♪
♪ This is the party of the year
Can y'all feel this? ♪
♪ Can y'all feel this? ♪
♪ And then, you see,
you just dance... ♪
LOLA:
THEY ARE, LIKE, SO GOOD.
(PHONE CHIRPS)
♪ Dance, dance, dance... ♪
♪ Party of the year ♪
♪ You can rock,
You can rock this ♪
SHAY:
IS IT THE BLACKMAILER?
JACK:
HE'S NOT GONNA DO SOMETHING
BEFORE WE COMPETE, IS HE?
WHAT? NO!
IT'S... IT'S ZIG.
HE WANTS TO WISH ME
GOOD LUCK.
I AM SO SORRY I PUT YOU
THROUGH ALL THIS.
THANKS FOR STICKING WITH ME.
I KNOW WHAT I DID
TO FRANKIE WAS WRONG,
BUT I WANTED TO PROTECT YOU.
AND IT WAS THE ONLY OPTION.
(CROWD CHEERS LOUDLY)
ZOE:
TOGETHER, WE CAN BEAT THOSE
DRAGONS AND GO TO NATIONALS.
AND WHEN WE DO,
IT'LL ALL HAVE BEEN WORTH IT.
YOU GIRLS MEAN THE WORLD TO ME.
LOLA:
WELL, AREN'T YOU GONNA GO GET
YOUR GOOD LUCK SMOOCH FROM ZIG?
YOU GUYS DON'T MIND?
SHAY:
WE'RE NOT ON
FOR TWO WHOLE GROUPS.
GO GET THAT KISS!
(LAUGHS)
ALLI:
I THINK WE ACTUALLY LOST MONEY.
CLARE:
HOW'S THAT EVEN POSSIBLE?
ALLI:
NO ONE LIKES POPCORN,
I DUNNO.
CLARE:
SINCE WHEN? THAT DOESN'T EVEN
MAKE ANY SENSE.
ELI:
(BREATHING HARD)
CLARE: MAY I HELP YOU?
ELI: MAY I HELP YOU?
WITH WHAT?
OUR BABY!
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME
IT WAS MINE?
CLARE: (GASP OF OUTRAGE)
I TRIED, AND I THINK
IF YOU'LL RECALL,
YOU CALLED ME - WHAT WAS IT?
OH YEAH, A "WHORE."
O-OKAY, BUT YOU KNOW
I WOULDN'T HAVE DONE THAT,
IF YOU'D JUST TOLD ME.
BECAUSE YOU HAVE A LONG HISTORY
OF TOTALLY RATIONAL REACTIONS.
I ADMIT, I'VE HAD MY TROUBLES
IN THE PAST...
YOU PUNCHED DREW
THREE WEEKS AGO!
BUT-BUT I'M CALMER NOW...
AND I'M HERE.
CAN WE-CAN WE JUST AT LEAST
TALK ABOUT THIS, PLEASE?
THERE'S NOTHING
TO TALK ABOUT.
LOOK, I KNOW YOU'VE TAKEN CARE
OF MOST OF THE DETAILS, BUT...
CAN I AT LEAST TAKE YOU TO ONE
OF THOSE BREATHING CLASSES
OR... SOMETHING? I...
ELI: I WANNA HELP.
CLARE: I DON'T NEED YOUR HELP.
I DON'T WANT IT.
BUT I'M THE FATHER.
WHO HAS A HISTORY OF LASHING
OUT WHEN ANY LITTLE THING
GOES AWRY.
WITH A BABY, THERE ARE
A LOT OF LITTLE THINGS.
I JUST... I DON'T FEEL LIKE
I CAN TRUST YOU.
♪♪
(DESK DRAWER OPENS AND CLOSES)
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
(CLEARS HIS THROAT)
LOOK, MILES...
NO, NO, NO. I JUST...
I NEED YOU TO LISTEN.
I'M SO SORRY ABOUT
THIS MORNING-
YOUR APOLOGIES
ARE WORTHLESS.
YOU DON'T CARE ABOUT US.
NO, I LOVE YOU. I LOVE YOU
AND THE TWINS VERY MUCH-
BULL!
LOOK, WE...
WE ARE JUST YOUR PROPS!
AND WHEN WE DON'T BEHAVE
EXACTLY PERFECTLY,
YOU LASH OUT AT US.
DO YOU WANT ME TO TELL YOU
THAT I'LL-I'LL TRY HARDER?
YOU'VE BEEN SAYING THAT FOR
MONTHS. IT MEANS NOTHING.
MR. H: WHAT DO YOU WANT, MILES?
MILES: I WANT YOU TO MOVE OUT.
(LAUGHS INCREDULOUSLY)
OF MY OWN HOUSE?
YOU'RE HURTING YOUR FAMILY.
OKAY... (LAUGHS)
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
THIS IS GETTING TO BE
A LITTLE BIT MUCH,
MILES: NO, NO...
MR. H: SO I THINK WE'RE DONE.
TAKE-TAKE TAKE THIS
SERIOUSLY.
PLEASE. YOU WANNA JUST
LISTEN TO YOURSELF?
BECAUSE YOU ARE TALKING
NONSENSE AS USUAL.
STOP! STOP!
THIS ISN'T NONSENSE!
DO YOU EVER THINK THAT
MAYBE YOU'RE THE PROBLEM?
THAT MAYBE YOUR
EXEMPLARY BEHAVIOUR
HAS CAUSED YOUR SISTER
TO THINK THAT IT'S OKAY
TO RUN AWAY
FROM HER RESPONSIBILITIES?
DO YOU-
DO IT.
COME ON, MILES.
IF YOU'RE SERIOUS ABOUT THIS,
JUST DO IT.
YEAH. JUST AS I THOUGHT.
(SNIFFLES)
(APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS,
CROWD CHEERS IN THE DISTANCE)
(DOOR CLICKS OPEN AND SHUT)
ZOE:
ZIG?
HELLO?!
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
YOU HERE?
(LIGHTS CLICK OFF,
ZOE GASPS, NERVOUS)
(RATTLES DOORKNOB)
(SHAKY BREATH)
(EXHALES NERVOUSLY)
YOU CAN'T KEEP ME IN HERE.
(SPEED DIALLING BEEPS)
(PHONE RINGS)
ZOE:
(SCREAMS AND SCURRIES AWAY)
(SHAKY BREATHS)
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
SCARY-VOICED PERSON:
I WANTED YOU TO QUIT THE TEAM,
OR ELSE.
BUT YOU DIDN'T LISTEN.
ZOE:
YOU'RE THE BLACKMAILER.
SCARY-VOICED PERSON:
AND NOW WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
A LITTLE CHAT
ABOUT EVERYTHING YOU DID WRONG.
LOLA: NOBODY'S SEEN HER.
JACK: BUT WE'RE UP NEXT!
OKAY, HAS ANYONE TRIED
HER PHONE?
SHAY:
NO ANSWER.
DREW:
AND NEXT TO THE FLOOR IS...
THE DEGRASSI PANTHERS!
(CROWD CHEERS)
JACK:
WHAT DO WE DO?
OKAY, WE CANNOT DO
THE ROUTINE WITHOUT HER.
I KNOW!
I CAN DO HER PART!
THEN WHO WOULD DO YOUR PART?
ACTUALLY...
BECKY, HOW'S YOUR LEG?
BECKY:
FEELS PRETTY GOOD TODAY.
AND THE OTHER ONE?
(DOOR CLICKS OPEN)
MILES: FRANKIE?
(DOOR CLICKS SHUT)
(RATTLES DOORKNOB)
(BANGS ON DOOR)
MILES: FRANKIE!
MAYA: JUST GIVE ME ONE SEC.
MAYA:
MILES? EVERYTHING OKAY?
I... I DON'T NEED YOUR HELP.
WHAT, HERE TO WATCH
POWER CHEER?
HAVE YOU SEEN FRANKIE
OR HUNTER?
NO, BUT I'VE ONLY BEEN
IN THE GYM,
HELPING WITH THE MUSIC.
WHY?
APPARENTLY THEY'RE HERE.
LOOK, IF YOU SEE THEM,
CAN YOU GIVE THEM THIS?
WHAT IS IT?
A GOODBYE LETTER?
FOR REAL?
I WAS KIDDING.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
I'M GETTING IN MY CAR AND
DRIVING AS FAR AWAY
FROM MY FAMILY AS POSSIBLE.
WHY?
IS IT YOUR DAD AGAIN?
NO, NO, IT'S...
IT'S ME!
I'M THE LOSER
WHO CAN'T MAKE THIS ALL WORK.
I'M BAD FOR MY BROTHER
AND SISTER.
I MAKE MY DAD CRAZY...
(CRUMPLES FLYER)
I HATE HIM!
BUT YOU CAN'T JUST LEAVE
YOUR SIBLINGS WITH HIM.
NO, I... I WISH I COULD
DESTROY HIM, I DO.
I... WANT TO ERASE HIM,
SO THAT HE CAN'T HURT ANYONE
ELSE EVER AGAIN.
BUT I CAN'T... I...
CAN'T DO ANYTHING EXCEPT LEAVE.
(LIGHTER CLICKS)
MAYA: HEY!
(FIRE WHOOSHES)
MAYA:
STOP THAT, MILES!
STOP IT!
(FLAMES CRACKLE)
DROP THAT!
DROP IT RIGHT NOW!
MILES! DROP IT!
(FLAMES CRACKLE)
(FLAMES WHOOSH
AND CRACKLE)
(FLAMES CRACKLE,
BANNER FALLS)
MAYA:
MILES, WE HAVE TO GO.
WE HAVE TO GO RIGHT NOW!
WE NEED TO CALL 911!
(FLAMES CRACKLE)
MY TEAMMATES ARE WAITING FOR ME
IN THE GYM.
I NEED TO LEAVE.
SCARY-VOICED PERSON:
NOT UNTIL YOU ANSWER
MY QUESTIONS.
PLEASE!
I... I CAN'T LET MY GIRLS DOWN.
SCARY-VOICED PERSON:
WHY DID YOU START
DEGRASSI NUDES?
WHAT IS THIS?
SCARY-VOICED PERSON:
YOU NEEDED THE MONEY,
DIDN'T YOU?
ZOE:
IS THAT... PLASTIC?
SCARY-VOICED PERSON:
THEN YOU BLAMED THE WHOLE THING
ON FRANKIE,
SO YOU'D STILL GET TO COMPETE,
DIDN'T YOU?
ZOE:
GET OUTTA MY WAY, CREEP!
FRANKIE:
NO! ANSWER THE QUESTIONS!
ZOE:
SO... YOU'RE BEHIND THIS?
I KNEW YOU WERE
THE BLACKMAILER.
WINSTON:
NO, IT WAS I!
ZOE:
YOU GUYS THOUGHT I WOULD
INCRIMINATE MYSELF ON TAPE?
I'M NOT ABOUT TO LOSE
TO YOU LOSERS.
(FLAMES ROAR AND CRACKLE)
AGHHH!
DON'T TELL ME YOU LIT A FIRE,
TOO!
WINSTON:
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
(FLAMES CRACKLE)
FRANKIE:
WE DIDN'T DO THAT.
WHY DIDN'T I PAY ATTENTION
DURING THAT FIRE SAFETY
ASSEMBLY?!
(CROWD CHEERS)
♪ We are young ♪
♪ We are young... ♪
♪♪
(CROWD CHEERS)
(CROWD SHRIEKS AND CHEERS)
♪♪
(FIRE ALARM RINGS)
(CROWD CLAPPING AND CHEERING)
(CROWD MURMURS,
ALARM BLARES)
LOLA:
I DON'T REMEMBER THIS PART.
BECKY:
DO YOU SMELL SMOKE?
THIS IS NOT A DRILL.
GO! GO, GO, GO!
COME ON!
EVERYBODY OUT!
DREW:
EVERYBODY, PLEASE CLEAR THE GYM
IN AN ORDERLY FASHION!
MAYA:
YOU'RE STILL GONNA LEAVE?
MILES:
YEAH, MY DAD'S NOT GONNA LOVE
I ADDED ARSON TO MY RESUME.
HUNTER:
YOU'RE OKAY.
WHAT ABOUT FRANKIE?
MILES: WHAT ABOUT HER?
HUNTER: I THINK SHE'S STILL
IN THE SCHOOL.
MILES: WHERE?
HUNTER: I DON'T KNOW!
MILES:
FRANKIE!
(COUGHING)
MAYA: FRANKIE!
MILES: FRANK-
(COUGHING)
HEY, HAVE EITHER OF YOU
SEEN FRANKIE?
UGH! WHERE'S FRANKIE?!
(SCREAMING) HELP! HELP US!
IN HERE! (COUGHING)
WINSTON:
I-I-I CAN'T GET THROUGH.
EVERYONE MUST BE TRYING
TO CALL THEIR PARENTS.
FRANKIE:
STUFF THAT UNDER THE DOOR
TO STOP THE SMOKE.
ZOE:
WHAT IF THEY DON'T FIND US?
I DIDN'T EVEN HAVE A CHANCE
TO SAY BYE TO MY MOM
THIS MORNING.
FRANKIE:
BREATHE THROUGH THESE.
NOBODY'S GONNA DIE, OKAY?
WINSTON:
BUT NO ONE KNOWS WE'RE IN HERE.
(COUGHING)
(CRYING)
THIS IS MY FAULT!
I NEVER SHOULD HAVE TRIED
TO BLACKMAIL ANYONE!
I'M SORRY, I JUST TRIED
TO GET YOU ON THE TEAM, FRANKS,
AND MAKE YOU HAPPY.
(VOICE BREAKS)
IT JUST ALL GOT OUT OF HAND.
ZOE:
WE'RE ABOUT TO BURN ALIVE
BECAUSE YOU COULDN'T FIGURE OUT
A BETTER WAY
TO CHEER UP YOUR LITTLE
GIRLFRIEND?
FRANKIE:
NO, WE'RE IN HERE
BECAUSE OF YOU!
YOU PUSHED ME TO DO THIS!
HEY, I DIDN'T LOCK YOU
IN A ROOM DURING A FIRE.
FRANKIE:
NO, BUT YOU DID FORCE US
TO SEND NAKED PICTURES
OF OURSELVES
TO PEOPLE WE DIDN'T EVEN KNOW.
THOSE GIRLS WOULD HAVE SAID NO
IF THEY COULD STAND UP TO YOU.
(COUGHING)
OH, I'M THE SCARY ONE?
FRANKIE:
YEAH, YOU'RE A BULLY!
THE ONLY REASON
THEY STUCK AROUND SO LONG
IS BECAUSE THEY'RE WORRIED
ABOUT GOING TO JAIL.
WHEN POWER CHEER IS OVER,
THEY'LL PROBABLY NEVER
SPEAK TO YOU AGAIN.
(CHOKING AND COUGHING)
SO UNLESS YOU COME CLEAN
ABOUT THE WHOLE THING -
BE HONEST FOR ONCE
IN YOUR LIFE -
YOU'LL RUIN
YOUR "FRIENDS'" LIVES, TOO,
AND THEY'LL HATE YOU FOREVER.
WINSTON:
(COUGHING)
ALL:
(GASPING AND COUGHING)
♪♪
(CROWD MURMURS)
(SNATCHES OF VOICES
OVER POLICE RADIOS)
MILES:
FRANKIE! YOU'RE OKAY,
YOU'RE OKAY.
I'M SO SORRY.
LET'S GET YOU CHECKED OUT,
COME ON.
ZIG:
HEY! HEY, HEY, HEY.
SHOULDN'T YOU GET CHECKED OUT,
TOO?
ZOE:
YOU ACTUALLY CAME?
ZIG:
YEAH, TO WATCH YOU,
BUT YOU DIDN'T COMPETE.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
NOT EVEN CLOSE.
BUT IT WILL BE.
AFTER I TAKE CARE
OF SOMETHING.
OKAY, UH...
CAN WE HANG OUT SOME TIME?
YOU'RE BETTER OFF
WITHOUT ME.
EVERYONE IS...
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER,
LOW HUM OF RADIO CHATTER)
EXCUSE ME, OFFICER?
THERE'S SOMETHING
I NEED TO TELL YOU.
ELI:
HEY. I CAME AS SOON AS I HEARD
ABOUT THE FIRE. ARE YOU OKAY?
YOU MEAN THIS WASN'T
YOUR HANDIWORK?
OH YEAH, I BURNED DOWN
THE SCHOOL.
WHAT, YOU'RE SERIOUS?
NO, I GUESS NOT.
BUT YOU HAVE DONE
CRAZY STUFF BEFORE.
LOOK, I'M NOT THAT GUY
ANYMORE.
I'VE CHANGED.
I'VE MATURED.
LOOK. THIS IS MY PAYCHECK
FROM WORK.
I'VE SIGNED IT OVER TO YOU.
USE IT FOR BABY STUFF, OKAY?
AND THIS IS A SCHEDULE
FOR THE PARENTS...
AND TOTS PROGRAMS
AROUND HERE.
I CIRCLED SOME OF THEM
THAT LOOKED GOOD.
AND THIS IS CLARENCE.
IT'S MY STUFFED WOLF
FROM WHEN I WAS A BABY.
I... I WANT HIM TO HAVE IT...
OR HER.
HIM.
HIM! OKAY.
LOOK, LOOK, I... I TRIED TO FIND
SOMETHING THAT WOULD MAKE YOU
TRUST ME,
BUT APPARENTLY
THAT'S REALLY, REALLY HARD!
SO ALL I CAN TELL YOU IS THAT...
I WANT TO BE SERIOUS
AND I PROMISE TO EARN
YOUR TRUST.
I WANT TO BE PART
OF HIS LIFE.
OKAY.
REALLY?
YOU'RE RIGHT.
HE SHOULD KNOW HIS DAD...
AND I COULD USE YOUR HELP.
(CHUCKLES)
FRANKIE:
I'VE BEEN CLEARED.
WE CAN GO.
(SIRENS WAIL IN THE DISTANCE,
CAR DOOR OPENS NEARBY)
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO HOME.
I ASSUME WE'VE HAD ENOUGH
BAILING ON RESPONSIBILITIES
FOR ONE DAY.
WHAT ABOUT, "I'M GLAD
YOU'RE ALIVE, FRANKIE"?
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
WELL, I MEAN, OBVIOUSLY.
(LAUGHS)
I CAME HERE FOR YOU,
YOU KNOW!
TO PROVE TO YOU I DIDN'T
DO THAT HORRIBLE STUFF.
I TORMENTED ANOTHER GIRL.
DAD, I NEARLY DIED!
MILES:
SEE? ALL HE CARES
ABOUT IS HIMSELF.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
YOU KNOW WHAT? I'VE HAD
JUST ABOUT ENOUGH
OF THAT KIND OF TALK.
CAN WE JUST DISCUSS THIS
AT HOME.
BUT IT'S TRUE.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH: HUNTER...
HUNTER: I SAW HIM HIT MILES.
FRANKIE: HE HIT YOU?
MR. H: IT WAS A HEATED MOMENT.
HUNTER:
NOT THAT HEATED.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
THIS IS WHY I WANTED HIM
OUT OF THE HOUSE.
JUST... (CLEARS THROAT)
(WHISPERS) GET IN THE CAR.
FRANKIE:
NO. WE'LL ONLY GO HOME
IF MOM COMES TO PICK US UP.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
YOU'RE GONNA CAUSE THIS KIND OF
SCENE SO CLOSE TO THE ELECTION?
OH, THIS IS LUDICROUS.
MILES: JUST GO.
MR. HOLLINGSWORTH:
ALL RIGHT.
IT'S GONNA BE OKAY.
MAYA: HEY.
MILES: HEY.
HOW'D THAT GO?
I THINK IT'S GONNA BE
ALL RIGHT.
THANKS FOR NOT
GIVING UP ON ME.
NO PROBLEM.
I'M JUST GLAD I DON'T HAVE
TO WORRY ABOUT YOU ANYMORE.
STILL... FEEL FREE TO CHECK IN
ON ME EVERY NOW AND AGAIN.
(LAUGHS)
FRANKIE:
SO IT TURNS OUT BEING TRAPPED
IN A FIRE MAKES YOU STARVING.
WANNA GO GRAB SOME FOOD,
TOGETHER?
MILES:
YEAH, I'D REALLY LIKE THAT.