YOU WANNA WAX DREW'S CHEST?!
YEAH, FOR A CHEER FUNDRAISER!
YES, OR NO?
I HAVE A LOT OF OTHER IDEAS.
I ONLY HAVE ONE.
(FRANKIE LAUGHS)
ARE YOU TRYING TO SEE MY-
WHAT? N-NO!
OKAY, YES,
BUT IT'S NOT MY FAULT.
I'M A GUY, WE'RE LIKE,
PROGRAMMED TO DO THAT.
LOOK, I LIKE YOU, WINSTON,
BUT I DON'T KNOW
IF I'M READY FOR THAT YET.
I MEAN, WE'VE ONLY BEEN
DATING FOR ONE MONTH,
TWO WEEKS AND 4 DAYS, RIGHT?
SOMEONE'S BEEN COUNTING.
PLUS, I DON'T WANNA GET CAUGHT
IN A COMPROMISING POSITION
BY MY PARENTS,
WHO ARE DOWNSTAIRS!
(SIGHS)
YOU MEAN, LIKE THIS?
FRANKIE: YEAH!
WINSTON:
FRANKIE HOLLINGSWORTH
IS SO TICKLISH!
(FRANKIE GIGGLES)
HUNTER:
I MAY VOMIT.
BUZZ OFF, HUNTER!
MILES:
FRANKS, MOM'S LOOKING FOR-
AHEM! FOR YOU.
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH:
HON, WE NEED YOU AT YOUR DAD'S
CAMPAIGN EVENT TOMORROW...
THIS ISN'T WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE.
YEAH!
WINSTON!
WINSTON: I'LL SEE MYSELF OUT.
NO MORE BOYS IN YOUR ROOM.
BUT WINSTON AND I WEREN'T
DOING ANYTHING.
AND EVEN IF WE WERE,
I SHOULD BE ALLOWED,
BECAUSE, ONE,
I'M FOURTEEN,
AND TWO, MILES HAS DONE
WAY WORSE.
HONEY, THIS IS DIFFERENT.
FRANKIE: WHY?
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH:
MILES CAN'T GET PREGNANT.
SOUNDS LIKE A CHALLENGE.
NEITHER CAN I,
BECAUSE I'M NOT HAVING SEX!
I'D LIKE TO KEEP IT THAT WAY
FOR THE FORESEEABLE FUTURE.
BUT MAYBE YOU CAN
JUST CONSIDER-
NO, FRANKIE!
THIS CONVERSATION IS OVER.
(SIGHS ANGRILY)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
OH, KISS ME NOW, I GOT US
ROLLER DERBY TICKETS!
YOU RULE!
I LOVE ROLLER DERBY!
JACK:
ME TOO.
BUT WHAT ABOUT BECKY?
CAN WE LEAVE HER ALONE
RIGHT NOW?
I DON'T KNOW.
SHE'S JUST SO SAD.
BECKY:
YOU KNOW I CAN HEAR YOU,
RIGHT?
IMOGEN:
YEAH...
I'M SORRY I CALLED YOU
PATHETIC.
YOU DIDN'T.
JACK:
BUT WE DON'T BLAME YOU
FOR BEING A LITTLE BIT OFF.
I MEAN, YOU DID
JUST FIND OUT
YOUR BOYFRIEND KNOCKED
ANOTHER GIRL UP.
EX-BOYFRIEND.
CLARE:
ARE YOU HIGH RIGHT NOW?
NO, OF COURSE NOT!
IT IS A MILLION DOLLAR IDEA!
CLARE:
HOW?! WHAT USE WOULD
A BIRD POSSIBLY HAVE-
AND, I'M DONE WITH
BEING PATHETIC.
I DON'T SEE DREW
MOPING AROUND
BECAUSE HE TOTALLY MESSED
EVERYTHING UP,
SO WHY SHOULD I?
WHICH MEANS I'M COMING
TO ROLLER DERBY TONIGHT,
WHATEVER THAT IS.
YOU WON'T FEEL LIKE
A THIRD WHEEL?
NO, BECAUSE I'M GOING
TO BRING SOMEONE.
WELL, HOW ARE YOU GONNA FIND
A DATE THIS FAST?
HOW DOES ANYONE DO
ANYTHING THESE DAYS?
TO THE INTERNET!
(THEY LAUGH)
TINY:
(LAUGHS) NOPE, NOT YET.
OH...
WHERE'S MILES?
HE'S IN THIS CLASS.
YOU THINK MAYA KNEW?
MAYBE SHE TURNED HIM!
WHAT ARE WE TALKING ABOUT?
WELL, UM...
MILES IS GAY!
YEAH, MAYBE.
YOU KNOW, HE'S PROBABLY
KISSING TRISTAN RIGHT NOW!
(MAKES KISSING NOISES)
CAN IT DUMBASSES,
HE'S JUST GOING THROUGH
SOME CRAP RIGHT NOW.
GRACE:
OH, MATLIN.
STILL HOLDING OUT HOPE
FOR MONEY-BAG MILES?
SO, YOU REALLY SAW NO SIGNS?
NO OBSESSION WITH DANCE MUSIC?
GUYS, THIS SERIOUSLY
ISN'T FUNNY!
GRACE:
YOU'RE TELLING ME!
WHEN DID WE DECIDE HOMOPHOBIC
JOKES WERE OKAY AGAIN?!
WHAT YEAR IS THIS?
MILES HAS BEEN ACTING
WEIRD LATELY.
SKIPPING CLASS AND STUFF,
I'M WORRIED SOMETHING'S WRONG.
BECAUSE HE'S GAY?
WHO'S HOMOPHOBIC NOW?
(BELL RINGS)
(CHAIRS CREAK)
LET'S TALK FUNDRAISING, LADIES!
WE NEED IDEAS,
BECAUSE TO BE THE BEST,
WE NEED TO HAVE THE BEST STUFF,
THE BEST UNIFORMS-
ARE YOU GUYS ALLOWED TO
HAVE BOYS IN YOUR ROOMS?
DUH, WHERE ELSE AM I SUPPOSED
TO MAKE OUT WITH THEM?
NO BOY IS WORTHY OF MY ROOM.
HOW DO I SHOW MY MOM
I DESERVE TO BE TREATED
THE SAME AS MY STUPID BROTHERS?
THAT I SHOULDN'T HAVE TO BE
A PERFECT LITTLE GIRL?
WHAT A DOUBLE STANDARD.
PLUS, NOW WINSTON AND I GET
LESS TIME TOGETHER,
WHICH MEANS WE'LL START
TO GROW APART,
AND THEN HE'LL PROBABLY
TOTALLY BREAK UP WITH ME!
SHAY:
OKAY, CRAZY-FACE,
CALM DOWN!
YEAH, JUST OOMFCHAT HIM
SOME SEXY PICTURES.
THAT'LL KEEP HIM HAPPY.
ZOE:
YOU GIRLS HAVE SOMETHING
TO SHARE?!
YEAH, I'D LIKE
TO SHARE MY RAGE
OVER THE VICIOUS DOUBLE
STANDARDS FOR GIRLS AND BOYS.
NOW, THIS I WANNA HEAR!
FRANKIE:
GREAT EXAMPLE, OOMFCHAT.
GUYS GET EXACTLY WHAT
THEY WANT: BOOBS.
WHAT DO GIRLS GET?
UH, I DON'T WANT TO SEE
JUNK PICS.
FRANKIE:
IF WE DO ANYTHING EVEN
A LITTLE BIT SEXY,
WE GET IN TROUBLE!
BOYS ARE THE SEX-CRAZED IDIOTS,
AND WE'RE THE ONES
GETTING CALLED NAMES!
GUYS THINK THEY HAVE A RIGHT
TO WHATEVER THEY WANT,
WHENEVER THEY WANT IT,
AND NO ONE WILL EVER THINK
DIFFERENTLY OF THEM.
FRANKIE:
YEAH, EXACTLY!
ZOE:
BUT GIRLS CAN ONLY BE
TWO THINGS:
"PERFECT LITTLE GIRLS," OR-
JACK: TROLLOPS.
FRANKIE: EXACTLY!
ZOE:
WELL, MAYBE IT'S TIME
WE TURN THIS ON ITS HEAD.
MAYBE IT'S TIME WE GET
WHAT WE WANT FOR A CHANGE!
EXACTLY!
WAIT, WHAT DO WE WANT?
MONEY!... DUH!
BECKY:
THERE HAS TO BE A BETTER GUY
OUT THERE FOR ME THAN DREW.
JACK:
YEAH, OKAY...
SO, WOULD YOU LIKE
TO HAVE KIDS?
WELL, NOT WHILE
I'M IN HIGH SCHOOL!
IMOGEN: HOLLA!
BECKY: WHOOP! WHOOP!
JACK: MMM! MM! MM! MM!
JACK: EVENTUALLY.
BECKY: YEAH.
JACK:
OKAY. AND HOW IMPORTANT
IS GOD IN YOUR LIFE?
WELL, HE HASN'T BEEN THERE
FOR ME LATELY-
BECAUSE HE WORKS
IN MYSTERIOUS WAYS!
I WILL PUT
"EXTREMELY IMPORTANT."
HOW CLOSE ARE YOU
TO YOUR FAMILY?
UH,
THEY USED TO BE MY ROCK...
AND THEY WILL BE AGAIN!
SOUNDS LIKE
"EXTREMELY CLOSE."
OKAY, LAST QUESTION!
UH, WHAT COLOUR BEST
DESCRIBES YOU?
RED, YELLOW, PURPLE,
OR GRAY?
DUH, YELLOW!
ARE YOU SURE?
BECAUSE I'VE BEEN FEELING
PRETTY BLUE LATELY.
LOOK, I KNOW THINGS
ARE WONKY RIGHT NOW,
BUT THIS IS OPERATION
"RESET BECKY," REMEMBER?
YELLOW EQUALS SUN AND SUN
EQUALS OLD BECKY, ERGO...
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YELLOW IT IS!
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
ONE HUNDRED PERCENT MATCH!
JACK:
THAT, LIKE, NEVER HAPPENS.
OKAY... CHRISTIAN,
GOOD FAMILY,
LOVES CHARITY WORK,
THINK CHRIS LIKES ROLLER DERBY?
IMOGEN:
THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
TO FIND OUT.
OKAY!
JACK AND IMOGEN:
YEAH! YAY!
(ALL LAUGH)
(WHISTLE BLOWS, BALL BOUNCES)
MILES?
MILES!
MILES, STOP!
MILES, NO!
(SCREAMS, HEAVY BREATHING)
(STARTLED GASPS)
(STUDENTS WHISPER)
GIRL:
SPAZ, YOU SCARED ME!
(BELL RINGS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
INTENSE DAY DREAM.
NEED TO TALK?
I WAS JUST DREAMING ABOUT...
THIS ALGEBRA TEST
I'M REALLY STRESSED ABOUT.
REALLY?
IT SEEMED PRETTY INTENSE FOR
A DREAM ABOUT SCHOOLWORK.
YEAH, WHAT CAN I SAY, MATH'S
NOT MY FAVOURITE SUBJECT.
OKAY, BUT JUST REMEMBER,
I'M ALWAYS AROUND,
AND, TALKING HELPS!
(SIGHS)
LET'S SEE IF YOUR BRILLIANT
PLAN CAN WORK, FRANKIE.
FRANKIE:
WHAT PLAN?
(COMPUTER KEYS CLICK)
GRACE?
(SIGHS)
GRACE!
LOVE THE PIERCINGS.
...AND YOUR SHIRT.
TIME IS MONEY, LADIES,
YOU'VE GOT TEN SECONDS. TEN.
FRANKIE, TELL HER ALL THAT
FEMINIST OOMFCHAT
MUMBO-JUMBO YOU SAID
AT PRACTICE.
GRACE:
NINE.
I WAS JUST SAYING IT SUCKS
THAT GIRLS ARE EXPECTED
TO OOMFCHAT NUDES TO GUYS
AND GET NOTHING BUT TROUBLE
IN RETURN.
SHE THINKS WE NEED TO CHARGE.
HOLD UP, I DON'T WANNA
OOMFCHAT NUDES FOR MONEY!
OKAY, WELL, I DO!
LAST TERM, GUYS DISTRIBUTED
NAKED PHOTOS OF ME
WITHOUT MY CONSENT.
NOW, IF THEY WANT THEM,
THEY'LL HAVE TO PAY.
GRACE:
EIGHT. AS MUCH AS I LOVE
A FEMINIST RECLAIMING OF NUDES,
WHAT DOES THIS HAVE
TO DO WITH ME? SEVEN.
WE NEED A WEBSITE THAT'LL SEND
ANONYMOUS OOMFCHAT REQUESTS.
CAN YOU DO THAT?
GRACE:
OFF-SHORE SERVERS, PROXIES,
SIX, DOABLE.
FRANKIE:
ZOE, NO, THIS IS CRAZY!
WE ALSO NEED TO TAKE
PAYMENT SECRETLY.
GRACE:
FIVE. PRE-PAID CREDIT CARDS
SHOULD WORK. FOUR.
ZOE, NO, WHAT IF SOMEONE
SCREEN GRABS THE PICS?
WHO CARES?!
NO ONE WILL KNOW IT'S US!
GRACE:
THREE!
ZOE:
THIS IS A WAY TO FIX
THE DOUBLE STANDARD.
BESIDES, DIDN'T YOU SAY
YOU WANTED TO SHOW YOUR MOM
THAT YOU'RE NOT
A "PERFECT LITTLE GIRL?"
GRACE: TWO.
I DIDN'T MEAN LIKE THIS!
GRACE:
ONE, TIME'S UP, POM-POMS.
WAIT, WILL YOU HELP US?
ONLY IF I KEEP TWENTY PERCENT.
LIKE I SAID, TIME IS MONEY.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
FINE.
PLEASURE DOING BUSINESS.
FRANKIE, YOU JUST SAVED
POWER CHEER!
YAY ME.
LADIES, I HAVE
THE PERFECT FUNDRAISER:
NUDE OOMFCHATS FOR MONEY!
JACK:
YOU'RE JOKING!
FRANKIE:
YOU'D THINK, BUT NO.
ZOE:
IT'S SAFE, ANONYMOUS,
AND IT'LL MAKE US ALL THE MONEY
WE NEED, EASILY.
IT ALL STARTS WITH
A SECRET WEBSITE.
BOYS PICK A GIRL
FROM A LIST OF HANDLES.
THEY PAY WITH A PREPAID
CREDIT CARD,
AND ENTER AN OOMFCHAT USERNAME.
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
THAT SENDS THE GIRL A REQUEST.
NOW, IT'S PICTURE TIME.
TO PROTECT US,
THERE ARE RULES.
NO FACES,
NO IDENTIFYING BACKGROUNDS,
JUST TAKE A PIC,
SEND IT BACK.
AT A DOLLAR A SECOND,
WE'LL HAVE ALL THE MONEY
WE NEED IN NO TIME.
LET'S VOTE,
ALL IN FAVOUR?
WAIT,
WHAT IF PEOPLE FIND OUT?
LIKE OUR PARENTS,
OR OUR TEACHERS?
NO ONE WILL KNOW IT'S US.
FRANKIE:
BUT WE WILL!
ZOE:
GIRLS, I KNOW THIS SEEMS CRAZY.
BUT GUYS TREAT US LIKE OBJECTS
EVERY SINGLE DAY.
IT'S GROSS,
AND TOTALLY UNFAIR.
AT LEAST THIS WAY,
WE GET SOMETHING IN RETURN.
THIS IS OUR WAY
OF FIGHTING BACK.
I AM NOT JUST "WAITING AROUND
FOR THE RIGHT GUY."
WE DON'T NEED TO SELL
OUR BODIES,
THERE ARE OTHER WAYS
TO MAKE MONEY!
ZOE:
THIS ISN'T JUST
ABOUT THE MONEY.
IT NEEDS TO BE UNANIMOUS.
DON'T MAKE US THROW YOU,
AND NOT CATCH YOU.
GIRL:
COME ON!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
I CAN'T BELIEVE
WE'RE DOING THIS.
ZOE:
ME NEITHER!
THIS IS GREAT!
OH, AND ONE THING:
NO ONE OUTSIDE THIS ROOM
CAN KNOW.
(DOOR SLAMS)
HI...
CAN YOU COME AND SIT DOWN
FOR A SECOND, SWEETHEART?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOU'RE FREAKING ME OUT.
MS. GRELL CALLED ME TODAY.
SHE SAID YOU HAD SOME KIND
OF NIGHTMARE IN CLASS?
YOU CAN TELL ME,
WHATEVER IT IS.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT MILES.
HAVE YOU TALKED TO HIM?
YEAH, BUT HE WON'T
SAY ANYTHING.
MAYBE HE'S SCARED TO TALK.
MAYBE IT'S ALL IN MY HEAD.
BUT WHAT IF IT'S NOT?
AND WHAT IF HE LIKE...
LIKE, HURTS HIMSELF?
OH, SWEETHEART!
THAT'S WHAT I WAS
DREAMING ABOUT,
THAT'S WHAT I'M REALLY
SCARED OF.
OF COURSE YOU ARE!
WHAT DO I DO?
FOR NOW,
YOU JUST SIT HERE,
AND YOU LET ME
TAKE CARE OF YOU.
(SIGHS)
IT'S OKAY.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(WHISTLE BLOWS, FANS CHEER)
ROLLER DERBY PLAYER:
MOVE IT!
OH, THIS IS SO COOL!
THIS IS AMAZING!
THIS IS AMAZING,
YOU WEREN'T KIDDING,
THIS IS WICKED FAST!
OH! OH!
LET'S GO GET SOME SNACKS,
I THINK I SAW CANDY.
(LAUGHS)
ISN'T THIS AWESOME?
I LOVE TRYING NEW THINGS,
AND MEETING NEW PEOPLE!
UH, SO,
DO YOU DO THIS OFTEN?
BLIND DATES? NO, I'M PRETTY
BUSY AT SCHOOL.
I RUN STUDENT COUNCIL,
THE DRAMA CLUB, RUN TRACK,
PLUS I'M SUPER INVOLVED
AT MY CHURCH.
I JUST HATE TO BE IDLE.
BECKY:
YEAH, ME, TOO.
THAT'S WHY I STARTED A POWER
CHEER TEAM THIS TERM.
CHRIS:
THAT'S AMAZING,
DO YOU LOVE IT?
I DID, UNTIL I BROKE
MY LEG IN A FALL,
AND HAD TO QUIT THE TEAM.
WHAT CAUSED YOUR FALL?
AN AMAZING STUNT?
I WAS ACTUALLY
A BIT DISTRACTED.
BY GOOD NEWS?
MY BOYFRIEND GOT ANOTHER
GIRL PREGNANT.
AT LEAST YOU REALIZED
WHAT KIND OF PERSON HE WAS
BEFORE YOU GOT TOO INVESTED,
AND HEY, MORE TIME WITH THAT
FAMILY YOU LOVE SO MUCH!
(LAUGHS UNEASILY)
(PLAYING A TUNE ON THE CELLO)
♪♪
(DOOR SLAMS)
MILES:
WHO THE HELL DO YOU THINK
YOU ARE?!
MILES?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WHAT AM I TALKING ABOUT?!
HOW ABOUT THE FACT THAT
YOU HAD YOUR MOM CALL MY MOM,
AND TELL HER THAT YOU WERE
WORRIED I MIGHT HURT MYSELF?!
OH MY GOD, MILES,
I'M SO SORRY,
THAT'S NOT WHAT I SAID!
I DIDN'T KNOW
SHE WAS GONNA DO THAT!
ARE YOU SERIOUS, MAYA?!
IF YOU'RE GONNA ACT
LIKE A CRAZY PERSON,
AT LEAST OWN UP TO IT,
OKAY?
NO, I SWEAR,
I HAD NO IDEA!
I WAS JUST TELLING HER
HOW WORRIED I WAS ABOUT YOU!
HOW MANY TIMES DO I HAVE
TO TELL YOU THAT I'M FINE?!
UNTIL I BELIEVE YOU,
I GUESS!
WELL THEN,
THAT IS YOUR PROBLEM!
GET OVER ME, MAYA, AND STAY
THE HELL OUT OF MY LIFE!
(DOOR SLAMS)
(SOBS)
WOW...
MONEY-BAGS IS A DORK.
I JUST KEEP MESSING
EVERYTHING UP!
HEY,
IF IT WEREN'T FOR YOU,
I'D STILL BE SQUATTING
IN THAT HOUSE OR WORSE.
SO YOU DON'T THINK
I'M A TOTAL BASKET CASE?
WELL... I MEAN, YOU'RE
DEFINITELY INSANE.
BUT YOU MEAN WELL.
THANKS.
(MAYA SOBS)
(LOUD CHEERING)
IMOGEN:
SO, DISH, ARE YOU AND CHRIS
GONNA GET MARRIED,
AND HAVE A BILLION BLONDE
BUBBLY BABIES?
BECKY:
I SURE HOPE NOT!
IMOGEN:
WHAT? WHY? WHAT'S WRONG?
I THOUGHT YOU LIKED HIM!
I HATE HIM, LIKE,
I REALLY, REALLY HATE HIM!
IMOGEN:
BUT HE'S ACTUALLY THE PERFECT
MATCH FOR YOU!
OKAY, THEN MAYBE
I HATE MYSELF!
HEY!
PLEASE,
TELL ME I'M NOT THAT-
JACK: POSITIVE?
BECKY: ANNOYING!
I WAS LIKE THAT BEFORE,
WHEN EVERYTHING WAS SIMPLER,
BUT I'M NOT THAT
PERSON ANYMORE!
WELL, IF HE'S NOT THE RIGHT
GUY FOR YOU, THEN WHO IS?
I-I NEED TO GO.
WAIT, NO, HOW ARE YOU GONNA
BREAK THE NEWS TO CHRIS?
WHOOO!
BECKY: I WAS KINDA HOPING
YOU COULD DO IT FOR ME,
IMOGEN: NO!
DON'T WORRY, HE'LL JUST SEE IT
AS ANOTHER OPPORTUNITY
TO MEET SOMEONE NEW.
GO.
THANKS!
(SIGHS)
♪ Let's fall under
golden slumber ♪
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
♪ Be with me
right here ♪
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH:
FRANKIE, YOU READY YET?
YOUR DAD'S EVENT'S
IN LESS THAN AN HOUR!
ALMOST.
♪ If you would hold on to me ♪
♪ Oh... onto me ♪
It'd be like living
in the sun
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH:
OH, WHAT ARE YOU WEARING?
OH, IT LOOKS GOOD, NO?
SOPHISTICATED.
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH:
UM... HERE, WEAR THIS ONE
INSTEAD.
FRANKIE:
UH, NO WAY!
MOM, I'M NOT FOUR.
NO, YOU'RE FOURTEEN.
WHY ARE YOU IN SUCH
A RUSH TO GROW UP?
MAYBE SO YOU'LL TRUST ME
TO DO WHAT I WANT,
WHEN I WANT,
AND WITH WHO I WANT!
OH, YOU'RE STILL MAD
ABOUT WINSTON?
OF COURSE I AM!
MOM, IT'S SO UNFAIR!
I'M EXPECTED TO BE A SAINT,
AND MY BROTHERS GET AWAY
WITH MURDER!
MILES HASN'T MURDERED
ANYONE YET, I DON'T THINK.
HA HA.
WELL, I DO EVERYTHING YOU ASK.
I KEEP MY GRADES UP,
I DO CAMPAIGN STUFF,
I DON'T DRINK,
AND I DON'T SMOKE.
FRANKIE, LOOK, I'M DOING
THIS TO PROTECT YOU.
AND WHAT'S NEXT,
LOCKING ME AWAY IN A TOWER?!
OH, DON'T THINK I HAVEN'T
CONSIDERED IT.
ARE YOU EVEN HEARING HOW
RIDICULOUS YOU'RE BEING?
I SHOULD BE TREATED EQUALLY
TO MY BROTHERS!
WITH EQUAL RULES!
AND I WOULD LIKE THE WORLD
TO BE A DIFFERENT PLACE.
SO THERE'S NOTHING I CAN DO
TO CHANGE YOUR MIND?
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH:
WELL, YOU COULD GET DRESSED.
WE'RE GONNA BE LATE.
UGH!
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
♪♪
(CAMERA CLICKS)
I LOOK STUPID.
YEAH, YOU DO LOOK STUPID,
YOU LOOK VERY STUPID.
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH:
LEAVING IN TEN!
OHHH! SEE, FRANKIE?
YOU LOOK ADORABLE!
ADORABLE?
I AM NOT ADORABLE!
(SIGHS)
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
♪♪
ARE THOSE BOOBS?
TELL MOM,
AND YOU'RE DEAD MEAT!
MRS. HOLLINGSWORTH:
COME ON, LET'S GO!
(SIGHS)
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
(CAR STARTS)
(SIGHS)
(CARS RUMBLE, SIREN WAILS)
OH!
HEY.
HI.
SO, HOW'S IT GOING
WITH CLARE?
IT'S GREAT.
(SIGHS)
OKAY, IT'S NOT GREAT.
IT'S MESSY,
AND COMPLICATED...
AND I MISS YOU LIKE CRAZY.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
YOU ARE THE LAST PERSON
WHO WANTS TO BE HEARING
ABOUT MY PROBLEMS.
DREW!
(GRUNTS PAINFULLY)
I'M OKAY WITH COMPLICATED.
♪♪
(CRUTCHES CLATTER)