Becky:
♪ He's never gonna slide
Into your DM's ♪
♪ You just have to put
Your faith in him ♪
♪ Believe he can give you
everything you need ♪
♪ Even if you don't
Get that read receipt ♪
Becky, Jonah:
♪ I ride for him,
He rides for me ♪
In ways
♪ I'll probably never see ♪
♪ But that's okay, ♪
♪ I've just gotta believe,
Believe, believe, believe ♪
♪ That's okay, ♪
♪ I've just gotta believe,
believe, believe, believe ♪
♪ I've just gotta believe... ♪
BECKY:
THAT'S THE BEST
WE'VE EVER SOUNDED.
(BOTH LAUGH)
JONAH:
ALL RIGHT. HERE WE GO.
BECKY:
WOW... WHAT?
JONAH:
WHAT, WHAT?
BECKY:
WELL, I FIGURED YOU
OF ALL PEOPLE
WOULDN'T CARE ABOUT
THE NO-PDA RULE.
JONAH:
NO, IT'S JUST-
WELL, THE BELL'S GONNA RING
IN A COUPLE OF MINUTES,
AND I JUST WANNA GET THAT
HIGH HARMONY NAILED.
♪♪
♪ What ever it takes ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh... ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
GRACE:
LOOK AT YOU, ACTUALLY
PARTICIPATING IN GYM CLASS.
MAYA:
YUP. NEW UNIT, NEW ATTITUDE.
GRACE:
TOO BAD. I WAS REALLY GETTING
INTO YOUR EXCUSES.
"TOO MANY SPIDER BITES"
WAS MY FAVOURITE.
MAYA:
HEY, I HAD TO! I MEAN,
DODGEBALL WAS BRUTAL
ON MY ANXIETY!
BUT NOW, I'VE GOT MY EYES
ON THE PRIZE.
GRACE:
WHY? TO GET IN SHAPE FOR ZIG?
MAYA:
OH, SHUT UP. I'M TRYING
TO IGNORE THAT.
GRACE:
IGNORE THE CRUSH YOU HAVE
ON THE BUFF GUY,
WHO BUNKS AT YOUR PLACE?
MAYA:
YES! IT'S A BAD IDEA.
YOU KNOW, AFTER EVERYTHING
WITH THE BREAK-IN AT MY HOUSE,
JUST BE NICE TO BRING A GOOD
MARK TO MY MOM, OKAY?
COACH ARMSTRONG:
(BLOWS WHISTLE)
LADIES, BIG SURPRISE TODAY.
OUR NEW UNIT WILL BE...
SALSA DANCING!
MAYA:
AN "A" WILL BE ALMOST TOO EASY.
GRACE:
SURE BEATS BALLS TO THE FACE.
COACH ARMSTRONG:
AND HERE'S THE SURPRISE.
YOUR PARTNERS WILL BE FROM...
THE BOYS' CLASS.
LET'S HIT THE DANCE FLOOR...
MAYA, YOU'LL BE WITH TRISTAN.
GRACE:
YOUR NEMESIS.
THE PLOT THICKENS!
MAYBE I CAN MAKE IT WORK?
MS. WOLFE:
IF YOU STOOD HERE,
YOU MIGHT SEE SMILING FACES,
BUT I SEE A MESS OF GENES
EXPRESSED IN WILD
AND WOOLLY WAYS.
(SNAPS HER FINGERS)
I'M PRETTY SURE WE CAN'T DO
OUR PROJECT ON YOUR BOYFRIEND'S
GENES.
BECKY:
WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER
THREE WEEKS.
SHOULDN'T HE WANT
TO KISS ME?
IMOGEN: HE DOESN'T?
BECKY: NOT LIKE DREW USED
TO AT LEAST.
I MEAN, HE NEVER WANTED
TO STOP KISSING ME.
IMOGEN:
THAT'S HOW IT WAS WITH JACK...
NO. YOU CAN DO THIS, IMOGEN.
(DEEP BREATH)
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK
JONAH'S DEAL IS?
IS IT POSSIBLE
HE IS SO INTO RELIGION
BECAUSE HE IS TRYING
TO PRAY THE GAY AWAY?
BECKY:
OH, COME ON!
SOMETIMES PEOPLE
ARE IN THE CLOSET!
JACK IS WITH HER PARENTS!
YOU REALLY THINK HE'S GAY?
IMOGEN:
ONLY WAY TO FIND OUT... ASK!
CLARE:
DID YOU KNOW THAT BOYS
ARE THREE TIMES MORE LIKELY
TO END UP IN THE ER
THAN GIRLS?
ALLI:
I BELIEVE IT.
DALLAS IS ALWAYS DOING DUMB
THINGS THAT GET HIM HURT.
DALLAS: YOU MEAN AWESOME
THINGS...
ALLI: ...THAT GET YOU HURT.
JENNA:
WELL, CONNOR NEVER HURTS
HIMSELF.
CONNOR:
WHY WOULD I JEOPARDIZE
MY HEALTH?
I JUST CALCULATE THE RISK
AND ACT ACCORDINGLY.
DALLAS:
SEE? ALL BOYS ARE DIFFERENT.
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW YOUR SON
IS GONNA BE UNTIL HE GETS HERE.
CLARE:
NO, ELI AND I HAVE READ
ABOUT THE CREATIVE BOY,
THE RAMBUNCTIOUS BOY,
THE QUIET BOY, THE ANGRY BOY.
WE'VE LEARNED COMMUNICATION
TECHNIQUES...
CALMING TECHNIQUES.
DALLAS:
SO, YOU THINK YOU'RE READY?
GREAT, I'VE GOT AN INTERVIEW
WITH A HOCKEY COACH-
ALLI:
MY MAN MIGHT GO TO BROWN!
DALLAS:
OH, IT'S A BIG "MIGHT."
BUT I GOT ROCKY TONIGHT.
AND THE TORRESES
HAVE THIS THING,
PLUS ALLI'S GOT HER PHYSICS
TEST TOMORROW.
CLARE:
Y-YOU WANT ELI AND I
TO WATCH HIM...?
DALLAS:
YEAH. JUST FOR A COUPLE
HOURS...
UNLESS,
YOU AREN'T REALLY READY.
CLARE:
NO. NO, WE-WE'RE READY TO DO
THIS FOR THE REST OF OUR LIVES.
A COUPLE OF HOURS SHOULD BE
NO PROBLEM.
(BELL RINGS)
DALLAS: OKAY. GREAT.
(SIGHS)
JONAH:
THESE TWO MAKE A CUTE COUPLE,
DON'T YOU THINK?
BECKY:
HM-HMM. WHAT ABOUT THESE TWO?
JONAH:
WELL, AREN'T THOSE BOTH DUDES?
BECKY:
IS THERE A PROBLEM WITH THAT?
JONAH:
YEAH. THEY CAN'T HAVE
OFFSPRING,
AND THEN WE WON'T BE ABLE
TO MAP THEIR POSSIBLE GENETIC
COMBINATIONS.
BECKY:
BUT IN LIFE - WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT TWO GUYS TOGETHER?
JONAH:
(SMALL LAUGH)
I... THINK THAT'S KIND
OF BEAUTIFUL.
REALLY?
JONAH:
YEAH, TWO RIPPED HUNKS
RUBBING THEIR OILY MUSCLES
AGAINST EACH OTHER?
I'M NOT GAY, BECKY!
OKAY. THEN WHY DIDN'T YOU
WANT TO KISS ME THIS MORNING?!
JONAH:
DO YOU KNOW WHAT IT MEANS
TO BE STRAIGHTEDGE?
IT MEANS I ABSTAIN -
FROM SMOKING... DRINKING.
DRUGS... AND FROM SEX.
BECKY:
WHOA, I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT SEX.
JONAH:
OKAY. BUT IN MY EXPERIENCE,
IF YOU'RE NOT CAREFUL,
THAT'S WHERE KISSING LEADS.
BECKY:
SO, YOU'VE HAD...
WITH HOW MANY GIRLS?
JONAH:
I'M NOT A VIRGIN, BECKY.
IT'S PROBABLY BEST
TO LEAVE IT AT THAT.
BUT THAT'S BEHIND ME.
I'M ABSTINENT, NOW.
I'M WITH YOU.
BECKY:
YEAH. AND YOU DON'T EVEN
WANT TO KISS.
JONAH:
OH, I WANT TO KISS YOU.
SO BADLY.
ALL THE TIME.
REALLY?
BUT ANY MORE THAN WE DID
THIS MORNING,
AND WHO KNOWS
WHAT MIGHT HAPPEN.
(SALSA MUSIC)
COACH ARMSTRONG:
MOVE THOSE HIPS PEOPLE!
LOOKING GOOD!
TRISTAN:
AH! YOU STOMPED ON MY TOE!
MAYA:
SORRY. I WAS JUST TRYING
TO GET THE MOVES RIGHT.
TRISTAN:
WELL, I THINK IT'S BROKEN.
MAYA:
IT'S NOT BROKEN.
WE'RE WAY BEHIND.
DO YOU KNOW HOW TO DO THE STEP
TOGETHER STEP THINGIE?
TRISTAN:
IT WON'T WIGGLE.
THIS LITTLE PIGGY DEFINITELY
NEEDS TO SEE A DOCTOR.
MAYA:
OKAY. JUST PUT THIS HERE.
TRISTAN:
YOU KNOW I'M THE GUY, RIGHT?
WHICH MEAN,
I'M SUPPOSED TO LEAD?
BUT BIG SURPRISE, MAYA MATLIN'S
STICKING HER NOSE
WHERE IT DOESN'T BELONG.
(TRISTAN SIGHS)
(SALSA MUSIC PLAYS, BELL RINGS)
TRISTAN:
AND THERE'S THE BELL.
YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT THIS UNIT
WOULD BE AN EASY A,
AND I COULD IMPROVE MY GRADE,
BUT IS THERE ANY PART
OF MY LIFE YOU WON'T RUIN?
(SALSA MUSIC PLAYS)
BECKY:
SO... TOTALLY NOT GAY!
TURNS OUT JONAH'S HAD SEX WITH
GOODNESS KNOWS HOW MANY GIRLS!
IMOGEN:
NINERS! EARMUFFS!
WINSTON:
UM, I'M IN GRADE TEN.
IMOGEN:
WE NEED A BREAK, ANYWAY.
TAKE FIVE.
FRANKIE:
CAN I STAY?
THIS SOUNDS JUICY.
IMOGEN:
NO.
BECKY:
SO... HE LIKES ME,
BUT HE ONLY WANTS TO KISS ME.
AND ONLY A LITTLE.
IMOGEN:
WELL, THAT'S PERFECT FOR YOU,
RIGHT?
YOU'RE SAVING YOURSELF
FOR MARRIAGE.
BECKY:
I KNOW, BUT WHEN WE KISS,
I GET THESE IMPULSES.
LIKE, I WANNA DO MORE,
I WANNA GRAB HIM,
AND I WANNA PUT MY HANDS
UNDER HIS SHIRT AND...
(IMOGEN LAUGHS)
OH MY GOSH,
I'M SUCH A PERVERT!
IMOGEN: NO, YOU'RE NOT!
BECKY: YES, I AM.
WHAT WOULD GOD SAY?
IMOGEN:
"GO GET SOME, GIRL!"
PROBABLY HE TALKS LIKE THAT,
RIGHT?
BECKY:
OKAY. LOOK, I DON'T WANNA
LOSE MY VIRGINITY,
BUT I REALLY LIKE HIM.
SO WHAT IF I CAN'T STOP
AT JUST KISSING ANYMORE?
IMOGEN:
YOU DO REALIZE THERE IS OTHER
THINGS YOU CAN DO, BESIDES
KISSING?
BECKY:
WHAT DID YOU AND JACK DO?
IMOGEN:
YOU WANT ME TO EXPLAIN
WHAT WE DID?
BECKY:
PLEASE!
FRANKIE:
THE WATER FOUNTAIN WAS BROKEN.
IMOGEN:
I HAVE TO GET BACK
TO REHEARSAL.
BECKY:
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
IMOGEN:
TALK TO HIM.
FIGURE IT OUT TOGETHER.
HOW DO I TALK TO HIM,
WHEN I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT?
IMOGEN:
YOU'RE A BIG GIRL.
LOOK IT UP.
ROCKY:
AAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHH!
CLARE:
ROCKY PLEASE!
ROCKY!
ROCKY! PLEASE PUT
YOUR PANTS BACK ON, OKAY?
OH! OKAY.
WHAT DO YOU NEED?
ARE YOU... ARE YOU HUNGRY?
FRUSTRATED? ANGRY?
WHAT DO YOU NEED?
ELI:
HONEY, I'M HOME!
CLARE:
(SIGHS) THANK GOODNESS.
UM, CAN YOU-
ELI:
I GOT THIS.
HEY BUDDY.
I GOT A SURPRISE FOR YOU, OKAY?
ROCKY: A SURPRISE?!
ELI: YEAH. ARE YOU READY?
(GASPS)
(CHUCKLES)
IS THAT A GUN?
YEAH. A WATER GUN.
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
YOU CAN'T JUST GIVE SOMEONE
ELSE'S KID A GUN.
ELI:
YEAH, BUT LOOK,
IT'S TOTALLY OCCUPYING HIM.
CLARE:
NO. YOU HAVE TO TAKE IT AWAY.
ELI: I DO?
CLARE: YOU GAVE IT TO HIM.
FINE.
ROCKY, LOOK, PAL. UM...
I GOTTA TAKE THE GUN BACK,
OKAY?
CLARE DOESN'T THINK
YOU SHOULD HAVE IT.
CLARE:
ARE YOU KIDDING?
ROCKY:
I HATE YOU.
(WATER SPLASHES)
CLARE: (GASPS) AH!
(ELI LAUGHS)
CLARE: ELI!
MAYA:
(SIGHS) WHAT DO I DO?
DEMAND TO SWITCH PARTNERS?
SAY I'M LIKE A SUPER BIG
HOMPHOBE OR SOMETHING?
ZIG:
OR YOU COULD TRY TO -
I DON'T KNOW-
LEARN TO ACTUALLY DANCE
WITH HIM.
YOU DON'T GET IT.
TRISTAN HATES ME.
(SALSA MUSIC PLAYS)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
(MAYA SIGHS)
ZIG:
ALL RIGHT NOW WE'RE GONNA DO
ONE TO THE RIGHT
AND THEN TO THE LEFT.
READY? ONE. TWO. THREE.
ONE. TWO. THREE.
LOOK AT THAT?
YOU GOT IT!
MAYA:
I JUST LEARNED
MORE IN 30 SECONDS
THAN I DID IN AN ENTIRE CLASS
WITH TRISTAN?
ZIG:
WELL, THREE REASONS, I'D SAY.
ONE: MY HIPS DON'T LIE.
TWO: I DID THIS UNIT LAST TERM.
B-PLUS!
AND THREE: YOU TRUST ME.
MAYA:
IT'S THAT SIMPLE, HUH?
ZIG:
AND OPEN.
IF YOU WANT THINGS TO WORK,
YOU GONNA HAVE TO TAKE
THAT RISK.
STOP IGNORING YOUR PROBLEMS
WITH TRISTAN,
AND JUST BE HONEST ABOUT THEM,
NO MATTER HOW PAINFUL
IT MIGHT BE.
MAYA:
WHOA!
ZIG:
NOW, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I HAVE A MUCH MORE DIFFICULT
DANCE TO CONQUER -
TRIGONOMETRY.
(READYING BREATH)
IMOGEN:
YOU'RE NOT DONE?
DON'T YOU HAVE TO PRESENT IN,
LIKE, TEN MINUTES?
BECKY:
DON'T YOU THINK I KNOW THAT?!
IMOGEN:
ARE YOU OKAY?
BECKY:
YOU TOLD ME TO LOOK UP...
SEX THINGS ON THE INTERNET...
I SAW SOME THINGS...
IMOGEN:
OH BOY.
BECKY:
YOU AND JACK DIDN'T...
(WHISPERS)
IMOGEN: NO!
BECKY:
WHAT ABOUT?
IMOGEN:
BECKY! WHAT SITES DID
YOU GO ON?
BECKY:
ALL OF THEM! WITH PEOPLE DOING
THINGS IN EVERY IMAGINABLE-
(BELL RINGS)
YOU KNOW WHAT?
MAYBE JONAH'S GOT IT RIGHT.
MAYBE WE ABSTAIN AND I STOP
HAVING THESE FEELINGS.
IMOGEN:
I DON'T THINK
IT'S THAT EASY.
BECKY:
YES, IT IS!
IT HAS TO BE.
TRISTAN:
YOU CALL FOR A PRACTICE AND
YOU'RE NOT EVEN CHANGED YET?
UNBELIEVABLE.
MAYA:
OKAY. I WANNA BE ABLE
TO LET YOU LEAD.
BUT BEFORE I CAN DO THAT
IN DANCE,
I HAVE TO BE ABLE DO THAT
IN LIFE.
TRISTAN:
WHAT DOES THAT EVEN MEAN?
MAYA:
JUST TELL ME
HOW YOU FEEL ABOUT ME.
TRISTAN:
SO YOU CAN TELL ME I'M WRONG
FOR FEELING THAT WAY?
MAYA:
I WON'T SAY ANYTHING.
PLEASE JUST SIT.
TRISTAN:
I HATE HOW YOU ALWAYS THINK
YOU KNOW WHAT'S BEST FOR ME.
YOU DON'T.
THIS YEAR, YOU'VE TAKEN AWAY
EVERYTHING GOOD
I'VE HAD IN MY LIFE.
FIRST IT WAS GRANT.
AND MAYBE THAT WASN'T PERFECT,
BUT YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE BLABBED.
AND THEN I GET MILES - MILES!
AND YOU BUTT IN AND MAKE HIM
FALL IN LOVE WITH YOU AGAIN.
AND YOU DON'T EVEN WANT HIM.
YOU GET TO HAVE THIS PERFECT
LITTLE LIFE
AND ALL THESE GUYS IN LOVE
WITH YOU, AND WHAT DO I GET?
NOTHING!
AND THE WORST PART IS,
WHEN YOU BETRAYED ME,
I LOST MY BEST FRIEND...
SO I DIDN'T EVEN HAVE ANYONE
I CAN TALK TO ABOUT IT.
MAYA:
I'M SORRY.
MY LIFE ISN'T PERFECT,
YOU KNOW.
ESPECIALLY WITHOUT YOU IN IT.
TRISTAN:
REALLY?
MAYA:
I'VE NEEDED YOU, TOO, TRIS.
NOW, CAN WE TRY SOME SALSA?
JONAH: HEY, ARE WE COOL?
BECKY: HEY...
BECKY:
YEAH, DEFINITELY.
NO PROBLEMO.
JONAH:
OKAY? 'CAUSE OUR STUDIO TIME'S
TONIGHT.
AND I DON'T WANT IT TO BE
AWKWARD AFTER OUR CONVERSATION.
NO, YOU WERE RIGHT.
JUST KISSING IS A-OKAY.
WE'RE GOOD.
(BELL RINGS)
MS. WOLFE:
BECKY AND JONAH,
MY LITTLE LAMBS,
ARE YOU READY TO WOW US?
LADIES AND GENTLEMAN,
HERE ARE BECKY AND JONAH,
SHARING ABOUT SHEEP.
LIGHTS!
JONAH:
(CLEARS THROAT)
OKAY. SO THE "BLACK SHEEP" CAN
MEAN THE BAD SEED IN A FAMILY,
BUT IT'S ALSO A CREATURE
THAT CAN GIVE US CLUES
ABOUT GENETIC INHERITANCE.
BECKY? THE CHART.
BECKY:
OH OOPS. I FORGOT TO LOAD
THE SITE. SORRY.
JUST...
(CLICK)
OH MY GOSH.
STOP IT! STOP!
PUSH STOP!
OH MY GOSH.
(STUDENTS MURMUR AND CHUCKLE)
(STUDENTS CHUCKLING)
WOOOO!
MS. WOLFE, I AM SO SORRY.
MS. WOLFE:
I'M AFRAID YOU'LL HAVE TO PLEAD
THAT CASE TO THE PRINCIPAL.
CLARE:
OKAY, I THINK THIS IS PART "A."
ELI:
THAT LOOKS LIKE A "C," TO ME.
CLARE:
YOU SHOULD JUST DO THIS
ON YOUR OWN.
ELI:
WHY I THOUGHT WE WERE BUILDING
IT, TOGETHER.
ISN'T THAT THE POINT?
CLARE:
BUT WHAT IF I SCREW IT UP?
AND THE A IS WHERE THE C'S
SUPPOSED TO BE
AND THE WHOLE THING COLLAPSES
ON THE BABY?
ELI:
THIS ISN'T ABOUT THE CRIB.
CLARE:
(SIGHS) WHAT IF I WAS WRONG
ABOUT THE GUN?
ELI:
YOU'RE STILL ON THAT?
CLARE:
WHAT IF IT WAS FINE
FOR ROCKY TO HAVE IT,
AND NOW THAT I MADE SUCH A BIG
DEAL, HE COVETS GUNS, FOREVER?
ELI:
YEAH, BUT WHAT
IF YOU WERE RIGHT ALONG
AND HE SHOULDN'T HAVE HAD IT
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
CLARE:
SEE? I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THE RIGHT ANSWER IS!
ELI:
WELL, MAYBE THERE ISN'T
A RIGHT ANSWER?
MAYBE THERE'S JUST
"RIGHT" FOR US.
AND THAT IS?
ER, HOW ABOUT ONLY WATER GUNS
THAT DON'T LOOK LIKE REAL GUNS?
CLARE:
OKAY, AND WE'LL HAVE RULES.
LIKE, NO POINTING IT
AT PEOPLES' FACES.
SEE? WE CAN DO THIS.
IT'S OKAY.
THE REAL MISTAKE WE MADE
WAS NOT TALKING ABOUT IT
BEFOREHAND.
(BELL RINGS)
BECKY:
HEY, MOM, I AM SO SORRY.
MRS. BAKER:
WITH THAT NEW PRINCIPAL,
YOU'RE LUCKY YOU ONLY GOT TWO
DAYS DETENTION, YOUNG LADY.
BECKY:
I SAID I'M SORRY.
WHAT MORE CAN I SAY?
MRS. BAKER:
TELL ME YOU'RE NOT ACTUALLY
DOING ANY OF THAT FILTH.
BECKY:
NO, OF COURSE NOT...
MRS. BAKER:
(RELIEVED SIGH)
BUT I WANT TO.
NOT ALL OF IT.
DEFINITELY NOT.
BUT I HAVE A BOYFRIEND,
AND I LIKE HIM-
MRS. BAKER:
YOU'RE TOO YOUNG.
BECKY: EVERYBODY ELSE IS...
MRS. BAKER: YOU'RE NOT
EVERYBODY, REBECCA.
BECKY:
OKAY. I KNOW, I'M A GOOD
CHRISTIAN GIRL,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
THAT I DON'T GET FEELINGS
AND I KNOW GOD DOESN'T
WANT ME TO ACT ON IT,
BUT HE ALSO GAVE THEM TO ME,
RIGHT?
(SIGHS)
THIS IS SO CONFUSING.
OKAY...
A CONVERSATION LIKE THIS MIGHT
HAVE KEPT YOUR BROTHER
OUT OF THE TROUBLE HE IS NOW.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO KNOW?
BECKY:
WILL I GO TO HELL IF I DO IT?
MRS. BAKER:
DO WHAT?
BECKY:
NOT IT IT, BUT, LIKE,
KISSING AND OTHER THINGS...
MRS. BAKER:
IT'S NEVER SIMPLE.
WHEN YOU GET THAT CLOSE
WITH SOMEONE
YOU BUILD STRONG EMOTIONAL
BONDS THAT...
IT CAN REALLY HURT YOUR HEART.
BECKY:
WILL GOD BE MAD?
MRS. BAKER:
THAT IS A CONVERSATION YOU'LL
HAVE TO HAVE WITH HIM, HONEY.
BECKY:
OKAY.
BUT IF YOU CAN'T TALK HONESTLY
ABOUT THIS STUFF WITH YOUR
BOYFRIEND,
THEN YOU ARE DEFINITELY
NOT READY.
OKAY.
(SIGHS)
(HUMMING)
ZIG:
SO I TAKE IT
THINGS WENT WELL WITH TRIS.
MAYA:
YES. AND THANKS.
YOU KNOW, IT IS IMPORTANT TO BE
HONEST ABOUT YOUR FEELINGS.
ZIG:
EXACTLY.
WHICH IS WHY I NEED TO BE HONEST
ABOUT SOMETHING WITH YOU.
I CAN'T FIX YOUR OTHER PROBLEM.
MAYA:
WHAT'S MY OTHER PROBLEM?
ZIG:
OH, YOUR-YOUR TWO LEFT FEET.
MAYA:
I'LL SHOW YOU
MY TWO LEFT FEET.
ZIG:
OH! CALM DOWN!
LOOK! YOU CAN'T EVEN KICK
WITH THEM.
MAYA:
YES, I CAN.
YOU JUST WAIT!
(ZIG LAUGHING)
MY SISTER SHOWED ME
SOME TAEKWONDO.
ZIG:
WELL, TRY IT, MATLIN.
JUST TRY IT.
♪♪
♪ Here is my heart ♪
♪ Coming around the bend ♪
(DOOR OPENS)
MRS. MATLIN:
SOME CALL HER A HERO.
SOME JUST CALL HER
A HARD-WORKING MOM
WHO BRINGS HOME
THE BURGERS PRIEST.
DIDN'T YOU HEAR ME?
BURGERS PRIEST.
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE EXCITED.
MAYA: YAY! THANK YOU!
ZIG: AWESOME! THANK YOU!
MAYA: THANKS MOM.
MRS. MATLIN: YEP.
BECKY:
♪ Because I don't feel
anyone holding my hand ♪
♪ Don't see an extra set
of prints in the sand ♪
♪ And I ran away,
Out here alone (alone) ♪
JONAH:
OKAY, IT'S LIKE
WE'RE GETTING WORSE.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
BECKY:
WE HAVE TO TALK
ABOUT SOMETHING.
UM, CAN WE TURN OFF THE MICS?
RANDY:
YEAH. NO PROBLEM.
BECKY:
THANKS.
JONAH:
IS THIS ABOUT WHAT I SAW
IN YOUR BROWSER HISTORY, TODAY?
BECKY:
KIND OF...
I LIKE YOU JONAH.
A LOT.
AND WHEN WE KISS, I FEEL
LIKE I'M ABOUT TO EXPLODE.
JONAH:
SO, JUST KISSING ISN'T ENOUGH?
BECKY:
I DON'T THINK SO.
JONAH:
BUT IF I LET GO WITH YOU,
I KNOW HOW QUICKLY
IT CAN ESCALATE.
BECKY:
BUT IT DOESN'T HAVE TO.
I'M NOT GONNA HAVE SEX
UNTIL MARRIAGE.
YOU CAN TRUST THAT I'M NOT
GONNA LET IT GO THAT FAR.
JONAH:
HOW FAR DO YOU WANT IT TO GO?
BECKY:
I DON'T REALLY WANT TO HAVE THAT
DISCUSSION IN FRONT OF RANDY.
OKAY. LETS KILL THIS TAKE
AND TALK ABOUT IT AFTER?
JONAH:
OKAY. AND BECKY?
BECKY:
OKAY. YEAH.
READY?
BECKY:
SO READY.
RANDY:
AND ROLLIN'.
CLARE:
(GROANS, CHUCKLES)
IT'S COLD.
ANYTHING GOOD?
ELI:
THERE IS A COUPLE.
DOCTOR:
I NEED TO DOUBLE-CHECK
SOMETHING.
ELI:
OKAY, HOW ABOUT PLAY-DOH?
IT PROMOTES UNLIMITED
CREATIVITY.
CLARE:
YOU DON'T MIND THE SMELL?
OKAY. FINE.
IT'S A YES.
ELI:
(CHUCKLES) OKAY... AH!
PIRATE COSTUMES?
CLARE:
YOU REALLY WANT TO PROMOTE
THAT KIND OF CRIMINALITY?
ELI:
OH YEAH. THE PEG LEG, THE EYE
PATCH - IT'S A GREAT LOOK.
(LAUGHS)
MAYBE HALLOWEEN-
WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT.
DOCTOR: MAY I?
CLARE: YEAH.
I'M AFRAID I HAVE SOME
UPSETTING NEWS.
I'VE DOUBLE CHECKED THE BATTERY
ON THE DEVICE,
AND WE STILL HAVE FURTHER TESTS
RUN ON THE BABY, BUT...
I'M NO LONGER HEARING
A HEARTBEAT.
(SHARP BREATH)