(KNOCKING)
ZIG:
WHY ARE THE DOORS LOCKED?
WINSTON:
DID YOU ALL GET THAT EMAIL
FROM IMOGEN
ABOUT A "SUPER IMPORTANT
REHEARSAL THIS MORNING"
WITH LIKE FIFTEEN
VARIOUS EMOJIS?
SHAY:
YEAH. SO... WHERE IS SHE?
(DOORS CLICK OPEN)
IMOGEN:
NOT TO WORRY,
MY LITTLE CHICKENS!
ALL WILL BE REVEALED!
JUST FOLLOW ME...
AND... BEHOLD!
(CAPTAIN WHO THEME MUSIC PLAYS)
WOW. THIS IS LIKE LEGIT.
ZIG:
UH, YEAH, IT'S AMAZING!
WINSTON:
IT'S EXACTLY LIKE
HOW I IMAGINED.
IMOGEN:
AW! NO TIME FOR TEARS, WINNIE!
WE STILL HAVE TO GET THROUGH
DRESS REHEARSALS AND TECH,
BEFORE OPENING!
EVERYONE ON STAGE!
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
(DOOR OPENS)
GRACE: ZIG!
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
UM, DAMON GOT SHOT
LAST NIGHT.
THE COPS DON'T SEEM
TO KNOW WHO DID IT.
I GUESS HE'S NOT TALKING,
OR CAN'T.
OH MY GOD.
TELL ME
YOU WEREN'T INVOLVED.
I...I-I HOPE NOT.
IMOGEN:
NOVAK! GET UP HERE!
ZIG:
UH... I... I HAVE TO GO.
IMOGEN: WHAT THE HECK?! WHERE?!
ZIG: I JUST... I-I HAVE TO GO.
IMOGEN:
YOU BETTER BE GETTING US ALL
BREAKFAST BURRITOS!
FOR EVERYONE ELSE,
REHEARSAL STARTS NOW!
♪ Whatever it takes! ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh... ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
TINY:
METAPHASE, ANAPHASE,
TELOPHASE... OKAY.
ZIG:
WHAT HAPPENED LAST NIGHT?
TINY: ZIG-
ZIG: WHEN YOU AND VINCE
HAD ME DRIVE YOU
TO THAT APARTMENT BUILDING,
DID YOU GUYS...
DID YOU GUYS SHOOT DAMON
WHILE I SAT IN THE CAR?
TINY:
I DIDN'T DO IT.
I SWEAR, I DIDN'T SHOOT HIM.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
VINCE HAD A GUN.
ZIG: THIS ISN'T HAPPENING.
TINY: VINCE JUST WANTED
TO SCARE HIM.
YOU KNOW, PAYBACK
FOR STABBING ME.
BUT THINGS GOT MESSY.
HE CAME AT ME AND... (SIGHS)
VINCE PULLED THE TRIGGER.
WHAT DO WE DO?
HE'S MY BROTHER, ZIG.
WE KEEP OUR MOUTHS SHUT.
BUT ISN'T DAMON JUST GONNA
TELL THE COPS WHO SHOT HIM?
NOT IF HE'S SMART.
(BELL RINGS)
HE USED TO BE MY FRIEND.
AND HE'LL PROBABLY BE FINE.
THEY'LL TAKE CARE OF HIM
IN THE HOSPITAL.
ZIG: MAYBE... MAYBE WE SHOULD
TALK TO JOSE.
TINY: NO.
HE'S HELPED US
WITH THIS STUFF BEFORE,
HE MIGHT KNOW WHAT TO DO.
WE CAN'T TELL ANYONE!
I GOTTA GET TO CLASS.
I HAVE A SCIENCE TEST.
BUT WHAT AM I SUPPOSED
TO DO?!
SAME AS ME.
PRETEND EVERYTHING'S NORMAL.
FRANKIE:
♪ Take off your mask ♪
♪ Let me see your face ♪
♪ Once I know the real you ♪
♪ We can get out
of this place ♪
FRANKIE AND WINSTON:
♪ All my life I've been
searching for someone like you ♪
♪ Show me who you are... ♪
WINSTON: I'M...
FRANKIE: SIMON?
(SIGHS)
IMOGEN:
ALL RIGHT, LOOKING GREAT!
YOU'RE GIVING ME ALL THE FEELS!
I'D LIKE TO LOOK AT
SOME SCENE TRANSITIONS.
I THINK THAT'S THE BEST
WE'VE EVER SOUNDED.
YOU'VE ALWAYS SOUNDED
AMAZING TO ME.
FRANKIE:
I DON'T KNOW
HOW YOU'RE FEELING,
BUT I'M GETTING PRETTY JITTERY
ABOUT OPENING NIGHT.
OH! THAT REMINDS ME,
I UH... GOT YOU SOMETHING.
ANTACID?
I KNOW HOW YOUR STOMACH
GETS WEIRD
WHEN YOU'RE ANXIOUS.
WOW. IT'S CRAZY THAT
YOU REMEMBERED THAT.
I REMEMBER EVERYTHING
ABOUT YOU, FRANKS.
FOR WHAT IT'S WORTH,
YOU HAVE NOTHING
TO BE NERVOUS ABOUT.
YOU'RE AMAZING AND...
AND I HOPE ONE DAY,
AFTER ALL THIS OVER,
WE CAN BE FRIENDS.
(SIGHS)
NURSE:
TO COMPLETE
YOUR VOLUNTEER HOURS,
YOU'LL BE ASKED TO WORK ONE
TO TWO SHIFTS A WEEK.
BECKY:
ISN'T THIS AWESOME?!
I HOPE WE GET TO DO COOL STUFF
LIKE CHANGE IVS,
OR GIVE INJECTIONS!
MAYBE THEY'LL LET ME
CHANGE A BANDAGE,
OR MAYBE WE'LL GET
TO OBSERVE A SURGERY,
LIKE AN APPENDECTOMY
OR A BONE RESETTING.
DALLAS:
UGH! WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
BECKY:
I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST FIND THAT STUFF... COOL.
I WATCHED A VIDEO ONLINE ABOUT
HOW TO PERFORM A TRACHEOTOMY,
SO IF YOU EVER NEED ONE,
I'M YOUR GIRL.
NURSE:
YOU'LL MOSTLY BE HANDING OUT
BOOKS AND CRAFT KITS.
DALLAS:
THANK GOD. BALLOON ANIMALS?
THAT I CAN HANDLE.
HE FAINTS AT THE SIGHT
OF BLOOD.
DALLAS:
I BLAME CLARE.
SHE WAS SUPPOSED
TO DO THIS WITH YOU,
UNTIL SHE GOT SUSPENDED.
NURSE:
OKAY, NOW EVERYONE FIND
YOUR PARTNERS
AND I'LL HAND OUT
YOUR ASSIGNMENTS.
BECKY:
UM, I DON'T-
I DON'T HAVE A PARTNER.
(OUT OF BREATH)
SORRY I'M LATE!
NURSE:
OH! YOU DO NOW! YOU TWO ARE ON
LIBRARY CART DUTY
AND, UH, THE REST OF YOU
CAN FOLLOW ME.
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
SO... HOW'S IT GOING?
THINGS OKAY WITH GUYLINER?
BECKY:
HIS NAME'S JONAH!
AND WHY WOULDN'T THEY BE?
DREW:
HONESTLY? I JUST DON'T GET
THE BEST VIBES FROM HIM, BECKS.
BECKY:
SHHHH!
LOOK, YOU DON'T
EVEN KNOW HIM.
YOU CAN'T PASS JUDGMENT
ON PEOPLE LIKE THAT!
DREW:
SURE I CAN!
I MEAN, FOR INSTANCE, AND I
DON'T KNOW THIS GUY PERSONALLY,
BUT I CAN TELL YOU
THAT HE...
GOT SHOT. WOW.
YOU SEE?
HE'S A VIOLENT CRIMINAL
WHO PROBABLY HAD IT COMING.
BECKY:
OR HE'S A MISUNDERSTOOD KID
WHO ACTUALLY LOVES THE BALLET
AND WAS JUST AT THE WRONG PLACE
AT THE WRONG TIME!
DAMON:
I'M ACTUALLY A GUY WHO WANTS
YOU TO GET OUT OF HIS ROOM
SO HE CAN GET SOME SLEEP.
BECKY:
OH MY GOSH!
I AM SO SORRY!
DREW: WE'RE GONNA... GO. GO.
BECKY: SORRY.
DREW:
(CLEARS THROAT)
NICE ONE, DOOFUS.
IF ANYONE ASKS, CAN YOU SAY
THAT WE WERE TOGETHER LAST
NIGHT?
MAYA: BUT... WE WEREN'T.
ZIG: I KNOW.
BUT CAN YOU JUST SAY
THAT WE WERE?
ZIG, WHAT'S GOING ON?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
VINCE SHOT DAMON LAST NIGHT.
TINY WAS THERE,
AND SO WAS I.
I... I WASN'T THERE,
BUT... I DROVE THE CAR.
MAYA: IS HE...?
ZIG: DEAD? N-NO.
BUT TINY SAYS THAT
WE CAN'T SAY ANYTHING
OR ELSE WE'LL ALL
GO TO JAIL.
MAYA: I WON'T, I PROMISE.
ZIG: MAYA, I'M REALLY SCARED.
I-I DIDN'T THINK VINCE
COULD DO SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
HE HAD A GUN IN THE HOUSE!
THE HOUSE WHERE YOU
JUST VISITED ME!
MAYA: IT'S OKAY...
ZIG: NO, NO, IT'S NOT OKAY!
AND NOW I'M ASKING YOU
TO BE MY ALIBI?!
WHAT THE HELL
IS WRONG WITH ME?
I'M SORRY FOR DRAGGING YOU
INTO ALL THIS.
IF YOU WANTED TO RUN AWAY
AND NEVER LOOK BACK,
I WOULDN'T BLAME YOU.
ZIG, I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
GRACE:
PILL'S LOOKING FOR YOU.
APPARENTLY THERE'S A DETECTIVE
WITH SOME QUESTIONS.
UH, YEAH.
YEAH, OKAY.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
FRANKIE:
HAVE YOU EVER NOTICED
THAT SUPER CUTE THING
WINSTON DOES WITH HIS MOUTH
WHEN HE'S NERVOUS?
SHAY:
NO. YOU ARE NOT GETTING BACK
TOGETHER WITH HIM.
FRANKIE:
BUT HE GAVE ME ANTACID!
BECAUSE HE REMEMBERED
I HAVE A NERVOUS STOMACH!
SO MAYBE IT WOULDN'T BE
THE WORST IDEA?
EXCEPT YOU'VE SAID
ON SEVERAL OCCASIONS,
AND I QUOTE, "DO NOT,
UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES,
LET ME GET BACK TOGETHER
WITH WINSTON BECAUSE...
IT WOULD BE
THE WORST IDEA."
YEAH, BUT I SAY A LOT
OF THINGS.
DO YOU REALLY THINK
YOU CAN TRUST HIM AGAIN?
AFTER HE... YOU-KNOW-WHAT
WITH YOU-KNOW-WHO?
OOH, ARE WE GOSSIPING?
WHO DID WHAT WITH WHO?
GIVE ME ALL THE DIRT!
YOU KISSED HER BOYFRIEND?
REMEMBER?
OH. THAT. BUT I'VE APOLOGIZED
A GAGILLION TIMES!
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO'S ALWAYS SAYING
YOU DON'T WANNA END UP
LIKE YOUR MOM,
MOONING AFTER A CHEATER.
FRANKIE:
SO YOU REALLY DON'T THINK
THERE'S ANY WAY FOR ME
TO TRUST WINSTON AGAIN?
ONLY IF YOU CAN PROVE
THAT HE WILL NEVER, EVER
CHEAT ON YOU AGAIN.
FRANKIE:
IF YOU WANT ME TO FORGIVE YOU
FOR KISSING MY EX-BOYFRIEND,
I NEED YOU TO DO
SOMETHING FOR ME.
LOLA:
WHAT?
TRY TO KISS MY EX-BOYFRIEND.
POLICE OFFICER:
(WHISPERING)
HE'S NERVOUS.
DETECTIVE TAYLOR:
(WHISPERING) OKAY. THANKS.
(DOOR CLICKS SHUT)
SO, ZIG,
I HEAR YOU'RE STARRING
IN THE SCHOOL MUSICAL!
ZIG: UH... YEAH.
DET. TAYLOR: THAT'S FANTASTIC.
YOU KNOW, I SAW "WICKED"
ON BROADWAY.
LOVE THAT IDINA MENZEL.
(CLICKS PEN)
(SNIFFS)
WELL, YOU'RE A SMART KID.
SOLID AVERAGE THIS TERM.
YOU HAVE MY GRADES
IN THERE?
YUP.
AND YOU'RE STILL LIVING
WITH DEON BELL
AND HIS BROTHER, VINCENT,
IS THAT RIGHT?
YEAH. HOW-
HOW DO YOU KNOW ALL THIS?
WELL, WE'VE BEEN KEEPING AN EYE
ON YOU FOR A WHILE NOW, ZIG.
TINY WAS STABBED
A FEW WEEKS AGO, RIGHT?
THAT MUST HAVE BEEN ROUGH.
UH, YEAH.
YEAH, IT WAS.
I'M SURE YOU HEARD BY NOW
THAT DAMON CARTER
WAS SHOT LAST NIGHT.
YOU TWO USED TO BE
FRIENDS, RIGHT?
UH, KIND OF. YEAH.
SO WHAT HAPPENED?
I DON'T KNOW. I GUESS WE JUST...
DRIFTED APART.
OR YOU GOT CAUGHT ON OPPOSITE
SIDES OF A TURF WAR?
WERE YOU INVOLVED IN THIS,
ZIG?
ZIG: NO.
DET. TAYLOR: OKAY.
IF YOU KNOW THINGS
AND YOU DON'T COME FORWARD,
NOT ONLY ARE YOU AN ACCESSORY
TO AN ATTEMPTED MURDER,
BUT YOU'RE LOOKING AT AN
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE CHARGE.
YOU COULD GO TO JAIL.
YOU EITHER DO THE RIGHT THING
AND HELP ME OUT,
OR YOU CONTINUE PROTECTING
WHOEVER YOU'RE PROTECTING,
AND... I WON'T BE ABLE TO DO
ANYTHING FOR YOU.
LET ME ASK YOU,
WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED LAST NIGHT?
(STUDENTS CHATTER,
BELL RINGS)
JONAH:
SO HOW WAS THE HOSPITAL?
I BET YOU LOOK CUTE IN
YOUR CANDY STRIPER UNIFORM.
BOTH:
(CHUCKLING)
SADLY, IT'S JUST
A NEON T-SHIRT,
AND VOLUNTEERING
WOULD BE GREAT
IF IT WASN'T FOR DREW.
HE KEPT BUGGING ME
ABOUT OUR RELATIONSHIP.
JUST IGNORE HIM.
HE'S JUST JEALOUS.
WELL, HE KEPT SAYING HE DOESN'T
THINK YOU'RE TRUSTWORTHY.
DO YOU BELIEVE HIM?
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
THEN WHO CARES
WHAT HE SAYS?
(LAUGHS)
WINSTON:
OKAY, EVERYONE!
HAND OVER YOUR YEARBOOK MONEY
OR ELSE IT'S NO LIFETIME
MEMORIES FOR YOU!
OH NO!
JONAH: WHAT?
BECKY: MY MONEY'S GONE!
I HAD TWO HUNDRED DOLLARS
IN HERE FOR YEARBOOK
AND PROM TICKETS.
MAYBE UH...
MAYBE YOU LEFT IT AT HOME?
NO, NO, NO.
IT WAS DEFINITELY IN HERE.
SOMEONE MUST HAVE
STOLEN IT!
ALL RIGHT, WELL UH...
YOU HAD YOUR PURSE WHEN
WE HAD COFFEE AT THE DOT
BEFORE YOUR SHIFT, RIGHT?
YEAH, AND THEN I HAD IT
WITH ME ALL DAY...
EXCEPT WHEN I FORGOT IT
IN A PATIENT'S ROOM
AND HAD TO GO BACK
TO GET IT!
YOU REALLY THINK A PATIENT
STOLE FROM YOU?
THERE'S NO ONE ELSE
IT COULD BE. (SIGHS)
ZIG:
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT REALLY SURE
ABOUT THESE PANTS.
IMOGEN:
NO TIME FOR NOTES,
NOVAK!
THE CAPTAIN WHO TRAIN
IS LEAVING THE STATION.
HAS ANYONE SEEN
MY SAFETY PINS?
I SHALL RETURN!
KEEP AN EYE ON HIM!
MAYA: WHOA!
ZIG: (LAUGHING)
SO EVERYTHING WENT OKAY
WITH THE DETECTIVE?
WELL, I... DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING
AND NO ONE ELSE ASKED.
I THINK THIS MIGHT ACTUALLY
ALL BLOW OVER.
NO ONE'S ASKED ME
ANYTHING EITHER, SO...
ZIG:
FANTASTIC!
I'M FINALLY FREE TO DO
ALL THE FUN STUFF IN MY LIFE,
LIKE THIS MUSICAL, AND...
THE SECURITY
CAMERA-FREE ZONE...
(KISSING)
TINY: SORRY TO INTERRUPT.
ZIG: OH!
MAYA: AH.
ZIG: HEY, MAN! (LAUGHS)
UH, WHAT'S UP?
WE NEED TO TALK.
NOT HERE.
ZIG:
I-I'M SURE IT'S NOTHING.
(JACKET RUSTLES,
ZIG SIGHS HEAVILY)
FRANKIE:
HEY!
WINSTON:
I'M REALLY GLAD
YOU AGREED TO LUNCH, FRANKIE.
HAM, EXTRA SWISS,
HONEY MUSTARD,
NO MAYO,
AND THREE DOTS OF HOT SAUCE.
FRANKIE: YOU REMEMBERED?
WINSTON: OF COURSE I DID.
FRANKIE:
YOU KNOW, ACTUALLY I HAVE
TO GO TO THE BATHROOM,
SO I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
(HAPPY SIGH)
SHAY:
FOR THE RECORD, I THINK
THIS IS A TERRIBLE IDEA.
NOTED!
OKAY, LO, YOU'RE UP!
WHAT DOES WINSTON RESPOND TO?
LOLA: UH, EYE CONTACT.
FRANKIE: AND?
HAND OR LEG TOUCHES?
YEAH, BUT NOTHING
TOO OBVIOUS.
LOLA:
DON'T WORRY, GIRL.
I GOT THIS.
ARE YOU SURE YOU WANNA
GO THROUGH WITH THIS?
I LIKE HIM SO MUCH, BUT...
I CAN'T LET HIM
BREAK MY HEART AGAIN.
I JUST HAVE TO MAKE SURE
I CAN TRUST HIM,
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
LOLA:
I LIKE YOUR GLASSES...
(UNCLEAR COMMENT)
OOH! HAVE YOU BEEN
WORKING OUT?
(GIGGLES)
(MOTORCYCLE RUMBLES NEARBY,
STUDENTS CHATTER)
ZIG:
WHAT'S GOING ON?
VINCE:
I HOPE YOU APPRECIATE
EVERYTHING
I'VE DONE FOR YOU, ZIG.
ZIG:
YEAH! YEAH, OF COURSE.
WITHOUT YOU, I'D BE HOMELESS.
VINCE:
GOOD. BECAUSE I CAN'T HAVE
A SNITCH LIVING UNDER MY ROOF.
YOU TOLD HIM THAT
I TALKED TO THE COPS?!
HE ASKED.
I WASN'T GONNA LIE.
ZIG:
WELL, I-I KEPT MY MOUTH SHUT.
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
YOU CAN TRUST ME, MAN.
VINCE: PROVE IT.
ZIG: HOW?
VINCE:
THERE'S A GUY WITH A LONG
STANDING DEBT FOR PRODUCT
AND I'VE HAD A HARD TIME
COLLECTING FROM HIM.
I NEED YOU
TO GET MY CASH FOR ME.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO DO THAT?
VINCE:
BY ANY MEANS NECESSARY.
WE'RE ALL FAMILY HERE, ZIG.
I NEED YOU
TO STEP UP FOR ME.
TINY: I DON'T THINK
HE SHOULD HAVE TO-
VINCE: STAY OUT OF THIS,
BABY BRO.
CAN YOU HANDLE THAT?
YEAH.
YEAH, I GOT THIS.
ANNOUNCEMENT OVER PA:
DR. PIER, DIAGNOSTIC IMAGING,
PLEASE.
DR. PIER,
DIAGNOSTIC IMAGING.
DAMON:
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I THOUGHT I ONLY HAD TO PUT UP
WITH VOLUNTEERS ONE DAY A WEEK.
BECKY:
'KAY, LOOK, YOU DIDN'T HAPPEN
TO... BY ANY CHANCE...
STEAL TWO HUNDRED DOLLARS
FROM MY PURSE, DID YOU?
WHAT? I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
BECKY:
BECAUSE THE MONEY'S MISSING
AND I LEFT MY PURSE HERE
YESTERDAY,
SO... THERE'S NO ONE ELSE
WHO COULD'VE-
DAMON:
YOU'RE JUST LIKE THE REST
OF THE IDIOTS AT OUR SCHOOL.
PASSING JUDGMENT ON PEOPLE
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW.
YOU GO TO DEGRASSI?
DAMON:
YES. AND I DIDN'T STEAL
YOUR MONEY.
I COULDN'T HAVE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
YOU COULDN'T HAVE?
I CAN'T WALK OR REALLY MOVE.
I GOT SHOT IN THE LEG.
(MACHINES BEEP)
OH MY GOSH.
DAMON:
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
SO EVEN IF I HAD WANTED
TO STEAL FROM YOU, NO DICE.
BUT IF IT WASN'T YOU,
THEN WHO?
THAT IS SO NOT
MY PROBLEM.
BECKY:
NO, OF-OF COURSE NOT.
I'LL-I'LL JUST GO.
I'M REALLY, REALLY SORRY.
(PHONE RINGS NEARBY)
LOLA AND WINSTON:
(LAUGHING)
SHAY:
AND TELL ME AGAIN WHY YOU
COULDN'T JUST TALK TO HIM?
I MEAN, AREN'T RELATIONSHIPS
SUPPOSED TO BE ABOUT HONESTY
AND COMMUNICATION
OR SOMETHING?
FRANKIE:
BECAUSE IF I ASK HIM, "ARE YOU
GONNA CHEAT ON ME AGAIN?"
OF COURSE HE'S GONNA SAY NO,
BECAUSE I'M SURE
THAT'S WHAT HE BELIEVES,
BUT SOMEWHERE LURKING
WITHIN HIS BIOLOGY
IS A HORRIBLE CHEATING MONSTER
JUST WAITING TO BUST OUT
AND BREAK MY HEART.
AT LEAST I IMAGINE
THAT'S HOW BOYS' BRAINS WORK.
I JUST HAVE TO BE SURE
HE HAS THAT PART OF HIMSELF
UNDER CONTROL
BEFORE I, YOU KNOW,
LET MYSELF TRUST HIM.
SHAY:
OH BOY.
FRANKIE:
OH, I'M CRAZY, AREN'T I?
SHAY:
YOU SAID IT, NOT ME.
FRANKIE:
THERE'S THE EYE CONTACT!
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME NOW.
LOOK!
LOLA:
I LIKE THESE PANTS.
THEY DO REALLY NICE THINGS
FOR YOUR CALVES.
(BELL RINGS)
WINSTON:
HEY, DO YOU WANT TO GO
SOMEWHERE MORE PRIVATE?
LOLA:
SURE.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
UH-OH.
UH-OH IS RIGHT.
(DOOR BURSTS OPEN)
JUST GET IN AND GET OUT.
THERE HE IS.
(HARD SHOVE)
JONAH: WHOA, TAKE IT EASY!
(HARD THUMP, STRUGGLING)
ZIG:
YOU OWE MONEY AND IT'D BE IN
YOUR BEST INTEREST TO PAY UP.
JONAH:
VINCE SENT YOU? CRAP.
LOOK, I KNOW I'M A FEW WEEKS
OVERDUE-
(HARD SHOVE)
ZIG: TRY MONTHS.
JONAH:
WELL, I TOLD HIM BEFORE -
I DIDN'T FORGET, OKAY?
THINGS HAVE JUST BEEN TIGHT.
AGH! I JUST CAME INTO SOME CASH
AND I WAS GONNA COME FIND HIM.
(STRUGGLING GRUNTS,
HARD THUMP)
LOOK, LOOK. MM. LOOK.
THAT'S ALL OF IT, OKAY?
TWO HUNDRED BUCKS.
JONAH: WE GOOD?
ZIG: YEAH, WE'RE GOOD.
(HURRIED FOOTSTEPS)
DREW:
OH! THERE YOU ARE.
LOOK, I WANTED TO APOLOGIZE
FOR BEING A JERK ABOUT JONAH.
BECKY: YEAH, SURE.
DREW: OH, COME ON, BECKY.
DON'T BE LIKE THAT, ALL RIGHT?
WE HAVE TO VOLUNTEER TOGETHER
AND I DON'T WANNA SPEND THE
WHOLE TIME FIGHTING WITH YOU.
SO IF YOU SAY HE'S A GOOD GUY,
THEN I'LL BELIEVE YOU...
(DREW'S VOICE FADES OUT)
OR AT LEAST I'LL TRY TO.
ALL RIGHT, MAYBE WE CAN GO
MINI-GOLFING TOGETHER
SOMETIME...
FRANKIE:
WHAT DO YOU THINK
HE'S DOING?!
SHAY:
MAYBE HE WANTED TO SHOW HER
HIS LOCKER?
WINSTON:
DON'T YOU JUST LOVE
MY LOCKER?
SHAY: SEE?
WINSTON: IT'S JUST SO...
PRIVATE.
SHAY:
UH-OH.
I KNEW IT!
FRANKIE! WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
FRANKIE:
I THINK THE BETTER QUESTION
IS WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
LOLA AND I WERE JUST HAVING
A FASCINATING CONVERSATION
ABOUT "THE CATCHER IN THE RYE."
FRANKIE:
GIMME A BREAK.
LOLA'S NEVER READ THAT BOOK.
I THINK YOU'RE MAKING
SOME UNFAIR ASSUMPTIONS
ABOUT OUR CANDY-HAIRED
FRIEND OVER HERE.
LOLA: HEY, THANKS.
FRANKIE: UGH!
WERE YOU GONNA KISS HER
OR NOT?!
WINSTON: HA! I KNEW IT!
FRANKIE: KNEW WHAT?!
THAT YOU WERE
SETTING ME UP!
I WAS TRYING TO SEE
IF I COULD TRUST YOU.
SO YOU COULDN'T JUST TALK TO ME
LIKE A NORMAL HUMAN BEING?!
FRANKIE:
THINGS WERE FEELING
SO GOOD BETWEEN US.
SO YOU SENT LOLA
TO ENTRAP ME?!
I WAS TRYING TO SEE
IF YOU WOULD CHEAT ON ME AGAIN!
I MADE A MISTAKE.
I'M NOT GONNA PRETEND
THAT I DIDN'T.
BUT IT WAS ONE,
TINY KISS, FRANKIE.
HE'S RIGHT, FRANKS.
WE DIDN'T EVEN USE TONGUE.
FRANKIE: OKAY, EW.
WINSTON: YOU CAN'T PUNISH ME
FOREVER,
AND YOU CAN'T KEEP PLAYING ME
HOT AND COLD.
YOU'RE BEING CRAZY.
FRANKIE: HEY-
WINSTON: WELL, IT'S TRUE!
YOU'RE ACTING LIKE
A TOTAL PSYCHO.
FRANKIE:
OKAY. WELL,
IF YOU REALLY FEEL THAT WAY,
THEN YOU CAN FIND SOMEONE ELSE
TO BE IN YOUR DUMB MUSICAL.
WINSTON:
WHAT'RE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I QUIT!
(RECEDING FOOTSTEPS)
HERE.
I AM JUST GLAD
THAT THIS IS ALL OVER.
NOT SO FAST.
WHAT'RE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
DAMON'S GUYS ARE
COMING FOR US.
THERE'S ALL SORTS OF THREATS
POPPING UP ONLINE.
FROM WHO?
TINY: JASON, MOSTLY.
ZIG: WAIT,
FROM OUR SCIENCE CLASS?
YEAH. HE'S ONE
OF DAMON'S BOYS.
"T AND HIS BOY ZIG
ARE GONNA GET IT
FOR WHAT THEY DID TO D.
BE SURE OF IT."
ZIG: BUT WE DIDN'T EVEN DO IT!
TINY: I DON'T EVEN THINK
IT MATTERS.
THEY'RE THREATENING
VINCE, TOO.
"TOMORROW NIGHT,
IT'S GONNA BE SHOWTIME
AT DEGRASSI
FOR ZIG AND HIS CREW."
DOES THAT MEAN SOMETHING'S
GONNA HAPPEN AT THE MUSICAL?
AT SCHOOL?
GRACE:
THAT'S NOT EVEN
THE WORST OF IT.
"ZIG AND THAT BLONDE OF HIS
BETTER WATCH THEIR BACKS."
GRACE:
MAYBE YOU GUYS
SHOULD TALK TO SOMEONE.
ESPECIALLY IF THIS IS
GONNA HAPPEN AT SCHOOL.
NO-NO, WE CAN'T.
IF ANYONE FINDS OUT
WHO SHOT DAMON,
ME, TINY, VINCE...
WE'RE ALL GOING DOWN.
TINY:
IF THEY'RE COMING FOR US...
I DON'T WANNA GET HURT AGAIN.
ZIG: WE'RE NOT GONNA
LET ANYTHING HAPPEN TO YOU,
OR ANYONE THAT
WE CARE ABOUT.
THEN WHAT DO WE DO?
RUN AND HIDE?
ZIG:
NO.
NO, WE STAND UP
AND WE FIGHT.
WINSTON:
♪ An incredible discovery, ♪
♪ A source of renewable energy ♪
ZOE:
♪ It's amazing! ♪
♪ I can't believe
It's true ♪
IMOGEN:
NO, ZOE, YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO CROSS TO STAGE RIGHT.
ZOE:
EVEN THOUGH I'M TRIPLE THREAT
WITH A PHOTOGRAPHIC MEMORY,
YOU CAN'T EXPECT ME TO LEARN
AN ENTIRE SHOW IN ONE DAY.
WINSTON:
WELL, YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO,
SEEING AS FRANKIE DECIDED
TO BAIL LAST MINUTE.
ARE YOU OKAY?
I KNOW YOU WROTE THIS
MUSICAL FOR HER.
FINE. I'M... GREAT.
I'M SURE ZOE WILL DO
A GOOD JOB.
HMPH!
NO, I'LL DO A GREAT JOB.
IMOGEN:
WE'RE JUST LUCKY
I MANAGED TO CONVINCE PILL
TO MAKE AN EXCEPTION TO ZOE'S
"NO EXTRA-CURRICULAR" RULE.
ZOE:
SHE COULD SEE YOU WERE IN
DESPERATE NEED OF A SUPERHERO.
MS. PILL:
IMOGEN.
COULD I SPEAK WITH YOU
IN PRIVATE PLEASE?
BUT YOU SAID IT WAS OKAY
FOR ZOE TO STEP IN FOR FRANKIE.
MS. PILL:
THERE ARE SOME CONCERNS
ABOUT THE MUSICAL GOING
FORWARD AS PLANNED
THAT I NEED TO DISCUSS
WITH YOU.
YOU'RE CANCELLING
THE MUSICAL?
WINSTON: WHAT?!
ZOE: THIS IS AN OUTRAGE!