♪ BUT SOMEBODY BETTER STOP ME ♪
♪ 'CAUSE MY FEET
DON'T TOUCH THE GROUND ♪
JIMMY:
(PLAYS SOLO)
♪ I CAN'T KEEP MY HANDS
OFF OF YOU ♪
JIMMY:
(PLAYS SOLO)
CRAIG:
♪ I CAN'T KEEP MY HANDS
OFF OF YOU ♪
ALL RIGHT, STOP.
STOP.
JIMMY...
LOOK, UNLESS YOUR
LAST NAME IS HENDRIX
AND YOU'VE COME BACK
TO ROCK US FROM THE GRAVE,
NO SOLOS WHILE I'M SINGING.
WE'RE NEVER GONNA GET
A WEDDING JOB.
CRAIG:
NO. NO, WE WILL.
AND-AND-AND EVERY CENT WE EARN
WE'LL SPEND ON RECORDING GEAR.
WE'LL BE ABLE TO CUT
OUR OWN RECORD.
(SCOFFS) LOOK,
THE MUSIC YOU HAVE US PLAYING
IS LAME.
AND WEDDING BANDS
ARE LAME.
ERGO,
YOU'RE LAME.
CRAIG:
NO, YOUR FUNK GUITAR IS LAME.
(ARGUING)
(CYMBALS REVERBERATE)
OKAY, OKAY.
WHAT'S LAME
IS SITTING AROUND
AND CRITICIZING.
UNLESS YOU HAVE
A BETTER IDEA.
WEDDINGS ARE GIGS,
I GUESS.
(HORN BEEPS)
THAT'S MY DAD.
UH YEAH,
JIMMY,
IS IT COOL
IF I GET A RIDE WITH YOU?
YEAH.
THANKS FOR BACKING ME UP,
EL.
I LIKE PLAYING WITH YOU.
THE BAND, I MEAN.
I'VE REALLY LEARNED A LOT.
WELL, IT SHOWS.
YOUR DRUMMING'S TIGHT.
NOT ON THAT LAST NUMBER.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, LET ME GIVE YOU
A LITTLE LESSON
IN FUNK DRUMMING.
IN FUNK,
IT'S ALL ABOUT
THE ACCENT BEAT.
SO IT'S LIKE...
(IMITATES BEAT)
(DRUMMING)
YOU GOT IT.
YOU GOTTA FEEL IT.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
JOEY:
WELL, THERE ARE A FEW OPTIONS
IN YOUR PRICE RANGE.
THERE'S THIS LITTLE BABY
RIGHT HERE.
IT'S GOT STYLE,
PERFORMANCE.
IT'S AN ALL-IN-ONE
COOL LITTLE PACKAGE.
DIANE:
MY EX-BOYFRIEND SAID I
SHOULDN'T BUY AN IMPORT.
JOEY:
WELL, I HAVE TO QUESTION
THE WISDOM OF ANY MAN
STUPID ENOUGH TO LET YOU GO.
THE MAN'S OBVIOUSLY A FOOL.
DIANE:
NO, I AM.
I'M THE ONE
WHO PUT HIS BAND UP
TO PLAY MY SISTER'S
WEDDING THIS WEEKEND
BEFORE HE DUMPED ME
AND FELL OFF THE FACE
OF THE EARTH.
SO YOU'RE LOOKING
FOR A WEDDING BAND?
UH, I HAVE A BAND.
WE CAN DO WEDDINGS.
DIANE,
THIS IS CRAIG.
HE'S A MUSICIAN,
CAR-HOP,
AND SHAMELESS
SELF-PROMOTER.
I SWEAR, EVERY OTHER BAND
IN THE CITY IS BOOKED.
I'M SCRAMBLING.
WELL, IF IT'S ALL RIGHT
WITH YOU,
YOU COULD COME BY THE HOUSE
TOMORROW NIGHT.
YOU CAN GET THE BAND
TO AUDITION FOR YOU
AND I CAN TALK YOU
INTO AN IMPORT.
OVER A GLASS OF WINE?
UH, YEAH.
IT'S A DEAL.
I'LL CALL YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
WHO'S THE MAN?!
YOU ARE, JOEY.
THAT'S RIGHT.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
CRAIG:
WHAT'RE THE ODDS?
JUST WHEN WE NEED
OUR FIRST GIG,
THIS GIRL WALKS RIGHT
ONTO THE LOT.
IT'S LIKE SOMEONE UP THERE
WANTS US TO PLAY A WEDDING.
THE GOD
OF MEDIOCRITY?
"DOWNTOWN SASQUATCH,
GO FORTH AND PLAY
THE CHICKEN DANCE."
(LAUGHING)
RIGHT?
SO,
THE OTHER NIGHT,
YOU AND ELLIE...?
WHAT?
WE REHEARSED SOME MORE.
WE DID SOME
HARDCORE FUNKING.
YOU DO HEAR THE WORDS
COMING OUT OF YOUR MOUTH?
WHATEVER.
WE HUNG OUT,
WE WATCHED A DVD.
OKAY,
WHICH ONE?
"CRAIG INTENTIONS"?
"HOW CRAIG GOT
HIS GROOVE BACK"?
90 PERCENT OF MY ISSUES
IN LIFE -
GIRLS, GIRLS, GIRLS.
TRUE.
SO THIS YEAR,
I'M A MONK.
JUST SCHOOL
AND THE BAND.
NO DISTRACTIONS,
NO DRAMA.
GOOD.
WELL, GOOD THING
YOU PUT THE CUTEST GIRL
IN SCHOOL ON DRUMS.
MAYBE YOU DIDN'T
HEAR ME.
(LAUGHING)
NO DISTRACTIONS,
EH BUD?
JT:
LIBERTY? WAIT UP.
HOW HAVE YOU
BEEN FEELING?
ARE STILL REPULSED BY
THE CONCEPT OF BREAKFAST?
ARE YOU EVER GONNA
TALK TO ME AGAIN?
OKAY, WHATEVER.
IF THERE'S SOMETHING
I CAN DO FOR YOU,
ANYTHING AT ALL,
I'LL DO IT.
YOU COULD MANGLE
YOUR MALE PARTS
IN A TRAGIC INDUSTRIAL
ACCIDENT.
MANNY:
HEY SPINNER. DARCY.
PETER:
HEY MANNY,
HAVE A SEAT.
CAN'T WE JUST CALL IT
WATER UNDER THE BRIDGE?
MY MOTHER'S HAD ME
ON LOCKDOWN FOR WEEKS.
PLEASE.
I'M NOT FINISHED.
CRAIG:
I THINK YOU ARE.
YOU DON'T TALK
TO HER,
YOU DON'T EVEN
LOOK AT HER...
EVER AGAIN,
OR YOU DEAL
WITH ME.
CLEAR?
CRYSTAL.
LET'S GET OUTTA HERE.
YOU OKAY?
SIMPSON'S A BIG FAN
OF THE MAYO.
IT'S LIKE GLOBULAR.
ARE YOU OKAY
IN A BIGGER SENSE?
DIDN'T YOU SEE
THE VIDEO?
YOU KNOW, ME,
LOTS OF VODKA,
LITTLE CLOTHING?
NO, I DIDN'T.
I MISSED IT.
OKAY, I DID.
BUT I CLOSED IT
REALLY QUICKLY.
UGGGH!
PLEASE LET ME DIE.
WHO CARES
THAT I SAW IT?
I DO, OKAY?
YOU'RE YOU.
IS IT WEIRD TO SAY
THAT I WISH
I WAS THERE THAT NIGHT?
TO STOP THAT FREAK
FROM FILMING YOU?
NO,
IT'S NOT WEIRD.
IT MAKES ME FEEL BETTER.
LIKE YOU'RE MY PROTECTOR.
WHAT ARE FRIENDS FOR,
RIGHT?
THERAPIST:
SO, CRAIG, TELL US WHAT'S
BEEN GOING ON WITH YOU.
CRAIG:
WELL, ELLIE AND I HAVE
AN AUDITION TONIGHT
FOR A WEDDING GIG.
(APPLAUSE)
SO I'M GOOD,
SO I'M FEELING GOOD.
I'M HAPPY.
YOU GUYS HAVE SEEN ME
DOWN IN THE DEPTHS,
SO IT'S GOOD TO BE COMING OUT
THE OTHER SIDE
FEELING STRONG.
BUT I GOTTA SAY,
I'D BE NOWHERE
WITHOUT THAT GIRL
OVER THERE.
ELLIE'S JUST BEEN INCREDIBLE.
THANKS.
(APPLAUSE)
THANK YOU.
JOEY, THAT'S WHAT
YOU'RE WEARING?
MY LEISURE SUIT'S
AT THE CLEANERS.
IN CASE YOU DIDN'T KNOW,
THERE'S AN INSANELY HOT WOMAN
WHO'S GOING TO BE OVER HERE
IN OH... IN 20 MINUTES.
I'M AWARE.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
YOU WERE ALL OVER
HER YESTERDAY.
I KNOW.
AND THEN I FOUND OUT
THAT DIANE IS 23.
I'M 34, CRAIG.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO
WITH A 23-YEAR-OLD?
DO YOU NEED ME
TO DRAW A DIAGRAM?
(LAUGHS)
WHAT?
AH, COME ON.
WHAT ABOUT YOU, HUH?
THAT ELLIE GIRL
SEEMS KIND OF CUTE.
SHE'S CUTE.
SHE'S A FRIEND.
SHE'S A FRIEND
WHO HAPPENS TO BE A GIRL.
SHE'S UM...
SHE'S FRIEND-GIRL,
IF YOU WILL.
JOEY:
UH YEAH,
TAKE IT FROM SOMEONE
WHO KNOWS -
THERE AIN'T NO SUCH THING.
CRAIG:
OKAY, UH...
THANKS FOR COMING DOWN
TO AUDITION US, DIANE.
(AMP FEEDBACK)
WE'RE DOWNTOWN SASQUATCH.
AW!
(FUNK MUSIC)
♪ EVERYBODY ♪
♪ GOT A SECRET ♪
♪ PARTY PEOPLE ♪
♪ GETTING DOWN ♪
♪ BUT SOMEBODY ♪
♪ LET HER STOP ME ♪
♪ 'CAUSE MY FEET DON'T
TOUCH THE GROUND ♪
♪ I CAN'T KEEP MY HANDS
OFF OF YOU ♪
♪ AND THERE'S NOTHING
I CAN DO ♪
♪ I CAN'T KEEP MY HANDS
OFF OF... ♪
♪ YOU! ♪
DIANE:
THEY'RE ALMOST TOO COOL
FOR MY SISTER.
JOEY:
WELL, I'M JUST HAPPY
THAT YOU WERE ABLE TO REPLACE
YOUR EX'S BAND.
(SIGHS)
I GUESS YOU MUST STILL BE
REELING FROM THAT.
THE BREAKUP,
I MEAN.
UH...I DON'T THINK SO.
WHO NEEDS 200 POUNDS
OF IDIOT
DROOLING ON THEM
ALL THE TIME?
NOPE.
DONE. OVER.
AND YOU CAN GET OVER SOMEONE
SO QUICKLY?
ALL 200 POUNDS?
JUST THE WAY I AM.
I KNOW WHAT I WANT
AND I ACT ON IT.
LIFE'S TOO SHORT.
CHEERS.
OOH, GOTTA GO.
REHEARSAL DINNER.
SO NOT LOOKING FORWARD
TO THIS WEDDING.
THERE NOTHING QUITE
SO DEPRESSING
AS BEING DATELESS
IN A BRIDESMAID'S DRESS.
THANK YOU.
WELL, UH...
IF YOU NEED A DATE,
I HAPPEN TO KNOW A NICE,
SINGLE GUY
WHO MATCHES MOST DRESSES.
WELL, IF YOU HAPPEN
TO SPEAK TO HIM?
TELL HIM DIANE WANTS HIM
TO BE HER DATE
AND TO CALL HER TOMORROW.
OKAY.
BYE.
(GIGGLING)
SPINNER: (ON THE PHONE)
DARCE, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
ON SUNDAY?
YEAH, I KNOW
YOU HAVE CHURCH.
WHAT ABOUT AFTER?
NOTHING, EH?
HEY, JIMMY AND I,
WE'RE GONNA JET.
SO I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
CRAIG:
WAIT,
WE'RE CELEBRATING.
NO, WE'RE STUDYING.
YOU'RE CELEBRATING.
YOUR DRUM LESSON?
SO GREAT.
I JUST WANTED
TO SAY THANKS.
I SHOULD THANK YOU
FOR SAVING THE BAND,
AND BACKING ME UP
ALL THE TIME.
WELL, I'VE HEARD YOU SAY
A LOT IN GROUP
ABOUT NEEDING PEOPLE.
I THINK WE ALL DO
SOMETIMES.
MANNY!
HEY, OVER HERE!
JOIN US.
I DIDN'T WANT TO INTERRUPT.
ARE YOU SURE YOU GUYS
DON'T WANT ANY PRIVACY?
WHO NEEDS PRIVACY?
WE'RE ALL FRIENDS HERE,
RIGHT?
RIGHT.
FRIEND CITY.
SO... CRAIGS,
ANYTHING YOU WANT TO SHARE
WITH YOUR BEST FRIEND
IN THE WHOLE WORLD?
I THOUGHT ELLIE
WAS YOUR BEST FRIEND.
ELLIE, ELLIE.
WHO'S ELLIE?
OH, YEAH!
SHE'S THAT CUTE,
SMART, FUNNY GIRL.
THE ONE YOU HAD A DATE
WITH LAST NIGHT.
IT WASN'T A DATE.
MONKS DON'T DATE.
IT WAS FRIENDS
HANGING OUT.
MATTER OF FACT?
MY OTHER FRIEND, MANNY,
JOINED US.
CUE THE ROMANTIC
TRAIN WRECK.
JOEY, HEY,
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
OH, UH...
I WAS JUST GETTING THESE...
UM.... UH...
BOTH:
PROPHYLACTICS?
JOEY:
YEAH.
YEAH, MARCO,
THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT I'M DOING.
BECAUSE, UH, WELL,
YOU GOTTA BE SAFE, RIGHT?
MARCO:
SURE.
JOEY:
SO YOU GUYS REMEMBER THAT,
OKAY?
NO GLOVE - NO LOVE.
EWWW.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE KILLING ME, MAN.
THIS THING IS
WAY TOO HEAVY.
(WHISTLES)
NEED A HAND?
(SNEEZES)
OWWWW! MY TOE!
SORRY.
I GOT DISTRACTED.
OH, CRAIG?
CHECK IT OUT.
HI GUYS.
ELLIE.
I INVITED MANNY ALONG.
I THOUGHT WE MIGHT NEED
AN EXTRA HAND.
ELLIE:
YEAH, VERY PRACTICAL
ROADIE COSTUME.
CRAIG:
WHY?
WHY MUST THEY BE SO HOT?
MARCO:
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO FIND YOUR FRIENDS HOT.
IT'S NOT MY FAULT.
I'M NOT THE ONE WHO SHOWED UP
LOOKING LIKE THAT.
WHAT?
YOU SAID YOU WERE
GOING TO BE A MONK.
THE MONK IS TIRED
OF THE MONASTERY, OKAY?
THE MONASTIC LIFE
JUST WASN'T FOR HIM.
AND NOW I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT TO DO.
OKAY, IF YOU'RE HERE
TO DO THINGS,
YOU SHOULD DO THINGS.
THERE'S NOTHING
ELSE TO DO.
UNLESS...
CRAIG LOVES
MY TAMBOURINE.
YEAH.
WE DON'T NEED ANY LOW-RENT
POP TARTS IN OUR BAND.
WELL, THEY DO SAY
THERE SHOULD BE
AT LEAST ONE ATTRACTIVE GIRL
IN EVERY BAND.
OH, YOU'RE NOT
CALLING ME UGLY.
GIRLS, THIS IS JOEY.
JOEY, THESE ARE MY FRIENDS
MIA AND KATHERINE.
HI.
DIANE:
JOEY HAS HIS OWN BUSINESS.
YEAH. I'M A SALES
REPRESENTATIVE
FOR PREVIOUSLY
LOVED VEHICLES.
(LAUGHING)
I'M A USED CAR SALESMAN.
YOU MIGHT HAVE SEEN
MY COMMERCIAL:
"GIVE YOU THE SHIRT
OFF MY BACK".
(LAUGHING)
NO?
CRAIG:
CHECK ONE, TWO. CHECK.
(LAUGHING)
MIA:
OH MY GOD,
YOU SO HAD US GOING THERE
FOR A SECOND.
THE GUY IN THE
JEREMIAH MOTORS AD
IS SO CHEESEBALL.
(LAUGHING)
CRAIG:
GOOD EVENING,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
WE'RE DOWNTOWN SASQUATCH!
LET'S DANCE.
UH, NO, NO.
C'MON,
IT'LL BE FUN!
JOEY:
YOU REALLY DON'T WANT
TO SEE ME DANCE.
♪ OOUUW! ♪
(FUNK MUSIC)
♪ EVERYBODY ♪
♪ GOT A SECRET ♪
♪ PARTY PEOPLE ♪
♪ GETTING DOWN ♪
♪ BUT SOMEBODY ♪
♪ LET HER STOP ME ♪
♪ 'CAUSE MY FEET
DON'T TOUCH THE GROUND ♪
RELAX.
DANCE WITH ME.
WHAT?
THESE ARE SOME
OF MY BEST MOVES.
(LAUGHS)
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
OH YEAH. OH YEAH.
THAT IS A GOOD ONE.
♪ I CAN'T KEEP MY HANDS
OFF OF... ♪
♪ YOU! ♪
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
MR. JIMMY BROOKS.
(PLAYING GUITAR)
COME ON!
MANNY:
I CAN'T! I CAN'T!
CRAIG:
COME ON!
YOU ARE A DANCING MACHINE,
MR. JEREMIAH,
AND YOU'RE
WEARING ME OUT,
MY DAD'S NAME
IS MR. JEREMIAH.
I'M PARCHED.
WELL, THEN...
WHY DON'T I
GET US A DRINK.
BE RIGHT BACK.
HI. CAN I GET
TWO RED WINES, PLEASE.
NO, WAIT.
WHISKEY SOURS
ARE HIPPER.
TWO WHISKEY SOURS.
KATHERINE:
UNLESS DIANE'S
REBOUNDING MAJORLY,
I DON'T SEE ANY EXCUSE.
MIA:
NO. I WAS TRYING TO COME UP
WITH A WAY
TO DESCRIBE HIS DANCING?
ALL I COULD THINK OF
WAS "SPASTIC DONKEY".
(LAUGHING)
KATHERINE:
OH, WOULD SOMEONE PUT
THAT DONKEY OUT TO PASTURE!
HE'S TOTALLY ROBBING
THE CRADLE.
MIA:
NO, DIANE IS TOTALLY
ROBBING THE GRAVE!
DIANE, I-
I'M NOT FEELING WELL.
IT JUST-
IT CAME ON SUDDENLY.
DID YOU CATCH
SOMETHING?
THANK YOU
FOR THE DANCE.
DOWNTOWN SASQUATCH:
♪ STEP ON DOWN ♪
♪ MOVE IT ALL AROUND ♪
♪ SHAKE YOUR BODY
TO THIS FUNKY SOUND ♪
♪ STEP ON DOWN ♪
♪ MOVE IT ALL AROUND ♪
♪ SHAKE YOUR BODY
TO THIS FUNKY SOUND ♪
CRAIG:
♪ LISTEN TO ME ♪
♪ IT'S SO GROOVY... ♪
(BAND BEGINS TO
FALL OUT OF SYNC)
(AMP AND MIC FEEDBACK)
MANNY:
DID YOU JUST THROW
A DRUMSTICK AT MY HEAD?
YOU COULD FEEL IT
THROUGH ALL THAT HAIRSPRAY?
AMAZING!
CRAIG:
WE APOLOGIZE.
WE'RE EXPERIENCING UH,
TECHNICAL DIFFICULTIES.
WE'LL BE BACK
FOR OUR NEXT SET IN 20.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
WHAT DO I DO?
OH WHOA, I'M TOO BUSY
ENJOYING NOT BEING YOU.
CRAIG:
ELLIE, WAIT.
WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON?
ELLIE:
YOU TELL ME.
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO CALLED HER.
WHO SAT THERE
DROOLING OVER HER
ALL NIGHT
LIKE SOME PERV.
AND THIS?
THIS ISN'T ME.
OKAY,
I DON'T DRESS UP.
I'M FLATTERED.
DON'T BE.
THIS IS FOR THE GIG.
THIS DOESN'T MEAN ANYTHING.
ELLIE...
WE DO GROUP TOGETHER.
YOU'VE SEEN ME DOWN
IN THE GUTTER.
LOWER THAN LOW -
LOWER THAN I WANT
ANYONE ELSE TO SEE ME.
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE
MY FRIEND,
MY REALLY GOOD FRIEND.
I'M SO GLAD
I CAN BE THERE FOR YOU.
ELLIE...
BYE.
SEE YOU IN GROUP.
HEY, YOU TOOK OFF
LAST NIGHT.
WHAT HAPPENED?
LET'S JUST SAY
THE DATE ENDED EARLY.
HEY, THAT'S MINE!
HOW WAS THE GIG?
CRAIG:
LET'S JUST SAY
THE GIG ENDED EARLY.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
TELL YOU ABOUT IT
LATER.
DIANE.
WHAT'RE YOU
DOING HERE?
IN YOUR RUSH TO BAIL
LAST NIGHT,
YOU FORGOT
YOUR HIDEOUS FAVOUR.
DON'T LAUGH.
I SPENT WEEKS
MAKING THOSE NASTY THINGS.
THIS IS PRETTY HIDEOUS.
IT'S ALMOST AS BAD AS ME
ON THE DANCE FLOOR.
JOEY, I LIKE
THE WAY YOU DANCE.
DIANA, I FEEL THE NEED
TO REMIND YOU
THAT I'M A 34-YEAR-OLD
SINGLE DAD,
WHO OWNS A USED CAR LOT.
I HAVE A HOUSE
I DON'T EVEN OWN-
AND I'M A 23-YEAR-OLD
GIRL
WHO'S TIRED
OF DATING BOYS.
A GIRL WHO WANTS A CUTE,
SWEET, DEPENDABLE GUY,
WHO REALLY MAKES
HER LAUGH.
A GIRL WHO ALSO MAKES
A KILLER FLORENTINE OMELET.
CAN I COME IN?
AS IF IT WASN'T EMBARRASSING
ENOUGH LAST NIGHT,
NOW YOU HAVE TO SEE ME
WITH MY JAMMIES ON.
I'M SORRY I RUINED
YOUR GIG.
CRAIG:
UH, THE SQUATCH
IS CUT OUT FOR WEDDINGS.
FUNERALS, MAYBE.
DESPITE THE FREAK SHOW,
I HAD FUN.
IT WAS NICE OF YOU
TO INVITE ME.
I HAD ULTERIOR MOTIVES.
EVER SINCE THAT
VIDEO CAME OUT,
THINGS HAVE SUCKED
FOR YOU.
SO I WANTED
TO CHEER YOU UP;
MAKE YOU SMILE AGAIN.
WHAT ARE FRIENDS FOR,
RIGHT?