SPINNER,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
SHHHH...
DARCY:
SOMEONE NEEDS A TIME OUT.
SOMEONE'S ALWAYS
GETTING A TIME OUT.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
IT'S FOR FRIENDSHIP CLUB.
YOU'RE WEARING A BIKINI
TO FRIENDSHIP CLUB?
YOU'RE GONNA GIVE POOR
BABY JESUS A HEART ATTACK.
YOU KNOW YOU SHOULDN'T
TALK LIKE THAT.
BESIDES, I MEANT FOR
THE CAMPING TRIP THIS WEEKEND.
OH, RIGHT.
CAMPING WITH
YOUR BIBLE BUDDIES.
SO GLAD
I'M MISSING THAT.
SPINNER,
YOU SAID YOU'D COME.
WAS I HIGH
AT THE TIME?
JAY:
SPIN, WHAT'S UP?
YOU IN THERE SHOPPING
FOR SOME NICE MINI-SKIRTS?
NO MAN.
CHECKING OUT
SOME MAN-THONGS.
OOOH...
OH HEY, MISSED A HELL
OF A PARTY ON FRIDAY.
PEOPLE WERE ASKING
ABOUT YOU.
DARCY:
JAY? THEY LET YOU OUT
ON PAROLE?
TIME OFF
FOR GOOD BEHAVIOUR.
OH HEY...
NUNS-R-US IS HAVING
A BLACK-AND-WHITE SALE.
YOU SHOULD REALLY
CHECK THAT OUT.
FUNNY.
YOU GUYS ALWAYS
HAVE TO DO THIS?
OH HEY, SPIN,
THIS WEEKEND WE'RE HAVING
A PARTY IN THE RAVINE.
WE'RE GETTING A KEG.
DUDE!
I AM SO THERE!
POSSIBLY.
MAYBE.
WE'LL SEE.
WELL, YOU LET ME KNOW
WHEN SHE'S MAKES UP
YOUR MIND FOR YOU.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
LINUS:
SO WE'RE ALL SINNERS.
BUT, YOU KNOW, IF WE ACCEPT
JESUS INTO OUR HEARTS,
WE'LL BE FREE.
BUT... WAIT A SEC,
IF WE'RE ALL SINNERS
THEN WHAT CAN JESUS DO?
HE CAN FORGIVE YOU.
EXACTLY.
AND YOU KNOW, THAT WAY,
YOU'LL GAIN ENTRANCE
TO HEAVEN.
YEAH, BUT THERE ARE
GOOD PEOPLE OUT THERE
WHO DON'T BELIEVE IN JESUS.
WHAT?
DO THEY JUST GO TO HELL?
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
LINUS:
LISTEN SPINNER,
THAT WAS A GREAT DEBATE.
I'M LOOKING FORWARD
TO SOME MORE.
SAY TOMORROW
AT THE RETREAT?
YEAH.
ABOUT THAT...
I HAVE PLANS TO WORSHIP
WITH A FRIEND.
THAT'S GREAT!
IS YOUR FRIEND
A BELIEVER?
YEAH, HE BELIEVES
IN THINGS...
LIKE BEER.
I COME BEARING
MORNING BAGELS.
I'VE GOT OUR COFFEES.
TWO CREAMS FOR YOU,
TWO SUGARS FOR ME.
OKAY, HAZEL,
WHAT'S THE BIG SECRET?
HAZEL:
THIS SUMMER - ROAD TRIP!
WE HIT THE SOUTHERN
U.S. OF A. -
ORLANDO, MEMPHIS,
ATLANTA -
ALL SUMMER.
WOW, THAT'S...
THAT'S GREAT.
ANNOUNCER:
ATTENTION STUDENTS.
HATZILAKOS:
A YEAR AGO TODAY,
TRAGEDY STRUCK DEGRASSI.
AND SINCE THAT DAY,
WE'VE BECOME
A DIFFERENT SCHOOL.
ZERO TOLERANCE FOR BULLYING,
AND AN OPEN DOOR POLICY
FOR STUDENT CONCERNS.
WE DID THIS TOGETHER.
SPINNER:
HEY JAY, LISTEN...
RADITCH KNOWS,
MAN.
JAY:
ABOUT JIMMY?
YEAH. I'M SURPRISED NOBODY'S
FIGURED IT OUT YET.
JIMMY SET THE WHOLE THING UP
PERFECTLY.
RICK:
YOU PRETENDED TO BE MY FRIEND.
AAAHHHHHHH!
HATZILAKOS:
I'D LIKE TO ANNOUNCE
THAT OUT OF THE MANY PROPOSALS
SUBMITTED,
THE WINNER IS...
A NEW MURAL,
TO BE PAINTED BY
JIMMY BROOKS!
(APPLAUSE)
PAIGE:
THAT'S AMAZING.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU
SUBMITTED A PROPOSAL!
ACTUALLY,
IT'S-IT'S ALL ON ELLIE.
SHE TALKED ME INTO IT.
GEE, ALL THESE PLANS
THAT I DIDN'T KNOW ABOUT.
WELL, JIMMY'S SUCH
A GOOD ARTIST,
AND WITH THE SHOOTING...
WE JUST THOUGHT
IT WAS RIGHT.
CRAIG:
GOOD JOB, MAN.
JIMMY:
THANK YOU.
CRAIG:
THIS IS GREAT.
SO TELL ME...
WHEN DID JIMMY AND ELLIE
BECOME A "WE"?
CRAIG:
SOMEONE LEFT YOU A CARD.
HOW SWEET.
SPINNER:
IT'S A NOTE, MAN,
FROM MY GIRLFRIEND.
HEY, JIMMY,
CONGRATULATIONS, MAN. EH?
LISTEN, I WANT TO HELP OUT
IF THERE IS ANYTHING I CAN DO.
WHATEVER.
PROBABLY NOT A GOOD IDEA,
SPIN.
SPINNER:
COME ON, GUYS.
LET ME HELP OUT.
LOOK, WHEN I SAID
YOU WERE DEAD TO ME,
I MEANT FOREVER.
YOU DON'T EXIST.
SO, THIS WEEKEND?
YOU, ME,
DOZENS OF HORNY HONEYS,
AND AN ICE COLD KEG OF BEER.
SOUND GOOD?
DUDE...
DO YOU EVER THINK ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED WITH...
YOU KNOW, THE SHOOTING...
WITH RICK.
SURE I DO.
THE WAY I SEE IT,
WE DID THE WORLD A FAVOUR.
AND JIMMY?
WE HELPED HIM TOO, RIGHT?
SPIN,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU'RE GETTING YOURSELF
ALL DEPRESSED!
YOU GOT SCHOOL
FOR THAT.
WHAT YOU NEED IS TO GET YOUR
MIND OFF THE DEPRESSING CRAP.
HAVE SOME FUN.
DUDE,
YOU ARE SO RIGHT.
SPINNER:
HEY UM...
IS MY NAME STILL ON
THAT SIGN-UP SHEET?
LOOK UNDER "I"
FOR "IDIOT".
I DON'T KNOW, SPIN.
THERE'S VOLLEYBALL,
BARBECUE.
I DON'T THINK
YOU CAN HANDLE IT.
YOU DON'T THINK
I CAN HANDLE IT?
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
♪♪♪
WELL... ALL RIGHT.
SO, IF I'M NOT
ON YOUR TEAM,
THAT PUTS ME ON
THE WINNING TEAM, RIGHT?
THAT'S FUNNY.
LUCKY MAN.
YOU'RE NOT HURTING.
KIM'S MY LIFE.
DUDE,
YOU'RE MARRIED?!
MARRIED?
NO. NO.
THIS IS A...
THIS IS A PRE-ENGAGEMENT
RING.
WE GAVE THEM TO EACH OTHER
LAST YEAR
WHEN WE PLEDGED
OUR ABSTINENCE.
SO YOU WILLINGLY GAVE UP...
WITH HER?
LINUS:
SPINNER, KIM AND I,
WE LOVE EACH OTHER,
AND WE LOVE JESUS.
THIS IS REALLY THE BEST WAY
TO SHOW IT, MAN.
YEAH, BUT IF JESUS
DIDN'T WANT US TO HAVE SEX,
HE'D MAKE EVERY GIRL LOOK
LIKE QUASIMODO'S SISTER.
I MEAN...
(CHUCKLES)
RELATIONSHIPS ARE NOT
ONLY ABOUT SEX.
THEY'RE ABOUT SPIRITUAL
CONNECTEDNESS, MAN.
COME ON.
ELLIE:
SO...ROAD TRIP THIS SUMMER.
GUESS WE'LL PUT THOSE
ART CLASSES ON HOLD.
I GUESS SO.
I HAVE A SUMMER JOB
ANYWAY.
THERE'S THIS TINY
COMIC BOOK COMPANY.
I'M DOING THEIR WEBSITE.
YOU'RE KIDDING.
THAT'S AMAZING.
ELLIE:
IT'S A JOB.
I WAS GONNA HIRE YOU
TO DO THE ART WORK,
BUT WHATEV.
HAZEL?
I DID NOT KNOW
YOU WERE COMING.
BUT SO GLAD
TO HAVE YOU HERE!
MARCO:
OKAY, THE FOUNTAIN'S DOWN,
AND I AM PARCHED.
AND SOMEONE HAS GOT
TO WASH THESE BRUSHES.
BOTH:
EW.
LOOKS LIKE THIS PROJECT
COULD USE
A LITTLE MORE
ORGANIZATION.
MARCO, I HAVE A CASE
OF WATER IN MY CAR.
WHY DON'T YOU GO GET IT?
PAIGE, I'LL WASH THESE BRUSHES.
AND ELLIE...
WHY DON'T YOU KEEP DOING
WHAT YOU'RE DOING?
(GUITAR PLAYING)
LINUS:
ALL RIGHT, GUYS...
OKAY,
BEFORE I SING THIS SONG,
I WANNA TALK ABOUT SOMETHING.
FEAR.
SPINNER,
WHAT SCARES YOU MOST?
SPINNER:
MS. KWAN?
(EVERYONE CHUCKLES)
BE SERIOUS.
MELINDA?
I'M SCARED OF DYING.
BUT WHY, MELINDA?
I MEAN, IF YOU'RE FORGIVEN
BY JESUS,
YOU'LL GO TO HEAVEN.
LINUS:
OKAY. BUT WHAT IF YOU DIE
BEFORE YOU MAKE PEACE?
SO BEFORE JESUS
COULD FORGIVE YOU?
YOU'D GO TO HELL.
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT THAT,
SPINNER?
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
DON'T YOU HAVE ANYTHING
YOU WANT TO BE FORGIVEN FOR?
NO.
NOT PARTICULARLY.
WHAT ABOUT YOUR FRIEND JIMMY?
WHAT ABOUT HIM?
NICE, DARCY.
NO BRAINWASHING, HUH?
SPIN, I DIDN'T TELL HIM
ANYTHING.
YEAH, THEN HOW'D
HE KNOW, DARCY?
HE'S PSYCHIC?
I GUESS I MENTIONED IT
TO KIM.
OH, THAT'S GREAT.
JUST SPILL MY MOST PRIVATE
SECRETS TO EVERYBODY.
WHO ARE YOU CALLING?
JAY.
MY FRIEND.
I'M OUTTA HERE.
SPINNER, PLEASE.
I'M SORRY THAT LINUS
AMBUSHED YOU.
HE SHOULDN'T HAVE.
IT WAS A MISTAKE.
NO, THIS WEEKEND
WAS A MISTAKE.
THIS WHOLE RELATIONSHIP
IS A MISTAKE.
JAY, WHAT'S UP, MAN?
(LOUD MUSIC COMES FROM CAR)
SPINNER:
IT'S ABOUT TIME, BUDDY.
LET'S GO.
SWEET MOTHER MARY.
WHO KNEW CHRISTIAN GIRLS
COULD BE SO HOT?
SPINNER:
YEAH, BUT TRUST ME,
THIS PLACE IS NO PARTY.
NOT YET.
NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I JUST DROVE
TWO HOURS FOR YOU.
AT LEAST LET ME JOIN
YOUR CHRISTIAN FRIENDS
FOR A TASTY HOT DOG
OR A COOL,
REFRESHING BEVERAGE?
ONE HOTDOG.
BEER STAYS IN THE CAR,
YOUR MOUTH STAYS SHUT,
AND SOMETHING ELSE
STAYS IN YOUR PANTS.
CLEAR?
I DON'T KNOW.
LET ME PRAY ON IT.
HAZEL:
HOW COME NOTHING RHYMES
WITH "ORANGE"?
IT'S SUCH A LONELY WORD.
AND WHAT'S NOT
A LONELY WORD?
HAZEL, CAUSE IT GOES
SO PERFECTLY WITH JIMMY.
THAT DOESN'T EVEN RHYME.
SO, ELLIE,
THIS COMIC BOOK WEBSITE,
ARE YOU GOING
TO USE FLASH?
UH, IT'S ALL CUSTOMIZED,
BUT I'M ALSO PUTTING
TOGETHER TEMPLATES.
I REALLY LIKE
THE CRIMSON KID.
FLASH...
YOU GUYS WERE TALKING
ABOUT COMIC BOOKS, RIGHT?
I'VE BEEN READING UP.
UM... WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT FLASH ANIMATION.
IT'S A COMPUTER THING.
IT'S COMPLICATED.
RIGHT.
AND I WOULDN'T GET THAT.
MY DAD JUST COULDN'T
TAKE IT ANYMORE
SO HE TOOK OFF
ON HIS HOG.
AND YOUR MOM?
WAS SHE OKAY?
WELL, I HELPED HER THROUGH
HER PAINKILLER ADDICTION,
BUT ONCE SHE WAS
IN DRUG REHAB,
IT WAS LIKE...
LIKE I WAS ADDICTED...
ADDICTED TO HELPING PEOPLE.
REALLY?
YEAH.
SO THAT'S WHEN
YOU LEFT SCHOOL?
AND HEADED DOWN
TO SOUTH AMERICA, YES,
TO THE MOUNTAINS OF ECUADOR.
I BUILT A CHURCH,
AND A ONE-ROOM SCHOOL
AND A WELL.
IT JUST FELT SO GOOD.
MAN, JAY IS QUITE
THE STORYTELLER.
YEAH, AND MELINDA'S NOT
THE SHARPEST TOOL IN THE SHED.
HEY, LISTEN,
I'M SORRY FOR
WHAT I SAID BEFORE.
I DIDN'T MEAN IT.
I CAN PARTY TOO,
YOU KNOW?
SO, DON'T THINK
I'M A COMPLETE LOSER.
I DON'T THINK
YOU'RE A LOSER.
I THINK
YOU'RE GREAT.
I REALLY FEEL LIKE
I CAN TALK TO YOU,
YOU KNOW?
JUST...NOT HERE.
MELINDA:
LET'S GO SOMEPLACE PRIVATE.
JAY?
CAN I TALK TO YOU
JUST FOR A SECOND?
JAY:
SPINNER, SLOW DOWN.
I WAS JUST ABOUT
TO REDEFINE BIBLE THUMPING.
NO, MAN.
YOU WERE JUST ABOUT
TO TAKE A HIKE.
PRAISE THE LORD!
GOD, THOSE FREAKS
REALLY GOT TO YOU.
HAVE YOU ALWAYS
BEEN THIS STUPID
OR AM I JUST
NOTICING IT NOW?
MAN, EVER SINCE
YOU MET MS. WWJD?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHO YOU ARE ANYMORE.
I MEAN, WHAT KIND OF HOLD
DOES SHE HAVE ON YOU ANYWAYS?
IS SHE THAT GOOD
IN BED?
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT,
MAN.
WE DON'T...
WE DON'T EVEN HAVE SEX.
NO SEX?
NOTHING?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
WHAT'S HER PROBLEM?
SHE BELIEVES IN SOMETHING,
ALL RIGHT?
IS THAT IMPOSSIBLE
FOR YOU TO GET INTO YOUR
TWISTED LITTLE BRAIN?
NO.
LOOK, WHATEVER.
I JUST WANT YOU
TO BE HAPPY.
DARCY:
HOPE YOU DON'T MIND.
I SCOOPED THESE
FROM YOUR CAR.
JAY:
MIND?
NO, I WASN'T GOING
ANYWHERE.
DARCY:
SOMETIMES...
YOU GOTTA BEND
THE RULES.
JUST A LITTLE.
OH, NICE CATCH.
NICE CATCH.
DARCY,
YOU GOING TO PARTAKE?
UGH! TASTES LIKE BARF.
YOU'VE TRIED BEER?
YEAH.
A BIT TOO MUCH OF IT
ONE NIGHT.
AGES AGO.
HENCE,
TASTES LIKE BARF.
WELL, CHEERS TO THAT.
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE GONNA NEED
ANOTHER ROUND.
I'LL GET IT.
NO, NO, NO.
I'LL GO.
JAY:
SO, UNDERNEATH THAT NUN'S HABIT
LIES A LIVING, BREATHING GIRL.
WHO KNEW?
SPINNER.
YEAH, RIGHT,
HE'S ALL ABOUT YOU
THESE DAYS.
I'VE NEVER SEEN HIM
LIKE THIS.
NOT ABOUT ANYBODY.
NOT MANNY?
PAIGE?
OH NO.
HE TOLD ME.
YOU'RE WAY BETTER
THAN PAIGE OR MANNY.
THING IS...
WHAT?
IT'S MANNY.
SHE'S MOVING IN ON HIM.
WHAT?
I THOUGHT
SHE WAS WITH CRAIG.
JAY:
SHE WANTS SOMETHING
ON THE SIDE WITH SPINNER.
I'M TALKING SEX.
HE KEEPS TRYING
TO FIGHT HER OFF BUT...
HOW LONG CAN
HE KEEP FIGHTING?
I MEAN, HE'S A GUY
AND...
WELL, IF HE DOESN'T
GET SOMETHING SOON,
THEN...
GAME OVER.
LOOK, IT'S JUST LIKE
YOU SAID, DARCY.
SOMETIMES YOU GOTTA
BEND THE RULES.
(SIGHS)
YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
DUDE,
I GOT ROUND TWO.
YOUR LADY AWAITS.
HEY... W-WHAT?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
ON SECOND THOUGHT,
NO NEED TO EXPLAIN.
DARCY,
I LOVE YOU.
(CRYING)
ARE YOU OKAY?
I'M FINE.
KEEP GOING.
HEY, WHAT'S WRONG?
WHAT'S WRONG?
IT'S OKAY.
JAY TOLD ME
ABOUT MANNY,
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
WAIT! WHAT?
WHAT MANNY?
I HAVEN'T SPOKEN TO MANNY
IN LIKE, A YEAR.
OKAY,
START AT THE BEGINNING.
WHAT DID JAY TELL YOU,
EXACTLY?
WHO IS YOUR SAVIOUR NOW?!
JAY:
SPINNER!
SPINNER:
WHY DID YOU DO IT, HUH?!
YOU SAID YOU WANTED
SOME ACTION.
I WAS JUST TRYING
TO HELP YOU GET IT!
NO. YOU JUST WANTED
TO RUIN IT,
LIKE YOU'VE RUINED
EVERYTHING IN MY LIFE -
JIMMY AND NOW DARCY.
JAY:
OH YEAH, OH YEAH.
I'M THE DEVIL.
I'M THE EVIL,
LOW-DOWN SINNER.
SOMEBODY SAVE ME!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
GET OUT OF HERE.
I NEVER WANT TO SEE
YOU AGAIN EVER.
GO.
GO!
HAZEL:
SO THIS WHOLE THING -
THIS MURAL -
THIS WAS ALL ABOUT HER?
JIMMY:
OF COURSE NOT.
AND I DIDN'T EVEN MEAN
FOR THAT GIRL TO BE ELLIE.
I GUESS IT LOOKS
A LITTLE BIT LIKE HER -
HAZEL:
A LITTLE BIT?
JIMMY,
THAT'S HER FACE
TO A TEE.
I CAN PAINT IT OVER.
THAT'S NOT THE POINT.
WHY DID YOU PAINT IT
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
OBVIOUSLY YOU LIKE HER.
BE HONEST.
OKAY.
HAZEL, LOOK...
I LOVE YOU.
BUT ELLIE, SHE...
SHE INSPIRES ME.
I SO DID NOT
NEED TO HEAR THAT.
JIMMY:
WELL, HEY, YOU WANTED HONESTY.
I'M BEING HONEST.
NO,
YOU'RE BEING A COWARD.
AND IF YOU WON'T SAY IT,
THEN I WILL.
SO HERE IT IS, JIMMY.
READY?
WE'RE THROUGH.
I'M SORRY...
FOR BRINGING
JAY HERE,
FOR WHAT HE SAID.
FOR EVERYTHING.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
YOU WERE TRYING
TO BE HIS FRIEND -
HIS ONLY FRIEND
BECAUSE, P.S.,
HE'S A JERK.
I LOVE YOU, SPIN.
YOU SHOULDN'T.
I HURT EVERYONE.
YOU, JIMMY...
I'M...
I'M NOT WORTH IT.
YOU ARE.
I KNOW IT.
JESUS KNOWS IT.
HOW CAN JESUS
FORGIVE SOMEONE
WHO GOT HIS
BEST FRIEND SHOT?
BECAUSE HE JUST DOES.
ALL YOU NEED TO DO
IS BELIEVE.
IT'S TOO LATE.
NO, IT'S NOT.
WE'LL FIND JESUS
TOGETHER.
OKAY?
OKAY.