JT:
SO WHAT NOW, MS. SAUVE?
PREGNANCY YOGA?
LAMAZE CLASS?
MAKE A DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENT.
AT THIS POINT,
THE HEALTH OF THE BABY
IS PARAMOUNT.
SO WHO KNOWS?
ONLY MY BROTHER
AND TOBY.
NOT YOUR PARENTS?
LIBERTY,
YOU'RE 6 MONTHS PREGNANT.
I KNOW, MS. SAUVE.
(SIGHS)
BUT MY FATHER...
THERE'S NO WAY
I CAN TELL HIM.
SO YOU'VE JUST BEEN
HIDING IT?
WELL,
LET'S TALK ABOUT OPTIONS.
IT'S LATE IN THE GAME
FOR AN ABORTION,
SO I ASSUME THAT'S OFF
THE TABLE.
ABSOLUTELY.
I WANT TO CARRY THIS BABY
TO TERM.
BUT AFTERWARDS...?
LIBERTY, THERE IS
NO AFTERWARDS, OKAY?
WHAT ABOUT ADOPTION?
I CAN REFER YOU
TO AN AGENCY.
JT:
YES, THAT'S PERFECT.
WE'RE IN.
WE?
JT, YOU BROKE UP
WITH ME.
YEAH,
BUT I'M STILL THE FATHER.
IF YOU DECIDE TO KEEP
THIS BABY,
THEN IT BECOMES
MY PROBLEM TOO.
SAUVE:
SO, DO YOU WANT ME
TO REFER YOU
TO AN ADOPTION AGENCY
OR NOT?
YES.
NO.
SOUNDS LIKE
YOU HAVE A PROBLEM.
(SIGHS)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
JT:
THE GLITTER STICKS
TO THE GLUE,
AND TA-DA!
YOU HAVE YOUR TIARA
LIKE MEGAN AND MADISON.
AND JUST LIKE OUR FAVOURITE
ROYAL PRIMATE -
PRINCESS APE - WEARS.
AND SHE'LL BE COMING UP NEXT!
SO STAY TUNED!
FLOOR DIRECTOR:
CUT, RESET.
HEY, TOBES.
WHAT'RE YOU
DOING HERE?
SURPRISE, SURPRISE.
YOU FORGOT.
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO CATCH
"CLOWN ACADEMY" TONIGHT.
SORRY.
BRAIN FART.
I TOTALLY FORGOT.
I'M DUE
AT THE PHARMACY.
TWO JOBS, SCHOOL,
PREGNANT EX.
NO WONDER YOUR BRAIN
IS FLATULENT.
WELL, THERE IS TWO SOLUTIONS
TO MY PROBLEMS,
MY CAREFREE FRIEND.
MOCHACHINO AND ADOPTION.
ADOPTION?
WOW, YOU SURE LIBERTY
WILL GO FOR THAT?
SHE'S FIFTEEN.
IT'S THE ONLY THING
THAT MAKES SENSE.
FLOOR DIRECTOR:
OKAY, JT. LET'S DO IT.
RIGHT.
OKAY...
WELL, TAKE TWO.
I'M GONNA GO
CONTINUE TO MAKE
A COMPLETE DINK OF MYSELF.
DIRECTOR:
ROLLING TAPE.
MAN:
ROLLING!
EMMA:
(CLEARS HER THROAT)
I'D TELL YOU GUYS
TO GET A ROOM,
BUT YOU HAVE A ROOM.
WHICH ALSO HAPPENS
TO BE MY ROOM.
WELL, TONIGHT
YOUR ROOM IS ALL YOURS
BECAUSE CRAIG IS TAKING ME
TO SEE A BAND.
IT'S FRIEND OF FRIENDS,
IT'S NOTHING SPECIAL.
I THOUGHT WE WERE STUDYING.
UNLESS...
I MEAN,
IT'S NOT REALLY A DATE,
IF YOU WANNA TAG ALONG?
YEAH.
ALMOST PERSUASIVE,
BUT I'LL PASS.
COME ON, EMMA.
IT'S TOTALLY COOL.
EMMA:
IT'S TOTALLY THIRD WHEEL,
CRAIG.
YOU GUYS ARE A COUPLE.
AND I'M... JUST ME.
PLUS, I HAVE A HOT DATE
TONIGHT.
IT'S A VERY SEXY RED.
HEY,
YOU SELL GLITTER GLUE?
WHAT CAN I SAY?
YOUR CRAFTWORK
ON TELEVISION...
IT INSPIRES ME.
YOU KNOW,
I CAN'T HELP BUT WONDER
WHY A GUY
WHO'S GOING TO SCHOOL
IS WORKING SO MANY HOURS.
YOU IN SOME KINDA TROUBLE,
STOCKBOY?
DON'T YOU HAVE
SOMEONE ELSE TO BUG?
JAY:
JUST SAYING...
IF YOU NEED MONEY,
TALK TO ME.
I GOT ALL SORTS OF
CREATIVE SOLUTIONS.
WELL, I CAN DO WITHOUT
YOUR BRAND OF CREATIVITY.
PUT THAT BACK.
ALL OF IT.
WHATEVER YOU SAY,
NARC.
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYS)
EMMA:
JAZZ COMBO,
OR RAISING MONEY
FOR CANCER RESEARCH?
FIGHTING CANCER -
EXCELLENT CHOICE.
NOW IF WE COULD
ONLY STOMP OUT JAZZ
IN OUR LIFETIME.
PETER:
HITTING THE PAVEMENT FOR
A CANCER-FREE WORLD TOO?
YEAH, YOU MEAN ONE
WITHOUT YOU IN IT?
IF YOU NEED A VICTIM
FOR YOUR NEXT
SEXPLOITATION FLICK,
KEEP LOOKING.
MY MOM TOOK
MY CAMERA.
I'M COMPLETELY
UNARMED.
LOOK, IF WE'RE BOTH GONNA BE
ON THE RELAY COMMITTEE,
MAYBE WE SHOULD
START OVER.
MAYBE YOU CAN
GET OUT OF MY WAY?
PA:
ATTENTION STUDENTS:
TODAY'S LUNCH SPECIAL
WILL BE SMOKED HAM
AND MASH POTATOES.
TOBY:
HEY!
MISS YOUR
MOCHACHINO FIX?
MY GRANDMA DECIDED THE HOUSE
NEEDED VACUUMING
AT 6 A.M.
YOU TELL HER ABOUT
THE BABY YET?
NO.
LIKE SHE NEEDS MORE
TO WORRY ABOUT.
LIBERTY!
HERE I GOT YOU SOME...
SOME GINGER TEA.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO HELP
WITH MORNING SICKNESS.
OH, THAT'S SWEET.
THANK YOU.
HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT...
YOU KNOW LIKE OPTIONS?
OR LIFE-PLANS?
NOT REALLY.
LISTEN...
DO YOU REALIZE
WHAT HAVING A KID MEANS?
I MEAN,
FOR YOUR FUTURE?
IT'S JUST NOT LOGICAL.
JT, I DON'T WANT TO ARGUE,
OKAY?
OKAY.
LET ME HELP YOU, OKAY?
I'VE HAVE AN ULTRASOUND
AT 2 P.M.
COME WITH ME?
SIMPSON:
BEFORE WE CONTINUE,
DOES ANYONE HAVE AN
ANNOUNCEMENT TO MAKE?
ABOUT SAY, HIMSELF BEING
AN UP-AND-COMING TV STAR?
BIG HIT WITH THE KIDS.
ON EVERY DAY AT 3:00 P.M.?
MR. SIMPSON,
PLEASE, DON'T.
PLEASE.
SIMPSON:
PEOPLE...
OUR NEXT UNIT
IN MEDIA IMMERSION
IS PRESCHOOL TELEVISION!
WATCH CLOSELY,
BECAUSE WE'RE GONNA LEARN
FROM A MASTER.
JT:
GOBBLE, GOBBLE, GOBBLE,
GOBBLE, GOBBLE...
IT'S ALMOST THANKSGIVING,
AND TODAY,
WE ARE GOING TO BE MAKING
NONE OTHER THAN...
A TURKEY!
GOBBLE, GOBBLE, GOBBLE,
GOBBLE, GOBBLE, GOBBLE...
BUT BEFORE WE MAKE
OUR TURKEYS,
I'M GOING TO NEED MY HANDY
DANDY LITTLE HELPERS!
WHERE ARE MY HANDY-DANDY
LITTLE HELPERS?
THERE THEY ARE!
GOBBLE, GOBBLE, GOBBLE,
GOBBLE, GOBBLE, GOBBLE...
THAT IS SO CUTE!
SHE'S RIGHT.
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME
ABOUT THIS?
YOU'VE ALWAYS WANTED
TO BE ON TV,
AND THERE YOU ARE.
SO DO YOU WANNA TELL HER
OR SHOULD I?
CRAIG:
OKAY, I'LL TELL HER.
WELL...
NO, NO, NO
YOU TELL HER.
YOU TELL HER -
IT'S TOO GOOD.
(CONTINUE ARGUING)
CRAIG AND I,
WE MET THIS REALLY
CUTE GUY.
AND HE'S TOTALLY
YOUR TYPE.
WELL,
CUTE IS MY TYPE.
CRAIG:
HIS NAME IS DEREK.
HE'S A BASKETBALL BUDDY
OF JIMMY'S.
HE'S IN GRADE 10,
BUT HE'S ALL RIGHT.
HEY DEREK!
WEIRD. WEIRD.
I MEAN,
IT'S-IT'S COSMIC.
WE WERE JUST TALKING
ABOUT YOU.
AMAZING.
YOU'D THINK
IT WAS A SETUP.
MANNY:
DEREK,
THIS IS MY SINGLE FRIEND,
EMMA.
DID I MENTION
THAT SHE'S SINGLE?
HEY EMMA.
UM, THESE GUYS
WERE TELLING ME
THAT YOUR PARENTS USED
TO GO TO DEGRASSI?
IT'S PRETTY WEIRD, EH?
IT'S A MAGICAL STORY.
I'LL TELL YOU
ALL ABOUT IT FRIDAY.
UH, FRIDAY?
LIKE, AT NIGHT?
IT'S A DATE.
HOW DOES HE
OR SHE LOOK?
I DON'T KNOW.
I CAN'T.
JT, PLEASE.
IT...
IT LOOKS...
REAL.
PASSED WITH
FLYING COLOURS.
LIKE MOTHER,
LIKE OFFSPRING.
THEY'LL BE HAPPY
TO HEAR THAT
AT THE ADOPTION AGENCY.
REALLY?
YOU'RE SURE?
NO.
I DON'T WANT TO
GIVE OUR BABY UP,
BUT YOU DO,
OBVIOUSLY.
LIBERTY,
IT'S NOT THAT EASY.
WE HAVE LIVES AHEAD OF US -
SCHOOL AND JOBS.
SO?
WE CAN DO IT.
ALL OF IT.
WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
BECAUSE YOU NEEDED IT.
LOOK...
I LOVE YOU, JT.
AND WHATEVER
YOU WANT TO DO
I'M FINE WITH IT.
LET'S KEEP THIS BABY.
BRIGHT AND EARLY,
AS REQUESTED.
MRS. COONEY:
WHO WANTS MUFFINS?
CARROT MUFFINS.
YOUR FAVOURITE.
LIBERTY:
GOOD MORNING,
MRS. COONEY.
MRS. COONEY:
OH LIBERTY,
I AM SO HAPPY
YOU'VE TAKEN THIS ONE BACK.
LUCK OF THE IRISH,
HE'S GOT.
WE'RE BOTH VERY LUCKY.
SPEAKING OF WHICH,
WE HAVE GREAT NEWS.
WE'RE HAVING A BABY.
YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
YEAH, WE ARE.
WE'RE GOING
TO BE PARENTS.
JAMES TIBERIUS,
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT IT TAKES
TO RAISE A CHILD?
YOU ARE FAR,
FAR TOO YOUNG.
WELL, I THOUGHT
THAT YOU COULD HELP US.
I MEAN, YOU RAISED MOM
AND ME.
AND I'M NOT PLANNING
TO SPEND MY RETIREMENT
GOING THROUGH IT AGAIN.
HAVE YOU THOUGHT
ABOUT ADOPTION?
WE'VE CONSIDERED IT,
BUT NO.
LOOK GRANDMA,
WE LOVE EACH OTHER, OKAY?
THAT'S ALL THAT MATTERS.
AND THE REST
WE'LL FIGURE OUT.
THE WAY YOUR FATHER
FIGURED IT OUT?
BY LEAVING YOU
AND YOUR MOTHER
WHEN THE GOING
GOT ROUGH?
I'M NOT LIKE HIM.
NOT AT ALL.
(SIGHS)
LET'S GO.
EMMA. HEY.
OKAY, LOOK...
IF WE'RE BOTH GONNA BE
THE RELAY FOR LIFE COMMITTEE,
DON'T YOU THINK WE SHOULD BE
A LITTLE BIT MORE CIVILIZED?
IT'S A CANCER RUN,
NOT A TEA PARTY.
I KNOW VIDEOTAPING MANNY
WAS STUPID,
BUT SHE ASKED ME
TO DO IT.
SHE WAS DRUNK
AND VERY PERSUASIVE.
AND YOU EMAILING IT
TO YOUR FRIENDS
MAKES IT RIGHT?
NO.
OF COURSE NOT.
PLEDGE FORMS FOR ALL YOUR
FABULOUS CANCER-FIGHTING
FRIENDS
AND FAMILY MEMBERS.
LEAVE NO WALLET UNTAPPED.
LOOK, I SHOULD HAVE NEVER
GONE FOR MANNY.
YOU, ON THE OTHER HAND -
MAJOR CATCH.
SMART, FUNNY,
INSANELY GORGEOUS.
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
I'M INTERESTED?
WE CARE ABOUT THINGS,
IMPORTANT THINGS.
MAYBE I HEARD THAT,
ONCE,
YOU WERE KINDA INTO ME.
PAIGE:
OKAY, BUTTS IN
THE BLEACHERS PEOPLE.
WE'LL GO OVER THE ROUTE.
THERE'S A MOVIE
TOMORROW NIGHT.
7:30 P.M.,
CINEMA 3.
SUPPOSED TO BE FUNNY.
I'LL BE THERE.
DON'T HOLD YOUR BREATH.
WHENEVER YOU'RE READY.
CURING CANCER
CAN ALWAYS WAIT.
LIBERTY:
JT, PLEASE DON'T MAKE ME
DO THIS.
JT:
LIBERTY, WE CAN'T KEEP
AVOIDING THIS, OKAY?
WE HAVE TO TELL YOUR PARENTS.
LIBERTY:
AFTER WHAT HAPPENED
WITH YOUR GRANDMA?
JT:
SO SHE DIDN'T TAKE IT
SO WELL.
LIBERTY:
THAT'S NOTHING, JT,
OKAY?
YOUR GRANDMA'S A LAMB.
MY PARENTS ARE LIONS.
JT:
WELL, LIBERTY,
YOU'RE THEIR DAUGHTER.
MAYBE THEY'LL UNDERSTAND.
LIBERTY:
IT'S NOT MY MOTHER,
IT'S MY FATHER.
HE'LL KICK ME OUT,
GUARANTEED.
(SIGHS)
WELL, LET HIM, OKAY?
BECAUSE WE'RE GOING
TO GET OUR OWN PLACE.
YOU, ME AND THE BABY.
YOU'RE SERIOUS?
I GUESS I COULD USE
MY SPELLING BEE MONEY.
YEAH.
AND I'LL TAKE MORE SHIFTS
AT THE PHARMACY.
AND I'LL QUIT
THE TV JOB.
JT, YOU CAN'T.
NO, I HAVE TO,
BECAUSE IT DOESN'T PAY.
BESIDES, THEY CAN JUST GET
SOMEONE ELSE TO MAKE TIARAS.
IT'S FINE.
SO... WE'RE NOT
TELLING THEM?
NO. NOT YET.
BECAUSE BEFORE WE JUMP,
WE'D BETTER HAVE
A SAFETY NET.
(SARAH HARMER'S
"BASEMENT APARTMENT" PLAYS)
♪ WELL YOU LIVE OUT ♪
♪ WHERE THE STREET ENDS ♪
♪ IN THE BASEMENT APARTMENT ♪
♪ WITH ONE OF YOUR FRIENDS ♪
♪ AND THE TAP DRIPS ALL NIGHT ♪
♪ WATER TORTURIN' THE SINK ♪
♪ THE FURNACE IS BURNING ♪
♪ BUT IT'S STILL COLD
I THINK ♪
♪ TOASTER STICKS ♪
♪ AND THE EMPTIES
ARE PILED ♪
♪ I HAVEN'T BEEN UPSTAIRS
IN A WHILE NOW ♪
♪ I GOTTA WASH THE SHEETS
ON MY BED ♪
♪ I GOTTA WATCH THOSE THINGS
THAT GO UNSAID ♪
♪ GOD, I WISH WE'D LEAVE IT
AT THIS ♪
♪ EVERY TIME I BREATHE ♪
♪ EVERY TIME I TRY TO LEAVE ♪
DEREK:
SO, YOU, MANNY AND CRAIG
BEEN FRIENDS FOR LONG, OR...?
EMMA:
MANNY FOREVER.
CRAIG FOR A WHILE.
DEREK:
CHECK IT!
IS THAT GROVER SMASH?
EMMA:
I THINK IT IS.
WHO IS GROVER SMASH?
ONLY HALF
OF THE LEPER TWINS.
TAG TEAM?
OH, WRESTLING.
JUST WON THE BELT.
WHICH OBVIOUSLY MEANS
SQUAT TO YOU.
WHAT ABOUT TV?
WHAT DO YOU WATCH?
MOSTLY "BRIDESHEAD
REVISITED" ON DVD.
I READ THE BOOK.
OH, COOL.
YOU KNOW, SOME WRESTLERS
HAVE THEIR OWN BOOKS TOO -
COMIC BOOKS!
THAT'S HOW I GOT
INTO WRESTLING -
READING COMICS WHEN MY DAD
TOOK ME HUNTING.
DUDE, UNTIL YOU HAVE
TASTED FRESH VENISON,
YOU HAVE NOT LIVED.
I'M A VEGETARIAN.
OH.
SO DO YOU EAT CHICKEN
OR-
DEREK.
UM LISTEN,
I HAD A GREAT TIME.
WELL, AN OKAY TIME.
ACTUALLY,
A HAD PRETTY LAME TIME.
SO LET'S JUST QUIT
WHILE WE'RE BEHIND?
SORRY.
LANDLORD:
THREE-QUARTER INCH PIPE.
LOTS OF PRESSURE.
THE LAUNDRY'S IN THE BASEMENT.
LIBERTY:
I CAN'T WAIT TO DO
OUR OWN LAUNDRY!
JT:
AND IT'S SO CLOSE
TO THE SCHOOL.
IT'S PERFECT.
IS IT PERFECT?
LIBERTY:
IT'S PERFECT.
WELL, RENT IS $750 A MONTH,
KIDS,
AND I'LL NEED FIRST
AND LAST UP FRONT.
TWO MONTHS RENT?
THAT'S $1500.
YEAH, WELL, THAT'S PRETTY
STANDARD PRACTICE, KIDS.
I CAN GIVE YOU A MINUTE
TO THINK ABOUT IT.
(EXHALES)
WE CAN'T AFFORD IT.
JAY:
NO FIVE-FINGER DISCOUNTS
THIS TIME - PROMISE.
JT:
BELIEVE ME, THEY DO NOT PAY ME
ENOUGH TO STOP YOU.
JAY:
SO I SAW SOME NEW REJECT
ON TV TODAY
TRYING TO KEEP KIDS
FROM EATING GLUE.
HE POACH YOUR SHOW?
NO. I QUIT.
THAT JOB DIDN'T PAY
AND THIS ONE DOES.
AH WELL, THIS IS WHERE
THE BIG BUCKS ARE, EH?
YEAH.
MINIMUM WAGE?
I'M A REAL TYCOON.
YOUR PROBLEM,
STOCKBOY -
TUNNEL VISION,
OKAY?
YOU NEED MONEY?
GET CREATIVE.
JAY, SPARE ME
THE LAME-ASS SCHEME.
SHUT UP AND LISTEN.
LOOK, YOU HAVE BEHIND-
THE-COUNTER PRIVILEGES.
WHERE THE GOOD STUFF IS.
YOU EVER HEARD OF OXYCODONE?
IT'S A PAINKILLER.
I KNOW PEOPLE
WHO'D BE WILLING
TO SELL THEIR MOTHERS
TO GET THEIR HANDS
ON THIS STUFF.
AND YOU GOT IT
RIGHT BACK THERE.
BUCKETS OF IT.
PETER:
EMMA, OVER HERE!
YOU CAN CANCEL THE BULK
I-HAVE-A-NEW-GIRLFRIEND
EMAIL.
I HAVE BEEN PLANNING
TO SEE THIS MOVIE FOR WEEKS.
YEAH, OF COURSE.
A CLASSIC TALE OF TRIUMPH
OVER ADVERSITY.
WHO KNEW CLOWN ACADEMY
HAD A FOOTBALL TEAM?
OR CHEERLEADERS!
FOR THE RECORD,
WHEN THE LIGHTS GO DOWN,
YOUR HAND STAYS
IN YOUR OWN POPCORN BAG.
I'M ON PROBATION.
GOTCHYA.
SO SHOULD I DRAW A LINE
DOWN THE CENTRE
OF THE ARMREST OR WHAT?
LINE'S MOVING.
NO MORE TALKING.