STUDENTS:
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
SPINNER:
COME ON, DEGRASSI,
AND DUNK THE DORK!
LINUS:
HEY...
WANNA TRY YOUR LUCK?
IT'S ONLY A BUCK
A BALL.
YOU'RE TELLING ME I GET
TO THROW BALLS AT HIM
FOR CHARITY?
YEAH.
COME ON, WHY NOT?
OKAY.
I'LL TRY MY LUCK.
HERE'S FIVE.
THANK YOU.
YEP.
SPINNER:
SHOW ME WHAT YOU GOT, JIMMY!
YES!
FIRST TIME TODAY!
WON'T BE THE LAST.
WELL, THAT WAS FUN.
I'M IN A CHARITABLE MOOD,
SO HOW ABOUT TEN MORE?
I THINK SPINNER
NEEDS A BREAK.
I THINK GAVIN
IS FINE.
OKAY.
I'M JUST WARMING UP.
NO, JIM, LOOK.
HE'S FREEZING.
I KNOW YOU HATE THE GUY,
OKAY?
BUT TODAY,
JUST CUT HIM SOME SLACK.
FINE.
WHATEVER.
THANKS, MAN, EH?
YOU SAVED MY BUTT.
LATER, SPINNER.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
SPINNER:
GIRLS, COULD I INTEREST YOU
IN THIS INTERESTING PAMPHLET
ABOUT JESUS?
PAIGE:
UM...SPINNER?
MAY I SUGGEST METHADONE
TO UH... KICK
THE CHRISTIAN HABIT?
IT'S NOT A HABIT,
PAIGE.
THIS IS FOR LIFE
AND BEYOND.
DANNY:
WITHOUT YOUR SHOES
AND YOU'RE YOUR PURSE?
I'D SAY...
MMMMM....
140?
MAYBE IF I WAS CARRYING
AN ENTIRE 8-YEAR-OLD!
THE SIGN SAYS "GUESS".
I GUESSED.
DEREK,
YOUR FRIEND'S AN IDIOT.
I'M AWARE.
SO, HOW MINUSCULE
ARE YOU?
DON'T ASK.
HEY!
THESE ARE FOR MOM.
DARN YOU
AND YOUR WHOLE "MAKE SPIKE
FEEL BETTER" CAMPAIGN.
TODAY, I NEED ALL THE HELP
I CAN GET.
IT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE HER
THIRD WEDDING ANNIVERSARY.
BUT I'VE GOT
A SURPRISE LATER
THAT'S REALLY GONNA
MAKE HER HAPPY.
MALE STRIPPERS...
DROPPING IT
LIKE IT'S HOT?
OH YEAH,
OH YEAH.
OKAY, I THINK REMOVING YOU
FROM PUBLIC
IS A GOOD IDEA
FOR US ALL.
MARCO:
SAFER SEX SEMINAR.
SAFER SEX.
OH, HEY, TOBY.
SAFER SEX SEMINAR.
CHECK IT OUT.
WE'RE GIVING OUT
FREE CONDOMS.
OOH,
I'M IN.
EXACTLY.
SAFER SEX!
ELLIE:
OKAY, I CANNOT BELIEVE
FRIENDSHIP CLUB
BRAINWASHED SPINNER.
JIMMY:
THERE'S NOT MUCH BRAIN
TO WASH-
MARCO:
GUYS, THEY DON'T BRAINWASH.
THEY'RE TOO BUSY SINGING
AND PRAYING AND STUFF.
ELLIE:
TOM-AY-TO, TOM-AH-TO.
RELIGION IS SO BORING
AND LAME.
HELLO?
CATHOLIC OVER HERE.
UM... MARCO?
YOU'RE GAY.
AND THEREFORE
I CAN'T BE CHRISTIAN?
ALL I'M SAYING IS,
THE CHURCH?
NOT TOO BIG ON THE GAYS.
WELL, THINGS ARE GOING
TO CHANGE.
IT JUST-
IT TAKE TIME.
WHATEVSKIS.
KIM:
WE JUST MADE $860.00,
AND IT'S ALL THANKS TO YOU,
SPIN.
THIS IS GONNA PUT FOOD
IN A LOT OF HUNGRY MOUTHS.
YOU SO ROCK.
"LET YOUR LIGHT SHINE
BEFORE MEN;
THAT THEY MAY SEE
YOUR GOOD DEEDS."
MATTHEW 5:16.
I'M PROUD OF YOU,
SPIN.
ALL I HAD TO DO
WAS GET WET.
THAT'S A REALLY
SMALL PRICE TO PAY
TO HELP STARVING KIDS.
STILL...
YOU DID A GREAT THING
FOR CHARITY,
AND YOU MADE FRIENDSHIP CLUB
LOOK GOOD.
YOU'RE THE MAN.
HEY...
CALL YOU LATER?
ALL RIGHT.
(MUFFLED MUSIC PLAYING)
SPINNER:
HEY...
HOPE YOU DON'T MIND ME ASKING,
BUT UM, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
SITTING HERE
LIKE LITTLE BOY BLUE?
I MEAN WHERE'RE
ALL YOUR PEOPLE?
WELL...
JIMMY AND ELLIE ARE DOING
THIS ART THING LIKE 24/7.
PAIGE AND ALEX...
PAIGE AND ALEX
HAVE MORPHED INTO PALEX.
AND CRAIG'S IN VANCOUVER
PURSUING FAME AND FORTUNE.
AND I'M HERE,
PURSUING BOREDOM.
SUCKS, MAN.
UM LISTEN...
IF YOU WANT TO,
WE COULD POSSIBLY,
MAYBE... HANG OUT?
OR NOT.
YOU KNOW, WHATEVER.
HEY!
YOU STILL LIKE
STUPID MOVIES?
DUDE, THE STUPIDER
THE BETTER.
EMMA:
COME ON, MOM.
A LITTLE LESS VACUUM,
A LITTLE MORE HAPPY!
BROWNIES,
THEY'RE HAPPY-MAKING.
NOT THAT I DON'T
APPRECIATE THE EFFORT,
BUT I'M FINE,
REALLY.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
EMMA:
YOU WANT EFFORT?
GO OPEN THE DOOR.
SURPRISE!
CAITLIN!
ALL THE WAY FROM L.A.,
DARLING.
YOU LITTLE SNEAK!
YOU DIDN'T TELL ME
SHE WAS COMING!
WELL, WHERE'S
THE SURPRISE IN THAT?
MARCO:
I CAN'T BELIEVE
WE JUST PAID MONEY
TO SEE THAT MOVIE.
WHAT?
CLOWN ACADEMY II
ROCKED, MAN.
I MEAN, YOU GOT...
SEXY CLOWNS,
CAR CHASES,
EXPLOSIVE DIARRHEA.
WHAT MORE COULD YOU WANT
IN A MOVIE?
WELL, IT'S GOOD TO SEE
YOUR TASTE IN MOVIES
HASN'T CHANGED.
WELL,
IT'S GOOD TO SEE
YOUR TASTE IN FASHION
HASN'T CHANGED.
DOES THE GAY SUPERHERO
KNOW YOU TOOK HIS BELT?
MARCO:
MAN,
YOU HAVE NOT CHANGED
AT ALL.
EXCEPT FOR THE HAIR.
AND UH...
THANK GOD FOR THAT.
FUNNY.
SO...
SPINNER,
OKAY, I HAVE TO ASK YOU
SOMETHING.
FRIENDSHIP CLUB.
NOW WHAT IS THE DEAL
WITH THAT?
ALL RIGHT.
BEGINNING OF THE YEAR,
MY OLD FRIENDS DIDN'T
WANT TO KNOW MY NAME.
BUT FRIENDSHIP CLUB
WELCOMED ME WITH OPEN ARMS.
THEY...
THEY'RE LIKE A FAMILY.
IT MUST'VE SUCKED
FOR YOU.
THE WHOLE GANG JUST
SHUNNING YOU ALL YEAR.
IT'S WATER OVER
THE BRIDGE, MAN.
BESIDES,
I'M NOT COMPLAINING,
AS LONG AS
YOU AND I ARE COOL.
RIGHT.
WE'RE COOL.
THANKS FOR THE VISIT.
IT HELPS.
SO HOW ARE YOU?
FOR REAL?
WHAT'S GOING ON
WITH YOU AND SNAKE?
WELL, I'M NOT
GONNA WAIT AROUND
WHILE HE CONTEMPLATES
HIS NAVEL,
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
THE MEANING OF LIFE.
HERE'S TO MOVING ON.
TO MOVING ON.
AND TO THE BEST
NON-ANNIVERSARY PARTY EVER.
MY BEST FRIEND,
MY GIRLS,
BROWNIES, WINE.
WHAT MORE
COULD I ASK FOR?
A BUFF GUY
IN A G-STRING
DROPPING IT
LIKE IT'S HOT, HUH?
SIMPSON:
HELLO!
ANYBODY HOME?
CAITLIN, HEY!
NICE OF L.A. TO SEND US UP
SOME SUNSHINE!
HI ARCHIE.
YOU CAN'T JUST
BARGE IN HERE ANYTIME.
I'M SORRY.
IT'S JUST UM...
I ORDERED THIS FOR YOU
MONTHS AGO
FOR OUR...
YOU KNOW.
I THOUGHT MAYBE
YOU SHOULD HAVE IT.
I'LL JUST...
I'LL LEAVE THIS HERE.
SPIKE:
SAPPHIRE.
MY BIRTHSTONE.
IT'S PERFECT.
IT'S ABSOLUTELY PERFECT.
PERFECT.
LINUS:
HEY, I WANT TO THANK YOU ALL
FOR COMING IN
SO EARLY THIS MORNING,
BUT UM...
WE HAVE A SERIOUS ISSUE
AT HAND.
I'M DISGUSTED...
THAT THE SCHOOL WOULD LET
MARCO DEL ROSSI RUN THIS.
DARCY:
BUT THE SCHOOL PROMOTES
SAFER SEX.
PLEASE.
EVERYONE KNOWS SAFER SEX
IS JUST CODE
FOR PROMISCUOUS SEX.
LINUS:
"JUST SAY YES TO SAFER SEX."
WHAT IS THIS?
THERE'S NO MENTION
OF ABSTINENCE AT ALL.
SPINNER:
YEAH, BUT ISN'T THERE,
LIKE, FREEDOM OF SPEECH
OR WHATEVER?
YOU'RE RIGHT,
THERE IS.
HE'S FREE TO TALK
ABOUT IMMORAL SEX
AND WE'RE FREE
TO TRY TO STOP HIM.
OKAY, LOOK, MARCO...
HE'S A FRIEND OF MINE.
AND THAT'S WHY
WE'VE NOMINATED YOU
TO TALK HIM INTO
CALLING THIS OFF.
WHO'S WE?
DARCY:
I DIDN'T VOTE FOR THIS.
I THOUGHT THIS CLUB WAS ABOUT
TOLERANCE AND RESPECT.
OH, WHAT ABOUT LOVE
YOUR NEIGHBOUR AS YOURSELF?
LINUS:
WE BELIEVE THAT.
BUT WE ALSO BELIEVE
IN ABSTINENCE,
AND CONDOMS MAKE KIDS
HAVE SEX.
DARCY...
THIS SEMINAR GOES AGAINST
OUR VALUES.
OKAY?
WE HAVE TO STOP IT,
AND SPINNER'S OUR MAN.
SPINNER:
DON'T BE SO SURE.
MARCO WILL FREAK.
LOOK, ARE YOU WITH US
OR NOT?
MORNING,
FELLOW MEMBERS OF THE WORST
CHEER-UP SQUAD EVER.
EMMA:
WHERE'S OUR VICTIM?
SHE WENT
TO THE SALON EARLY.
PROBABLY TO SWALLOW DYE.
BUT I'M BRAINSTORMING
ON HOW TO GIVE
THE CHEER-UP SQUAD
A MAJOR COMEBACK.
(WHISPERING)
MALE STRIPPER.
CAITLIN:
SO FAR, I'VE GOT UH...
GIRL MOVIE MARATHON,
CRAFT NIGHT,
FACE PAINTING
AND COTTON CANDY.
YEAH, I KNOW,
I GOT NOTHIN'.
I'VE GOT AN IDEA!
HOW ABOUT WE GET
A MALE STRIPPER?
WOULD YOU SHUT UP
ALREADY?!
THERE'S NO WAY SHE COULD KEEP
A STRAIGHT FACE THROUGH THAT.
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA!
GREAT IDEA?
CAITLIN:
GET ME THE YELLOW PAGES
AND THE PHONE.
WE ARE HAVING A PARTY!
WOO!
CAITLIN:
OH, YES!
SPINNER:
UH, I-I NEED TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT SOMETHING.
DO YOU HAVE A SEC?
NAH, SPIN.
NOW'S NOT A GOOD TIME.
OKAY, BUT JUST
THIS SEMINAR,
YOU THINK MAYBE
IT'S A BIT MUCH?
WHAT EXACTLY
IS A BIT MUCH?
MAN, YOU GUYS ARE GIVING
OUT CONDOMS.
YEAH. WE'RE PROMOTING
SAFER SEX.
DON'T DO IT.
EXCUSE ME?
JUST CANCEL THE SEMINAR,
OKAY?
WHAT?!
SPIN, GIVE ME...
GIVE ME
ONE GOOD REASON WHY?
CONDOMS MAKE KIDS
HAVE SEX, MAN.
OH... WHOA...
WOW, THAT'S RETARDED.
WHERE DID YOU GET
THAT FROM, HUH?
SOME STUPID PAMPHLET?
HEY, I DIDN'T WANNA GET NASTY,
BUT WHAT YOU'RE DOING
IS IMMORAL, MARCO.
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU
TO SAY THAT, SPIN?
DUDE, IT'S IN THE BIBLE.
THIS IS WRONG, OKAY?
THIS IS SIN.
WOW.
JIMMY WAS SO RIGHT.
I SHOULD'VE NEVER
GIVEN YOU SECOND CHANCE.
HATZILAKOS:
RIGHT.
I APPROVED THE EVENT.
SO WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
THEY'RE GIVING OUT CONDOMS,
MS. H.
IT'S GOING TO MAKE KIDS
RUN OUT AND HAVE SEX.
GIVING OUT CONDOMS
DOES NOT MAKE KIDS HAVE SEX.
YOU TWO ARE AWARE THAT
SOME TEENAGERS HAVE SEX.
LINUS:
AND SOME DON'T.
WE BELIEVE
IN ABSTINENCE.
HATZILAKOS:
WELL, NOT EVERY TEENAGER DOES.
WE HAD A GONORRHEA OUTBREAK
IN THE SCHOOL LAST YEAR
SO IF GIVING OUT CONDOMS
HELPS AVOID IT,
THEN I'M ALL FOR IT.
MS. HATZILAKOS,
PLEASE,
CANCEL THIS THING.
IT'S-IT'S WRONG.
I'M AFRAID
WE DON'T SEE EYE TO EYE
AND I'M NOT CANCELLING IT.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
A GOOD CHRISTIAN.
YOU'RE ON VERY THIN ICE
RIGHT NOW, GAVIN.
DON'T MAKE ME REGRET
LETTING YOU BACK
INTO THIS SCHOOL.
HEY, EVERYBODY.
JUST WANTED TO REMIND YOU THAT
THE SAFER SEX SEMINAR
WILL BE HELD TODAY
AFTER SCHOOL IN THE GYM.
SO IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS....
SPINNER:
I TRIED TO STOP HIM.
I REALLY DID.
SO MUCH FOR HELPING YOU.
SPINNER, THIS ISN'T
ABOUT HELPING ME.
OKAY? IT'S ABOUT
RIGHT AND WRONG.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
MS. HATZILAKOS WOULD DO
IF WE WENT ON THERE
AND TOLD EVERYONE
WHAT WE BELIEVED?
MS. ANTI-CHRISTIAN.
IT'S LIKE WE'RE
THE BAD GUYS.
'CAUSE THE SYSTEM
IS AGAINST US.
WELL, I'M SICK OF IT.
THAT'S THE SPIRIT,
BRO.
WE GOTTA TAKE
THIS SCHOOL BACK,
MAKE IT SAFE
FOR THE NORMAL PEOPLE.
"NO SEX IS SAFE SEX?"
YEAH. WE'RE FIGHTING BACK,
ME AND LINUS.
IT'S A BIT EXTREME,
DON'T YOU THINK?
SO YOU WANT MARCO
GIVING OUT CONDOMS?
NO,
NOT REALLY,
BUT HE HAS THE RIGHT TO.
YEAH, THAT'S WHAT
MS. HATZILAKOS SAID.
SO...
SO I DON'T ANSWER TO HER,
'KAY?
I ANSWER TO SOMEONE
A LOT HIGHER.
WHO? LINUS?
HAVE YOU EVER LISTENED
TO LINUS?
I MEAN REALLY LISTENED
TO HIM?
HE'S GOT A LOT OF VIEWS
THAT ARE-
YOU KNOW, MAYBE YOU SHOULD
JUST STAY OUT OF THIS,
OKAY?
FINE.
WHOA!
SEMINAR'S STARTING.
YOU READY?
SPINNER:
YEAH, I'M READY.
BOY:
CHOOSE ABSTINENCE!
GIRL:
ABSTINENCE IS THE ANSWER!
SPINNER:
ABSTINENCE EQUALS SAFE SEX!
NO! SHHHH!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
ARE YOU OUT OF YOU MIND?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE,
WITH SIGNS?
WE HAVE THE RIGHT
TO PROTEST.
LIKE YOU HAVE THE FAINTEST IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE PROTESTING.
WE'RE JUST TRYING
TO EDUCATE PEOPLE.
YOU'RE PROMOTING
PROMISCUITY.
STUPIDITY.
ELLIE:
YOU THINK IT'S BETTER THAT
PEOPLE HAVE UNWANTED BABIES?
I THINK IT'S BETTER
PEOPLE DON'T HAVE SEX
UNLESS THEY'RE MARRIED.
STOP!
LOOK,
JUST LEAVE US ALONE.
GO HOME, GO TO CHURCH,
DO WHATEVER.
LINUS:
WHY DON'T YOU TRY
GOING TO CHURCH?
I DO,
EVERY SUNDAY.
AND THEY LET YOU IN?
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED
TO MEAN?
LINUS:
I THINK YOU KNOW
EXACTLY WHAT IT MEANS.
THE BIBLE IS CLEAR
ABOUT SEXUAL DEVIANCY.
WHAT?!
WHO IS THIS BIGOTED FREAK?
LINUS:
SO I'M A FREAK.
IT'S BETTER
THAN BEING A HOMO.
SPINNER:
WHOA, WHOA...
GUYS, TAKE IT EASY.
NO SPINNER,
SHUT UP!
YOU AND YOUR FRIEND,
JUST GO TO HELL.
SO WE CAN VISIT YOU,
FAG?
TIM:
COME ON, STOP! STOP!
DON'T LET THEM CORRUPT YOU,
SPINNER.
IT'S WHAT THEY DO.
LINUS, IF I WERE YOU,
I WOULD START WALKING,
NOW.
LIZ:
FINALLY, WE GET TO FIND OUT
WHAT'S FOR DINNER?
WHAT'S THE SURPRISE?
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
SPIKE:
WITH CAITLIN IN CHARGE,
WHO KNOWS?
IT'LL BE ELEGANT
AT ANY RATE.
CAITLIN:
DINNER IS SERVED!
(CHEERING)
SPIKE:
THIS IS OUTRAGEOUS!
MANNY:
TRY THE DYNAMITE ROLLS.
EMMA:
I HEAR THEY'RE DYNAMITE!
CAITLIN:
I HOPE EVERYONE'S HUNGRY
BECAUSE DESSERT
IS THEIR SPECIALTY!
WOMAN:
TAKE IT OFF!
(CHEERING)
SORRY,
DO YOU NOT LIKE CHOCOLATE?
SPIKE:
NO, I LOVE CHOCOLATE.
YOU JUST LOOK LIKE SOMEBODY.
MY HUSBAND.
THERE,
IT'S ON THE HOUSE,
FOR STILL HAVING ANYTHING
TO DO WITH ME.
I'M GETTING USED
TO FORGIVING YOU.
IF ONLY MY BEST FRIEND
COULD SEE IT LIKE THAT.
YOU SHOULD GO OVER THERE.
IT'S LIKE WALKING
INTO THE LION'S DEN.
DARCY:
COME ON, SPIN.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT TO LOSE?
SPINNER:
UH, MARCO...
I JUST WANTED YOU TO KNOW,
I AM NEVER TALKING
TO LINUS AGAIN, OKAY?
EITHER HE'S OUT
OF THE FRIENDSHIP CLUB
OR I AM.
MARCO:
SPIN, YOU DO WHATEVER
YOU WANT,
CAUSE REALLY,
I COULDN'T CARE LESS ABOUT YOU
AND YOUR STUPID CLUB.
I'M NOT LIKE HIM,
OKAY?
SPINNER,
THIS IS NOT THE TIME.
SPINNER:
NO, IT'S NEVER GOING
TO BE THE TIME!
YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
JIMMY, SHUT UP!
MARCO,
I AM NOT HOMOPHOBIC.
YOU KNOW THAT, OKAY?
ALL I EVER WANTED TO DO
WAS BE YOUR FRIEND AGAIN.
I SCREWED IT UP,
OKAY?
AND I AM REALLY,
REALLY SORRY.
I FEEL TERRIBLE.
IN THIS CASE,
TERRIBLE IS GOOD.
I MEAN, YOU SAID YOU
AND SNAKE ARE OVER.
YOU NEED TO START
DEALING WITH THAT.
I CAN'T.
YOU DON'T HAVE A CHOICE,
HON.
YOU SAID THE RELATIONSHIP
IS OVER.
NOT FOR ME.
CAITLIN...
I'M STILL IN LOVE
WITH HIM.
(CRYING)
SPINNER...
YOU REALLY ARE LOST,
AREN'T YOU?
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.