MARCO, ARE WE STILL
FISHING THIS WEEKEND?
YEAH.
YEAH, OF COURSE.
LOUISE, I THINK OUR BOY
IS GOING CRAZY!
LOOK, HE'S TALKING TO HIMSELF.
(CHUCKLES)
YOU'RE FUNNY, PA.
IT'S FOR THE SCHOOL PLAY.
WE'RE HOSTING THE CITY
DRAMA FESTIVAL.
MARCO...
DON'T TELL ME
YOU'RE BECOMING AN ACTOR.
NO. NO, THIS IS JUST
A FAVOUR FOR MR. SIMPSON.
I'M NOT BECOMING AN ACTOR.
MR. DEL ROSSI:
RIGHT.
BECAUSE YOU'RE LEARNING
THE PRINTING BUSINESS WITH ME.
PA, WE'VE DISCUSSED THIS.
SOCIAL WORK.
I WANNA HELP PEOPLE.
(MOCKS)
...HELP PEOPLE.
NO, LOOK, SOCIAL WORK
IS A GOOD JOB.
COUSIN LOU
BECAME A SOCIAL WORKER.
COUSIN LOU?
PLEASE, COUSIN LOU
IS A FINOCIO!
PA...
COUSIN LOU IS A GREAT GUY.
HE HELPS PEOPLE.
YEAH, BUT HE DOESN'T HELP
HIS POOR MOTHER.
HIS MOTHER WOULD LOVE
A GRANDCHILD ONE DAY.
BUT FROM COUSIN LOU?
GOOD LUCK.
SO HE'LL ADOPT.
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
MR. DEL ROSSI:
NO BIG DEAL?
MARCO, FOR A PARENT
TO RAISE A HOMOSEXUAL?
IT'S LIKE A FAILURE.
AN EMBARRASSMENT.
OH REALLY?
WELL, LET ME TELL YOU THAT...
THAT I HAVE A REHEARSAL
AND I DON'T KNOW
MY LINES.
BYE.
BYE, BYE.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
TOBY:
HE MADE CONFESSION OF YOU...
AND GAVE SUCH A...
MASTERLY REPORT.
TOBY:
MASTERLY REPORT...
STRESSED MUCH?
MARCO:
THERE'S NO WAY
I'M EVER GONNA MEMORIZE
THESE LINES.
RELAX,
IT'S NOT LIKE
YOU'RE THE STAR
OR THE SCHOOL'S HOPES
TO WIN THIS DRAMA FESTIVAL
ARE RIDING ON YOU.
WAIT, YOU'RE HAMLET,
RIGHT?
IT IS RIDING ON YOU!
YEAH.
SOMEONE REMIND ME
TO KILL HIM...
AFTER I'M DONE
MEMORIZING THIS.
HMM,
I'LL REMIND YOU,
ONCE YOU REMIND ME
WHY WE VOLUNTEERED TO DO THIS.
BECAUSE WE THOUGHT
IT'D BE FUN.
AND BECAUSE SIMPSON GAVE US
THAT WHOLE "HELP ME,
HELP DEGRASSI" SPEECH.
BECAUSE SOMEONE KNEW
THAT CUTE, NEW GUY
HAD ALREADY VOLUNTEERED?
WHO?
TIM?
OKAY.
OKAY, HE'S OKAY.
I MEAN, IF YOU LIKE
THAT WHOLE DARK,
MYSTERIOUS THING.
MM, YEAH.
QUEL TURN-OFF.
PERFECT.
WHAT ARE YOU,
THE LEANING TOWER OF PETER?
IT'S COMPLETELY CROOKED.
I WASN'T TALKING
ABOUT THE POSTER.
OKAY.
LET ME SET
ONE THING STRAIGHT:
YOU ARE NEVER GETTING
ANYWHERE WITH ME.
NEVER SAY NEVER.
AW, BUT IT'S FUN.
NEVER, NEVER, NEVER, NEVER,
NEVER, NEVER, NEVER.
YEAH, EASY TO SAY,
BUT IT'S HARDER TO MEAN.
AND I KNOW YOU DON'T.
PLEASE.
LOOK,
IF YOU HATE ME SO MUCH
WHY DID YOU GO ON A DATE
WITH ME THE OTHER NIGHT?
IT WASN'T A DATE.
IT WAS AN APPRAISAL.
OH YEAH?
AND HOW DID I DO?
MY FILES ARE CONFIDENTIAL.
NOW THAT'S PERFECT.
SEE YOU AROUND.
PAIGE:
O, WHAT A NOBLE MIND
IS HERE OVERTHROWN!
THE-THE COURIER'S...
CRAIG:
COURTIER'S.
PAIGE:
COURTIER'S, SOLDIER'S,
SCHOLAR'S, EYE...
FAGGOT.
CRAIG, DON'T.
DON'T.
TIM, HEY.
WHOA.
YOU OKAY?
YEAH. I'M FINE.
HERE DUDE,
LET ME TAKE YOU TO THE NURSE.
NO.
MARCO, I'M FINE.
WELL, LET ME
DO SOMETHING?
ANYTHING?
HEY, SORRY ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED TODAY.
DEGRASSI'S PRETTY COOL,
BUT THERE ARE IDIOTS
EVERYWHERE.
SO...
WHO HAVE YOU TOLD?
NO ONE.
EXCEPT MY BEST FRIEND.
WELL, MY FORMER BEST FRIEND.
OH. DIDN'T GO WELL THEN,
I TAKE IT.
MY BEST FRIEND
SINCE GRADE THREE
CALLED ME A FAG
AND PUNCHED ME
IN THE FACE.
WELL, YOU'LL FIND
A NEW FRIEND.
RIGHT.
IT'S JUST...
I DON'T KNOW ANYBODY WHO WOULD
EVEN BEGIN TO GET THIS.
YOU DO NOW.
TIM, LOOK...
I'VE BEEN WHERE YOU ARE,
OKAY?
TWO YEARS AGO,
I WAS YOU.
SO I CAN HELP YOU.
AND I WANT TO HELP YOU.
AS A FRIEND.
THANK YOU, MARCO.
YOU'RE LIKE MY YODA.
OH, YEAH.
WELL, MEMORIZE LINES,
WE MUST.
ANGRY SIMPSON WILL BE,
HMM?
(CHUCKLES)
EMMA:
TICKETS FOR THE DRAMA FESTIVAL?
TICKETS?
TICKET?
ALLOW ME.
HI, I'M PETER.
HI.
DEGRASSI'S HOSTING
THE CITY DRAMA FESTIVAL.
IT'S A PRESTIGIOUS EVENT.
IT'S GONNA DO A LOT
FOR THE SCHOOL.
SO WE'RE ASKING EVERYONE
TO COME OUT
AND SHOW THEIR SUPPORT.
THANK YOU.
SELLING'S IN MY BLOOD.
MY DAD'S A CAR SALESMAN.
IMPORTS, MAINLY.
MAYBE HE COULD GIVE ME
SOME POINTERS.
I COULD SURE USE THEM.
I'LL GIVE YOU
SOME POINTERS.
SAY TODAY, 4 P.M.,
AT THE DOT?
I WALKED RIGHT
INTO THAT ONE.
COME ON, JUST GO OUT
WITH ME AGAIN.
OKAY PETER,
MY BEST FRIEND
HATES YOU.
I CAN'T BE SEEN
TALKING TO YOU.
YOU NEED TO BACK OFF.
WAS HE BOTHERING YOU?
IT'S OKAY.
IT'S NOT.
HE WAS HARASSING YOU.
WE NEED TO DO SOMETHING
ABOUT HIM.
MARCO,
I'M SUCH AN IDIOT.
I LEFT THE COMPUTER ON
AND I FORGOT TO LOG OUT.
OH,
CLASSIC BEGINNER'S MISTAKE.
MY DAD SAT DOWN
AND THERE IT WAS -
A GAY TEENS CHATROOM.
SO HE CONFRONTED ME,
AND THE NEXT THING I KNOW,
I'M OUT THE DOOR,
RUNNING.
OH MY GOD.
WHERE DID YOU GO?
NOWHERE;
EVERYWHERE.
I JUST HAD
TO KEEP MOVING.
IT'S SCARY OUT THERE.
TIM, YOU CAN'T
DO THAT AGAIN.
IT'S DANGEROUS.
YOU HAVE TO GO HOME.
WHAT IF HE KICKS ME OUT?
WE'LL FIGURE IT OUT
THEN.
BUT FIRST,
YOU GOTTA GO HOME
AND FACE YOUR DAD.
RIGHT.
AND TELL HIM WHAT?
JUST TELL HIM
THE TRUTH.
I MEAN, YOU HAVE TO SHOW HIM
THE REAL YOU, RIGHT?
AND SHOW HIM THE TIM
THAT YOU'VE BEEN HIDING
ALL THESE YEARS.
SO I JUST WALTZ UP TO MY DAD
AND SAY "I'M GAY".
AND THEN WHAT?
WELL... OKAY.
FIRST?
HE'LL LOSE IT.
IT'LL GET NASTY
AND UGLY.
BUT... THEN IN TIME,
HE'LL SEE IT'S
WHO YOU REALLY ARE.
AND HE'LL WAKE UP
ONE MORNING
AND HE'LL SAY
"MY SON'S GAY,
AND THAT'S ALL RIGHT".
OKAY.
I'M GONNA DO IT.
I'M GONNA DO IT, MARCO.
I'M GONNA TELL HIM.
PETER:
THE BAND IS GONNA BE
REALLY GOOD.
THEY'RE GONNA PLAY SOME HITS
AND SOME OF THEIR OWN STUFF.
IT'S GONNA BE GOOD.
THE GUITARIST IS SO GOOD.
MY FRIEND IS A DRUM-
AM I INTERRUPTING?
ONLY SLIGHTLY.
LOOK, MY DAD'S GOING TO BE
OUT OF TOWN
SO THERE'S NOTHING IN THE WAY
OF US HAVING FUN.
JUST COME.
'KAY.
YOU'RE HAVING A PARTY?
YOU'RE BUSY WITH THE FESTIVAL,
REMEMBER?
WHICH I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE BAILING ON.
I'VE MORE THAN ENOUGH DRAMA
IN MY LIFE THESE DAYS.
WHAT'S THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
YOU BLOW HOT AND COLD,
EMMA.
YOU FLIRT,
AND THEN YOU SHUT ME DOWN.
FACE IT,
YOU'RE A TEASE.
WELL, YOU'RE A JERK.
(KNOCK AT THE DOOR)
OH TIM?
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
I'M SORRY, MARCO.
I GOT YOUR ADDRESS OFF
THE PLAY CONTACT LIST.
I HAVE NOWHERE
ELSE TO GO.
LOOK, I DID IT
JUST LIKE YOU SAID.
I COME OUT TO MY DAD
AND HE KICKED ME OUT.
HE ACTUALLY KICKED ME OUT.
(CRYING)
MR. DEL ROSSI:
MARCO, WHAT'S GOING ON
IN HERE?
NOTHING.
PA, THIS IS MY FRIEND,
TIM.
HE'S UPSET.
MRS. DEL ROSSI:
LET'S GO BACK
TO THE DINNING ROOM.
NO. NO.
I'M SORRY FOR BARGING IN
LIKE THIS.
IT'S JUST...
I JUST CAME OUT
TO MY DAD.
CAME OUT?
CAME OUT WHERE?
MARCO:
NO, HE GOT INTO A FIGHT
WITH HIS DAD
OVER THE UH...
THE PLAY.
HIS DAD-HIS DAD JUST DOESN'T
LIKE HIM BEING AN ACTOR.
I CAN UNDERSTAND.
ACTING IS NOT A REAL JOB.
IT'S FOR THE...
(WHISTLES)
PAPA?
CAN YOU LEAVE US ALONE,
PLEASE?
TIM. OKAY,
LET ME EXPLAIN THIS-
DON'T, MARCO.
JUST DON'T.
TIM. WE'LL SEE YOU
AGAIN TONIGHT?
YEAH.
HEY, MY MOM'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE MORE THAN WELCOME
TO STAY HERE.
IT'D MAKE ME FEEL BETTER.
I FEEL KINDA RESPONSIBLE.
MR. DEL ROSSI:
RESPONSIBLE?
WHAT DID YOU DO?
MARCO:
NOTHING, PA.
I JUST...TALKED TIM
INTO JOINING THE CAST.
MR. DEL ROSSI:
YEAH, TIM...
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I DON'T MUCH LIKE ACTING,
BUT YOUR FATHER,
HE KICKED YOU OUT
BECAUSE OF THAT?
TIM:
YOU SEE MY FATHER THINKS
ACTING'S A WASTE OF TIME.
WHAT DO YOU THINK,
MARCO?
YOU KNOW,
ABOUT ACTING?
ABOUT PRETENDING TO BE
SOMEONE YOU'RE NOT?
I DON'T KNOW, BUD.
I GUESS YOU JUST GOTTA PLAY
THE PART AS WRITTEN.
YEAH,
BUT YOU'RE SO GOOD AT IT.
I MEAN, WHEN YOU ACT,
YOU'RE IT'S LIKE PACINO.
YOU FOOL EVERYBODY.
THANK YOU.
I HAVE TO GO.
MOM, DAD,
HERE ARE THE TICKETS.
FESTIVAL STARTS AT NOON.
IL DETESTE LA PLUIE.
HOW DO I SPELL DETESTE?
DETESTE...
EMMA:
DETESTE AS IN HATE?
P-E-T-E-R.
OKAY, THAT'S AT LEAST
TEN PETER REFERENCES
IN THE LAST TWO HOURS.
I JUST HATE
WHAT HE DID TO YOU.
AND WAITING FOR KARMA TO GET HIM
IS BORING ME.
IT WON'T ACTUALLY BE KARMA.
IT'LL BE A GIRL.
ACHILLES HEEL, LIKE.
MANUELLA,
VOUS ETES UN GENIUS!
AN EYE FOR AN EYE.
BABY,
THAT'S A TELEPHONE,
AND YOU MIGHT WANT
TO USE IT
TO CALL THE MEN
IN WHITE COATS
BECAUSE THEY PICK UP.
IT'S A CAMERA PHONE.
SO...?
SO PETER NEEDS TO LEARN
THAT PAYBACKS ARE HELL,
AND I HAPPEN TO THINK
HE NEEDS TO LEARN IT
FROM US.
AND THAT'S WHY YOU'RE
MY BESTEST FRIEND
IN THE WHOLE
WIDE WORLD.
SMILE FOR
A PICTURE.
CHEESE.
NERVOUS?
YEAH.
BUT NOT BECAUSE
OF THE PLAY THOUGH.
TIM STAYED OVER
LAST NIGHT.
I HOPE YOU WERE SAFE.
WHAT? NO!
TOTALLY MISSING
THE POINT.
LOOK,
HE CAME OUT TO HIS DAD.
WHO THEN,
GET THIS,
PROMPTLY KICKED
HIM OUT.
WOW.
I JUST WENT FROM
EXCITEMENT TO HORROR
IN FIVE SECONDS.
ACTING HAS PUT ME IN TOUCH
WITH MY EMOTIONS.
PAIGE,
THIS IS SO MY FAULT.
OKAY...
WELL, I KIND OF
MADE HIM THINK
THAT I ALREADY
WAS OUT TO MY DAD.
YOUR DAD?
THE GUY WHO THINKS YOU LISTEN
TO BRITNEY IN THE CAR
BECAUSE IT PUTS CHICKS
IN THE MOOD?
I KNOW.
I WAS JUST TRYING
TO HELP HIM, OKAY?
INSPIRE HIM.
BE HIS MENTOR;
HIS YODA.
TOO LATE,
IT IS NOT.
HMM.
YEAH.
BELIEVE ME,
IT DEFINITELY IS.
(SIGHS)
TIM HATES ME.
HE WON'T.
NOT AFTER YOU COME OUT
TO YOUR FATHER.
(DANCE MUSIC)
EMMA.
WERE YOU EXPECTING
SOMEONE ELSE?
NOT EXPECTING;
MAYBE HOPING.
WELL, I WAS HOPING
YOU'D ACCEPT AN APOLOGY.
I WAS BEING UNFAIR
SENDING MIXED SIGNALS.
SO WHAT'S THE SIGNAL NOW?
GREEN FOR GO.
LET'S SEE
WHAT WE CAN DO.
(APPLAUSE)
THAT WAS A SCENE
FROM "PYGMALION",
PLAYED BY DAVID JONES
AND JEN WALKER
FROM CARSON HILL.
MR. SIMPSON,
YOU GOTTA BREATH.
AND BY A SLEEP TO SAY
WE END THE HEARTACHE.
BY THE THOUSAND-
AND THE THOU...
MARCO?
YOU CALLED?
I DID.
YEAH.
PA, WE NEED TO TALK.
SURE.
BEFORE THE PLAY STARTS,
PA, THERE'S SOMETHING THAT
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
IT'S ACTUALLY
ABOUT TIM.
I'VE BEEN HELPING HIM
LATELY
BECAUSE HE'S YOUNGER
AND HE'S CONFUSED.
HE'S GAY.
AND TIM THOUGHT
THAT YOU-
NO. YOU BROUGHT HIM
INTO MY HOUSE?
NO PA, I'M TRYING
TO TELL YOU SOMETHING.
I DON'T WANT
TO HEAR IT!
IT'S NOT ABOUT TIM.
THAT BOY IS GOING HOME.
I DO NOT WANT A QUEER
UNDER MY ROOF.
WHAT IF YOU ALREADY
HAVE ONE?
YOU'LL BE LATE
FOR YOUR PLAY.
MARCO:
PA.
I GOTTA GO
FIND YOUR MOTHER.
I-I DON'T KNOW
WHERE SHE IS.
YOU KNOW HOW SHE IS.
SHE GETS LOST SO EASILY.
MARCO:
WHAT? YOU'RE GONNA PRETEND-
YOU GONNA PRETEND THAT
I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING TO YOU?
PA!
BOY:
WE GOT TO GO.
CRAIG:
AND THY BEST GRACES
SPEND IT AT THY WILL!
BUT NOW, MY COUSIN HAMLET,
AND MY SON-
HAMLET?!
A LITTLE MORE THAN KIN,
AND LESS THAN KIND.
PETER:
WOW.
EMMA:
UNDO SOME THINGS-
NO, SILLY, ON YOU.
PETER:
I'M UH...
I'M SORRY ABOUT THE ROOM
OR WHATEVER.
EMMA:
IT'S OKAY.
UH...
CAN WE JUST...
PETER:
IT'S JUST,
UM, I HATE IT.
EMMA:
WHAT ABOUT YOUR BELT?
PETER:
NO.
I JUST WISH I COULD TAKE YOU
SOMEPLACE BETTER.
IT'S JUST MY DAD PRACTICALLY
USES THIS PLACE
AS A STORAGE LOCKER.
THREW ME IN HERE
WITH EVERYTHING ELSE
HE DOESN'T WANT.
EMMA:
WOW. YOU HAVE NO PRIVATE SPACE.
I CAN'T DO THIS.
MY ROOM,
SINCE THE BABY?
I'M STUCK IN THE BASEMENT
WITH THE LAUNDRY
AND THE MOULD
AND SNAKE'S OLD BOWLING SHOES.
SO I CAN RELATE.
I NEED TO GO.
MARCO:
ALAS, POOR YORICK.
I KNEW HIM, HORATIO.
HE HATH BORE ME ON HIS BACK
A THOUSAND TIMES AND NOW...
HOW ABHORRED.
HOW ABHORRED
IN MY IMAGINATION IT IS.
MY GORGE RISES AT IT.
AND HERE HUNG THOSE LIPS
THAT I-
I'M SORRY.
SORRY.
I HAVE TO DO THIS.
DAD?
I'M GAY.
PAIGE:
WAY TO GO, MARCO!
HERE HUNG THOSE LIPS
THAT I HAVE KISSED
I KNOW NOT HOW OFT.
DID YOU GET AWESOME SHOTS
OF HIS FLAT GOOFY BUTT?
DOES HILARITY ENSUE?
WILL I LAUGH, CRY, PEE?
EMMA:
MANNY, IT DIDN'T WORK.
NO!
HE BARELY NOTICED ME.
I GUESS, I'M A LOUSY
BOND GIRL.
WE'LL GET HIM NEXT TIME,
DON'T WORRY.
AND WE'LL PUT LAXATIVES
IN HIS FOOD,
RIGHT BEFORE A TEST
AND KABBBBLAAM!
THAT'D BE FUNNY.
MRS. DEL ROSSI:
MARCO, HOW WAS THE REST
OF THE PLAY?
MARCO:
AFTER MY LITTLE BIT OF IMPROV?
IT'S NOT BAD, I GUESS.
WE DIDN'T WIN.
I HAVE WORK EARLY TOMORROW.
SO WE'RE NOT GOING
TO TALK ABOUT THIS?
I AM TOO TIRED
FOR TALKING.
NO, PA, STOP.
STOP.
DID YOU EVER KNOW, HUH?
ALL THESE YEARS.
PA, DID YOU EVER KNOW
THAT I WAS GAY?
STOP SAYING THAT.
I CAN'T.
PA, IT'S TAKEN ME
SEVENTEEN YEARS TO SAY IT.
I'M GAY.
GAY.
I AM TOTALLY GAY!
THIS IS FUNNY TO YOU?!
NO!
NO, PA, THIS IS NOT FUNNY
AT ALL!
I JUST CAME OUT TO YOU
IN FRONT OF THE ENTIRE SCHOOL!
DOES THAT SOUND LIKE
A JOKE TO YOU?
LOOK,
YOU'RE MY BOY
AND I LOVE YOU.
YOU'RE THE BEST SON
A FATHER COULD EVER WANT.
BUT THIS PART OF YOU
I DON'T WANT TO KNOW.
I CAN'T KNOW ABOUT.
THEN YOU DON'T WANT
TO KNOW ME.
(SIGHS)
HE WILL, MARCO.
ONE DAY.
YEAH.