(SIGHING)
WHO'S THE EVIL GENIUS
WHO MADE MORNING
SO FRIGGING BRIGHT?
PAIGE:
OH, PROBABLY THE SAME
EVIL GENIUS
WHO DECIDED THAT THERE
SHOULD BE SCHOOL DAYS
AFTER CRAZY
MOVIE PREMIERES.
ALEX:
CRAZY?
IS THAT THE VERB
YOU'RE GONNA USE
TO DESCRIBE LAST NIGHT?
ADJECTIVE.
AND CONSIDERING I VOLUNTARILY
SLEPT ON THE DOWNSTAIRS COUCH,
CRAZY SEEMS ABOUT RIGHT.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO SLEEP
ON THE COUCH.
YOU WOULD'VE BEEN SAFE
IN THE ROOM WITH ME.
WE'RE GONNA BE LATE,
AND I HATE BEING LATE.
SO YOU SHOULD UH...
YOU SHOULD GET READY.
NOW IF I COULD JUST
FIND MY BUS PASS
THAT WOULD BE
ABSOLUTELY BRILLIANT.
PAIGE?
PAIGE:
YOU KNOW,
THE BUS PEOPLE
SHOULD REALLY JUST...
JUST GIVE A-A-AN IMPLANT
OR A... OR A TATTOO,
AND I COULD SAVE-
PAIGE!
HEY, I'M ALEX,
YOUR FRIEND?
CAN YOU JUST TALK TO ME?
I CAN'T EVEN BEGIN
TO PROCESS
WHAT HAPPENED LAST NIGHT.
NOT WITH OUR LITTLE
SISTER-ACT-SLUT-DANCE
OR... THE DRAMA WITH
YOUR MOM'S BOYFRIEND.
YOU CALL THAT DRAMA?
I CALL THAT REALITY TV.
PAIGE:
THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
THIS IS NOT FUNNY.
THERE IS A GIRL IN MY BED,
ALEX.
YOU.
IT'S LIKE I WOKE UP IN SOME
WEIRD MOVIE WITH SUBTITLES -
THE KIND OF MOVIE
THAT I HATE -
AND I CAN'T DEAL WITH IT,
OKAY?
I CAN'T DEAL WITH YOU.
ALL RIGHT,
I'M JUST GONNA GO RUB
SOME TOOTHPASTE ON MY TEETH,
AND THEN YOU CAN WALK
20 PACES AHEAD OF ME
ALL THE WAY
TO THE BUS STOP.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
PAIGE:
HI, HI, HI.
SORRY I'M LATE.
HAZEL:
HEY, WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOU LAST NIGHT?
YOU AND ALEX WENT
IN THE VIP PARTY
AND - POOF! -
YOU NEVER CAME
BACK OUT.
UM, I'M NOT QUITE SURE
HOW TO DESCRIBE
WHAT HAPPENED...
EXACTLY.
WHY?
DID YOU MEET
SOMEBODY?
YOU DID?!
IS HE FAMOUS?
WOULD I KNOW
WHO HE IS?
FAMOUS? NO.
BUT UM... YOU MIGHT
KNOW WHO... HE IS.
SORRY TO INTERRUPT.
THE ASSEMBLY'S
AT 4:00 P.M.,
SO WE SHOULD REALLY
START REHEARSING
THAT NEW CHEER.
YOU KNOW, THE BIG
"THANK YOU KEVIN SMITH"
ASSEMBLY;
THE ONE THAT YOU'VE WRITTEN
THE NEW CHEER FOR.
YOU HAVE WRITTEN IT,
RIGHT?
SURE, HON.
UM, I'VE GOT IT ALL
WORKED OUT IN MY HEAD.
SO LET'S MEET BACK
HERE AT NOON
AND I WILL HAVE
THE MOST BRILLIANTISH CHEER
TYPED UP AND READY
FOR REHEARSING.
OKAY, GREAT!
WHEN YOU ASKED
FOR A RIDE,
I THOUGHT YOU HAD
SOMETHING TO TELL ME.
(MOTORBIKE APPROACHING)
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU LET HIM
KEEP THAT STUPID MOTORBIKE.
AW, IT'S HARMLESS...
IN A MID-LIFE CRISIS
SORT OF WAY.
HE LOOKS HAPPY.
EMMA:
MOM, BE HONEST,
HE LOOKS STUPID.
THAT BIKE WAS SUCH
A MISTAKE.
SOMETIMES YOU HAVE TO LET
PEOPLE MAKE MISTAKES.
THAT'S WHAT LOVE'S
ALL ABOUT.
EMMA?
EMMA, I KNOW YOU
HATE ME RIGHT NOW -
NOT THAT I DON'T
DESERVE IT, BUT-
FOR HAVING AN AFFAIR
WITH THE PRINCIPAL?
I THINK YOU DESERVE
JUST A DROP
OF ANGER FOR THAT.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
IT'S NOT AN AFFAIR,
ALL RIGHT?
IT STOPPED AT KISSING.
AND I PROMISE IT'LL NEVER,
EVER HAPPEN AGAIN.
I HAVE TO GET TO CLASS.
SPIKE:
(HONKING THE HORN)
BYE, GUYS.
HATZILAKOS:
HOW'RE YOU DOING TODAY?
GOOD.
MORNING, EMMA.
DON'T TALK TO ME.
HEY.
CAN I ASK YOU
A TEENSY QUESTION?
DO YOU EVER
THINK ABOUT GIRLS?
UH... INTERESTING
QUESTION
FIRST THING
IN THE MORNING.
NOW, DID YOU MISS THE YEARS
THAT I DATED YOUR BROTHER?
BUT JUST BECAUSE
YOU'RE GAY,
THAT DOESN'T MEAN
YOU CAN'T THINK
ABOUT GIRLS
EVERY NOW AND THEN,
RIGHT?
ARE YOU TRYING TO HOOK ME UP
WITH SOMEONE?
OH WICKED.
DOES THAT MEAN
THERE'S A GIRL OUT THERE
WHO LIKES ME?
NO.
THE OBJECT OF FEMALE
AFFECTION'S...
PRETTY MUCH ME.
YOU?
OH, I KNEW IT!
IT'S HEATHER SINCLAIR.
PAIGE, I'VE SEEN THE WAY
SHE LOOKS AT YOU-
EW! DOUBLE EW!
NO, IT'S...
IT'S NOT HEATHER SINCLAIR.
ALEX.
HEY.
PAIGE:
HI.
HEY,
PULL UP A CHAIR.
HEY, YOU TWO STILL NEED
TO TELL ME ABOUT
THAT VIP PARTY
LAST NIGHT.
ALEX:
I THINK I'M GONNA SIT
OVER HERE TODAY.
WHOA.
PAIGE, IT'S-IT'S ALEX?
SHE KISSED ME
LAST NIGHT.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
SIMPSON:
MORNING, CLASS.
AS YOU KNOW, KEVIN SMITH
WILL BE VISITING US TODAY.
I WANT YOU TO TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF HIM BEING HERE
AND PREPARE SOME SMART
MEDIA QUESTIONS FOR HIM.
WAITING FOR SOMEONE?
OH LOOK,
HERE I AM IN AN ALLEY
AND A RAT APPEARS
JUST LIKE MAGIC.
I FOUND THESE UNDER THE TABLE
AT THE CLUB.
I THOUGHT MAYBE YOUR NEW
BESTEST GIRLFRIEND
MIGHT WANT THEM BACK.
JUST GIVE ME THE SHOES
AND GO AWAY.
FIRST I WANT YOU
TO TELL ME
WHAT IT IS YOU THINK
YOU COULD POSSIBLY
HAVE IN COMMON
WITH A STUCK-UP
CHEERLEADER.
PAIGE:
SORRY I TOOK SO LONG!
I SEEM TO HAVE INTERRUPTED
FUN TIME WITH JAY,
WHICH LOOKED
KIND OF HOT.
NOT. IN FACT,
IT'S BEEN CANCELLED.
REPLACED BY
FUN TIME WITH PAIGE.
PAIGE:
ALEX? WE NEED TO TALK.
THIS CAN'T HAPPEN.
I'M NOT A...
A LESBIAN.
AND YOU THINK I AM?
WELL, YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO KISSED ME.
WHAT ARE YOU, FIVE?
AND FOR THE RECORD,
YOU KISSED ME BACK.
I'M NOT EVEN SUPPOSED
TO LIKE PEOPLE LIKE YOU.
PEOPLE WHO WEAR BLACK
WITH NAVY
AND WHO HATE
EVERYTHING...
AND EVERYONE.
I DON'T HATE YOU.
EVEN IF YOU ARE ONE
OF THE POPULAR IDIOTS
WHO DRINKS LATTES
AND READS
STUPID MAGAZINES
AND LAUGHS
WAY TOO LOUD.
I HAVE TO LAUGH
WHEN I'M AROUND YOU.
I CAN'T REALLY HELP IT.
AND I HAVE TO BE BETTER
WHEN I'M AROUND YOU.
I CAN'T HELP IT
EITHER.
JAY:
NEED A COUPLE OF HANDS
FOR YOUR POMS?
HAZEL:
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
JAY:
WORLD PEACE,
A SALAMI SUB,
AND A CHANCE TO TALK
TO MY GOOD FRIEND, HAZEY.
WE'RE NOT FRIENDS.
SO YOU DON'T WANNA
HEAR MY NEWS THEN.
THAT PAIGE HAS GONE
THE GAY-WAY.
EXCUSE ME?
JAY:
YOU HEARD ME.
YEAH, I SAW YOUR FRIEND
AND MY EX
DOING SOME SERIOUSLY
SEXY DANCING LAST NIGHT.
SO? YOU NEED
TO GET OUT MORE.
GIRLS DO THAT STUFF
ALL THE TIME.
JAY:
AND I JUST SAW PAIGE
LAY A BIG OL' SMOOCH
ON ALEX.
YOU'RE TRYING TO TELL ME
THAT'S SOMETHING
THAT GIRLS DO
ALL THE TIME?
I'M NOT GETTING
INVOLVED IN THIS.
LISTEN,
DO YOU REALLY THINK
THAT PAIGE WANTS TO END
HER DISTINGUISHED
HIGH SCHOOL CAREER
AS THE SCHOOL LESBO?
YOU'RE BEING
DISGUSTING.
I'M BEING HONEST.
AND WHAT ABOUT YOU,
HUH?
ARE YOU LOOKING FORWARD
TO THOSE INEVITABLE RUMOURS
ABOUT YOU AND PAIGE?
IS THAT HOW YOU
WANNA BE REMEMBERED?
HAZEL:
PAIGE, I NEED TO SPEAK TO YOU.
KINDA BUSY RIGHT NOW.
I'LL BET YOU'LL BE EVEN
BUSIER LATER...
WITH HER.
PAIGE...
I'VE GOT YOU.
WHAT'RE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I'M TALKING ABOUT ALEX.
WHAT IS SHE DOING HERE?
IS SHE LIKE
YOUR GIRLFRIEND NOW?
OOF!
DON'T WORRY,
I'M FINE.
WHO TOLD YOU?
JAY.
PAIGE, DID YOU
BECOME A LESBIAN
AND NOT TELL ME?
NO, NO, HAZEL...
I'M NOT A LESBIAN.
HELLO!
MATT? SPINNER?
I'VE DATED LOTS OF GUYS.
WELL, THEN HOW COME JAY
SAW YOU KISSING ALEX?
UM...
I JUST...
GOT CAUGHT UP
IN A MOMENT.
AND THAT'S ALL?
OF COURSE.
IT WAS TOTALLY STUPID.
IT MEANT NOTHING.
SHE MEANS NOTHING.
ALEX...
DON'T BOTHER.
HOW COULD YOU?
I DO NOT LIKE GIRLS.
I CANNOT LIKE GIRLS.
THEN WHY DID YOU
KISS ME?
I DON'T KNOW.
I FELT BAD.
I DIDN'T WANT
TO HURT YOU.
WHO NEEDS YOUR PITY,
HUH?
I DON'T!
KEVIN:
WELL...
OH, UM...
EXCUSE ME WHILE I GO UH...
FLUSH MY HEAD DOWN THE TOILET.
MS. HATZILAKOS:
OKAY, WE'RE READY TO BEGIN.
CAN I HAVE EVERYONE'S
ATTENTION, PLEASE?
CAN EVERY-
(LOUD MIC FEEDBACK)
CAN I HAVE EVERYONE'S
ATTENTION!
PLEASE GRAB YOUR SEATS,
WE'RE GONNA BEGIN.
NOW!
THANK YOU.
AT THIS TIME LAST YEAR,
DEGRASSI WAS STRUGGLING
OUT OF AN AWFUL TRAGEDY.
AND THEN CAME KEVIN SMITH.
(APPLAUSE AND CHEERING)
HE CAST OUR SCHOOL
AS THE BACKDROP FOR HIS MOVIE
"JAY AND SILENT BOB
GO CANADIAN, EH?"
AND AS A TOKEN
OF OUR GRATITUDE,
MR. SMITH...
I WOULD LIKE TO PRESENT YOU
WITH AN HONORARY DIPLOMA.
NO. THANK YOU.
(APPLAUSE)
BUT BEFORE WE MAKE IT
COMPLETEY OFFICIAL,
OUR SPIRIT SQUAD WOULD LIKE
TO SEND YOU ON YOUR WAY,
IN STYLE.
PAIGE?
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
I HAVEN'T COME UP
WITH ANYTHING.
JUST IMPROVISE.
OKAY, UH... GO.
DO SOME CARTWHEELS!
OKAY.
PAIGE:
GIVE ME A "K"!
"K!"
PAIGE:
GIVE ME AN "E"!
"E"?
GIVE ME A...
V-I-N-S-M-I-T-H!
YAY!
UH...
(SMATTERING OF APPLAUSE)
MOM, I'M FINE.
DON'T SEEM FINE TO ME,
LITTLE GIRL.
BUENOS DIAS,
SENIORITAS!
THAT'S NOT YOUR
MOTORCYCLE HELMET.
WHERE'S ALL THE KEVLAR?
I SOLD IT.
THE MOTORBIKE, THE HELMET,
THE WORKS, BECAUSE...
WE'RE GOING TO MEXICO!
YOU, ME, EMMA AND MANNY
WILL BE SPENDING A WEEK
ON THE MAYAN RIVIERA
AT THE END OF TERM!
BUT WHAT ABOUT JACK?
THE GRANDMAS ARE ALREADY
FIGHTING FOR HIM!
IT'S ALL BEEN TAKEN CARE OF.
SPIKE:
OH... I LOVE YOU SO MUCH!
I DON'T DESERVE
SUCH A PERFECT HUSBAND.
STOP IT!
JUST STOP IT!
EMMA?
WHAT IS IT,
SWEETHEART?
TELL ME WHAT'S WRONG.
IT'S ABOUT ME.
IT'S...IT'S SOMETHING I DID.
ALEX:
WHY IS IT THAT EVERY TIME
I TURN A CORNER,
THERE YOU ARE?
JAY:
I'M LIKE ONE OF THOSE
ANNOYING POP SONGS.
ONCE I GET STUCK IN YOUR HEAD,
I'M IMPOSSIBLE TO GET RID OF.
WHAT DO YOU WANT, JAY?
REALLY?
MY LIFE SUCKS.
OKAY, I'M KICKED OUT
OF SCHOOL,
SEAN MOVED AWAY,
SPINNER'S FOUND THE LORD...
AND THE ONLY PERSON
WHO EVER REALLY GOT ME
WON'T EVEN GIVE ME
THE TIME OF DAY.
I'M NOT PERFECT,
I KNOW THAT.
BUT... I GET YOU,
YOU KNOW?
THE REAL YOU.
'CAUSE YOU AND ME,
WERE THE SAME.
YOU KNOW? WHY-
WHY DO YOU WANT
TO FIGHT THAT?
KEVIN:
...SHOOT IT!
PITCH THE ROCK, SIR,
PITCH IT!
JASON:
WHAT'S UUUUUP!
OH COME ON!
YOU SUUUCCCCCK!
DON'T HATE THE PLAYER, SON,
HATE THE GAME.
KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
OH, MISS MICHALCHUK!
WANNA SHOOT SOME HORSE
WITH US?
OR ARE YOU RUNNING OFF
TO A SPELLING BEE
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
OH, ABOUT THE CHEER...
PLEASE KNOW THAT I'VE COMPOSED
MORE CHEERY BEFORE.
NOBODY'S EVER DONE A CHEER
IN MY HONOR, SO BY DEFAULT,
YOUR CHEER, FOR ME,
WAS ABOUT THE BEST
I'VE EVER HAD.
SO THANK YOU.
I WAS KINDA DISTRACTED.
DISTRACTED, HUH?
LET ME GUESS,
BY SOME KIND OF ACID-TONGUED,
RAVEN-HAIRED BEAUTY
FROM THE WRONG SIDE
OF THE TRACKS, MAYBE?
KEVIN, JASON,
YOUR TAXI'S HERE.
KEVIN:
THANK YOU, MS. HATZILAKOS.
LET ME ASK YOU A QUESTION.
DO YOU LIKE THIS GIRL?
LIKE, YOU KNOW,
"LIKE HER" LIKE HER?
YEAH, I LIKE HER,
BUT I'M NOT GAY.
MY BROTHER IS GAY,
I'M STRAIGHT.
I ALWAYS HAVE BEEN.
YOUR BROTHER'S GAY?
MY BROTHER'S GAY,
TOO.
EVEN GOT MARRIED
TO A GUY.
REALLY?
YEAH,
IT WAS THE HOTTEST WEDDING
I'VE EVER BEEN TO IN MY LIFE.
REALLY, REALLY COOL,
HANDS DOWN.
ALMOST MADE ME WANT
TO SWITCH TEAMS.
ALMOST.
LOOK, I'M PROBABLY
THE LAST GUY IN THE WORLD
WHO SHOULD BE GIVING YOU
ADVICE ON THIS VERY SUBJECT,
BUT I DON'T KNOW...
YOU GUYS SEEMED HAPPY
THE OTHER NIGHT, YOU KNOW?
AND THAT'S KINDA RARE
AND WHETHER IT'S GAY,
STRAIGHT, BI, WHATEVER,
IT'S KINDA WORTH INVESTIGATING
A LITTLE FURTHER, I'D SAY.
JUST MY TWO CENTS.
YOU'RE JUST GONNA
STAND THERE
STARIN' AT ME
AFTER I'VE DROPPED
THAT WISDOM ON YOU?
C'MON,
THAT'S YOUR MOVE!
GO CHASE THE GIRL,
SILLY!
SIMPSON:
IT WAS A MISTAKE!
IT WAS JUST A KISS!
SPIKE:
WHAT ABOUT EMMA?
WHAT ABOUT HER FEELINGS?
SIMPSON:
LOOK, BELIEVE ME,
IT WAS NEVER MY INTENTION
TO INVOLVE HER IN THIS.
SPIKE:
JUST GO!
I'M SO SORRY,
EMMA.
BUT I'M GONNA GO
STAY AT JOEY'S,
JUST FOR AWHILE.
NO! NO, YOU CAN'T!
GO UP THERE AND CONVINCE HER
TO LET YOU STAY.
EMMA, LISTEN...
WHAT I DID
WAS HORRIBLE BUT...
I WOULD NEVER
HAVE DONE IT
IF THERE WASN'T SOMETHING
WRONG WITH ME.
I GOTTA GO FIGURE
THAT OUT.
DO YOU LOVE MY MOTHER?
OF COURSE.
AND JACK?
EM, HE'S MY SON.
WHAT ABOUT ME?
YOU KNOW I DO.
SO WHAT'S TO FIGURE OUT?!
(SOBBING)
JAY:
THIS IS NICE, HUH?
JUST LIKE OLD TIMES.
I SAID YOU COULD COME IN
AND WATCH TV, JAY.
THAT'S ALL.
THIS DOESN'T
MEAN ANYTHING.
YEAH, SURE, LEXI.
WHATEVER YOU SAY.
(DOOR SLAMS)
CHAD.
HEEEY!
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME.
YOU BEEN WORKING HARD?
NO, HARDLY WORKING!
WHERE ARE YOU AT,
BUD?
OH YOU KNOW,
HERE AND THERE.
JUST TRYING TO KEEP
MYSELF OUT OF TROUBLE.
EMILY:
OH GIMME SOME SUGAR,
YOU HANDSOME DEVIL! HELLO.
LOOK AT YOU...
YOU ARE LOOKING AS BEAUTIFUL
AS EVER, EMILY.
AW, SUCH A CHARMER!
I ALWAYS KNEW THIS ONE
WAS A KEEPER, LEXI.
SORT OF REMINDS ME
OF OL' CHAD HERE.
I AM SO GLAD THAT YOU FINALLY
CAME TO YOUR SENSES
AND TOOK JAY BACK,
BABY.
I HAVEN'T TAKEN
HIM BACK.
WELL, NOT YET.
NO! NOT EVER!
I NEED SOME AIR.
'KAY.
I'VE BEEN TRYING
TO WORK UP THE NERVE
TO RING THE DOORBELL.
WE DON'T HAVE ONE.
WELCOME TO MY WORLD.
ANY ROOM IN IT
FOR A STUPID GIRL?
I ALREADY HAVE
ONE OF THOSE.
WELL, HOW ABOUT...
ROOM FOR...
SOMEONE WHO'S READY
TO STOP WORRYING SO MUCH
ABOUT WHAT OTHER
PEOPLE THINK?
MIGHT BE ROOM FOR HER.
ALEX,
I'M SORRY ABOUT BEFORE...
WHAT I SAID.
WHATEVER PAIGE,
IT'S COOL.
NO, IT'S NOT.
I SAID YOU WERE
NOTHING TO ME,
WHICH...
WHICH IS A TOTAL LIE.
BECAUSE RIGHT NOW?
YOU'RE PRETTY MUCH EVERYTHING.