(CRAIG PLAYING GUITAR)
PORSCHE 911 CARRERA.
FIRE ENGINE RED.
FULL LEATHER INTERIOR.
THAT'S WHAT I'D BUY.
WOW,
THAT IS SO '80S.
WHAT?!
FLIP THOSE COLLARS UP,
MR. MANNING.
OKAY,
SO WHAT ARE YOU GONNA BUY
AFTER WE'RE DISCOVERED
AT THE NORTHERN
SOUND SHOWCASE?
I GUESS I'D INVEST
THE MONEY,
BUY A CONDO OR...
A SMART CAR.
OR BOTH.
(YAWNING)
DON'T.
STOP.
STOP DOING THAT!
(PLAYFUL GIGGLING)
CRAIG.
MANNY'S ON THE PHONE
FOR YOU.
TELL HER I'M STUDYING.
DOESN'T LOOK LIKE STUDYING.
THANKS, MOM.
ELLIE:
SPEAKING OF STUDYING,
SOMEONE IS SUPPOSED
TO BE PREPARING
FOR HIS HISTORY PRESENTATION.
CRAIG:
WHO CARES?
NOW THE SHOWCASE
IS IN TWO DAYS,
SO DROP THAT BOOK
AND GRAB THOSE STICKS.
'CAUSE NO MATTER WHAT,
WE ARE GONNA WIN THIS THING.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
CRAIG:
SO THERE WAS THIS PART
OF FRANCE
AND GERMANY WANTED IT BAD.
SO THEY UH...
CROSSED THE BORDER-
AND THEY TOOK THIS DETOUR
BECAUSE...?
CRAIG:
BECAUSE...
WELL, SIMPLE...
LET SEE,
IT'S RIGHT HERE.
AFTER THAT ONE GUY KILLED
THAT ARCHDUKE, UH...
(WHISPERS)
FRANZ FERDINAND.
(COUGHS)
ELLIE, GESUNDHEIT.
THANKS.
CRAIG:
EUROPE'S TREATIES
WERE ALL MESSED UP,
AND GERMANY TOOK ADVANTAGE
OF IT.
TOBY:
SO, LIBERTY AND I ARE GOING
TO REPRESENT DEGRASSI
AT THE METRO TORONTO
STUDENTS ASSEMBLY.
BUT WE NEED YOUR INPUT,
SO EMAIL US
YOUR THOUGHTS,
AND WE'LL COMPILE THEM.
MEETING ADJOURNED.
SO HOW ARE YOU GETTING
TO THE ASSEMBLY?
'CAUSE I WAS THINKING...
THAT IF YOU NEEDED A LIFT,
JT COULD DRIVE YOU.
TOBY, YOU KNOW
I DON'T TALK TO JT.
YEAH,
BUT I WISH YOU WOULD.
BECAUSE THIS SUCKS,
OKAY?
I MEAN, I'M FRIENDS
WITH BOTH YOU.
WELL, I'VE GOT ENOUGH
ON MY PLATE
WITHOUT WORRYING
ABOUT THAT.
HOW'S IT GOING,
ANYWAY?
WITH THE BABY,
I MEAN.
MY DOCTOR TOLD ME
TO TAKE IT EASIER -
FOR THE BABY.
HE SAYS I'M OVER-STRESSED,
BUT I THINK I'M FINE.
WELL,
I'M HERE TO HELP -
STUDENT COUNCIL,
WHATEVER.
AND NOT JUST 'CAUSE
I'M YOUR VICE, OKAY?
TOBY:
SHE'S FINE.
SHE'S STRESSED BUT...
YOU KNOW, HER DOCTOR
TOLD HER TO TAKE IT EASY,
FOR THE KID.
WHAT?
THE BABY'S IN DANGER?
I DIDN'T-
I DIDN'T SAY THAT.
WELL, IS LIBERTY
IN DANGER?
LOOK, CALM DOWN.
LIBERTY'S FINE.
I'LL MAKE SURE
SHE TAKES IT EASY.
GOOD.
SO WILL I.
JT, IF LIBERTY FINDS OUT
WE'VE BEEN HAVING
LITTLE MEETINGS,
I'M DEAD.
MURDERED.
JT:
SORRY.
BUT I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING,
OKAY?
WHAT OTHER CHOICE
DO I HAVE?
JIMMY:
"AND, THUS,
CRAIG FAILS HISTORY."
MY POOR BABY.
CRAIG:
IT'S ONE GRADE,
SO WHAT?
UM...
UNIVERSITY.
UM, GETTING INTO
UM...YOUR LIFE.
YEAH,
BREATHE, MARCO.
THEY'VE ALREADY
SUBMITTED OUR GRADES.
ANYWAY, WHO ACTUALLY
WANTS TO GO?
REALLY?
OKAY,
BESIDES THE TWO OF YOU.
HI, I'M ELLIE NASH,
FUTURE JOURNALISM SCHOOL
STUDENT
AND ROVING REPORTER.
AND YOU'RE
SO ANNOYING.
JIMMY:
SO EL, YOU'RE...
YOU'RE REALLY TAKING
NEXT YEAR OFF
TO LIKE...
TO FOLLOW CRAIG AROUND
OR WHATEVER?
CRAIG:
NO.
SHE - AND WE -
ARE GOING TO SPEND IT
CUTTING OUR FIRST ALBUM
AFTER WE'RE DISCOVERED
AT THE NORTHERN SOUND SHOWCASE.
THAT WAY, NO WASTING
THE NEXT FOUR YEARS
ON SOME USELESS B.A.
WHICH IS WORTH AN F.
JIMMY:
GAVIN.
WHAT'S THIS LITTLE NUMBER?
IS THIS UH...
IS THIS A COPY OF YOU AND DARCY
SINGING "JESUS LOVES ME"?
NO, THAT'S MONEY MONEY.
OUR DISHWASHER'S
THEIR LEAD GUITARIST
AND THEY ARE YOUR COMPETITION
AT THE NORTHERN SOUND SHOWCASE.
AND THEY'RE GOOD.
(CLACKING DRUM STICKS)
CRAIG:
ALL RIGHT!
♪ WAKE UP!
GLAD TO MEET YOU ♪
♪ I NEVER MET YOU BEFORE ♪
♪ YOU CAME WITH THE FEELING ♪
♪ IT DROVE ME OUT
MY FRONT DOOR ♪
♪ WAY OUT!
SOON TOGETHER ♪
♪ WALKING AND TALKING
OUT MY FRONT DOOR ♪
♪ TOO LATE ♪
♪ GLAD TO MEET YOU ♪
♪ I NEVER MET YOU BEFORE ♪
♪ WAKE UP, EVERYBODY ♪
♪ LIVIN' THE DREAM
THAT DROVE ME WHERE EVERYBODY ♪
♪ WHERE I MET YOU
AND YOU MET ME ♪
♪ AND WE THREE GROOVED
TO THE BEAT
♪ TO THE BEAT -
THREE! ♪
♪ APPLESEED CAME BACK
WITH A VENGEANCE ♪
♪ WHAT ARE WE IN
APPREHENDIN' OUR FRIENDS ♪
♪ YOU TOO,
LITTLE BOY BLUE ♪
♪ CAME BACK AND GOT BACK
AND GOT THE FLU ♪
ANNOUNCER:
THANK YOU.
THAT WAS DOWNTOWN SASQUATCH.
NOW GIVE IT UP
FOR MONEY MONEY!
MONEY MONEY:
♪ WE ARE NOT WORTH THAT MUCH ♪
♪ OH SHE ♪
♪ ONLY WANTS ME FOR... ♪
♪ MY MONEY! OH MY... ♪
♪ MY MY MY MONEY! ♪
(CHEERING)
OKAY.
OKAY,
THEY'RE GOOD.
BUT THEIR TIES MAKE ME
WANT TO STRANGLE THEM.
LEO:
CUTE GIRL'S GOT A POINT.
LEO DAVIES.
HEY, I'M CRAIG.
THIS IS-
GOTCHA.
SO GOOD SHOW TONIGHT.
LIKED THE SONG,
LOVED THE VOCALS.
THANKS.
IT'S TOO BAD MONEY MONEY
BLEW US OFF THE STAGE.
OH, THEY'RE GOOD,
BUT THEIR SOUND'S
BEEN PLAYED,
SO IS THEIR LOOK.
NO DEPTH.
SO WE'VE GOT DEPTH?
DEFINITELY.
THE BAND'S A LITTLE ROUGH.
YEAH. NOT SO
COORDINATED HERE.
YEAH,
BUT IT WORKED.
I LIKED IT.
AND...
I'D LIKE TO MANAGE YOU.
JOEY:
UH, CRAIG,
DANCING WITH THE STARS
IS ON?
A MANAGER... OKAY?
A REAL,
MUSIC INDUSTRY MANAGER
HAS SIGNED US TONIGHT.
THAT'S AMAZING,
CRAIG!
WOW!
YEAH, UM...
LEO'S GONNA WORK WITH US
TO SHARPEN OUR SOUND.
HE'S GOING TO INTRODUCE US
TO A&R, RECORD COMPANIES.
TOMORROW WE HAVE
A PHOTO SHOOT SET UP.
THAT IS AMAZING,
BUDDY.
AND WELL...
SPEAKING OF POTENTIALLY
AMAZING NEWS,
THIS LETTER ARRIVED
FOR YOU TODAY.
FROM U OF T.
OH WOW.
UH... I GOT-
I GOT EARLY ACCEPTANCE.
AND A FULL SCHOLARSHIP.
WHAT?!
OH, CRAIG,
THAT IS AWESOME!
CONGRATULATIONS,
BUDDY!
OH, WE'RE SO PROUD
OF YOU!
CRAIG,
SUMMER WITH YOUR BAND;
FREE UNIVERSITY
IN THE FALL.
YOU'RE TOTALLY SET.
YEAH...
OKAY. HOLD ON.
THIS IS SO GREAT
AND EVERYTHING,
BUT UM, I DON'T KNOW
IF FOR SURE I CAN DO THIS.
I MEAN, I HAVE TALK
TO LEO FIRST.
OKAY CRAIG,
I KNOW YOU'RE EXCITED, OKAY?
BUT THIS IS SCHOOL;
THIS IS YOUR FUTURE.
CRAIG:
MY FUTURE'S MUSIC.
OKAY? I'M NOT GOING
TO GIVE THIS UP.
LIKE...
SORRY, THIS IS THE OPPORTUNITY
OF A LIFETIME.
♪♪♪
♪ WAKE UP!
GLAD TO MEET YOU ♪
♪ I NEVER MET YOU BEFORE ♪
HAWKE,
THIS AIN'T WORKING
FOR ME.
(CONSIDERING)
UH...
MARCO,
STEP OVER HERE.
OKAY.
LEO:
AND JIMMY, SCOOT OVER HERE,
BESIDE MARCO.
UM WAIT,
ISN'T HE BLOCKING
MY DRUMS?
YOU'RE OUR CHICK
ON STICKS.
YOU CAN SELL IT
FROM BACK THERE.
(WHISTLES)
THANKS.
CRAIG, I NEED YOU
TO STEP FORWARD.
FORWARD.
YEAH, GOOD.
OKAY, HAWKE?
YEAH?
UH... LEO?
I'M KIND OF ABOUT
"THE BAND".
DUDE,
THIS IS DIFFERENT.
SEE NOW "THE BAND"
IS ABOUT YOU.
♪♪♪
LEO:
OKAY, HAWKE...
(LOUD CAMERA CLICK)
HEY.
LEO SAID
HE'S RUNNING LATE.
UM... EL?
CHICK ON STICKS
IS GONNA SELL IT
FROM OVER HERE, YO.
LEO:
OKAY.
SO...
NORTHERN SOUND SHOWCASE
ALWAYS ASKS A FEW BANDS BACK
FOR THEIR FINAL NIGHT.
THIS YEAR THEY'VE ASKED BACK
MONEY MONEY,
THE AUNT SELMAS
AND DOWNTOWN SASQUATCH.
CRAIG:
YOU'RE SERIOUS.
LEO:
PLUS, ONE OF THE EXECS
IS INVITING HIS FAVOURITE BAND
OUT TO VANCOUVER
TO CUT A DEMO WITH JAKALOPE.
WHICH IS HUGE.
WAIT,
SO IF THIS RECORD GUY
LIKES US,
WE SPEND THE SUMMER
IN VANCOUVER?
LEO:
YEAH, GUYS,
THIS WOULD HAPPEN
NEXT WEEK.
YOU'D BE ON A FLIGHT
ON SUNDAY NIGHT.
FOR HOW LONG?
AS LONG AS IT TAKES.
WEEKS. MONTHS.
MARCO:
WAIT, WHAT-WHAT ABOUT SCHOOL?
WE HAVE EXAMS,
PAPERS.
WE'LL SCREW UP
OUR ENTIRE YEAR.
LEO:
SO? THIS IS A ONE SHOT DEAL.
IT'S MORE IMPORTANT
THAN SCHOOL.
GUYS, DON'T WORRY
ABOUT THIS STUFF.
WORRY ABOUT POLISHING
YOUR SOUND.
IT'S A LITTLE ROUGH.
OH, BUT...
ROUGH'S PART
OF OUR CHARM.
LEO:
ROUGH'S GONNA HOLD YOU BACK,
ESPECIALLY AROUND
THE DRUMMING.
LEO, WE'LL BE FINE.
SHE'LL BE FINE.
YOU HAVE MY WORD ON IT.
(SIGHS)
OKAY.
I THOUGHT WE'D GO
THROUGH THE SONG
FROM START TO FINISH,
JUST DRUMS.
CRAIG, THIS IS
A HOPELESS CAUSE.
I'M NOT A GOOD DRUMMER.
HEY, WE HAVE NO TIME
FOR NEGATIVITY, OKAY?
LET'S JUST FOCUS HERE.
OKAY.
(DRUMMING)
IS THAT BETTER?
THAT'S PERFECT.
JUST KEEP GOING.
WE GOT A GIG
AT THE SHOWCASE.
ANOTHER ONE.
THE BAND GETS TO-
THE BAND, THE BAND...
THE BAND IS ALL
THAT YOU CARE ABOUT.
THIS SHOWCASE MATTERS,
MANNY.
MANNY:
RIGHT NOW,
IT LOOKS LIKE THE ONLY THING
THAT MATTERS IS ELLIE.
MANNY!
MANNY...
HATZILAKOS:
LIBERTY, I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU WERE STILL HERE.
OH, WE'RE JUST
FINISHING UP.
HATZILAKOS:
LISTEN, IT CAME
TO MY ATTENTION...
WELL, LET ME REPHRASE THAT.
I'M CONCERNED ABOUT YOU,
LIBERTY.
YOUR BABY IS DUE SOON,
YOU'VE WORKING
AWFULLY HARD,
AND YOU JUST SEEM STRESSED.
STRESSED?
AND WHAT WOULD GIVE YOU
THAT IDEA?
HATZILAKOS:
WELL, WITH ALL DUE RESPECT,
I THINK YOU SHOULD STEP ASIDE
AND YOU SHOULD LET TOBY
GO ALONE TO THE ASSEMBLY.
MS. HATZILAKOS,
IS THIS BECAUSE YOU DON'T
WANT A PREGNANT STUDENT
REPRESENTING THE SCHOOL?
HATZILAKOS:
NO LIBERTY.
IT'S BECAUSE
I WANT TO MAKE SURE
THAT YOU GET THE REST
THAT YOU NEED.
UH... TOBY,
YOU DIDN'T TALK TO HER,
RIGHT?
ME? NO!
NO, NO, NO, NO...
I WAS JUST...
OH MY...
LOOK AT THE TIME!
I HAVE TO GET THE MATERIALS
READY FOR...
FOR THE ASSEMBLY.
CHOP-CHOP.
♪ I NEVER MET YOU BEFORE ♪
♪ WAKE UP, EVERYBODY ♪
♪ LIVIN' THE DREAM
THAT DROVE ME WHERE ♪
♪ THREW THE BODY WHERE ♪
♪ I MET YOU
AND YOU MET ME ♪
♪ AND WE THREE GROOVE
TO THE BEAT
♪ TO THE BEAT -
THREE ♪
♪ APPLESEED CAME BACK
WITH A VENGEANCE ♪
♪ WHAT ARE WE IN
APPREHENDING OUR FRIENDS ♪
♪ YOU TOO,
LITTLE BOY BLUE ♪
♪ CAME BACK
AND GOT BACK ♪
♪ AND GOT THE FLU ♪
WELL, IT'S BETTER.
BETTER,
BUT IT'S NOT GOOD.
SEE, A ROUGH SOUND
IS ONE THING,
BUT...
YOUR DRUMMER
CAN'T KEEP TIME.
CRAIG:
WE'VE WORKED ON THAT.
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE TO.
THERE ARE A LOT OF GREAT
DRUMMERS IN THIS TOWN.
ELLIE:
MR. DAVIES, PLEASE...
I'M NEW,
BUT I'M DEDICATED.
I'LL PRACTICE
ALL NIGHT.
HONEY, YOU'RE NOT
CUT OUT FOR THIS.
JUST LIKE I'M NOT CUT OUT
TO FLY AIRPLANES.
THEM'S THE BREAKS.
I HOPE TORONTO HAS A LOT
OF GREAT SINGERS, TOO.
OKAY.
LIBERTY:
ET TU, TO-BAY?
(PAINED GROAN)
SO...
YOU USED MY PREGNANCY
TO STAGE A COUP D'ETAT?
NICE.
LIBERTY, THAT'S NOT
WHAT HAPPENED.
REALLY.
THEN WHO WENT
TO MS. HATZILAKOS, HMM?
OKAY, IT WAS ME.
I'M THE BLABBER.
TOBY "THE BLABBER" ISAACS.
THAT'S ME.
BUT LIBERTY,
IF I WAS PREGNANT?
AND, YOU KNOW,
MY DOCTOR TOLD ME
TO SLOW DOWN?
THAT'S WHAT I'D BE DOING
RIGHT NOW.
YEAH...
WHATEVER, TOBES.
I'M GOING TO THE ASSEMBLY
AND YOU'RE DRIVING ME.
(ENGINE RATTLES
AND BACKFIRES)
(ENGINE DIES)
UH...
THIS ISN'T CARSON HILL.
YEAH.
I KNOW.
BUT MY BUBBIE'S CAR
DOESN'T SEEM TO GET THAT.
I'M CALLING A CAB.
DON'T EXPECT A RIDE
BECAUSE TRAITORS HAVE TO WALK.
I'M NOT A TRAITOR.
YOU ATTEMPTED TO OUST ME
FROM MY PRESIDENCY.
YOU,
TRAITOROUS YOU.
LOOK, I DON'T WANT
YOUR STUPID JOB.
SO WHY BLAB
TO HATZILAKOS?
I DIDN'T.
I BLABBED TO JT,
AND JT BLABBED TO HATZILAKOS.
BECAUSE THIS WHOLE TIME
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO HELP HIM
KEEP UP WITH YOU.
WHILE AT THE SAME TIME
HELP YOU GET READY
FOR THIS STUPID CONFERENCE.
BUT THE ONLY PERSON I HELPED
WAS MYSELF -
ACHIEVE INSANITY!
COME ON...
(HITS STEERING WHEEL)
LIBERTY:
THERE'S A REASON
I DON'T TELL JT
ABOUT ANY OF THIS.
HE- (GASPS)
LIBERTY?
OH, THAT'S DISGUSTING.
WHAT?
WHY IS THERE WATER
ON THE FLOOR?
TOBY... IT'S-IT'S TIME.
TOBY:
TI-TIME? T-WHAT?
WHAT TIME?
TIME FOR-
NO! NO. NO.
NOT HERE.
NOT IN MY BUBBIE'S CAR!
DIAL 9-1-1.
BUT DON'T MAKE A BIG DEAL
ABOUT IT.
(INDISTINCT VOICES
OVER RADIOS)
(MURMUR OF VOICES)
LIBERTY:
TOBY, I'M SORRY.
TOBY:
IT'S OKAY.
YOU'RE GONNA BE FINE.
DON'T WORRY.
BUT THE ASSEMBLY-
IT DOESN'T MATTER,
OKAY?
♪♪♪
NEW SONG?
I LIKE IT.
JUST LIKE THAT.
YOU KNOW, IT DOESN'T
EVEN NEED LYRICS.
IT'S NOT REALLY
A SONG THEN, IS IT?
SOMETIMES YOU DON'T NEED
ALL THE EXTRA STUFF.
SOMETIMES SIMPLER
IS BETTER.
I'M NOT A SOLO ACT.
BUT YOU COULD BE.
I DON'T CARE.
THIS ISN'T ABOUT ME.
THIS IS ABOUT THE BAND.
ELLIE, WE WERE GONNA
DO THIS TOGETHER.
CUT OUR ALBUM,
SOLD-OUT SHOWS.
A JUNO, A GRAMMY.
CRAIG, I CAN'T DRUM.
YES, YOU CAN.
NO, I CAN'T.
AND MARCO'S NOT MUCH
BETTER ON BASS,
AND JIMMY WANTS TO PAINT.
LEO...
GOD, FACE IT,
HE ONLY WANTED YOU.
WE WERE JUST...
EXCESS BAGGAGE.
CRAIG, I REALLY THINK
YOU SHOULD GO
TO THE SHOWCASE TONIGHT,
JUST LIKE THIS -
YOU AND YOUR GUITAR.
I REALLY THINK
YOU COULD WIN.
OKAY.
LET'S SAY I DO PLAY
THE SHOWCASE,
AND I DO WIN.
THAT MEANS LEAVING.
WHAT ABOUT MANNY?
OR JOEY? OR ANGIE?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT THEM.
THEY'LL MANAGE.
THEY'LL BE FINE.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
I'LL WAVE GOOD-BYE
'CAUSE I HAVE TO.
CRAIG...
GO TO THAT CLUB
AND KNOCK THEM DEAD.
FOR ALL OF US.
ANNOUNCER:
EVERYONE WELCOME TO THE STAGE
FROM DOWNTOWN SASQUATCH,
CRAIG MANNING.
♪ THE DAY IS LONG ♪
♪ THE FLIGHT AND SONG ♪
♪ BUT I DON'T EVEN LISTEN ♪
♪ THE BLUE BIRD HIDES ♪
♪ A PIECE OF NIGHT ♪
♪ I DON'T EVEN TRY... ♪
THE ADOPTION COUNSELLOR
IS IN THE HALL.
SHE'S TALKING
TO YOUR PARENTS.
CRAIG:
♪ EVERY MAMA GONE MISSING ♪
♪ EVERY PAPA GONE MAD ♪
♪ I'LL TAKE A CHANCE ♪
♪ IT'S NOT ROMANCE ♪
♪ BUT SOMETHIN' MORE IMPORTANT ♪
♪ SO GIVE ME WINGS ♪
♪ LET ME SING
IT'S ALL BEEN DONE BEFORE ♪
♪ FOR ANY GIRL
THAT'S UNHAPPY ♪
♪ FOR ANY BOY THAT IS BAD ♪
♪ EVERY MAMA GONE MISSING ♪
♪ WHOA... ♪
♪ EVERY PAPA GONE MAD ♪