MALE REPORTER:
AN ACCIDENT ON THE Q.E. WEST
AT TRAFALGER HAS TRAFFIC...
YOU GUYS ARE ON YOUR OWN
FOR BREAKFAST.
AND LUNCH,
AND SUPPER.
AND EVERY MEAL
AFTER THAT.
WE COUNT ON YOU, EM.
I COUNT ON YOU.
AND WHAT A SUPER JOB
I'M DOING.
SPIKE:
YOU ARE.
LOOK, I GOTTA GO
OR I'LL BE LATE
GETTING JACK
TO DAY CARE.
SNAKE CALLED AGAIN.
HOW NICE FOR HIM.
I... AM... SO... FAT.
DON'T EVEN TALK
ABOUT FAT,
I'M THE FAT ONE
IN THIS HOUSE.
ALL THIS FAST FOOD,
NO WONDER I'VE GAINED
ALL THIS WEIGHT.
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
I HAVE A MEETING WITH
BERNICE FEIN ON FRIDAY
AND I CAN'T EVEN FIT
INTO MY LUCKY JEANS.
"DUMP THE LUMPS"
BERNICE FEIN?
AS IN THE AGENT FROM HELL?
(SIGHS) IF SHE'S SATAN,
THEN THAT EXPLAINS WHY
SHE'S THE BEST AGENT IN TOWN.
SHE CALLED BECAUSE SHE SAW ME
IN THE KEVIN SMITH MOVIE,
WANTS TO AUDITION ME AGAIN.
(GRUNT OF EFFORT)
CRISIS DOWN HERE!
LOOK AROUND YOU.
"CRISIS" IS ACTUALLY
AN EPIDEMIC.
MY THIGHS ARE AN EPIDEMIC.
AND THEY'RE TAKING OVER
THE WORLD.
WE ARE GOING TO TAKE CONTROL.
I AM GOING TO TAKE CONTROL.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
MANNY.
PIE CHARTS?
WE'VE DONE PIE CHARTS
EVERY YEAR
SINCE GRADE FOUR.
IT'S A CHORE WHEEL.
MANNY:
(SIGHS) OKAY, DOES IT
HAVE LAUNDRY ON IT?
BECAUSE I'M OUT
OF UNDERWEAR
AND THIS COMMANDO CHAFING
IS KILLING ME.
NOT UP TO YOUR USUAL
STANDARD.
OKAY,
MANNY YOU ARE ON LAUNDRY.
I'M ON HOMEWORK
AND EXERCISE
AND GROCERY SHOPPING
AND CLEANING
AND MOM MANAGEMENT.
THAT SHOULD BURN
A FEW CALORIES.
I SINCERELY HOPE SO.
YOU'RE A STICK,
AND YOU'RE INSANE.
MOM! I'M HOME!
MANNY:
SHE'S WORKING LATE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
BABY PEDICURE?
DO YOU KNOW HOW MUCH FAT
IS IN ONE CHIP?
I BROUGHT YOU CELERY.
CELERY HAS NEGATIVE CALORIES
BECAUSE YOU BURN CALORIES
WHILE YOU'RE CHEWING.
AND THIS...
I AM NOT EATING PAPER.
NO MATTER HOW MANY
CALORIES IT BURNS.
IT'S A DIET DIARY.
WE MARK DOWN EVERY MORSEL
THAT GOES INTO OUR MOUTHS.
GREAT.
MORE HOMEWORK.
DO YOU WANT TO GET
THIS AGENT?
THINK OF IT AS FUN.
THINK OF IT
AS A CHALLENGE.
(UNENTHUSIASTIC) WOO-HOO,
LET THE FUN BEGIN.
(BACHMAN TURNER OVERDRIVE
PLAYING)
♪♪♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU AIN'T
SEEN NOTHIN YET ♪
♪ B-B-BABY, NO,
YOU AIN'T SEEN NOTHIN YET ♪
WITH A VOICE LIKE THAT?
IT'S NO WONDER "THE ZITS"
NEVER WENT ANYWHERE.
DIANE AND SIMPSON:
OHHH!
I'VE HEARD HIM SING
IN THE SHOWER, SNAKE?
AND THE POT
SHOULD REALLY STOP
CALLING THE KETTLE BLACK.
SAUCY...
BUT A KEEPER.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S KEEP THIS
PARTY GOING.
I'VE GOT JUST THE NUMBER.
IT'S A CLASSIC LITTLE DITTY
I LIKE TO CALL
"ROCK THE CASBAH".
(GIGGLES)
(ENGLISH ACCENT)
OY! KICK IT, MATE!
("SOMETIMES WHEN WE TOUCH"
PLAYS)
WHAT?
I DIDN'T...
THAT'S "SOMETIMES
WHEN WE TOUCH".
(SOFT CHUCKLE)
ABORT! ABORT!
HEY, WHAT'S WRONG?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
IT'S OUR SONG.
STUPID MACHINE.
SORRY SNAKE, UH...
BUTTONS GET MIXED UP
SOMETIMES.
(MUSIC STOPS)
IT'S JUST THAT UH...
I MISS HER SO BAD,
YOU KNOW?
I MISS MY FAMILY.
TOTAL CALORIES: 110.
TOTAL GRAMS OF FAT: 2.
TOTAL FLAVOUR: ZERO.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO DO MATH
WHEN I'M STARVING?
I THINK MY STOMACH'S
DIGESTING ITSELF.
BUT WE ARE NOT
FEELING HUNGRY,
WE ARE FEELING LIGHT.
AS IN L-I-T-E?
OKAY, YOU NEED
TO JOG ONE MILE
AT SIX MILES AN HOUR
TO BURN OFF
110 CALORIES.
OKAY, I'M GOING
TO GET A DIET POP
AND PRETEND
IT'S A MILKSHAKE.
PAIGE:
OW!
UH... TWIGS AND BERRIES?
YOU GIRLS PRACTICING
TO BE ON SURVIVOR?
IT'S CALLED A DIET.
MM... TOTALLY WISHING
I HAD YOUR WILLPOWER.
WHEN BATHING SUIT SEASON
COMES AROUND,
PREPARE TO BE HATED
BY A JEALOUS ME.
SUDDENLY I'M STUFFED.
(LAUGHS) WHEN ARE WE
RUNNING THAT MILE?
OR FIVE? (LAUGHS)
EMMA AND MANNY:
(LAUGHING)
BOTH:
(PANTING)
(LAUGHING)
WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
NOTHING.
I JUST FEEL ALL... FLOATY.
(LAUGHING)
ME TOO.
IS THAT GOOD?
SOMEONE WANNA TELL ME
THE PUNCHLINE?
SEE YOU INSIDE.
WHOA! EMMA.
YOU OKAY?
YOU GOT THE NEWBORN
COLT LEGS THING GOING.
WE'RE TRAINING
FOR CROSS-COUNTRY.
OH, WOW!
THAT'S-THAT'S GREAT,
I HAD NO IDEA.
YEAH. THE THINGS YOU MISS
WHEN YOU LEAVE YOUR FAMILY.
SO HOW'RE THINGS
AT JOEY'S?
GOOD. OKAY.
NOT TOO BAD.
TERRIBLE, ACTUALLY.
(EXHALES)
I MISS YOU GUYS.
HAVE YOU TRIED
TELLING MOM THAT?
OH, I WOULD
BUT THAT WOULD INVOLVE
HER ACTUALLY RETURNING
MY PHONE CALLS.
SO WHY DON'T YOU TELL HER
IN PERSON?
COME OVER TONIGHT.
THINK YOUR MOM
WOULD LIKE THAT?
MAYBE IF YOU MADE US DINNER
LIKE YOU USED TO?
EMMA!
YOU ARE A GENIUS!
NOW THIS I COULD
GET USED TO.
WHAT'S THE AH...
WHAT'S THE OCCASION?
YOU HAVE A SURPRISE GUEST
FOR DINNER.
A GUEST CHEF ACTUALLY.
SNAKE.
EMMA?
TELL ME YOU DIDN'T.
WHAT, I THOUGHT
YOU MIGHT LIKE
A NICE HOME-COOKED MEAL,
FOR ONCE.
(KNOCK AT THE DOOR)
I'LL GET IT!
SIMPSON:
DUNH-NA-NA-NAH!
ONE ORDER
OF VEGGIE MOUSSAKA.
EMMA'S OOEY-GOOEY
FAVOURITE.
ACTUALLY UM,
MANNY AND I ARE GONNA GO
FOR A WALK.
NO, GIRLS,
STAY.
WHY DON'T YOU TWO
SET THE TABLE.
(SNIFFS)
OH MY GOD, RICOTTA!
CREAM AND BUTTER
AND EVERYTHING ELSE
THAT I SEE IN MY DREAMS.
WE HAVEN'T STARVED
FOR TWO DAYS
JUST TO RUIN IT IN
10 MINUTES OF GLUTTONY.
SO WHAT DO WE DO?
WE SIT AT THE TABLE
WITH MOM AND ARCHIE
AND TRY TO MAKE THEM HAPPY.
AND THE FOOD WE JUST PUSH
AROUND YOUR PLATES.
(WATER DRIPS)
KITCHEN FAUCET'S
STILL LEAKING, HUH?
I SHOULD GET MY WRENCH
AND UH...
IT'S FINE,
ARCHIE.
DO YOU KNOW HOW MUCH WATER
YOU'RE WASTING?
MY WRENCH IS DOWNSTAIRS-
JUST LEAVE IT!
PLEASE.
THIS MOUSSAKA
IS AMAZING.
EMMA, I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU
TOUCH YOURS.
EMMA:
SURE I HAVE.
YOUR COOKING IS SOMETHING
WE'VE REALLY MISSED AROUND HERE.
SIMPSON:
WELL, I MISS COOKING
FOR YOU GUYS.
I MISS A LOT OF THINGS.
SITTING HERE AT THIS TABLE,
I REALIZE THAT
THIS IS WHERE I BELONG,
AND I NEVER SHOULD'VE LEFT.
YOU DIDN'T LEAVE,
SNAKE.
I KICKED YOU OUT.
REMEMBER?
IT'S BEEN LONG ENOUGH, SPIKE.
AND I...
I THINK I'VE LEARNED
MY LESSON.
I'M READY TO COME HOME.
OH, AND THAT'S
YOUR DECISION TO MAKE?
SIMPSON:
NO, IT'S OUR DECISION
BUT YES,
I HAVE A SAY IN IT.
YOU HAD YOUR SAY
AND IT INVOLVED
ANOTHER WOMAN!
GIRLS...
I THINK YOU NEED
TO GO TO YOUR ROOM.
SIMPSON:
SPIKE, I CAME OVER HERE
WITH A PEACE OFFERING
AND THIS IS WHAT I GET.
SPIKE:
YOU THINK A PAN OF MOUSSAKA
IS GONNA MAKE EVERYTHING
BETTER?!
SIMPSON:
NO, I DON'T!
I THOUGHT MAYBE WE COULD TRY
TO BE CIVILIZED-
FIGHTING.
ONLY FIGHTING.
FIGHTING'S A START,
RIGHT?
IT'S BETTER THAN
NOT TALKING AT ALL.
I GUESS.
SPIKE:
FINE! GET OUT OF MY HOUSE!
I JUST WISH I KNEW
HOW IT WAS GONNA
TURN OUT.
I HATE NOT KNOWING
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN.
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN.
I AM GOING TO EXPLODE
FROM ALL THAT OOEY-GOOEY
MOUSSAKEEY.
I WISH I WOULD EXPLODE.
WE COULD TRY AND RUN IT OFF.
IT'LL ONLY TAKE
OH, SIX HOURS.
IF I MOVE,
I'LL BARF.
IT CAN'T BE HEALTHY
TO BE THIS FULL.
WE COULD GET RID OF IT.
LIKE HOW, PUKING?
ISN'T THAT KIND
OF EXTREME?
DESPERATE TIMES
CALL FOR DESPERATE PURGING.
MANNY;
IT'S NOT CALLED PURGING,
IT'S CALLED BULIMIA.
DON'T BE SO DRAMATIC.
THESE ARE SPECIAL
CIRCUMSTANCES.
YOU'LL FEEL BETTER, MANNY.
COME ON.
(ANXIOUS SIGH)
NOW FOR THE MOMENT
OF TRUTH.
MANNY:
COULD I GO TO THE BATHROOM
FIRST?
THAT'S GOTTA BE HALF A POUND.
(GASPS)
EM, I LOST THREE POUNDS!
THREE POUNDS
IN FOUR DAYS!
(CHUCKLING)
I LOST THREE,
THREE, THRE-
FOUR... POUNDS.
I LOST FOUR POUNDS?!
EM, YOU ARE OFFICIALLY
MY LIFESTYLE GURU.
LIKE BOB ON OPRAH!
OKAY, SO IF WE RESTRAIN
OURSELVES TODAY
AND WORK OUT AFTER SCHOOL,
WE MIGHT BE UP TO FIVE POUNDS
BY TOMORROW.
AH, NO-NO-NO.
THERE'S A BUTTER TART
IN THE CAF
WITH MY NAME ON IT.
MANNY, NO.
IF WE'RE HAPPY
WITH LESS THAN OUR GOAL,
WE'RE ONLY DISAPPOINTING
OURSELVES.
YOU'VE GOT AN AGENT
TO IMPRESS.
THIS IS SERIOUS.
OKAY, BOB.
♪♪♪
JOEY:
OKAY, I GOT IT.
CHANGE HER OIL.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YOU REALLY THINK DOING
AN OIL CHANGE ON SPIKE'S CAR
IS GOING TO WIN
HER BACK?
SNAKE, I'M SPIT-BALLING
HERE, OKAY?
WORK WITH ME,
BUDDY.
OKAY UH...
THE ROOF'S A MESS.
I COULD HELP REDO IT.
YES! AND YOU CAN GET
ALL HOT AND SWEATY
WHILE YOU'RE DOING IT.
CHICKS DIG THAT!
SEXY SNAKE!
SNAKE THE SEXY ROOFER!
I LIKE IT!
DIANE:
(EXASPERATED GASP)
COME ON!
WOMEN DON'T WANT AN EPISODE
OF "THIS OLD HOUSE".
THEY WANT A LITTLE ROMANCE.
THEY WANT TO KNOW
THEY'RE SPECIAL.
SPIKE IS SPECIAL TO YOU,
RIGHT?
SO PROVE IT.
SHOW HER WHAT'S
IN YOUR HEART.
I DON'T KNOW THAT SPIKE'S
THAT INTERESTED
WHAT'S IN MY HEART,
RIGHT NOW.
DIANE:
SHE WILL BE.
TRUST ME.
JUST REMIND HER WHY
SHE FELL IN LOVE WITH YOU
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
WOO HER.
PLEASE STOP SAYING MY NAME.
(LOUD WHISPER)
STOP!
MANNY...
(EXHALES)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
UM, A LITTLE KNOWN FACT
IS THAT PEPPERONI SQUELCHES
AUDITION STRESS.
THAT'S A LIE.
OKAY...
I'M JUST PLAIN
NAKED HUNGRY!
HUNGER IS A FEELING,
MANNY.
THIN IS A SKILL.
DAMAGE CONTROL TIME.
(LOCKER SLAMS)
MANNY:
NO!
I'LL COVER FOR YOU.
MY JEANS STILL FIT,
GENERAL.
MANNY, YOUR BODY
IS A REFLECTION OF YOU.
THE AGENT IS GOING TO SEE
THAT YOU'RE UNDISCIPLINED.
THE AGENT'S GOING TO SEE
THAT I HAVE ENERGY
AND ROSY CHEEKS,
AND THAT I DON'T
HAVE PUKE BREATH.
THIS IS SO
"TYPICAL MANNY".
GIVE UP WHEN THE GOING
GETS TOUGH.
IT'S ONE SLICE OF PIZZA,
EM!
IT'S FAT AND STARCH
AND GREASE.
WHY NOT JUST POUR POISON
DOWN YOUR THROAT?!
(DRY CHUCKLE)
OKAY.
THERE IS JUST A LITTLE
TOO MUCH CRAZY IN HERE.
(HARD THUD)
GIRL:
WHAT'S GOING ON?
SOMEONE GET A TEACHER.
HATZILAKOS:
EMMA?
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
EMMA?!
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
JUST SIT STILL.
NO, I'M JUST DIZZY,
I THINK.
I THINK IT'S THE FLU
OR SOMETHING.
WHOA! WHOA! WHOA!
DID YOU EAT TODAY?
YES!
WHAT DID YOU EAT,
EMMA?
EMMA...
IT'S OKAY,
YOU CAN TALK TO ME.
I'M HERE FOR YOU.
THAT'S FUNNY.
(EXHALES)
(IRRITATED SIGH)
THE GIRLS AT THE SALON
TOLD ME YOU WERE ON BREAK.
ARE YOU SELLING ROSES
IN RESTAURANTS?
WHAT'S WITH
THE PENGUIN SUIT?
I WAS WEARING A T-SHIRT
ON OUR WEDDING DAY.
AND I WANTED TO MAKE SURE
I DID THIS RIGHT.
SPIKE,
YOU ARE MY EVERYTHING.
AND IF YOU LET ME
COME HOME
I'LL BE WORTHY OF YOU
THIS TIME
BECAUSE YOU DESERVE
EVERYTHING.
YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL.
YOU HURT ME.
I KNOW.
NO.
YOU DON'T REALLY KNOW.
I LOVED YOU
SINCE I WAS SIXTEEN.
YOU WERE THE ONE GUY
I THOUGHT WAS GOOD,
THE ONE GUY I WAS SURE
I COULD COUNT ON.
COUNT ON ME NOW...
BECAUSE I LOVE YOU.
BECAUSE I'LL NEVER GIVE UP
UNTIL YOU TAKE ME BACK.
(EXHALES)
♪ YOU ASK ME IF I LOVE YOU ♪
♪ AND I CHOKE ON MY REPLY ♪
♪ I'D RATHER HURT YOU HONESTLY ♪
♪ THAN MISLEAD YOU WITH A LIE ♪
♪ AND SOMETIMES WHEN WE TOUCH ♪
♪ THE HONESTY'S TOO MUCH ♪
♪ AND I HAVE TO CLOSE
MY EYES AND HIDE ♪
♪ I WANNA HOLD YOU- ♪
OKAY.
TWO CONDITIONS.
DONE.
NO KISSING ANYONE
BUT ME -
EVER AGAIN!
AND NO SINGING
EVER AGAIN.
(APPLAUSE)
HOW'D THE AUDITION GO?
SHE SAID I HAD "MOXIE".
WHICH MEANS...?
I HAVE AN AGENT!
I'M SO HAPPY FOR YOU.
AND I'M SO WORRIED
ABOUT YOU.
I HEARD YOU FAINTED.
AND THESE DISMEMBERED
MODELS ARE DISTURBING.
IT'S INSPIRATION.
FOR WHEN I WANT TO LOSE
A POUND.
OKAY, BUT YOU'VE LOST,
LIKE, SEVEN.
YOU'RE STARTING
TO SCARE ME.
I'M GROSS, MANNY.
I LOOK DISGUSTING.
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
YOU ATE?
A COUPLE DAYS AGO.
I FEEL GOOD.
BUT YOU LOOK SICK.
AND THE WAY YOU'RE TALKING,
YOU MIGHT BE SICK.
OKAY. SNAKE'S BRINGING HIS
SPECIAL LASAGNA OVER TONIGHT.
I'LL EAT SOME.
HE'S COMING BACK?
THAT'S THE JUICE.
AND I'M ALL OVER
THAT LASAGNA.
MAY THIS DIET
REST IN PEACE.
MANNY:
GOOD.
BECAUSE I NEED YOU HEALTHY,
EMMA.
YOU'RE MORE THAN JUST
MY LIFESTYLE GURU, YOU KNOW.
ALL:
(LAUGHING)
HEY, EVERYONE, CHEERS.
YOU ARE AN AMAZING
FAMILY.
ALL:
CHEERS!
OOP!
OH W-W-W-WAIT!
ACTUALLY,
I HAVE AN ANNOUNCEMENT.
EMMA:
ARE YOU GUYS GONNA FINALLY
STOP CALLING EACH OTHER
BY YOUR HIGH SCHOOL
NICKNAMES?
MANNY:
(CHUCKLES)
NOT A BAD IDEA,
BUT NO.
UH, AS YOU ALL KNOW,
I STILL HAVE
A MOTORCYCLE FUND.
WHICH I WOULD LIKE TO USE
NOT TO BUY
ANOTHER MOTORCYCLE WITH,
BUT TO TAKE US ALL
TO THE SHOPPING CAPITAL
OF THE WORLD -
NEW YORK CITY.
NEW YORK?
ARE YOU SURE?
I'VE DONE ALL THE BORING,
PRACTICAL MATH
AND WE'RE GOING, BABY.
SPIKE:
ALL RIGHT!
WAIT.
WHO'S INCLUDED IN "WE"?
WELL UM, YOU ARE PART
OF THE NELSON-SIMPSON CLAN,
ARE YOU NOT?
I LOVE YOU!
I LOVE YOU GUYS!
HOW MANY EMPTY SUITCASES
CAN I BRING?
(JOKINGLY CAUTIONS MANNY)
HEY, WHOA! HEY.
EMMA:
OKAY, THIS IS-
THIS IS BEYOND ANYTHING.
IT ACTUALLY MIGHT BE ONE
OF THOSE MOMENTS.
SO I'M GONNA
GET THE CAMERA.
SIMPSON:
OH YEAH! CHEERS GUYS!
SPIKE:
CHEERS!
MANNY:
SIMPSON:
WOO HOO!
(TOILET FLUSHES)