PETER:
ONE, TWO, THREE... ACTION!
DO YOU THINK THAT AGENT
IS EVER GONNA CALL ME?
DO YOU THINK THAT PETER GUY
IS EVER GONNA NOTICE ME?
WE'VE BEEN COMING HERE
FOR WEEKS.
OKAY.
WHAT IF I STOOD UP?
DO I HAVE, LIKE,
LUMPY CHAIR DENTS
IN MY THIGHS?
ALL RIGHT,
YOU'D NEED FAT
ON THEM - OR ANY.
EMMA:
LOOK. HE'S TALKING TO THAT
TURQUOISE TANKINI TRAMP.
I HATE HER.
YOU'VE ALREADY WON.
YOU DON'T NEED
A TANKINI
TO HIDE
YOUR BUDDHA BELLY
OR SHORTS TO CAMOUFLAGE
YOUR BUTT.
EMMA:
MANNY...
HE'S LOOKING AT YOU.
MANNY:
PLEASE.
I'M NOT HIS TYPE.
HE'S LOOKING AT YOU -
YOU ARE.
THAT IS THE FIRST GUY
I'VE LIKED
SINCE HURRICANE SEAN
BLEW THROUGH
MY EMOTIONAL TRAILER PARK.
EM, I HAVE ONE GOAL
THIS YEAR,
AND IT AIN'T ANONYMOUS
HOT-DUDE-AT-POOL.
I'M GONNA BE AN ACTRESS.
GO AHEAD, SMILE,
'CAUSE I'M DOING IT.
WHATEVER IT TAKES?
I'M DOING.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best that I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
PAIGE:
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT WE,
THE MOST CURSED CLASS
IN HISTORY,
ACTUALLY MADE IT
TO SENIOR YEAR?
ALL:
NO.
HAZEL:
I GUESS ASHLEY
DIDN'T MAKE IT.
CRAIG:
YET. SHE'LL BE HERE.
RIGHT, EL?
DEFINITELY.
HEY!
SHE'S A BIG AGENT.
SHE'S PROBABLY
JUST BUSY.
JT:
TRUST PAPA SUPAFRY,
OKAY?
THE ACTING WORLD
IS ALL ABOUT BRUTAL REJECTION.
HATZILAKOS:
YOU PUT IN A LOT OF WORK
THIS SUMMER,
AND THAT'S WHY
I'M LETTING YOU BACK.
BUT ONE SLIP-UP,
AND I MEAN ONE,
AND YOU'RE OUT
THAT DOOR.
GOT IT.
I WON'T DISAPPOINT YOU,
MISS H,
I SWEAR TO GOD.
MALE VOICE OVER P.A.:
CAN I HAVE YOUR ATTENTION,
PLEASE.
A SET OF KEYS WAS FOUND
UNDER THE BLEACHERS IN THE GYM.
IF YOU'VE LOST YOUR KEYS...
SPINNER:
HEY GUYS.
LOOK WHO'S BACK?
JIMMY.
UH... GOOD SUMMER?
HEY.
GUY:
HEY MANNY.
HE'S ACTUALLY HERE.
YOU CAN DO IT.
UH, I'M TOO NERVOUS!
(LAUGH) HI.
WELCOME TO EMMA,
I'M DEGRASSI.
NICE TO MEET YOU,
DEGRASSI.
MANNY:
IT'S A TRADITION -
BACKWARDS GREETING.
WE ALL DO IT FIRST DAY.
SO YOU'RE MANNY
AND I'M...?
PETER.
I KNOW YOU.
YOU'RE THE ACTRESS
FROM THE KEVIN SMITH FILM.
YEAH.
I'M A DIRECTOR.
WELL, ASPIRING, ANYWAY.
YOU GOT AN AGENT?
I SENT MY PHOTOS
TO BERNICE FEIN AND...
SHE'S THE BEST
IN THE CITY,
SO, I'M JUST WAITING
FOR A CALL.
PETER:
FOREVER.
THAT'S HOW LONG YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE TO WAIT.
YOU GOTTA MARCH
RIGHT INTO HER OFFICE,
LOOKING LIKE A MILLION BUCKS,
AND DEMAND TO SEE HER.
MY DAD ALWAYS SAYS,
"IF YOU WANT SOMETHING IN LIFE,
DON'T ASK.
JUST TAKE."
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
EXCUSE ME.
HELLO?
ELLIE:
ASHLEY HASN'T EMAILED
IN A WEEK.
SHE'S TOTALLY DISAPPEARED.
MARCO:
OKAY... UH...
MAYBE-MAYBE-MAYBE
SHE'S GONNA SURPRISE CRAIG?
HMM? SHOW UP
AT HIS BIRTHDAY TOMORROW.
IT'S TOMORROW?
WHAT DO WE DO?
OH MANUELLITA,
I DIDN'T MAKE LUNCH.
I JUST CAME
FOR MY CREDIT CARD.
UH... LEFTOVERS?
OR A TOASTY SANDWICH?
I COULD THROW TOGETHER
AN OMELET.
MOM, IT'S MY CREDIT CARD,
AND I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHY YOU GUYS DON'T LET ME
KEEP IT.
YOUR DADDY AND I
JUST WANT YOU
TO BE RESPONSIBLE.
I AM!
I WORKED REALLY HARD
ON THE MOVIE
TO MAKE ALL THAT MONEY.
SOMETIMES WE ARE CONCERNED.
WHAT YOU WEAR,
WHERE YOU GO...
WITH BOYS.
AND YOUR GRADES.
WHAT, DO YOU THINK
I'M RETARDED?
I'M NOT!
I CAN MANAGE!
I'M SMART!
I JUST...
I JUST NEED SOME
NEW CLOTHES FOR SCHOOL,
OKAY MOM?
FIFTY DOLLARS ONLY,
OKAY?
YOU KNOW HOW
YOUR DADDY IS.
HE'LL CHOP OFF
OUR HEADS.
OKAY.
THANKS, BYE.
MARCO:
I DID A SAFARI
IN MASAI MARA,
AND HONEST EL,
IT BLEW MY MIND.
(GIGGLING)
WHAT?
YOU TWO HAVE
HAND SIGNALS?
WE DON'T EVEN HAVE
HAND SIGNALS.
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
OH... GOOD,
IT'S FROM ASH.
NOT GOOD.
WAY... WAY NOT GOOD.
UH... THAT...
THAT IS-
THAT IS NOT CRAIG.
IT'S ALISTAIR,
AKA "ALI",
AKA THE REASON SHE'S...
STAYING IN ENGLAND.
WHAT? OH...
NICE BIRTHDAY PRESENT.
ELLIE:
OKAY, WE HAVE TO THROW HIM
THE GREATEST,
MOST ROCKINGEST
PARTY EVER.
WOW.
DID YOU JUST SAY
ROCKINGEST?
YEAH.
I'M THAT UPSET
FOR HIM.
♪ LOVES ALIVE IN THE CITY ♪
♪ I FEEL IT DEEP DOWN ♪
♪ SOON I'LL BE SITTIN' PRETTY ♪
♪ I'M GONNA BREAK NEW GROUND ♪
♪ THE ROAD AHEAD
DON'T SCARE ME ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THE FUTURE'S
MINE TO HOLD ♪
♪ SO WHY CHANGE ME? ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT IT'S LIKE ♪
♪ LET 'EM WALK IN MY SHOES ♪
♪ STEP BY STEP
I'M GETTING THERE ♪
♪ YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT IT'S LIKE ♪
♪ IN A WORLD SO BRAND NEW
♪ FOR A GIRL
THAT'S GETTING THERE ♪
♪ BUT I SWEAR
I'M GETTING THERE ♪
TWO MINUTES,
I PROMISE.
I WON'T LEAVE.
AND I'LL STARE
AT YOU...
REALLY, REALLY HARD.
SPARE TWO MINUTES
FOR PEST CONTROL?
THANKS, BERNICE.
"AND IN THE MIDST
OF ALL THAT RESCUING,
IN THE MIDST
OF ALL THAT CLAWING FOR HOPE,
NOBODY MADE IT
OUT OF OUR WEDDING ALIVE."
A GLASS OF MILK,
HONEY.
YOU WANT ME TO- ?
BERNICE:
I MEAN, IT'S NICE - MILK.
UH... IT'S KINDA BORING.
DANNY, TAKE A LOOK
AT THE WALL BEHIND ME.
TELL ME WHAT
YOU SEE, DEAR.
A BUNCH OF REALLY
GORGEOUS PEOPLE.
MM-HM.
BUT THEY'RE NOT
JUST GORGEOUS.
THEY'RE SPECIAL.
THEY HAVE "IT".
LOOK AT ROBIN.
ROBIN HAS "IT".
ROBIN IS SPECIAL.
WHAT'S SO SPECIAL
ABOUT YOU?
HMM?
EXACTLY MY POINT.
SO, YOU GO FIGURE THAT OUT
BEFORE YOU COME BACK HERE.
OH, AND A WORD OF ADVICE?
STOP WITH THE BEANS AND RICE
AND UH...
DUMP THE LUMPS.
COME.
(HORN BLARES)
(SCREAMS)
HI, EMMA?
CAN YOU MEET ME
DOWNTOWN, NOW?
EMMA:
UGH, LOOK AT THAT ASS.
SHE SAID
"DUMP THE LUMPS".
OKAY, SHE'S OUT
OF HER MIND.
AND I'M A GLASS
OF MILK.
OKAY, YOU ARE OUT
YOUR MIND.
MANNY,
YOU ARE GORGEOUS.
YOU DO NOT NEED
TO CHANGE.
REMEMBER WHEN YOU GOT
YOUR PERIOD IN CLASS-
SHH...
REMEMBER WHEN YOU GOT
YOUR PERIOD IN CLASS
AND EVERYONE
WAS LAUGHING AT YOU
AND YOU JUST TOLD THEM ALL
TO SHUT UP?
I FEEL LIKE THAT
EVERY DAY.
LIKE EVERYBODY'S
JOKING ABOUT ME,
AND I CAN NEVER
GET THEM TO SHUT UP.
AND A PLASTIC SURGEON
CAN CHANGE THAT?
THEY WON'T BE LAUGHING
WHEN I'M FAMOUS.
MANNY SANTOS?
SO, SOME OFF MY UH...
THIGHS AND,
MY...
YOUR BOTTOM?
YES, BUT I THINK MY...
BOSOM?
YES, I THINK
THEY'RE FINE
OR... IT -
OR MY BUST -
I THINK IS FINE.
BUT CONSIDER...
A LARGER BUST
WILL ACTUALLY HELP
BALANCE OUT
YOUR LOWER HALF.
SO IF WE COMBINE LIPO
WITH BREAST AUGMENTATION,
I CAN CREATE FOR YOU, MANNY,
A VERY, VERY STRIKING FIGURE.
OH, OKAY.
I WANNA DO IT.
LET'S DO IT.
OKAY.
THERE'S SOME DETAILS
THAT WE HAVE TO DISCUSS
INCLUDING THE RISKS,
OF COURSE.
FINE. HOW MUCH?
(LAUGHS) AH WELL...
SIX THOUSAND IS THE AVERAGE
COST OF AN IMPLANT,
PLUS OR MINUS,
DEPENDING ON MODEL,
ET CETERA.
UH... LIPOSUCTION,
MORE OR LESS $3000.
I HAVE ENOUGH.
AND PARENTAL CONSENT?
I HAVE ENOUGH...
OF IT.
I'M SORRY,
I HAVE IT.
AND (AHEM) HOW SOON?
UH, SIX, SEVEN
OR EIGHT WEEKS
UNTIL THERE'S AN OPENING
IN THE O.R.,
BUT THAT'S ONLY
IF YOU BOOK NOW
AND LEAVE A DEPOSIT.
OTHERWISE-
DO YOU TAKE
CREDIT CARDS?
HEY, SPINNER.
HAVE ANY COFFEE?
SPINNER:
YEAH, THEY TELL ME
THAT'S WHAT THE CUPS ARE FOR.
ONE TO GO,
PLEASE.
HM... PARTY SUPPLIES, EH?
I KNOW SCHOOL'S EXCITING
BUT...
IT'S CRAIG'S BIRTHDAY.
SO WHAT, YOU GUYS
BEST FRIENDS NOW?
NO, NO...
I JUST...
I KINDA FEEL RESPONSIBLE
SINCE MY FORMER BEST FRIEND'S
RUINED THE GUY'S LIFE.
OOPS,
ASH DID IT AGAIN.
SHE PLAYED
WITH HIS HEART,
GOT LOST-
ANYWAY...
NOW I'VE GOT NO PLACE
TO THROW HIM
HIS CHEER-UP PARTY.
WELL, YOU KNOW I COULD
GET US THAT WHOLE CORNER.
I MEAN YOU.
YOU GUYS CAN HAVE
THAT WHOLE CORNER.
REALLY?
YEAH, THAT'S NO PROBLEM.
I'M HERE FOR
THE NIGHTSHIFT ANYWAY.
CAPTAIN COOK?
DIDN'T WE ALREADY DO HIM
IN LIKE, GRADE FOUR?
PETER:
YEARS LATER,
PETER WAS TO LOOK BACK
AND REMEMBER
HOW CUTE IT WAS
WHEN SHE MADE FUN
OF HIS HISTORY PROJECT.
OKAY, WAIT, WAIT.
I HAVE THIS IDEA
FOR A MOVIE.
IT'S ABOUT A GIRL
LIKE YOU -
SMART, FIERY,
NOT TOTALLY HIDEOUS.
CHARMING, THANKS.
BUT I DUNNO.
WHY NOT?
A GOOD MOVIE
UNDER YOUR BELT?
YOUR AGENT
WOULD LOVE THAT.
YOU DID GO TALK
TO THAT AGENT,
DIDN'T YOU?
YEAH, BUT SHE SAID
I NEED SOME WORK.
SO DO IT.
AND LISTEN TO THIS:
"I HAD THE AMBITION
NOT ONLY TO GO FARTHER
THAN ANY MAN HAD EVER GONE,
BUT TO GO AS FAR
AS IT WAS POSSIBLE TO GO."
YOU FREE TONIGHT?
MY FRIEND'S HAVING
A PARTY.
UM... SORRY,
I CAN'T.
BECAUSE?
MANNY:
JUST BECAUSE BUT...
YOU SHOULD ASK EMMA
IF SHE'S FREE.
I WILL ASK HER
BUT UH...
HERE'S THE ADDRESS
FOR YOU -
JUST IN CASE.
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
THEY LET HIM BACK
AFTER WHAT HE DID.
IT MAKES ME SICK.
BLAH BLAH, SPINNER.
THAT'S SO LAST YEAR.
I WANT THE LATEST
WITH THE PRINCESS
ASHLEY DIARIES.
HOW'S CRAIG DOING
POST DUMPAGE?
WELL. REALLY WELL.
MARCO:
YEAH, 'CAUSE UM...
HE DOESN'T KNOW YET.
OH.
ELLIE:
HEY, IT'S THE GUY'S BIRTHDAY.
IT CAN AT LEAST WAIT
TILL TOMORROW, RIGHT?
THERE HE IS!
ALL:
SURPRISE!
(CHEERING AND BLOWING
PARTY HORNS)
WHO DID THIS?
I HATE SURPRISES.
(LAUGHING)
EVERYONE:
ELLIE:
HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
CRAIG:
THANK YOU,
THANK YOU!
THIS IS GREAT!
SORRY.
HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
A DOCTOR'S OFFICE
CALLED TODAY...
TO GET PERMISSION...
FOR BREAST SURGERY?!
OKAY. WAIT.
I HAVE TO EXPLAIN.
I WAS JUST... ASKING.
I WAS... CURIOUS-
JOSEPH:
DON'T LIE!
YOU MADE A DEPOSIT!
I CALLED THE CREDIT CARD
COMPANY.
I'M TRYING TO BE
AN ACTRESS.
I NEED TO MAKE CHANGES -
FOR MY JOB.
SCHOOL'S YOUR JOB.
AND THE ONLY CHANGING
YOU SHOULD DO
IS INTO-
INTO DECENT CLOTHES.
MY CLOTHES ARE FINE.
DO YOU THINK I SACRIFICED
ALL MY LIFE
SO YOU COULD BE
A LOOSE GIRL?
I'M NOT A LOOSE GIRL!
THEN WHY YOU WANT
BIGGER BOOBS, HUH?
HUH?
WHAT KIND OF GIRL
WANTS THAT?
A GOOD GIRL?
NO!
ONLY A SLUT.
JULIETTA:
MANUELLA! WAIT!
JOSEPH!
(SOBBING)
(PARENTS ARGUING)
THERE ARE TWO EXTRA
SCOOPS IN THERE.
I WON'T TELL.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY,
MAN.
YEAH.
I GOTTA GET BACK.
UH, CRAIG,
I'M SORRY ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED, EH?
IT SUCKS.
I MEAN,
YOU'RE A GREAT GUY,
AND YOU DESERVED
BETTER THAN THAT.
BETTER THAN WHAT?
BETTER THAN ASHLEY.
MAN, I KNOW ALL
ABOUT IT, OKAY?
ALL ABOUT WHAT?
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
ELLIE SAID THAT...
NOTHING.
IT'S NOTHING.
NOTHING. IT-
ELLIE:
TIME TO OPEN PRESENTS?
IT'S TIME TO TELL
THE TRUTH.
WHAT IS GOING ON
WITH ASHLEY?
IF YOU TOLD SPINNER,
YOU CAN TELL ME.
SHE WANTED TO
TELL YOU HERSELF.
SHE WANTED TO WAIT
TILL THE TIME WAS RIGHT.
WHATEVER.
JUST TELL ME.
SHE MET SOMEONE.
WAIT...
YOU KNEW AND
YOU DIDN'T TELL ME?
DON'T SHOOT THE MESSENGER,
CRAIG.
WE-
CRAIG:
YOU KNEW, TOO-
DID EVERYBODY KNOW?
SCREW YOU.
(LOUD MUSIC BLARING)
JENN:
ARE THEY VINTAGE?
LOOK LIKE VINTAGE.
EMMA:
YEAH, THEY'RE FROM THAT
LITTLE STORE
AT DUNDAS AND GRACE.
HEY MANNY!
WHAT'RE YOU
DOING HERE?
I WAS JUST BORED,
I GUESS.
SO, HOW'D YOU KNOW
ABOUT THIS PARTY?
PETER:
HEY MANNY,
GLAD YOU COULD MAKE IT.
I GUESS
HE INVITED YOU.
JENN:
OH!
THAT EXPLAINS IT.
PETER INVITED HER.
HE DOES GO FOR GIRLS
LIKE THAT.
(MEAN GIRLS GIGGLE)
MANNY,
WHAT IS GOING ON?
HAVE YOU BEEN CRYING?
NO, I'M FINE.
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE.
HI, CAN I BORROW
SOME VODKA?
(MUSIC BLARING)
ELLIE:
HOW IS HE?
MARCO:
WELL, HE'S BASHING ON
THE POOR DEFENSELESS DRUM KIT,
BUT HE'LL BE FINE.
UGGGGGHHHH!
SO TERRIBLE.
EL, IT'S NOT
YOUR FAULT,
OKAY?
DON'T WORRY, I THINK
HE KINDA SAW IT COMING.
THEN WHY DO I FEEL
SO AWFUL?
'CAUSE YOU LIKE HIM.
MARCO, HE'S MY BEST FRIEND'S
BOYFRIEND.
YEAH, BUT...
NOT ANY MORE.
YEAH.
WELL...
YOU'RE STILL WRONG.
(MUSIC BLARING)
(INDISTINCT PARTY CHATTER)
(NEW SONG BLARING)
MANNY:
AND THEN, MY DAD
CALLED ME A SLUT.
MUST BE QUITE
THE CONVERSATION.
I THINK IT'S TIME
FOR YOU TO GO HOME,
LITTLE GIRL LOST.
I'M NOT
A LITTLE GIRL.
(GIGGLING)
HAVE YOU EVER KNOWN A GIRL
WHO GOT A BOOB JOB?
OR IS GONNA?
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT TALKING
ABOUT YOU.
THAT'S WHAT I SAID!
I SAID MY BOOBS
ARE GREAT,
AND DOCTOR SAID
I'M WRONG.
WELL, MAYBE YOU NEED
A SECOND OPINION?
MAYBE WE SHOULD MAKE
A LITTLE MOVIE...
'CAUSE CAMERAS NEVER LIE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE RIGHT, MANNY.
CAMERAS NEVER LIE.
IN FACT,
THIS CAMERA...
WILL GIVE A PERFECT
SECOND OPINION.
I'M GONNA BE
AN ACTRESS,
LIKE, ACADEMY AWARD WINNING,
AND YOU CAN SELL THIS
FOR A MILLION DOLLARS!
'CAUSE I'M GONNA BE FAMOUS!