EMMA:
LATER, SKATER.
MANNY:
THANKS, SPIN.
HEY, THERE'S DARCY.
HEY, YOU SHOULD'VE
COME IN FOR COFFEE.
WHAT'S UP?
HEY.
SPINNER:
COME ON, I THOUGHT YOU GUYS
WOULD NEVER LEAVE.
GO, GO, GO!
WORK. EXAMS.
I NEEDS ME
SOME DARCY.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
I HAVE SOMETHING
TO SHOW YOU.
KIM GOT ME A JOB
AS A COUNSELOR.
DARCY DOES
SUMMER CAMP.
SOUNDS LIKE
MY KIND OF MOVIE.
SUCKS I'M GONNA HAVE TO
STAY HERE IN TORONTO
AND MISS IT.
WITH LOTS...
AND LOTS OF OTHER GIRLS
AROUND.
DARCY, I DON'T WANT TO BE
WITH ANYONE ELSE.
YOU'RE EVERYTHING TO ME.
(LAUGHS)
SORRY, SPIN.
WE CAN'T.
WE TOOK A VOW.
TO REMAIN VIRGINS
TILL MARRIAGE.
(SIGHS)
VIRGINS, YEAH.
TOTALLY.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
YOU'RE CHIPPER
FOR SOMEONE
WHO WAS ON THE PHONE
WITH CRAIG
UNTIL 3 A.M.
IT'S YOU
IN THE FOOD LINE.
BEATS THE HOSPITAL.
YAY, THERAPY!
ALTHOUGH,
COMPARED TO THE CAF?
HOSPITAL FOOD
GETS A BAD RAP.
OH NO.
FOOD AND DRINKS.
WE NEED REFRESHMENTS
FOR THE VARIETY SHOW,
AND I STILL DON'T
HAVE A TECH CREW.
MANNY,
YOU'RE THE DIRECTOR
AND THE LEAD ACTOR.
THIS IS YOUR SHOW,
TAKE CHARGE.
SPINNER:
I'VE BEEN READING BLOGS
BY CHRISTIAN TEENS,
ON ABSTINENCE.
IT'S ALL ABOUT PREVENTION.
SO, WE HAVE TO FIND WAYS
TO STAY BUSY.
MANNY:
OKAY, ALL YOU DEGRASSI-ITES!
THE VARIETY SHOW
NEEDS VOLUNTEERS.
SO, C'MON EVERYONE!
SHOW SOME SUPPORT!
DANNY:
TAKE IT OFF!
OOH! OOH! OOH!
HOW PERFECT
IS THIS?
MAN, WHEN GOD
ANSWERS PRAYERS,
HE'S QUICK.
SIGN US UP, MANNY!
MANNY:
OMIGOSH, SPINNER,
YOU ARE MY HERO.
(CLEARS THROAT)
AND YOU TOO, DARCY.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
MS. HATZILAKOS:
SO, GRAD WEEKEND
IS ALMOST HERE,
AND OUR 50TH ANNIVERSARY
VARIETY SHOW
IS COMING TOGETHER
VERY NICELY.
AND ATTENTION SPANS
ARE ZERO,
SO IT MUST MEAN
THAT IT'S TIME
FOR MY POST-SECONDARY
PREPAREDNESS CLASS.
FIRST UP... FINANCES.
UM, MY HOPED FOR UNIVERSITY,
BANTING,
PLETHORA OF SCHOLARSHIPS,
BUT WHEN IT COMES TO ME
THEY HAVEN'T BEEN
SO ACCEPT-Y, YET.
WELL, ACCEPTANCES
ARE JUST TRICKLING IN.
AND I'M SURE WHEN
YOURS COMES IN PAIGE,
YOU'LL BE PREPARED.
I'M PREPARED
FOR A NERVOUS BREAKDOWN
IF IT DOESN'T.
MAYBE I'LL GET
A TATTOO.
HELLO?
DISCUSSING
THE FUTURE HERE -
MY FUTURE.
AS IN THINGS THAT COULD AFFECT
THE REST OF MY LIFE.
OR I COULD LEARN
HOW TO PLAY THE BASS.
THESE ARE YOUR
FUTURE PLANS?
THINGS THAT COULD
HAPPEN NEXT WEEK?
ALEX:
IT'S CALLED
"LIVING IN THE NOW".
AND WE BOTH KNOW
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING
ABOUT THE NOW IS ME.
LOOK! THE BIG ENVELOPE
FROM BANTING.
AND EVERYONE KNOWS
THE BIG ENVELOPE
MEANS YOU GET IN.
AND I DID!
I GOT IN.
WE ARE SO OUT OF HERE!
YOU'RE LATE,
AND OUR BOSS HAS BEEN
BREATHING DOWN MY NECK.
UM, WHAT PART OF,
"WE ARE SO OUT OF HERE"
DIDN'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
WE? I DIDN'T
GET INTO BANTING.
MALE CUSTOMER:
AND DON'T FORGET,
TOPPING HALFWAY,
AND THEN AGAIN ON TOP.
THANKS.
WELL, MAYBE
YOU COULD COME WITH?
WE COULD GET OUR OWN
COZY LITTLE PLACE?
ALEX:
SOUNDS COZY.
BUT WHAT WOULD I
ACTUALLY DO...
IN KINGSTON?
YOU COULD WORK.
GET A TRANSFER
FROM THE MOVIE THEATRE.
YOU CAN KEEP THAT TOPPING
COMING, MISS.
ALEX:
YOU'LL BE STUDYING
YOUR BUTT OFF
AND MAKING NEW FRIENDS.
AND I'LL STILL BE
DISHING OUT POPCORN?
MALE CUSTOMER:
MISS, DO I NEED TO SHOW YOU
WHAT I MEAN BY MORE TOPPING
MYSELF?
(BUTTER SLOSHES)
CAN'T WAIT
FOR YOUR HEART ATTACK.
NEXT TIME YOU INSULT
A CUSTOMER?
MAYBE NOT IN FRONT
OF YOUR MANAGER.
ALEX, CAN I SEE YOU
IN MY OFFICE?
(SIGHS)
STOP. STOP.
DO I HAVE COOTIES
ALL OF A SUDDEN?
NO, I JUST...
I DON'T WANT IT
TO GO TOO FAR, OKAY?
(IRRITATED EXHALE)
I BET IF MANNY WERE HERE,
SHE'D BE ALL OVER YOU.
JUST LIKE IN THE CAF.
AW, THAT WAS NOTHING.
THAT'S JUST MANNY'S WAY.
SHE'S ALWAYS LIKE THAT.
I CAN ONLY IMAGINE
WHAT SHE WAS LIKE
WHEN YOU TWO
WERE GOING OUT.
YOU WANT
A PLAY-BY-PLAY?
SPARE ME.
I CAN BARELY STAND
THE IDEA
OF YOU BEING WITH HER
AT ALL.
TRUTH IS,
WHEN I WAS WITH MANNY,
WE DID NOTHING TOGETHER.
ZIP.
YOU'RE SERIOUS?
YEAH, I WASN'T EVEN
INTO HER THAT WAY.
HER WHOLE SEXUAL PAST...
AW, IT JUST
TURNED ME OFF.
SO YOU'RE REALLY
A VIRGIN?
SPINNER:
I'M SO VIRGINAL...
MARY'S JEALOUS.
(LAUGHING)
I FEEL SO BAD NOW,
ABOUT MANNY.
YOU KNOW, IF SHE JUST REPENTED
AND PURIFIED HERSELF,
HER PAST COULD TOTALLY
GO AWAY.
YOU CAN DO THAT?
YEAH,
IT'S A CEREMONIAL THING.
I THINK IT COULD
REALLY HELP HER.
HEY!
CANDY AND A CHICK FLICK?
SOMEONE'S GOT IT BAD.
YEAH WELL,
IT'S NO "CLOWN ACADEMY II".
BUT IF DARCY'S HAPPY,
I'M HAPPY.
BUT YOU'RE NOT.
MM, I'M GREAT.
EVERYTHING'S PEACHY.
BANTING?
YOU'RE LOOKING AT
THEIR NEWEST ACCEPTEE.
PAIGE,
THAT'S AWESOME!
GET OVER HERE!
WHOA! BANTING IS LIKE
THE HARVARD OF THE NORTH.
I AM LIKE,
SO HAPPY FOR YOU.
THIS IS SO COOL.
OH, CANDY'S ON ME.
IT'S MY TREAT.
THE EVIL ONE MADE ME
CLEAN THE BATHROOMS.
THEN SHE FIRED ME.
FOR THE TOPPING
INCIDENT?
STRIKE THREE:
GOODBYE POLYESTER;
HELLO UNEMPLOYMENT.
I DON'T WANT
THIS STUPID JOB.
IT'S TIME TO MOVE ON,
DO SOMETHING ELSE.
ANYTHING IN MIND?
RIGHT NOW?
NO.
I JUST GOT FIRED.
CAN WE LAY OFF
THE CAREER PLANNING,
JUST FOR TONIGHT?
I HAVE TO GO.
SEE YOU TOMORROW?
SPINNER:
I SAW THESE LAST NIGHT.
THEY'RE CLADDAGH RINGS.
SEE...
WHEN THE HEART
FACES THE BODY,
IT MEANS COMMITMENT.
BEING HONEST AND TRUE
TO EACH OTHER.
SPINNER,
THEY'RE BEAUTIFUL.
TO OUR FUTURE TOGETHER.
I LOVE IT.
(BIKE BELL RINGS)
MANNY:
AND ONE... TWO... THREE...
FOUR...
CUT IT.
THERE'S MY FAVOURITE
TECHIE!
THE LIGHTING BOARD
NEEDS A FRIEND.
GET ACQUAINTED.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
HE SO HAS A THING
FOR CHEERLEADERS.
YOU'RE NUMBER THREE.
AND A LOCK TO LEAD
THE SQUAD NEXT YEAR.
YOU THINK SO?
MANNY:
YEAH, YOU'RE PRETTY,
YOU'RE GRACEFUL,
A NATURAL DANCER.
PLUS, YOU DIDN'T
GET KICKED OFF
'CAUSE EVERYONE SAW
YOUR BOOBS.
SO THAT'S A BONUS.
MANNY?
I'VE BEEN THINKING.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU WANT
A FRESH START?
THE DOOR'S ALWAYS OPEN
AT FRIENDSHIP CLUB.
(CHUCKLES)
UM, SWEETIE,
THE NUN-LIFESTYLE RULES
AREN'T EXACTLY MY SCENE.
TRUST ME,
ANYONE CAN CHANGE.
I MEAN, LOOK AT SPIN.
PRAYER, ABSTINENCE...
HE'S A BELIEVER.
AS IN ABSTI-NO-SEX?
KUDOS TO YOU FOR MAKING
THAT HAPPEN WITH SPIN.
YOU MUST BE
A MIRACLE WORKER.
WAIT. UM,
ARE YOU SAYING THAT
YOU AND SPINNER
HAVE HAD SEX?
DARCY,
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
WHAT HAS HE BEEN
TELLING YOU?
MS. KWAN:
CONGRATULATIONS
ON ALL YOUR HARD WORK.
BELIEVE ME,
NO MATTER WHAT YOU DO,
YOU'LL THANK ME
FOR YOUR EXCELLENT
COMMUNICATION SKILLS.
ALEX.
THANKS FOR NOTHING.
OH, "A MINUS".
I AM ON FIRE.
THAT'LL IMPRESS THE PANTS OFF
ANY ADMISSIONS OFFICE.
JIMMY:
I HOPE SO.
BECAUSE I'M A COUPLE
CREDITS SHORT,
AND UH...
IT'S STILL ALL
UP IN THE AIR.
ALEX:
YOU DON'T KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN,
AND THE SKY ISN'T FALLING?
AMAZING.
MM. SHE'S HIGH
ON CARPE DIEM.
SIDE EFFECT
OF BEING FIRED.
I'LL GET ANOTHER JOB.
OR THERE'S ALWAYS WELFARE.
GREAT PLAN, ALEX.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE FUN.
FUN.
DO YOU EVEN KNOW
WHAT THAT IS?
THIS, THIS IS FUN.
DO YOU REALIZE
HOW CLOSE I AM
TO THAT SCHOLARSHIP?
YOU WANT FUN?
LET'S CUT CLASS TOMORROW.
DO SOMETHING
WE'VE NEVER DONE BEFORE;
SOMETHING WILD
AND CRAZY
AND TOTALLY NUTS.
OR THERE'S A SALE ON
AT THE MALL.
YOU'RE STARTING
WITH THE 60S,
THEN MOVING ON
TO THE 1800'S?
THIS IS A MESS!
OKAY, IT'S CALLED
CREATIVE LIBERTY, LIBERTY.
AND I AM AN ACTOR,
NOT A HISTORIAN.
FINE. BUT I DON'T THINK
CHARLOTTE DEGRASSI
HAD AN MP3 PLAYER.
I NEED TO STEAL
YOUR BOYFRIEND, DARCY.
LIBERTY:
NATE HAS MONO.
SPINNER, YOU ARE VICTOR.
MANNY - CHARLOTTE.
W-W-WAI-WAIT.
I'M ON LIGHTING.
I'M MORE OF
A BEHIND-THE-SCENES
KIND OF GUY.
YEAH,
THE SHOW'S IN TWO DAYS.
WE DON'T HAVE TIME
TO DISCUSS THIS.
READ, NOW.
UM... CHARLOTTE,
PROMISE ME
YOU'LL BE MINE FOREVER.
OF COURSE, VICTOR.
OUR LOVE SHALL LAST
A LIFETIME.
MARRY ME,
CHARLOTTE.
I WILL, VICTOR!
I WILL!
(QUICK KISSING SOUNDS)
SPINNER AND MANNY:
(LAUGHING)
WHAT WAS THAT?
UM, IT'S JUST PART
OF THE SKETCH, SWEETIE.
IT'S IN THE SCRIPT.
MANNY,
I'M NOT STUPID.
YOU'RE CONSTANTLY
FLIRTING WITH MY BOYFRIEND.
YOU STILL LIKE HIM.
OKAY,
I'M BACK ON LIGHTING.
UM, WHO WANTS TO BE
MANNY'S ACTING PARTNER?
ANYBODY?
YEAH, NOT SURPRISING.
WHAT IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
MANNY, EVEN YOU CAN
BECOME PURE AGAIN.
ALL IT TAKES
IS REPENTANCE.
YEAH,
I'LL GET RIGHT ON THAT.
WELL, YOU SHOULD,
CONSIDERING YOU ARE
THE SCHOOL'S BIGGEST SLUT.
YOU ARE THE LAST PERSON
TO EVER CALL ME THAT.
MALE STUDENT:
OH! OH!
OHHH!
MANNY AND DARCY:
(SOUNDS OF STRUGGLE)
SPINNER:
GIRLS! MANNY!
MANNY!
GET UP!
HAVE YOU TWO GONE
COMPLETELY PSYCHO?
YOU LIED ABOUT BEING
A VIRGIN, SPINNER.
SHE TOLD ME.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
GET- GET BACK TO WORK
PLEASE!
GET GOING!
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
STARING AT?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
OKAY. HOW'S THIS?
GOOD MORNING,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
FRIENDS AND FAMILY,
TEACHERS
AND ADMINISTRATORS-
OH, I THINK YOU LEFT OUT
THE JANITOR?
PAIGE, IT'S A VALEDICTORIAN
SPEECH.
I WANT TO BE INCLUSIVE.
REFILLS?
WHOA!
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU JUST LIVED
THROUGH A COUNTRY SONG.
MY DOG IS FINE.
MY TRUCK RUNS TOO.
MUST BE GIRL TROUBLE.
MARCO:
HA, NO KIDDING.
YOU DIDN'T HEAR ABOUT
THE DARCY/MANNY CAGE MATCH?
SPINNER:
DUDE, DON'T REMIND ME.
DARCY'S COMPLETELY CONVINCED
THAT THERE'S SOMETHING
GOING ON WITH ME AND MANNY.
(SCOFFS)
JEALOUSY IS A NASTY THING.
SPINNER:
'KAY, BUT THERE'S NOTHING
TO BE JEALOUS OF
'CAUSE I'M NOT CHEATING
WITH MANNY.
THAT'S BESIDES THE POINT, HON.
DARCY IS JEALOUS
OF YOUR PAST,
NOT YOUR PRESENT.
THERE'S NOTHING YOU CAN DO.
UNLESS YOU CAN -
I DON'T KNOW -
SOMEHOW CREATE A TIME MACHINE
AND ERASE THAT PAST.
ALEX:
YOU SHOULD ADD THIS
TO YOUR LIST.
I THINK YOU MIGHT
REALLY LIKE HER.
THANKS, HON.
UM, SO...
HAVE YOU GIVEN ANY THOUGHT TO,
YOU KNOW, BANTING?
THE FUTURE?
NOPE.
IT'S MONTHS AWAY.
WHY WOULD IT EVEN BE
CROSSING MY MIND?
BECAUSE...
IT'S IMPORTANT
TO HAVE A PLAN;
TO KNOW WHAT'S
GOING ON;
TO HAVE SOME
SORT OF DIRECTION.
IT'S ALSO IMPORTANT
TO HAVE FUN.
WHICH, BY THE WAY,
TODAY HAS BEEN COMPLETELY
AND UTTERLY LACKING.
FINE. WHAT'S FUN?
SHOW ME.
I DON'T KNOW.
TAKE THAT CD.
EXCUSE ME?
YOU'VE NEVER STOLEN ANYTHING
IN YOUR LIFE BEFORE,
HAVE YOU?
AND I'M NOT ABOUT
TO START.
IT'S A RUSH.
JUST TRY IT.
NO THANK YOU,
REALLY.
(ALARM BEEPS)
(ANGRY SIGH)
PAIGE:
HI, I'M SORRY.
THAT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
MARCO:
SURE YOU WANT TO DO THIS?
SPINNER:
DUDE, I'M SURE, OKAY?
THE QUESTION IS,
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
I MEAN,
YOU AND FRIENDSHIP CLUB
DIDN'T EXACTLY
HIT IT OFF.
AH, OLD NEWS, BUD.
I'M JUST, I'M HAPPY YOU
EVEN ASKED ME TO HELP.
HEY GUYS.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
SPINNER:
YOU ARE MY EVERYTHING.
AND RIGHT NOW,
IN FRONT OF ALL OUR FRIENDS,
I WANT TO START OVER.
WITH A CLEAN SLATE.
I WANT TO PURIFY MYSELF
AND BECOME A VIRGIN...
AGAIN.
IT'S NOT JUST A MATTER
OF SAYING IT.
DARCY, I WAS UP ALL NIGHT
MEMORIZING SCRIPTURE.
I WANT TO DO THIS.
I, GAVIN MASON,
PROMISE TO HONOUR GOD
WITH MY BODY.
I WILL RESIST TEMPTATION
AND TO SAVE MYSELF
FOR MARRIAGE.
"COME NOW,
LET US REASON TOGETHER,"
SAYS THE LORD.
"THOUGH YOUR SINS
ARE LIKE SCARLET,
THEY SHALL BE AS WHITE
AS SNOW."
PAIGE:
THAT WASN'T FUNNY.
IT WAS STUPID
AND EMBARRASSING.
COULD YOU NOT BE
SUCH A DRAMA QUEEN?
CAN YOU NOT BE SO IMMATURE?
I CAN'T DO THIS.
CAN'T DO WHAT?
THIS "LIVING IN THE MOMENT"
THING.
I NEED STRUCTURE:
PLANS, IDEAS,
AND...
MAYBE JUST A LITTLE EXCITEMENT
ABOUT THE FUTURE -
OUR FUTURE.
IT'S YOUR FUTURE,
PAIGE,
NOT MINE.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
IT MEANS I HAVE TO
FIGURE OUT WHAT I WANT;
WHAT'S GOOD FOR ME.
FOLLOWING YOU
TO BANTING?
WORKING SOME CRAP
MINIMUM-WAGE JOB
AND BEING YOUR LAPDOG?
DOES THAT SOUND GOOD?
MAYBE I'LL GO TO COLLEGE,
MAYBE I'LL JOIN THE ARMY,
MAYBE I'LL START A BUSINESS -
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I HAVE TO
FIGURE IT OUT,
ON MY TIMETABLE.
WHAT'RE YOU TRYING
TO SAY?
I THINK YOU CAN
FIGURE IT OUT.
YOU ALWAYS WERE
THE SMART ONE, PAIGE.
HMM...
SMILING AND CHEWING.
THAT'S TALENT.
I'M HAPPY,
FOR YOU.
'CAUSE YOU GET TO
START ALL OVER AGAIN.
(DOG BARKS)
WELL, IT FEELS GOOD.
IT'S LIKE BEING
FACTORY FRESH.
MAN, WHO WOULDA THOUGHT
I'D BE VIRGIN AGAIN?
NOT AFTER LAST SUMMER.
BUT WAIT,
YOU AND MANNY WERE TOGETHER
DURING THE SCHOOL YEAR.
I DON'T GET IT.
UM...
DARCY, MANNY?
SHE WAS MY FIRST...
BUT SHE WASN'T MY LAST.
HOW MANY EXACTLY?
TWO.
YOU HAD SEX
WITH TWO OTHER GIRLS?!
SPINNER:
YEAH, BUT THAT WAS BEFORE
I MET YOU.
UH, BEFORE I FOUND CHRIST.
SINCE THEN I'VE DONE
NOTHING WRONG.
BUT YOU LIED!
SO,
I WAS STILL CLEANSED.
IT'S ALL GOOD.
NO. IT'S NOT.
HOW AM I EVER GOING
TO TRUST YOU?
YOU LIED TO ME, SPINNER.
THIS WHOLE THING,
IT'S NOT-
IT'S NOT ABOUT LYING
OR GOD OR ANYTHING,
EXCEPT YOU
AND YOUR STUPID JEALOUSY!
WHATEVER. OKAY?
BELIEVE WHAT YOU WANT
TO BELIEVE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I BELIEVE,
DARCY?
I BELIEVE I WILL NEVER
BE CLEAN ENOUGH -
NOT FOR YOU.
WE'RE THROUGH, OKAY?
IT'S OVER.
SPORTS ANNOUNCER:
SWING AND OH,
A LINE DRIVE TO CENTRE LEFT.
GOING... GOING...
JAY:
I'M NOT HERE
TO BUG YOU, OKAY?
I'M-I'M WATCHING THE GAME
WITH CHAD.
OR... I WAS
BEFORE HE PASSED OUT.
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU
GOT HIT BY A BUS.
PAIGE MICHALCHUK,
BREAKUP EXPRESS.
YOU LOOKING FOR
A SHOULDER TO CRY ON?
ER, MAYBE JUST
A QUICK REBOUND?
JAY, I'M NOT BI.
I'M NOT CONFUSED.
I'M A LESBIAN -
AN ACTUAL LESBIAN -
WHO JUST BROKE UP
WITH HER FIRST GIRLFRIEND
AND IT SUCKS.
I'M SORRY.
THAT'S ONE OF THE FIRST TIMES
I'VE SAID I'M SORRY
AND ACTUALLY MEANT IT.
THAT'S ONE OF THE FIRST TIMES
YOU'VE SAID SORRY,
AND I ACTUALLY
BELIEVED YOU.
UM, DO YOU WANNA WATCH
SOME TV WITH ME?
NO FUNNY BUSINESS,
JUST FRIENDS HANGING OUT?
FINE.
(SNORTS)
(DOOR CHIMES JINGLE)
HOT DATE WITH YOUR
COURSE CALENDAR?
(EXHALES) UM...
ALEX AND I BROKE UP.
I JUST NEEDED TO BE ALONE.
WELCOME TO SPLITSVILLE.
YOU'RE IN THE RIGHT PLACE.
YOU TOO?
MAN, I WISH I WAS GETTING
OUT OF HERE, LIKE YOU.
HMM.
DO NOT ENVY ME.
SURE, I GOT INTO BANTING,
BUT...
WHAT IF I BLOW IT?
WHAT IF EVERYONE SEES
THAT I AM JUST THIS...
THIS BIG FAKER
WHO DOESN'T BELONG THERE?
PAIGE, YOU TOTALLY
BELONG THERE.
TAKE IT FROM SOMEONE
WHO KNOWS, OKAY?
YOU'RE AMAZING.
YOU ALWAYS HAVE BEEN.
THANKS.
NO EXTRA CHARGE.
OH, MAN, THE TIME.
UH, CAN I DRIVE YOU HOME?
SURE.
THAT'D BE GREAT, SPIN.