(MUFFLED MUSIC BLARES FROM CAR
THEN STOPS)
WHAT? NOW?
I DON'T EVEN HAVE
MY BEGINNER'S.
OH COME ON,
MY LITTLE SPEED DEMON.
OKAY, SO...
GIVE 'ER SOME GAS.
OMIGOD, IT'S WORKING!
I'M DRIVING!
JT:
YOU DID FINE.
YOU DID WONDERFUL,
OKAY?
NOW,
WE'LL GO CELEBRATE.
I'VE GOT TO JUDGE
VIDEO ANNOUNCEMENTS
IN 15 MINUTES.
WELL, BELIEVE ME,
THAT'S WAY MORE
THAN ENOUGH TIME.
LIBERTY...
DO WE HAVE TO TALK
ABOUT THIS?
JT:
I JUST...
I WANNA KNOW IF IT'S SOMETHING
I'M DOING, OKAY?
BECAUSE EVER SINCE
SCHOOL STARTED
YOU'VE BEEN LIKE...
AN ICEBERG.
YOU KNOW, STUDENT
COUNCIL PRESIDENT
COMES WITH A LOT
OF RESPONSIBILITY,
IF YOU EVEN KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS.
WHATEVER YOU SAY,
YOUR MAJESTY.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
SIMPSON:
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR WIN,
MADAM PRESIDENT.
LIBERTY:
THANK YOU, MR. SIMPSON.
TOBY:
OKAY, WE'LL BE READY
TO START AUDITIONS
JUST AS SOON AS OUR STUDENT
COUNCIL PRESIDENT ARRIVES...
WITH HER MAN-SERVANT.
HA HA.
I'M ACTUALLY HERE
TO AUDITION.
FOR I SEEK NOT ONLY
TO INFORM,
BUT TO ENTERTAIN,
AS WELL.
YOU'RE AUDITIONING?
IS THERE A PROBLEM
WITH THAT?
I'M SORRY,
BUT EARLY MORNINGS?
WRITING COPY?
BEING ON TIME?
DOES THAT SOUND LIKE
JT YORKE TO YOU?
LIBERTY, THIS IS KINDA
IMPORTANT TO ME.
WHEN THAT LITTLE LIGHT
GOES ON,
IT'S A RUSH.
IT DRAWS ME IN.
LIKE A MOTH
TO A BUG ZAPPER.
ARE YOU SURE BECOMING
AN ENTERTAINER
IS A RESPONSIBLE,
MATURE CAREER PATH?
WHAT'S THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
NOTHING.
DO WHAT YOU WANT, JT.
JT:
I'LL JUST SEE YOU
IN CLASS.
I'LL AUDITION TOMORROW.
SPINNER:
A-MINUS?!
YES!
KWAN:
NICE WORK, GAVIN.
KEEP IT UP
AND YOU MIGHT EVEN
PASS THIS YEAR.
GOT ANY TIPS ON HOW TO GET PAST
KWAN'S MARKING SYSTEM?
OH, I GOT TIPS,
LOTS OF TIPS,
AND UM... I'D BE HAPPY
TO SHARE 'EM WITH YOU
ANY TIME, ANY PLACE,
ANY SUBJECT.
I'VE GOT A TIP
FOR YOU.
THE FLIRTING?
LAME.
OKAY, SO WE'LL TRADE.
I'LL HELP YOU WITH ENGLISH;
YOU HELP ME FLIRT.
SO... YOU FAILED
LAST YEAR?
YEAH, I HAD SOME PROBLEMS.
WHAT KIND OF PROBLEMS?
MY DOG... GOT SICK
WITH LEUKEMIA.
ALL HIS FUR FELL OUT
RIGHT AROUND EXAMS.
AND I WAS JUST TOO BROKEN UP
OVER SPARKY-
WOW...
NOT ONLY ARE YOU
BAD AT FLIRTING BUT...
YOU SUCK AT LYING,
TOO.
KWAN:
OKAY CLASS, LET'S BEGIN.
GAVIN, ATTENTION, PLEASE.
JT:
TOBES.
WANNA HANG OUT
TONIGHT?
DON'T YOU HAVE TO RUB
LIBERTY'S FEET OR SOMETHING?
LOOK, IT'S JUST...
THE WAY SHE TALKS
TO YOU?
YOU GOTTA BE THE MAN,
JT.
OH, BELIEVE ME,
TOBES,
I HAVE BEEN THE MAN,
OKAY?
ALL SUMMER LONG.
YOU AND LIBERTY
HAVE BEEN...
GETTING OUR FREAK ON?
OH, YEAH.
DOZENS OF TIMES.
SHE ESPECIALLY LIKES IT
WHEN I-
♪ OH CAAA-NA-DAAAA!
OUR HOME AND NATIVE LAND- ♪
OKAY, I'LL STOP.
SO... WHY IS SHE BARKING
ORDERS AT YOU?
SHE JUST BECAME STUDENT
COUNCIL PRESIDENT, OKAY?
MY VIRGINAL FRIEND.
SHE'S STRESSED.
SO MAYBE ALL SHE NEEDS
IS A LITTLE...
DE-STRESSING.
SPINNER:
JIMMY.
C'MON, MAN,
WILL YOU JUST GIMME A CHANCE?
IT'S A WHOLE NEW YEAR.
LOOK, JUST 'CAUSE
THEY LET YOU BACK,
IT DOES NOT CHANGE
WHO YOU ARE.
SPINNER:
BUT I HAVE CHANGED, MAN,
I HAVE.
(ANNOUNCEMENTS IN BACKGROUND)
LISTEN, I'VE GOTTA
TELL YOU SOMETHING.
'KAY? THE TRUTH.
I WAS...
I WAS EXPELLED LAST YEAR.
OKAY.
THAT'S A START.
WHY?
I GOT ROPED
INTO SOMETHING.
WE PLAYED A LITTLE PRANK
ON THIS GUY,
AND HE WENT PSYCHO.
HE CAME TO SCHOOL SHOOTING.
I KNOW ALL ABOUT IT.
I JUST DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE INVOLVED.
ONLY IN THE MOST
INDIRECT WAY.
AND I'VE- I'VE MORE
THAN PAID FOR IT,
BUT PEOPLE AROUND HERE,
THEY...
THEY WON'T EVEN
LOOK AT ME.
I'M PERSONA NON GROTTO,
AND IT SUCKS.
LOOK, A BUNCH OF US
ARE MEETING UP AFTER SCHOOL.
ROOM 208.
WHY DON'T YOU COME,
HANG OUT?
HEY, I READ YOUR DANCE
COMMITTEE BUDGET -
ON TIME, UNDER BUDGET.
PRESIDENT VAN ZANDT SHOOTS!
SHE SCORES!
THE CROWD GOES WILD!
WEIRDO TEACHER OVERLOAD.
DIAGNOSIS:
SIMPSONITIS.
IT'S NOTHING.
MINOR HEADACHE.
I MEAN,
IT'S UNDERSTANDABLE.
YOU'RE SPINNING
A HUNDRED PLATES AT ONCE.
HEY, MAYBE CIRQUE DU SOLEIL'S
HIRING.
DON'T WASTE YOUR
"A" MATERIAL ON ME.
OKAY.
JUST TELL ME ONE THING.
WHAT'RE YOU
DOING TONIGHT?
WORK, WORK
AND MORE WORK.
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
YOU'RE GONNA COME
WITH ME
AND OUR FRIENDS
TO MOVIE NIGHT.
BUT THERE'S THE BUDGET,
AND AGENDAS TO COLLATE,
MEMOS TO WRITE...
ALL OF WHICH CAN WAIT.
OKAY. COOL.
I'LL PICK YOU UP.
JT?
YOU'RE REALLY GREAT.
I KNOW.
(PEOPLE TALKING
IN LOW VOICES)
DARCY:
EVERYBODY?
THIS IS SPINNER.
SPINNER:
HI.
WHY'RE YOU GUYS ALL SITTING
IN A CIRCLE?
YOU SHOULD MOVE
THOSE CHAIRS.
IT'S SPINNER'S
FIRST TIME HERE
SO WHO WANTS TO TELL HIM
THE FIRST RULE
OF FRIENDSHIP CLUB?
ALWAYS TALK
ABOUT FRIENDSHIP CLUB.
RIGHT.
SPREAD THE WORD.
OKAY, SO SINCE
I'VE GOT THE FLOOR,
I GUESS
I'LL KICK US OFF TODAY.
CLUB MEMBERS:
OUR FATHER, WHO ART IN HEAVEN,
HALLOWED BE THY NAME.
THY KINGDOM COME.
THY WILL BE DONE,
ON EARTH AS IT IS IN HEAVEN.
GIVE US THIS DAY...
JT:
OH, POLYESTER'S
IN THIS SEASON?
PAIGE:
20 MOVIE THEATRES
IN THIS CITY,
AND EVERYONE FROM DEGRASSI
COMES TO THIS ONE.
WHAT?
I'LL HAVE ONE EXTREME
CORN BUCKET -
DOUBLE TOPPINGS -
UM... A COLA TUB.
ACTUALLY, MAKE THAT
ROOT BEER, PLEASE,
AND TWO BENDY STRAWS.
MANNY:
UGH! ENOUGH WITH THE PDA.
EMMA:
SORRY GUYS,
BUS TOOK FOREVER.
ANOTHER ADVANTAGE
OF DATING JT.
MY MAN'S GOT A CAR.
AND MY LADY GETS A RIDE
WHENEVER SHE WANTS.
ACTUALLY, I GAVE LIBERTY
A REALLY GOOD DRIVING LESSON.
SHE'S PRETTY HANDY
WITH THE OLD STICK SHIFT.
OKAY, ENOUGH ABOUT
YOU AND LIBERTY'S SEX LIFE!
JT:
UH...HEY, UH,
GOOD HUSTLE, PAIGE.
YEAH, THAT'LL BE
$400 DOLLARS.
LIBERTY:
MAYBE THIS'LL TEACH YOU
TO KEEP PRIVATE MATTERS
PRIVATE.
YOU STILL HAVE
TO PAY FOR THAT.
I'VE CALLED.
I'VE EMAILED.
IF I GIVE YOU A LIFT,
WILL YOU TAKE THAT
AS AN APOLOGY?
LOOK,
I'M SORRY.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE MADE
THOSE JOKES TO TOBY
ABOUT OUR SEX LIFE.
YOU SHOULD NEVER HAVE TOLD HIM
ABOUT OUR SEX LIFE, PERIOD.
IT WAS STUPID.
I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU'RE MAKING
SUCH A BIG DEAL OUT OF THIS?
BECAUSE YOU TALK
WITHOUT THINKING.
YOU'RE IMMATURE.
YOU'RE A CLOWN.
YOU TREAT ME
LIKE A KID, OKAY?
YOU BOSS ME AROUND
AND YOU WOULDN'T EVEN
LET ME AUDITION
FOR THE VIDEO ANNOUNCEMENTS.
YOU DECIDE EVERYTHING.
GROW UP, JT.
JT:
RESPECT ME, LIBERTY.
OKAY AND THEN MAYBE WE CAN MAKE
A DECISION TOGETHER FOR ONCE.
LIBERTY:
WE DID.
LAST SUMMER,
REMEMBER?
WHEN WE DECIDED TO USE
THE KING SIZE CONDOM?
THE ONE THAT SLIPPED OFF?
I'M PREGNANT.
JT!
(LOUD CRASH,
GLASS SHATTERS)
PASSERBYS:
ARE YOU OKAY?
(INDISTINCT COMMENTS
OF CONCERN)
JT:
OH MY GOD!
WHAT...
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
HATZILAKOS:
WHAT HAPPENED?
ARE YOU OKAY?
WE'RE FINE.
A DOG RAN
ONTO THE ROAD.
JT SWERVED.
HE DID EVERYTHING
HE COULD.
HATZILAKOS:
WELL, YEAH...
ACCIDENTS WILL HAPPEN.
WHY DON'T YOU GO INSIDE?
I'LL TALK TO THE POLICE.
I'M JUST GLAD
YOU'RE OKAY.
SIMPSON:
SO, WHAT DRAWS US TO SOME
ADVERTISING AND NOT TO OTHERS?
IS IT THE LOOK?
THE HOOK?
OR IS IT...?
OKAY. (CLAPS)
PEEPERS UP FRONT,
PEOPLE.
IT'S TIME TO PARTNER UP.
LIBERTY AND JT,
NICE OF YOU TO JOIN US.
HOW LONG
HAVE YOU KNOWN?
A WHILE.
A WHILE?
WHAT'S A WHILE?
DAYS? WEEKS?
TRY MONTHS.
THREE.
LIBERTY.
I DON'T WANT
TO BE PREGNANT,
OKAY?
MORNING AFTER MORNING
I WAKE UP AND GUESS WHAT?
I STILL AM.
WELL,
UH, WHAT ABOUT A...
AN ABORTION?
I DON'T EVEN WANT
TO THINK ABOUT THAT,
LET ALONE TALK ABOUT IT.
AND ARE YOU SURE THAT
YOU'RE REALLY PREGNANT?
DO YOU NEED PROOF?
FINE. GO BUY
A PREGNANCY TEST.
YOU HAVEN'T DONE ONE?
A WOMAN JUST KNOWS,
JT.
THERE ARE A VAST
MULTITUDE OF SIGNS.
INCLUDING FREQUENT URINATION.
MR. SIMPSON?
IS THIS SEAT TAKEN?
NO.
YOU WERE AWFULLY
SPLITSVILLE LAST NIGHT.
DIDN'T LIKE THE CLUB?
IT WAS CHRISTIAN.
SO? I JOINED
A COUPLE OF MONTHS AGO.
IT'S FUN.
GUESS I'M NOT INTO THE...
JOINED-HANDS-GROUP-PRAYER
VARIETY OF FUN.
RIGHT,
'CAUSE THAT'S ALL I DO.
JUST BECAUSE
I'M CHRISTIAN
DOESN'T MEAN I WON'T CREAM YOU
IN LASER TAG.
OOH, LASER TAG.
WHAT A PARTY.
UM, WHAT ELSE DO YOU DO?
WEENIE ROASTS?
I LIKE HORROR MOVIES,
MAKE FART JOKES,
WATCH THE OCCASIONAL
ULTIMATE FIGHTING CHALLENGE.
YOU'RE ALLOWED
TO DO THAT?
YES.
I'M NOT IN SOME CULT,
SPINNER.
I DO PRETTY MUCH
ANYTHING I WANT.
UM, ARE YOU ALLOWED
TO DRINK COFFEE?
LIKE, SAY, TONIGHT,
AT THE DOT?
(BABY CRIES OUT)
♪♪♪
(BABY SQUEALS)
SHE IN THERE AGAIN?
GET COMFORTABLE.
SHE'S GONNA BE AWHILE.
PROBABLY ALL BUNGED UP.
YOU ARE AN IGNORANT
LITTLE PUKE!
YOU KNOW NOTHING
ABOUT LIBERTY, OKAY?
SO JUST TAKE MY ADVICE,
AND GET LOST!
MAN, YOU GOT ISSUES.
(TOILET FLUSHES)
IT'S POSITIVE?
TOBY:
YOU MISSED IT!
HEATHER SINCLAIR AUDITIONED
WITH A DANGLER.
SHE HAD A BOOG HANGING
FROM A NOSE HAIR!
YOU OKAY ENOUGH
TO DO THIS?
YEAH, IT'S MINE.
ALRIGHTY.
SO UM...
I'LL POINT TO YOU
AND THAT'S
WHEN YOU START.
HELLO, I'M, JT YORKE WITH
YOUR MORNING ANNOUNCEMENTS.
I... UM... OKAY.
GOOD MORNING.
CONGRATS TO OUR
SENIOR GIRLS RELAY TEAM,
WHO KNOCKED UP-
(NERVOUS LAUGH)
UH... WHO KNOCKED OFF...
RIVAL CARSON HILL,
AND ARE NOW
GUARANTEED A BERTH...
UM... A BERTH IN...
I'M GONNA BE SICK.
TOBY:
OKAY. UH... NEXT?
THAT WENT GREAT.
I'LL JUST HAVE TO NOTIFY
HEATHER SINCLAIR
SHE HAS THE JOB.
I CAN DO BETTER,
OKAY?
I TOLD YOU
NOT TO AUDITION.
ENTERTAINMENT IS NOT A PRACTICAL
CAREER PATH FOR YOU.
WILL YOU STOP?
JUST STOP TRYING
TO CONTROL ME - PLEASE.
FINE, I'LL FOCUS ON
CONTROLLING OTHER THINGS.
LIKE MY VOMITING.
LIBERTY?
WE NEED TO GET YOU A DOCTOR,
AND GET YOU CHECKED OUT.
ACTUALLY,
I'LL TAKE CARE OF THAT.
MEDICAL CONCERNS,
TELLING PARENTS,
ALL THE PRACTICAL DETAILS.
WHILE I JUST STAND AROUND
AND WATCH?
JT:
THE CANYON HOPPER XT.
IT'S AMAZING IT STILL WORKS.
TOBY:
YEAH. I FOUND IT
CLEANING OUT THE GARAGE.
TECHNICALLY
IT'S HALF YOURS.
YEAH WELL, WE SOLD
A LOT OF GOLF BALLS.
TOBES?
LIBERTY'S PREGNANT.
WOW.
YEAH.
OKAY. OKAY, UM...
THEY HAVE- THEY HAVE
SUPPORT GROUPS, RIGHT?
AND UH...
YOU CAN TALK TO MISS SAUVE
AT SCHOOL AND...
AND TELL YOUR PARENTS.
ACTUALLY, THERE'S
A BIGGER PROBLEM.
A BIGGER PROBLEM THAN
LIBERTY BEING PREGNANT?
YEAH, HER.
LIBERTY.
EVERYTHING SHE USED
TO LIKE ABOUT ME?
SHE NOW HATES.
I MEAN, SHE TREATS ME
LIKE CRAP, TOBES.
UM...
JUST TALK TO HER.
TELL HER TO QUIT IT.
DOESN'T WORK.
NOTHING WORKS.
WHAT AM I GOING
TO DO?
CORNER TABLE.
NICE.
YEAH, IT'S ONE OF THE PERKS
OF WORKING HERE.
HERE.
MADE SOMETHING FOR YOU.
HMM. GREEN DAY,
MISSY E.,
UH... ARCADE FIRE?
COOL.
NOT WHAT I EXPECTED.
YOUR TURN.
TELL ME SOMETHING
ABOUT YOURSELF
THAT I WOULDN'T
EXPECT.
ALL RIGHT.
THIS GOES RIGHT
IN THE VAULT, RIGHT?
YOU KNOW THOSE LITTLE
MR. HANDSOME CONTESTS?
BEAUTY PAGEANTS FOR BOYS?
YOU ARE LOOKING
AT LITTLE MR. HANDSOME,
AGE FOUR THROUGH SIX.
(LAUGHS)
SO, WHAT HAPPENED
AFTER SIX?
GOT UGLY, I GUESS.
(LAUGHS)
JIMMY:
JUST A HEADS UP?
YOU SHOULD BE CAREFUL
WITH THIS GUY.
HE'S DANGEROUS,
YOU KNOW.
JIMMY-
HE TENDS TO GET
PEOPLE SHOT.
THAT'S NO GOOD.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT HE TOLD YOU BUT...
I DOUBT IT'S THE TRUTH.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
I'M GOING TO
ASK YOU THIS:
CAN I DO THE MORNING
ANNOUNCEMENTS?
NO.
OKAY.
I'M GONNA ASK AGAIN.
JT, WE'RE NOT TALKING
ABOUT THIS.
LIBERTY, IF WE CAN'T TALK
ABOUT THIS,
THEN HOW ARE WE GONNA DEAL
WITH THE FACT
THAT YOU'RE PREGNANT?
WE'RE NOT;
I AM.
OH, THAT'S GOOD TO KNOW.
JUST LIKE YOU
TO MAKE A JOKE.
THAT'S WHAT YOU USED
TO LIKE ABOUT ME, REMEMBER?
IS THAT I MAKE JOKES?
YEAH, WELL,
EVERYTHING'S CHANGED.
I DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR JOKES.
THIS IS SERIOUS.
I CAN'T TRUST YOU
TO DEAL WITH THIS.
FINE.
THEN I CAN'T DEAL
WITH YOU.
THAT'S IT, LIBERTY.
I'M DONE.
YOU'RE BREAKING UP
WITH ME?
NOW?
LOOK, WHATEVER
YOU HAVE TO SAY,
I'VE HEARD IT ALL BEFORE,
OKAY? SO...
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO BOTHER.
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME
THE WHOLE STORY?
SPINNER:
BECAUSE...
JIMMY WAS MY BEST FRIEND.
I BASICALLY CUT
HIS LEGS OFF.
I DON'T LIKE
TO BROADCAST THAT.
YOU DIDN'T SHOOT HIM.
NO,
BUT I MIGHT AS WELL HAVE.
IT WAS TOTALLY MY FAULT.
I KEEP TRYING
TO TALK TO HIM BUT...
YOU CAN'T MAKE
JIMMY FORGIVE YOU,
ESPECIALLY IF YOU HAVEN'T
FORGIVEN YOURSELF.
YEAH, I GET IT.
FRIENDSHIP CLUB.
RIGHT?
BLAH BLAH BLAH.
NO,
I'M TALKING ABOUT YOU.
BECAUSE I LIKE YOU.
HERE...
IF YOU STILL WANT
TO GET TO KNOW ME BETTER.
LIBERTY?
I GOT A JOB...
AT A DRUG STORE.
YOU DID?
SO NOT ONLY WILL I BE ABLE
TO SHARE THE COSTS,
BUT WHEN THE BABY COMES,
I'LL GET A PRETTY GOOD DISCOUNT
ON DIAPERS, TOO.
WHY DID YOU DO THAT?
BECAUSE...
I WANT TO HELP.
AND IT'S THE ONLY WAY
I KNOW HOW.
AND I DIDN'T NEED
YOUR PERMISSION.
THAT WAS A PLUS,
TOO.
WE'RE NOT BACK TOGETHER.
I KNOW.
BUT I'M NOT GONNA
ABANDON YOU,
AND I'M NOT GONNA
ABANDON THIS BABY.
I'VE NEVER-
NEVER NEEDED HELP
ON ANYTHING.