MARCO:
WE MUST HAVE DONE SOMETHING
AWFUL IN OUR PAST LIVES
TO DESERVE THIS HELL.
PAIGE:
OH, JUST WAIT UNTIL UNIVERSITY.
ACCORDING TO DYLAN,
IT ONLY GETS HARDER.
HE SAID MCGILL'S TOUGH.
DYLAN?
HOW IS THE SATAN CHILD
ANYWAY?
ELLIE:
QUESTION:
WHO'S STILL BITTER
OVER LAST YEAR?
ANSWER:
OH, MARCO DEL ROSSI.
MARCO:
STOP!
I AM SO OVER THAT GUY.
I'VE ALREADY FORGOTTEN
WHO WE'RE TALKING ABOUT.
GREAT.
SO THEN LET'S TALK ABOUT
STALKER BOY -
TIM, YOUR LOVESICK SHADOW.
MARCO:
GUYS, CAN YOU BE NICE?
YOU KNOW WE'VE BEEN SORTA
SEEING EACH OTHER.
EMPHASIS ON THE "SORTA".
YOU GUYS HAVEN'T EVEN
BEEN ON A DATE YET.
TIM:
HEY, YOU GUYS.
WOW, IT LOOKS LIKE A BRAIN-BOMB
WENT OFF IN HERE.
MARCO:
(CHUCKLING) YEAH.
WELL, STUDYING
FOR EXAMS IS KILLER,
BUT YOU ARE WELCOME TO JOIN
THE CARNAGE IF YOU DARE.
SUPER. FIRST ROUND
OF CAFFEINE'S ON ME.
OH, I'M OUT.
MY RIDE JUST SHOWED UP.
HE'S IN TOWN?!
PAIGE,
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
HEY, MARCO.
HEY... HI.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
MAY I?
UH, ACTUALLY, THE SEAT'S
SAVED FOR SOMEONE.
MY BOYFRIEND... TIM.
TIM, MEET MY EX, DYLAN.
HE WAS...
HE WAS JUST LEAVING.
LATER, MARCO.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
MR. ELLIS:
OKAY PEOPLE,
NO TALKING,
NO CELL PHONES,
NO BATHROOM BREAKS
UNTIL YOU'RE DONE.
OKAY.
FLIP 'EM AND HAVE FUN.
LIBERTY:
SO...
IGNEOUS ROCKS ARE PURE,
WHEREAS SEDIMENTARY ROCKS
ARE MADE OF OTHER FORMS
OF ROCKS. SEE?
WHY DO I CARE?
BECAUSE IF YOU FAIL,
DAD'LL SEND YOU
TO SUMMER SCHOOL... AGAIN.
DEREK,
METAMORPHIC ROCKS?
ARE ROCKS THAT HAVE
BEEN TRANSFORMED
WITH HEAT AND PRESSURE.
SOMEONE'S BEEN LISTENING
TO ME.
SOMEBODY'S A BIGGER NERD
THAN YOU.
DEREK:
THAT'S HIS WAY OF SAYING
WE'D BE FLUNKING OUT
RIGHT NOW
IF IT WEREN'T FOR YOU.
WELL, I DO AIM TO PLEASE.
DEREK:
WE STILL STUDYING TONIGHT?
MAYBE WE CAN ORDER PIZZA
AND TALK?
ELLIE:
IF I FAILED, WHICH I DID,
I'LL BE STUCK AT DEGRASSI
FOREVER.
PAIGE:
THEN IT'S SETTLED.
TONIGHT, WE NEED TO HAVE
SOME FUN.
WHAT?!
WE HAVE AN ENGLISH
EXAM TOMORROW?
WHICH YOU'VE STUDIED FOR
NON-STOP FOR WEEKS.
IF YOU DON'T RELAX
AND HAVE SOME FUN,
YOU'RE GOING TO CRACK,
MARCO.
SO WHO'S WITH ME?
PAIGE:
NICE. THERE'S THIS PLACE,
"THE OTHER TEAM".
IT'S A GAY CLUB,
SO WE DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT GETTING HIT ON.
ALEX:
GREAT.
ELLIE:
YEAH, GREAT.
SO ARE YOU GOING
TO ASK TIM TO COME?
I DON'T KNOW,
DO I REALLY WANT TO BE
HIS FIRST SERIOUS BOYFRIEND?
I MEAN, I START UNIVERSITY
IN THE FALL AND-
AND DYLAN'S BACK
IN TOWN.
HE'S SINGLE,
HAS BEEN FOR AWHILE,
AND HE KNOWS
HE SCREWED UP.
PAIGE...
WHEN I SAY DYLAN
BROKE MY HEART,
I MEAN THAT HE TOOK IT,
FROZE IT,
HE THEN DROPPED IT
FROM THE CN TOWER,
AND RIPPED IT TO SHREDS,
OKAY?
OKAY.
ALL I'M SAYING,
IF YOU'RE SO READY
TO MOVE ON,
THEN WHY AREN'T YOU
DOING IT?
MRS. VAN ZANDT:
LIBERTY, CAN WE TALK TO YOU?
LIBERTY:
THIS IS EXACTLY WHY I PUT
THE SCHEDULE ON THE FRIDGE.
HOME BY 5:00,
CHEMISTRY UNTIL 7:00,
TUTORING UNTIL 8:00.
IT'S IMPORTANT.
MORE IMPORTANT THAN
MR. ELLIS' CHEM EXAM?
YEAH.
I DOUBT THAT.
THE ADOPTIVE PARENTS
PHONED TODAY.
THEY'RE MOVING
TO SEATTLE.
BUT NO,
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
WE HAVE AN OPEN ADOPTION.
WELL, LEGALLY,
THE BABY IS THEIRS.
THEY HAVE THE RIGHT
TO MOVE.
AND MY RIGHTS?
OH YEAH,
I GAVE THOSE UP.
THEY ASKED IF YOU'D LIKE
TO SEE HIM ONCE MORE
BEFORE THEY LEAVE.
TO SAY GOODBYE.
I SAID GOODBYE
WHEN I GAVE HIM UP.
HAZEL:
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M STANDING IN LINE
FOR SOMETHING OTHER
THAN LIBRARY BOOKS.
PAIGE:
I CAN'T BELIEVE MY BRAIN
IS WORKING WELL ENOUGH
FOR ME TO EVEN SPEAK ENGLISH.
TIM:
HEY!
THIS IS REALLY EXCITING.
I MEAN, I'VE NEVER BEEN
TO A GAY CLUB BEFORE.
HAVE YOU?
HEY! YEAH.
YEAH,
I CAME HERE ONCE WITH...
HEY, LOOK,
THE LINE IS MOVING.
LET'S...
OKAY.
LIBERTY:
SO, UPPER CANADA
BECAUSE IT'S UP
THE ST. LAWRENCE RIVER;
LOWER QUEBEC
BECAUSE IT'S AT THE END.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
ALL RIGHT, PIZZA!
YOU EACH OWE ME
EIGHT BUCKS.
SO, THAT'S HISTORY.
WHAT NEXT?
BIOLOGY?
CAN I ASK YOU
SOMETHING PERSONAL?
SURE.
I'M ALL EARS.
IT'S ABOUT YOUR BABY.
DID YOU EVER CONSIDER
KEEPING HIM?
LIKE WHEN YOU HELD HIM.
WAS IT HARD
TO LET HIM GO?
GET OUT!
I'M SORRY.
I'M ADOPTED.
IT'S JUST SOMETHING
I ALWAYS WONDERED.
GET OUT!
I MEAN IT.
I DON'T CARE
IF YOU WERE ADOPTED,
DROPPED BY A STORK
OR ABDUCTED BY ALIENS.
GET OUT!
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
HEY, OKAY.
SO YOU WERE BUSY
TELLING ME
HOW MUCH YOU LIVE
FOR THE OSCARS.
I LIVE AND DIE FOR THEM.
MARCO:
OH MAN, ME TOO.
SO QUIZ ME.
OKAY UM...
BEST SUPPORTING ACTRESS,
1994.
UH...UH...
OH, DIANNE WIEST,
"BULLETS OVER BROADWAY".
DESPITE UMA THURMAN'S
OUTSTANDING PERFORMANCE
IN "PULP FICTION".
PERFORMANCE IN
"PULP FICTION", I KNOW.
HEY TIM,
I'M GONNA BE RIGHT BACK,
OKAY?
OKAY.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
DID PAIGE
PUT YOU UP TO THIS?
NO. I DID.
JUST HEAR ME OUT.
I MISS US.
I MISS YOU.
YOU'RE CUTE,
YOU'RE SMART,
AND YOU'RE FUNNY.
AND I MADE A HUGE
MISTAKE.
YEAH.
YOU DID MISTAKE, DYLAN,
TONIGHT.
COMING HERE.
I'M WITH TIM NOW.
HE'S MY BOYFRIEND.
UM...
SORRY FOR INTERRUPTING,
BUT I WAS JUST GONNA GO
GET SOME MORE WATER AND-
ELLIE:
OKAY, SO...
JANE EYRE, WHICH I FINISHED
READING AN HOUR AGO -
DON'T GET IT.
MARCO:
OKAY, THINK OF IT THIS WAY.
I'M ROCHESTER-
OF COURSE.
YEAH.
TIM IS JANE EYRE
YOU KNOW, BECAUSE HE'S SIMPLE,
SWEET,
AND UNCOMPLICATED.
AND DYLAN
IS CRAZY BERTHA,
LOCKED AWAY
IN THE ATTIC.
OKAY,
IT'S ABOUT MOVING ON
AND PUTTING THE PAST
BEHIND YOU,
WITH THE RIGHT PEOPLE.
JUST THINK OF IT
LIKE SALVATION.
(PHONE RINGS)
HOLD UP.
MUST BE ANOTHER EMAIL
FROM TIM.
OKAY, THAT THING
IS ONE STEP AWAY
FROM YOU BECOMING
AN ANDROID.
IT'S FROM DYLAN.
WE ARE THROUGH!
OVER!
SO DON'T SEND ME
STUPID LITTLE EMAILS.
YOU CAME ALL THE WAY
TO MY PLACE
TO TELL ME
NOT TO EMAIL YOU?
RIGHT.
THIS IS
SO NOT OVER,
NOT EVEN CLOSE.
WHY NOW? HUH?
WHAT IS WITH
THE STALKER ROUTINE?
WHY? YOU JUST HAPPEN TO BE HOME
FOR THE SUMMER?
YOU DON'T GET IT,
DO YOU?
I'M HOME FOR THE SUMMER
BECAUSE OF YOU.
I STILL LOVE YOU,
MARCO.
MARCO:
DON'T.
DON'T CALL ME.
DON'T TEXT ME.
DON'T EMAIL ME.
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT ME.
LEAVE ME ALONE.
ALL RIGHT GUYS,
TIME'S UP.
PASS 'EM IN.
I DIDN'T EVEN
FINISH THE EXAM.
HOW DID YOU GET IT DONE
SO QUICKLY?
MAYBE BECAUSE
I NEVER STARTED.
HEY...
HI.
SO I KNOW YOU ONLY
HAVE ONE MORE EXAM LEFT,
AND I SHOULD HAVE GIVEN THIS
TO YOU BEFORE,
BUT...
MARCO:
OH... (CHUCKLES)
WOW. THANKS.
GOOD LUCK
NEVER GOES OUT OF STYLE.
KWAN:
TIME'S UP, EVERYONE.
HAND THEM IN.
AND CONGRATS,
EXAMS ARE DONE!
I'M SO TIRED,
I THINK I MIGHT HAVE ANSWERED
THE SECOND ESSAY QUESTION
WITH WHITE STRIPES LYRICS.
(MARCO LAUGHS)
SO WHAT DO YOU SAY
TO A LITTLE RYAN REYNOLDS
MOVIE FIESTA TONIGHT?
OH YES,
I AM SO IN.
OH BUT... TIM.
I KINDA PROMISED HIM
A DATE.
OH. UM...
WELL, BRING HIM.
WE'LL GIVE HIM
A GOOD GOING OVER.
MAKE SURE HE'S GOOD ENOUGH
FOR OUR MARCO.
AND THE SATAN CHILD?
HOCKEY PRACTICE.
SO?
SO, I'LL BRING THE CHIPS.
GOOD. SEE YOU.
COOL.
IT WAS ONE STUPID EXAM.
WORTH 30 PERCENT
OF YOUR GRADE.
SO?
YOU DON'T CARE?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND YOU.
THIS ISN'T THE GIRL
I KNOW.
MRS. VAN ZANDT:
HAROLD, STOP.
DANNY:
DEREK AND I ARE SUPPOSED TO BE
STUDYING HERE TONIGHT, DAD.
AND YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
AT A PLAY, REMEMBER?
MM-HM.
THIS ISN'T OVER.
WE WON'T BE LATE.
DANNY:
I APPRECIATE YOU BEING
THE DEMON SEED
AND TAKING THE HEAT OFF ME,
BUT I HAVE A REPUTATION
TO UPHOLD.
FEMALE ANATOMY 101.
TO ALBERT EINSTEIN!
(COUGHS)
DAD DOESN'T KNOW
WHO I AM ANYMORE,
SO LET'S REALLY MESS
WITH HIS MIND.
PAIGE:
OKAY, DON'T FREAK.
DYLAN PROMISED HE'D BE
OUT OF HERE BY NOW.
MARCO:
WHAT?
(GROANS)
PAIGE...
PAIGE:
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
WE'LL BE WATCHING
IN THE BASEMENT ANYWAYS.
COME ON,
EVERYONE'S DOWNSTAIRS.
ANTOINE,
BEFORE YOU GO, MAN.
CHECK OUT MY TATTOO.
DUDE!
THAT'S AWESOME.
TIM:
UM...
MARCO, WHAT ABOUT THAT RYAN
REYNOLDS MOVIE FIESTA
THAT YOU PROMISED?
YEAH. YEAH.
LET'S GO. COOL.
HOCKEY PRACTICE IS CANCELLED.
WHY DON'T YOU GUYS JOIN ME
FOR A LITTLE POKER?
TEXAS HOLD 'EM?
NO THANKS.
I THINK WE'RE GONNA PASS
ON THAT ONE.
I FIGURED
YOU'D WIMP OUT.
EXCUSE ME?
COME ON, MARCO,
WHO'RE YOU KIDDING?
YOU'RE ALWAYS
"PLAYING IT SAFE".
YOU'RE WAY TOO CHICKEN
TO GAMBLE.
REALLY?
WHAT'S THE BUY-IN?
(SLURRING)
AND HERE'S TO DRESSING ME
IN OVERALLS
UNTIL GRADE NINE.
UH, YOU MIGHT WANNA
PACE YOURSELF.
YEAH. WELL,
I THINK THAT YOU THINK...
THAT I THINK
THAT YOU THINK...
ATTENTION.
SOFTWARE GLITCH.
DEREK:
I THINK...
YOU'VE HAD ENOUGH.
LIBERTY:
(STRUGGLING)
LET GO! LET GO!
(MIRROR SHATTERS)
OH NO.
NO, NO, NO.
MOM AND DAD
ARE GONNA KILL ME.
I'M A STUPID, USELESS,
MESSED UP...
LIBERTY, IT'S A MIRROR.
YOUR FACE DIDN'T BREAK IT
THIS TIME,
SO WHY SO UPSET?
BECAUSE MY BABY IS GONE.
HE'S GONE ACROSS THE COUNTRY
AND I ABANDONED HIM.
DEREK:
I NEVER GOT TO MEET
MY BIRTH-MOTHER.
NOT SURE I EVER WILL.
SHE COULDN'T TAKE CARE OF ME,
SO SHE MADE SURE I ENDED UP
IN A FAMILY THAT COULD.
I KNOW IT WAS HARD
FOR HER TO DO.
HOW DO YOU KNOW
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED?
DEREK:
SHE TOLD ME.
I MEAN, IN A LETTER.
SHE GAVE ME A SORT
OF TREASURE CHEST.
I SEE YOUR TWO
AND RAISE FOUR.
SEE YOU BACK.
BY RAISING TEN?
TIM!
I'M SORRY,
THEY WERE ALL MESSY.
DYLAN:
UH!
BET'S ON THE TABLE.
ALL... IN.
MARCO, MAYBE
YOU SHOULD FOLD.
YOU SURE YOU WANT
TO DO THAT, DEL ROSSI?
PRETTY RECKLESS.
THAT'S WHAT BEING RECKLESS
IS ALL ABOUT, MY FRIEND.
JUST DOING,
NOT THINKING.
HURTING WHOEVER YOU WANT
IN THE PROCESS.
WHAT THE HELL
IS YOUR PROBLEM?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
I WANT TO KNOW
WHY YOU HURT ME?
HOW?!
HOW YOU COULD JUST HURT ME
LIKE THAT, DYLAN?!
I...
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I'VE APOLOGIZED
AND I'VE TRIED
TO MAKE THINGS BETTER.
SO I'M NOT GONNA KEEP
BEATING MYSELF UP
JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE STUCK.
OH,
I'M NOT STUCK.
YOU ARE.
DATE TIM,
PLAY IT SAFE.
DATE A BUNCH OF GUYS.
THAT DOESN'T CHANGE
THE FACT
THAT EVERYTHING COMES DOWN
TO YOU AND ME.
EVERYTHING.
TIM:
DYLAN'S CRAZY.
I MEAN, WHAT HE SAID
WAS TOTALLY OUT OF LINE.
I MEAN,
'CAUSE YOU KNOW,
WE'RE GOOD FOR EACH OTHER,
RIGHT?
TIM, YOU'RE GREAT.
OH, YOU'RE PERFECT,
ACTUALLY.
AND I'M-
HEY LOOK, I'M REALLY PROUD
OF ALL THE STEPS
YOU'VE TAKEN THIS YEAR.
WELL,
IT'S ALL BECAUSE OF YOU.
AND I'M THINKING THAT,
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE GONNA BE
AWAY NEXT YEAR BUT...
I'LL CAN COME VISIT.
AND I'VE GOT
A BUS SCHEDULE,
AND I'VE MAPPED OUT
SOME TIMES-
TIM!
I...I WANTED TO MOVE ON.
YOU AND I,
WE CONNECTED BUT...
MARCO, I GET HOW DIFFICULT
THESE THINGS CAN BE,
AND HOW MUCH DYLAN
MEANT TO YOU.
THAT'S EXACTLY THE POINT.
TIM, HE STILL DOES.
YOU USED ME.
NO.
NO. NO.
I WOULDN'T DO THAT.
I'M REALLY SORRY.
GO BACK TO YOUR STUPID,
LYING, CHEATING EX.
'CAUSE YOU KNOW WHAT,
MARCO?
YOU ARE PERFECT FOR HIM.
DEREK:
SO YOU'RE BOTH GROUNDED
FOR A MONTH?
DANNY:
AND I DIDN'T EVEN GET TO SEE
LIBERTY PUKE HER GUTS OUT.
JUST WHAT EVERY KID
NEEDS TO KNOW:
THE INNER WORKINGS
OF DEGRASSI.
DEREK:
WELL, IT'S A PART OF YOU,
RIGHT?
JT:
HERE IT IS,
ISSUE NUMBER ONE
OF "THE CRIMSON KID".
A COMIC BOOK, JT?
YEAH.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW MUCH THAT'S WORTH?
IT'S MY MOST VALUABLE
POSSESSION,
AND I WANT HIM TO HAVE IT.
WELL, I'D LIKE IT
IF BOTH OF YOU
PUT SOMETHING IN AS WELL.
I WANT THE BABY TO KNOW
HE HAD LOTS OF GOOD PEOPLE
THINKING OF HIM.
DYLAN, IF YOU EVER
HURT ME AGAIN, I...
I WON'T.
HEY, EVEN IDIOTS GROW UP
AT SOME POINT.
I'M A SLOB.
OKAY?
I'M RECKLESS.
AND I'M YOUR EXACT OPPOSITE.
BUT YOU MEAN EVERYTHING
TO ME, MARCO,
AND I WANT
ANOTHER CHANCE.
OH,
YOU ARE SUCH A JERK.
WHAT? I...