ALEX:
YOU COULD BE IN ONE OF THESE
UNIVERSITY GUIDES.
EVERYBODY IN HERE
LOOKS SO HAPPY.
SAY IT
IN YOUR SQUEAKY VOICE.
(SQUEAKY VOICE)
EVERYBODY LOOKS SO HAPPY.
(PAIGE CHUCKLES)
I'M BORED.
MAYBE I SHOULD
EAT SOMETHING.
20 UNIVERSITIES
AND COLLEGES
ARE COMING TO DEGRASSI
ON WEDNESDAY.
SO?
LOOK,
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
YOU'RE APPLYING TO BANTING -
WORRY ABOUT CHOOSING
THE RIGHT SUV
FOLLOWING GRADUATION.
ALEX...
OH...
UM... WANT TO TAKE
MY SHIFT TOMORROW?
I NEED THE MONEY.
WANT TO KNOW WHY?
MATT'S BACK.
NOW SAY IT
IN YOUR SQUEAKY VOICE.
PAIGE:
HE CALLED ME LAST NIGHT.
ALL OUT-OF-THE-BLUE.
BY THIS TIME TOMORROW?
MATT AND I WILL BE REUNITED.
RESUMING QUEL GRAND ROMANCE.
ALEX:
GREAT.
NOW I'M BORED,
NAUSEOUS AND IRRITATED -
ALL AT THE SAME TIME.
WELL, I'M JUST
PLAIN OL' HAPPY.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
JT: (CLEARS THROAT)
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
YOUR NEW PRESIDENT.
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
MARCO:
LOOKS LIKE LIBERTY
WON SCHOOL PRESIDENT.
WAS THERE AN ELECTION?
THERE WAS AN ACCLAMATION.
AND NO, YOU DIDN'T
MISS ANYTHING.
SO MATT'S BACK TONIGHT.
MMM...
MINI HOORAY.
NOW BACK TO ME.
LOOK, I NEED TO DECIDE
MY FUTURE
OVER MY LUNCH
OF CABBAGE ROLLS.
APPLY TO BANTING.
BANTING IS FOR RICH KIDS
AND FREAKISH
GENIUS-SAVANTS.
DID YOU SIGN-UP FOR THOSE
COLLEGE INFO SESSIONS TOMORROW?
WHY DO YOU DRONE ON
ABOUT ME GOING TO COLLEGE?
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT
TO COME BACK FOR THE REUNION
TO FIND OUT MY FORMER
FRIENDS ARE LOSERS.
THE SIGN-UP SHEET'S
IN GUIDANCE. GO.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
PERINO:
SO PRIME MINISTER TRUDEAU
HAD TWO CHOICES.
HE COULD EITHER BRING IN
MARTIAL LAW,
OR LET THE QUEBEC RIOTS
ESCALATE.
HE CHOSE THE FIRST.
WHY?
IS ANYBODY PAYING
ATTENTION ANYMORE?
PAIGE?
UM...
HE HAD TO DO WHAT WAS BEST
FOR THE COUNTRY.
SOUNDS LIKE YOU,
PAIGE.
SOMETHING TO SHARE,
ALEX?
PAIGE LIKES TO DECIDE
WHAT'S BEST FOR PEOPLE, SIR,
AND JAM IT
DOWN THEIR THROATS.
OH...
WHAT IS YOUR PROBLEM?
YOUR JUDGMENTAL SELF.
ALEX? SHUT UP.
PERINO:
OKAY.
I'M NOW GOING TO BRING IN
MARTIAL LAW.
YOU CAN WORK THIS OUT LATER -
IN DETENTION.
NO. NO, NO, NO, SIR.
NOT TODAY.
SIR, YOU CAN POSTPONE
DETENTION FOR WORK, RIGHT?
I HAVE TO WORK TONIGHT.
PAIGE:
AND I HAVE A DATE!
A BEYOND LIFE-CHANGING DATE!
SIR?
SIR!
OH... (SIGHS)
(COACH BLOWS WHISTLE)
JIMMY:
OKAY GUYS,
BRING IT IN. LET'S GO!
HUSTLE. LET'S GO!
WHAT'S GOING ON, GUYS?
I'M JIMMY BROOKS,
ASSISTANT COACH,
AND I'LL BE WATCHING YOU
SHOOT TODAY.
WHY?
SO I CAN HELP YOU GET BETTER.
LOOK, I'VE PLAYED FOR THIS TEAM
THREE YEARS IN A ROW.
TEAM CAPTAIN
EACH AND EVERY ONE,
EXCEPT FOR LAST YEAR.
YOU'RE THE GUY
THAT GOT SHOT.
JIMMY:
UH, MOST PLAYERS
MAKE THE MISTAKE
OF NOT SETTING THEIR FEET
BEFORE THEY SHOOT.
NOT LIKE THIS, RIGHT?
OKAY, YOU SET YOUR FEET -
THAT'S COOL -
BUT YOU'RE NOT USING
YOUR LEGS.
SO?
THE POWER FROM YOUR SHOT
COMES FROM YOUR LEGS,
NOT THE HANDS.
THE HANDS JUST GUIDE THE BALL.
CAN YOU MENTALLY WILL
THIS THING TO GO FASTER?
I'VE TRIED.
ALL WEEK I'VE TRIED.
SIMPSON:
GOT A MINUTE?
OH YEAH,
YOU'VE GOT 30.
(LAUGHS)
I'VE BEEN SAVING
THAT ONE.
UM... LOOK, PAIGE,
YOU LISTED YOUR TOP THREE
CHOICES FOR UNIVERSITY
BANTING, BANTING, BANTING.
IT'S GOOD TO AIM HIGH,
SIR.
YOU'VE AIMED
FOR THE HIGHEST.
WELL, THE BUSINESS PROGRAM
I'M APPLYING FOR
IT'S EXTREMELY SELECTIVE.
ONLY 30 APPLICANTS
ACCEPTED ANNUALLY.
ALL THE MORE REASON
FOR A PLAN B.
KEEP A SECRET?
MY MOM'S
BESTEST GIRLFRIEND,
SHE'S HEAD OF ADMISSIONS.
WELL,
IT SOUNDS LIKE YOU GOT
YOUR WHOLE LIFE PLANNED OUT,
PAIGE.
I KNOW WHAT'S BEST
FOR ME.
NOW, SIR,
I SNIPED AT ALEX
IN CLASS;
HE DISTRIBUTED
MANNY SANTOS'S BREASTS
THROUGH THE SCHOOL
ELECTRONICALLY.
I DON'T BELONG HERE.
FAR BE IT FOR ME
TO STAND IN THE WAY
OF YOUR PERFECT LIFE.
HEY, IF SHE GETS TO GO,
CAN I?
ISN'T THIS YOUR FIRST
OF FIVE WEEKS DETENTION?
YEAH,
MS. HATZILAKOS -
OH, I MEAN, YOUR MOMMY -
WOULD SAY NO.
♪♪♪
THESE KIDS, HAZE,
I DO NOT KNOW WHERE
THEY LEARNED TO SHOOT,
BUT THEY'RE GONNA HAVE ME
BUSY ALL YEAR.
WELL, THEY COULDN'T HAVE
A BETTER COACH,
COACH BROOKS.
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
DEREK:
LESS POWER ON THAT BALL.
FASTER ON THOSE CROSS-OVERS.
ALL THE COACHES OUT THERE
AND THEY GIVE US A CRIPPLE?
COME ON, MAN.
THANK YOU.
♪♪♪
PAIGE.
(LAUGHS)
SORRY ABOUT THE BAG.
I DIDN'T GET A CHANCE
TO GO HOME.
CAME STRAIGHT
FROM THE AIRPORT.
I-I LIKE THAT
I'M YOUR FIRST STOP.
YOU'RE SCRATCHY.
OH YEAH,
THE BEARD.
AND YOUR HAIR...
YEAH, IT'S NOT HEALTHY
TO WASH IT TOO MUCH.
SOMETHING I LEARNED
THIS SUMMER.
OKAY, HERE.
PRESENTS DON'T HAVE TO WAIT
UNTIL AFTER DESSERT.
OH... IT'S A...
IT'S AN ORGANIZER.
YOU SAID YOUR LIFE
WAS CHAOS.
YEAH,
I WASN'T COMPLAINING.
MATT,
I'M APPLYING TO BANTING.
BANTING? WOW.
THAT'S AIMING
FOR THE STARS.
YEAH.
AND ONCE I GRADUATE
FROM BUSINESS SCHOOL,
I'LL BE ABLE
TO AIM EVEN HIGHER.
EVERYBODY WHO GRADUATES
FROM THERE DOES WELL.
AND I WAS THINKING THAT,
WITH ME MOVING TO KINGSTON
FOR SCHOOL...
MAYBE YOU'D CONSIDER
MOVING, TOO?
UH... I KNOW YOU WANT
THIS WHOLE...
BIG MONEY
EXECUTIVE THING,
AND THAT'S-THAT'S GREAT...
FOR YOU.
BUT MY LIFE'S
JUST NOT SET.
I'M RE-EVALUATING THINGS.
YOU'LL FIGURE IT OUT.
WHAT?
LIKE YOU'VE FIGURED IT OUT?
I MEAN, PAIGE LIKE...
YOU ALWAYS HAVE THE ANSWERS,
BUT YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
THE QUESTIONS.
I HAVE A BUDDY
IN VANCOUVER...
WHO SAYS THAT HE CAN GET ME
A JOB PAINTING HOUSES.
SO WHEN WILL I SEE YOU?
DO I GET TO SEE YOU?
YOU KNOW,
I-I FEEL LIKE SUCH A JERK.
YOU GOT ME A PRESENT
AND I DIDN'T...
BRING YOU BACK ANYTHING.
HERE.
YOU'RE DUMPING ME?
AND GIVING ME DRUGS?
PAIGE, I CAN'T BE EXPECTED
TO SIGN UP FOR THIS BORING,
ROUTINIZED LIFE
YOU'VE GOT LAID OUT.
I DON'T EXPECT ANYTHING,
MATT.
I WAS HOPING
THAT YOU WOULD WANT
TO BE WITH ME,
THAT'S ALL.
PAIGE, I...
COME ON, PAIGE.
PAIGE: (SIGHS)
THE MOST HUMILIATING PART?
AFTERWARDS.
"THE PUBLIC TRANSIT
RIDE-OF-SHAME."
BUS?
YOU COULDN'T TAKE A CAB?
OH, WHY BE
HYSTERICALLY EMOTIONAL
IN FRONT
OF ONE CABDRIVER
WHEN YOU'VE GOT
THE ENTIRE TTC?
WOW. LOOK, I HAVE TO GET
TO A SEMINAR
FOR UNIVERSITY
IN NUNAVIT.
MARCO,
COME TO BANTING.
YOU'RE GOING
TO BE OKAY?
YOUR FACE IS PUFFIER
THAN USUAL.
DOES THAT
ANSWER YOUR QUESTION?
SO YOUR DATE
DIDN'T GO WELL?
AREN'T YOU GOING
THE WRONG WAY?
COLLEGES YOU WANT TO SPEAK
TO ARE INSIDE.
I'M NOT TALKING
TO ANY COLLEGES.
FINE.
TAKE IT.
IT'S A PRESENT.
YOU'RE PULLING OUT
A JOINT?
ON THE FRONT STEPS
OF DEGRASSI?
HOW VERY UN-YOU
OF YOU.
WOULD YOU GO
IF YOU'RE STONED?
I'LL GO
IF YOU'RE STONED.
MY CLOTHES AREN'T GONNA SMELL,
AREN'T THEY?
OR MY HAIR?
OOH, 'CAUSE YOU KNOW,
SOMETIMES IN MOVIES,
CHARACTERS EYES
LIKE GLOSS OVER
AND THEY START TO NOD
THEIR HEAD A LOT.
YOU'RE NODDING.
SO IT'S TRUE?
IT DOES SUCK -
MATT DUMPING YOU.
♪♪♪
UNIVERSITY REP:
HAVE YOU THOUGHT OF SUDBURY
AS A POTENTIAL
POST SECONDARY SCHOOL?
HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT SUDBURY
AS A POTENTIAL
POST SECONDARY SCHOOL?
(LAUGHING)
LET'S ROCK AND ROLL.
UNIVERSITY REP:
WE HAVE A STATE-OF-THE-ART
CAMPUS,
GREAT FACILITIES,
GREAT LIBRARY,
POOL...
(LAUGHING)
OUR UNIVERSITY HAS AN
INTERNATIONAL REPUTATION
FOR EXCELLENCE
IN ACADEMICS.
BUT OUT ROOT STRENGTH
LIES IN OUR PASSION
FOR TEACHING OUR STUDENTS
HOW TO BECOME LEADERS
AND INNOVATORS.
TODAY, WE'RE GOING TO DISCUSS
OUR 10 WORLD CLASS FACULTIES
AND THEIR ADMISSION
REQUIREMENTS.
DEREK,
I WANNA TALK TO YOU.
YEAH, WHAT'S UP?
GOT SOME MORE
POINTERS TO SHARE?
TEACH ME HOW TO JUMP?
WHOA! EASY.
WHAT MAKES YOU SO ARROGANT?
YOU THINK YOU'RE
BETTER THAN ME?
WHAT?
ANSWER MY QUESTION.
DUDE,
BACK OFF, NOW.
MAKE ME.
WHAT'S WRONG,
YOU SCARED?
YEAH, I'M SCARED.
I'M SCARED OF HURTING
A CRIPPLE.
ARMSTRONG:
HEY!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
HE STARTED IT.
I'M IN A WHEELCHAIR!
ARMSTRONG:
WELL, WHATEVER HAPPENED,
IT'S OVER.
I'LL SEE YOU TWO
AT PRACTICE.
HOW ARE ALL THESE PEOPLE
SUPPOSED TO AFFORD
UNIVERSITY OR COLLEGE?
LOTS AND LOTS
OF STUDENT LOANS.
WHAT IF YOUR
ONLY COLLATERAL
IS YOUR MOTHER'S
WELFARE CHEQUE?
THE POINT IS TO PAY BACK
THE LOAN
AFTER YOU GRADUATE.
YEAH, RIGHT.
OFF MY WELFARE CHECK.
(LAUGHS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
SO I'M APPLYING TO BANTING.
WHAT?
(HAPPY SQUEALS)
WHAT CHANGED YOUR MIND?
MARCO:
I WANT TO DO SOCIAL-
SIMPSON:
PAIGE?!
I'LL CONFESS,
WHEN YOU SAID YOU HAD
A FAMILY FRIEND AT BANTING,
I DID NOT
BELIEVE YOU.
SHE'S HERE?
SIMPSON:
WELL, SHE'S LEAVING,
BUT I SAID I COME GET YOU
BEFORE SHE GOES.
SHE'LL BE IN
THE RESOURCE CENTRE.
ALEX:
PAIGE, PAIGE!
THIS PERSON -
SHE'S A FAMILY FRIEND?
YES.
WHICH MEANS...
NOT ONLY AM I GONNA
LOSE OUT ON BANTING,
BUT...
MY PARENTS ARE GOING
TO FIND OUT
I'M A POTHEAD,
TOO.
BLOW IT OFF.
I CAN'T JUST-
JUST BLOW IT OFF.
IT'S REMARKABLY EASY.
MY ENTIRE FUTURE
DEPENDS ON THIS.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND YOU.
BECAUSE YOU DON'T
HAVE A FUTURE.
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
SIMPSON:
(KNOCKING) PAIGE?
HAVE A GOOD INTERVIEW,
PAIGE.
JIMMY:
OKAY GENTLEMEN,
BRING IT IN FOR ME, PLEASE.
OKAY, YOU CAN'T WIN
WITHOUT FUNDAMENTALS,
SO TODAY, WE'RE GONNA WORK
ON OUR THREE-POINT SHOOTING.
OKAY.
GIVE ME THE BALL.
SUPERSTAR.
THAT'S HOW YOU SHOOT
A THREE-POINT SHOT.
DEREK:
REALLY.
'CAUSE THIS IS
HOW I DO IT.
SO...
WHAT DID YOU THINK?
I THINK IT'S TIME
TO TAKE YOU TO SCHOOL.
GIVE ME THE BALL.
LET'S SEE
WHAT YOU GOT.
HANDLE YOUR BUSINESS.
IT WAS EASY.
BYE, BYE.
TEAM:
OOH, YEAH!
I GOT THIS.
TEAM:
(LAUGHS) YOU SUCK.
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU JUST GOT BEAT
BY A CRIPPLE.
UH, MS. MYERS?
ELIZABETH? LIZ?
PAIGE, HEY.
SO, YOU WANT TO COME
TO BANTING.
THAT'S PRETTY EXCITING.
UH...
YEAH, IT IS UM...
EXCITING.
PRETTY.
MAYBE WE CAN FINALLY
GET YOUR MOTHER UP
FOR REGULAR VISITS,
HUH?
DEFINITELY.
LOTS AND LOTS OF MOM.
SO THIS FAIR...
DID YOU FIND IT
AT ALL HELPFUL?
NOT REALLY.
YOU DIDN'T FIND
ANY OF THE UNIVERSITIES HERE
INTERESTING?
INTERESTING.
THAT'S AN INTERESTING
QUESTION.
WERE THEY INTERESTING?
WOW...
WHO'S TO SAY?
WHY BANTING?
WELL, YOU'RE THE-
THE HARVARD OF THE NORTH.
I MEAN, NOT YOU,
MS. MYERS.
ELIZABETH. LIZ.
BUT BANTING,
I MEAN.
ELIZABETH:
BANTING HAS A CACHE, YES.
BUT WHAT ALSO ATTRACTS YOU
TO OUR UNIVERSITY?
WELL...
IT'S VERY GREEN.
SORRY, PAIGE,
I FEEL I HAVE
TO ASK YOU THIS.
WHY DO YOU WANT TO PURSUE
A CAREER IN BUSINESS?
I HAVE ABSOLUTELY NO IDEA.
AND I AM SO HIGH.
(LAUGHING)
DEREK:
WHOA! DUDE, STOP!
WAS THAT A FLUKE?
PLEASE, TELL ME
THAT WAS A FLUKE.
ARE WE TALKING
ABOUT ME
SINKING IT
FROM THE TEN SECOND LINE?
AND NOT JUST THAT.
FOUR - IN A ROW.
FROM A CHAIR,
WITH NO JUMP.
TRY 12.
I'VE DONE 12 IN A ROW
FROM A CHAIR
WITH NO JUMP.
LOOK, YOU GOTTA
TEACH ME THAT.
COME ON.
OKAY.
BUT WHEN YOU'RE SHOWING OFF
FOR YOUR FRIENDS -
AND I KNOW YOU WILL -
TELL THEM YOU LEARNED IT
FROM YOUR COACH,
NOT THE GUY
WHO GOT SHOT.
YOU GOT IT.
STIR THE POPCORN
AND DON'T TALK TO ME.
IF IT'S ANY COMPENSATION,
MY MOM'S BESTEST FRIEND
IS ALSO HER INFORMANT.
AND I'M GROUNDED
UNTIL I DIE.
OR GO TO UNIVERSITY.
YOUR PARTY TO CELEBRATE
MY DEMISE
CAN COMMENCE NOW.
WHAT HAPPENED TO
THE YOU-NOT-TALKING IDEA I HAD?
I WAS A TOAD TO YOU.
A WARTY, BUMPY,
GREEN-SKINNED
HORNY TOAD.
BUT YOU WERE RIGHT.
NO, I WASN'T.
I'M NOT.
ALEX.
PAIGE, I DON'T HAVE
A FUTURE, OKAY?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHERE
I'M SLEEPING TONIGHT.
THE WAY MY MOM
AND HER STUPID BOYFRIEND FIGHT,
I MIGHT BE AT HOME
OR I MIGHT BE
AT A WOMEN'S SHELTER.
SO HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO PLAN
FOR SOMETHING LIKE
UNIVERSITY?
NO.
I'M WEARING THIS
THE REST OF MY LIFE.
YOU'RE NOT.
ODDS ARE I AM.
WELL, GOOD TO KNOW.
THAT'S TWO OF US
WHO ARE SCARED.