(MUFFLED THUMP OF MUSIC)
(DOOR BANGS SHUT)
HEY.
GOT YOUR CALL,
SO... HERE I AM.
WHAT'S UP, STOCKBOY?
GOT SOMETHING TO TELL ME?
YEAH, I HEARD UH...
I HEARD "CLOWN ACADEMY'S"
AWESOME.
YOU MIGHT WANT
TO CHECK IT OUT.
YEAH.
THANKS FOR
THE MOVIE TIP.
WHY DID YOU REALLY
CALL ME HERE?
THIS IS THE GUY
YOU TOLD ME ABOUT?
YOU TOLD HIM
ABOUT ME?
JUST SHOW AARON
WHAT YOU GOT
BEFORE HE LOSES
HIS TEMPER.
OXYCODONE.
SWEET.
YOU DID GOOD.
$800.00
WOW,
I KINDA NEED MORE.
HERE'S ANOTHER $400 -
TOWARDS YOUR NEXT SCORE.
ADMINISTRATION FEE.
SO THERE YOU GO,
STOCKBOY.
THERE'S YOUR FIRST
DRUG DEAL.
(VOMITS AND COUGHS)
CROWD:
(CHUCKLING)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
TOBY:
SHOWER MASSAGER, HELLO!
AND A GREAT VIEW
OF THE YOGA STUDIO
ACROSS THE STREET.
MAN,
THOSE HONEYS ARE FLEXIBLE.
FIRST AND LAST.
I DON'T KNOW, KID.
I GET THE FEELING
I COULD BE TAKING
A REAL BIG RISK HERE.
BUT YOU'RE NOT,
OKAY?
MY GIRLFRIEND AND I
WE'RE VERY QUIET,
WE'RE VERY RESPONSIBLE-
LANDLORD:
VERY PREGNANT.
ARE YOU SURE YOU TWO
CAN AFFORD THIS PLACE?
RAISING KIDS
AIN'T CHEAP.
YES, I'M AWARE, SIR,
BUT I'M ALL OVER IT.
I'VE-I'VE GOT
A GOOD REALLY JOB.
ALL RIGHT.
WELCOME TO THE BUILDING.
(BABY CRYING)
FEVER STILL UP?
EAR INFECTION,
THE SEQUEL.
I CAN DROP YOU OFF.
(BABY WALES)
YOU SURE YOU'RE OKAY TO DRIVE
ON TWO HOURS SLEEP?
I'M ON A FIRST-NAME BASIS
AT THE HOSPITAL.
I COULD GET THERE
WITH MY EYES CLOSED.
DINNER IS-
MEATLESS MEATLOAF MONDAY,
AS USUAL.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU GO AHEAD.
I'LL BIKE, ALL RIGHT?
CRAIG:
BYE GUYS.
SIMPSON:
NOW THIS MUST BE
JEREMIAH MOTORS'S
FAVOURITE NEW CLIENT.
DIANE BOUGHT A CAR
AND THE SALESMAN
WAS A NO-CHARGE OPTION.
(WEAK CHUCKLE)
I'M ARCH- SNAKE.
SO YOU'RE
THE NOTORIOUS SNAKE.
STILL TEARING UP THIS PLACE
LIKE YOU AND JOEY USED TO?
UH SADLY, NO.
I'VE BECOME ONE OF THE TEACHER
I USED TO GAVE HEADACHES TO.
HEY, HOP IN.
WE'RE HITTIN' THE OPEN ROAD.
TOP DOWN, WIND BLOWING
THROUGH OUR... YOU KNOW.
I GOTTA PUNCH THE CLOCK.
JOEY:
JUST AROUND THE BLOCK,
SNAKE.
BE SPONTANEOUS.
JOEY, IN MY LIFE SPONTANEOUS
IS A FOUR-LETTER WORD.
MY FRIEND,
YOU GOTTA LEARN HOW TO LIVE.
DO SOMETHING FOR YOURSELF.
YOU DESERVE TO.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
ALL RIGHT.
CIAO!
TELL ME YOU'RE NOT JOKING.
I'M DEADLY SERIOUS.
LET THE DAYS OF SINFUL
COHABITATION BEGIN.
TWO DAYS AGO
WE COULDN'T AFFORD THIS.
WHAT'S THE CATCH?
I UH...
I TALKED TO MY GRANDMA
AND SHE'S LOANING ME
THE MONEY.
THE WAY SHE HANDLED
THE PREGNANCY NEWS,
I'M SURPRISED.
WELL, IT TOOK A LOT
OF PERSUADING
AND SHERRY.
JT, THAT'S AMAZING!
SO WHEN DO WE MOVE IN?
AS SOON AS WE TELL
YOUR PARENTS.
I WAS HOPING WE COULD SKIP
THAT STEP.
BUT WE HAVE TO TELL THEM,
LIKE TODAY.
MRS. VAN ZANDT:
EXCUSE ME?
YOU'RE DOING WHAT?
LIBERTY:
I'M MOVING IN WITH JT.
WHY WOULD YOU
WANT TO DO THAT?
SO YOU CAN-
SO YOU CAN BE WITH HIM?
I HAVE A NAME, SIR.
I WASN'T TALKING TO YOU.
WELL, YOU WILL BE,
OKAY?
BECAUSE I'M THE FATHER
OF YOUR FIRST GRANDCHILD.
MRS. VAN ZANDT:
(SQUEALS)
MOM, DAD,
PLEASE TRY NOT
TO BE ANGRY.
(LAUGHS)
WE'LL TAKE CARE
OF EVERYTHING -
OURSELVES,
THE BABY.
EVERYTHING.
DAD,
PLEASE SAY SOMETHING.
WHAT WOULD YOU
LIKE ME TO SAY?
THAT I'M HAPPY?
THAT I'M PROUD OF YOU?
I KNOW. I'M STUPID.
SO STUPID.
MR. VAN ZANDT:
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT,
LIBERTY.
IT'S THE FAULT OF THAT FOOL
STANDING BESIDE YOU.
STOP IT, DAD.
OKAY,
JT'S BEEN AMAZING.
HE'S TAKING GOOD
CARE OF US.
MRS. VAN ZANDT:
LIBERTY, YOU'RE OUR DAUGHTER,
AND WE'LL HELP YOU
ANYWAY WE CAN.
WHICH IS WHY WE CAN'T ALLOW
YOU TO MOVE OUT.
WE NEED YOU HERE
TO HELP YOU THROUGH THIS -
AS A FAMILY.
I GET IT,
YOU WANT JT
OUT OF THE PICTURE.
I NEVER WANT TO SEE HIM HERE
AS LONG AS I LIVE!
WELL, THAT'S UNFORTUNATE.
BECAUSE JT'S
NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
JT, LET'S START PACKING.
♪♪♪
LOOKS LIKE SNAKE
SHED HIS OLD SKIN.
DON'T MAKE ME THINK
ABOUT HIS SKIN.
SO THAT MUST BE
YOUR SPORT BIKE
PARKED IN THE LOADING ZONE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
BOLD NEW LOOK
FOR THE SCHOOL?
SOMEWHERE VALENTINO ROSSI
IS WALKING AROUND
IN HIS UNDERWEAR.
GRAZIE.
NO IDEA WHO THAT IS.
MOTO GP WORLD CHAMPION.
AH, I GATHER
THIS IS A NEW HOBBY?
YES, IT IS.
BUT I HAVE TO ADMIT
I HAD NO IDEA YOU WERE
A MOTORCYCLE FAN.
YEAH...
ROCK ON, MS. H.
JUST MOVE THE MOTORCYCLE.
PRONTO.
LIBERTY:
EXCUSE ME, SIR.
BY WHOM MUST ONE
BECOME IMPREGNATED
IN ORDER TO RECEIVE
SOME SERVICE?
NOT IN THE MOOD
FOR PITHY BANTER?
NOT SINCE I REALIZED
I'LL BE SPENDING EVERY WAKING
MOMENT HERE
IF WE'RE GONNA LIVE
TOGETHER.
WELL, ON AVERAGE,
A BABY GOES THROUGH
TEN DIAPERS A DAY.
THIS JOB'S WORTH IT
FOR THE EMPLOYEE DISCOUNT.
MR. MCKAY:
JT.
WE SEEM TO BE MISSING
SOMETHING.
I DIDN'T SEE ANYTHING.
NO ONE'S BEEN BACK THERE.
HONEST.
YOU DON'T THINK SOMETHING'S
BEEN STOLEN, RIGHT?
NO. I DIDN'T SAY
ANYTHING'S BEEN STOLEN.
RIGHT. WELL...
I JUST GUESSED
BASED ON YOUR
WORRIED EXPRESSION.
WELL, WE'RE MISSING
A GREAT DEAL OF OXYCODONE.
IT'S A POWERFUL DRUG,
SO YOU CAN UNDERSTAND
MY CONCERN.
YUP.
YEAH, IT'S-IT'S TOTALLY
UNDERSTANDABLE.
SEE OR HEAR ANYTHING,
YOU TELL ME,
HUH?
WHAT'S THE MOST IMPORTANT
ELEMENT OF A RELATIONSHIP?
I DON'T KNOW.
LOVE?
HONESTY.
SO TELL ME,
HONESTLY,
THE MISSING DRUGS
AND THE APARTMENT -
NO RELATION?
I JUST THOUGHT
IT WAS A GOOD IDEA.
YOU STUPID, THOUGHTLESS,
IMBECILE!
YOU WILL DESTROY EVERYTHING.
OW! STOP!
YOU COULD GO TO JAIL.
YES, THAT THOUGHT
CROSSED MY MIND.
THEN WHY DID YOU DO IT?
WE NEEDED THE MONEY,
OKAY? BAD.
LOOK, I'LL JUST-
I'LL GET SOME CASH
AND I'LL BUY THE DRUGS
BACK FROM THE DEALER.
AND THEN I'LL GIVE THE DRUGS
BACK TO THE PHARMACY.
AND EVERYTHING WILL BE FINE,
OKAY?
HONEST.
WAY TO GET MY HOPES UP.
TOBY:
COME ON FIT.
IT'S FOR CHARITY!
JT:
LIBERTY MADE IT LOOK SO EASY.
TOBY:
REMIND ME NOT TO TAKE ANYTHING
ELSE OFF HER PLATE.
IS THE LAST PARAGRAPH
OF AN ARTICLE REALLY NECESSARY?
I COULD SHOW YOU
A TRICK OR TWO
FOR A PRICE.
ANYTHING. NAME IT.
$1200 DOLLARS,
TODAY.
(CHUCKLING)
I'LL PASS.
TOBY, I'M SERIOUS.
OKAY, WELL,
GET THE MONEY BACK
FROM YOUR LANDLORD.
I ALREADY TRIED,
OKAY?
IT'S NON-REFUNDABLE.
LOOK, TO GET THE RENT MONEY,
I HAD TO DO SOMETHING - BAD.
AND NOW I NEED TO UNDO IT,
OR I'M IN TROUBLE.
TOBY:
OKAY, FINE.
BUT WHERE AM I SUPPOSED
TO GET $1200 TODAY?
DON'T YOU HAVE BONDS
OR SOMETHING?
(LAUGHS)
ARE YOU CRAZY?
IF I TOUCH THOSE BONDS
MY MOM GOES BANANAS.
JUST SCREW IT, OKAY?
I NEED HELP!
OF A MENTAL VARIETY.
TOBY,
I'M ASKING YOU NICELY.
I NEED THAT MONEY.
JT, YOU NEED TO LET GO.
NOW.
SEE? THIS IS WHY
YOU HAVE NO FRIENDS.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
GET AWAY FROM ME!
STAY AWAY.
SIMPSON:
HARD TO BELIEVE
THAT JACK IS ASLEEP
AND WE'RE ALL SITTING DOWN
TOGETHER, HUH?
PLEASANT SURPRISE,
ACTUALLY.
TALK ABOUT SURPRISES!
WHAT ABOUT THE JAW-DROPPING
ARRIVAL
YOUR HUBBY MADE
AT SCHOOL YESTERDAY?
SPIKE:
EXCUSE ME?
WHAT DID HE DO?
POP A WHEELIE
ON HIS BICYCLE?
YOU DIDN'T KNOW?
EMMA? BEANS?
DIDN'T KNOW WHAT?
SOMEONE FILL ME IN HERE.
OH UH...
JOEY HAS A FRIEND
WHO'S SELLING A MOTORCYCLE.
LOANED IT OUT TO ME
FOR A FEW DAYS
TO TRY IT OUT.
YOU'RE BUYING
A MOTORCYCLE?
WITH WHAT -
COUCH TREASURE COINS?
I WAS GOING
TO TALK TO YOU.
YOU WILL.
LATER.
I CUT YOU SOME SLACK,
STOCKBOY.
BUT I'M RUNNING LOW
ON PATIENCE.
WELL, THAT MAKES YOU
A PRETTY BAD DOCTOR THEN,
DOESN'T IT?
HA HA.
SPEAKING OF DOCTORS,
AARON IS CONSIDERING
SENDING YOU TO ONE.
SO YOU MIGHT WANNA
QUIT WITH THE JOKES.
I GAVE YOU AN ADVANCE.
WHICH I NEVER SHOULD
HAVE ASKED FOR, OKAY?
I'M GONNA GET YOU
ALL OF YOUR MONEY BACK.
REALLY?
YEAH, BUT I JUST NEED YOU
TO GIVE ME THE DRUGS BACK -
ASAP -
SO THAT I CAN GIVE THEM BACK
TO THE PHARMACY.
(NERVOUS LAUGH)
DUDE, DON'T.
THAT'S IN CASE
YOU DIDN'T KNOW...
I RUN THE SHOW.
AND I DON'T WANT
MY MONEY BACK.
I WANT MORE DRUGS.
I'LL GO TO THE COPS.
AND WHAT?
WHAT, YOU GONNA GET YOURSELF
THROWN IN JAIL
FOR STEALING DRUGS?
THAT'S A SMART MOVE.
JT, JUST GET THE MAN
WHAT HE WANTS.
THIS WILL ALL BE OVER.
MR. MCKAY:
HEY! COME BACK HERE!
JT, CALL SECURITY.
I CAUGHT THIS SHOPLIFTER
RED-HANDED.
YEAH, SURE.
SURE THING.
HOW WORRIED
SHOULD I BE?
I'LL DRIVE CAREFULLY.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
IS THIS THE START
OF YOUR MIDLIFE CRISIS?
AH, "THE TALK".
SPIKE, IT IS A MEANS
OF TRANSPORTATION.
IT DOESN'T MEAN ANYTHING.
THEN WHY ALL THE CLOAK
AND DAGGER?
LOOK, DAY IN, DAY OUT,
I'M MR. STRAIGHT
AND NARROW, OKAY?
IT'S WORK, FAMILY.
WORK, FAMILY.
IT'S JUST SO PREDICTABLE,
HUH?
SORRY IF WE'RE CRAMPING
YOUR STYLE.
HEY, I'M HAPPY TO MAKE
SACRIFICES FOR YOU
AND FOR THE KIDS,
THERE HAS TO BE MORE TO LIFE
THAN ROUTINE.
TELL ME WE HAVE NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
I WISH I COULD.
WE'LL GO TO MY PARENTS.
WE'LL GET THEIR HELP.
MY DAD'S A LAWYER.
I DON'T NEED A LAWYER.
I NEED A SUPERHERO
TO KEEP A DRUG DEALER
FROM KILLING ME.
WHAT DRUG DEALER?
THE GENTLEMAN WHO FINANCED
OUR APARTMENT.
HE MADE ME STEAL AGAIN.
AGAIN?
BUT MR. MCKAY WAS
ALREADY SUSPICIOUS!
HE'LL CATCH YOU!
MAYBE NOT, OKAY?
MAYBE MR. MCKAY
WON'T NOTICE.
AND MAYBE I'LL TOTALLY
GET AWAY WITH IT.
AND MAYBE WE'LL BE FINE.
I THOUGHT
YOU'D CHANGED.
YOU'D GROWN UP.
LIBERTY,
I HAVE CHANGED.
YEAH.
NOW YOU'RE A DRUG DEALER.
JT:
HERE.
NOW GO RUIN SOMEONE
ELSE'S LIFE.
WHAT?!
ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND!
HUH?!
HEY, EASY.
EASY.
I GOT HIM.
I GOT HIM!
YOU GOT ME INTO THIS.
YEAH, AND I JUST
SAVED YOUR BUTT.
OR WERE YOU TWO GUYS
GOING TO KISS?
NOT THAT IT'S ANY
OF MY BUSINESS
WHAT TEAM YOU PLAY FOR.
JUST ASK THE GIRL
WHO'S CARRYING MY KID.
UH-OH.
BUN IN THE OVEN.
YEAH.
AND THANKS TO THESE,
I'M DEAD TO HER.
COME ON, MAN.
IT'LL BE OKAY.
IT'S OKAY?
I LOST MY GIRL.
I LOST MY BEST FRIEND.
I LOST MY JOB
AND MY FAMILY.
AND NOW I'M PROBABLY
GOING TO JAIL.
HEY, BUMMER TIMES.
LEAST THERE'S A PARTY.
WORKING LATE AGAIN?
NOT RIDING THAT BIKE
OUTSIDE,
ENJOYING THE LAST RAYS
OF SUNSHINE?
I'M GIVING IT BACK.
IT'S THAT OR THE WIFE.
MMM...
MY EX HAD A CHOICE ONCE:
ME OR THE INTERN.
SOME PEOPLE
MAKE YOU WONDER, HUH?
TOO BAD ABOUT THE BIKE.
IT REMINDS ME OF THE ONE
I USED TO OWN.
WOW.
TRYING TO WRAP MY HEAD
AROUND THE IDEA
OF YOU ON A SPORT BIKE.
WHY IS THAT SO HARD
TO FIGURE?
BECAUSE I'M A WOMAN?
BECAUSE YOU'RE MY PRINCIPAL.
WELL, I USED TO BE
A WILD CHILD IN MY DAY.
A LOT HAS CHANGED.
BUT I STILL LOVE MOTORCYLES.
AS A MATTER OF FACT...
I WAS GONNA ASK YOU
FOR A RIDE.
(MUSIC PLAYS)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
JAY:
HEY, CHECK IT OUT.
STOCKBOY'S GONNA BE A PAPPY.
AARON:
HEY CONGRATS, STUD.
THIS ONE'S ON ME.
(LAUGHING)
ACTUALLY, IT'S ON ME.
(LAUGHTER)
JAY:
HEY. HEY BUDDY!
HEY!
SOMEBODY GET THE CAR!
HE'S FAST,
HE'S FURIOUS,
HE'S COVERED
IN KEVLAR!
HEY SNAKE.
GOOD MORNING,
JOEY.
I GOING TO NEED TO TALK
TO THAT FRIEND OF YOURS;
ITS RIGHTFUL OWNER.
OH, DON'T YOU WANT TO SEE
HOW THE COOL-ECTOMY GOES
BEFORE YOU GIVE
THE SUIT BACK?
THAT WON'T BE NECESSARY.
THIS IS FOR THE KEVLAR
AND THE WHEELS
THAT GO WITH IT.
SNAKE...
THIS IS EXACTLY
WHAT YOU NEED.
MR. VAN ZANDT:
I SPOKE TO MR. MCKAY.
TRIED TO EXPLAIN
THE SITUATION.
WE'RE GOING TO TRY
TO WORK OUT A DEAL.
BUT DON'T HOLD YOUR BREATH.
THANKS, DAD.
MR. VAN ZANDT:
YEAH.
JT:
STOMACH PUMP ONE.
JT ZERO.
HOW CAN YOU MAKE
JOKES ABOUT THIS?
COUNSELING,
SUICIDE-WATCH?
BELIEVE ME,
IT'S NO JOKE.
WELL, I'M GLAD
YOU'RE GETTING HELP.
JT, DID YOU TRY
TO KILL YOURSELF?
(CRYING)
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
LEAVING ME ALONE
WITH ALL THIS?
I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY TOO.
LIBERTY,
I SCREWED UP, OKAY?
DON'T TAKE IT OUT
ON THE BABY.
WE BOTH SCREWED UP.
I'M GOING TO
THE ADOPTION AGENCY.
JT, IT'LL BE FOR THE BEST.
(CRYING)