TANYA KIM:
HEY, I'M TANYA KIM
FROM ETALK DAILY.
I'M HERE WITH KEVIN SMITH
AND HIS COSTAR JASON MEWES...
TELL ME
WHAT A GREAT GUY I AM,
'CAUSE I HAVE
TWO TICKETS
TO THE PARTY OF THE YEAR.
CHECK IT OUT.
WHO DID YOU
STEAL THOSE FROM?
I WAS INVITED.
I WORKED ON THE MOVIE,
REMEMBER?
AND I WAS GOING TO ASK YOU
TO BE MY PLUS ONE.
TOO BAD GOING WITH YOU
IS A MINUS 20.
LEXI...
'KAY,
LET'S RAISE HELL TOGETHER
LIKE WE USED TO,
HUH?
I'M GOING WITH
PAIGE MICHELCHUCK.
YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
THE QUEEN OF DEGRASSI
IS TAKING THE QUEEN
OF THE TRAILER PARK
TO THE PREMIERE?
I PREFER TO BE KNOWN AS
"QUEEN OF DON'T NEED JAY,
AND NEVER DID".
TANYA KIM:
HEY, ARE YOU GUYS HAPPY
TO BE BACK IN CANADA?
KEVIN SMITH:
I AM INSANELY HAPPY
TO BE BACK IN CANADA.
CANADA - THE MOTHER LAND;
TORONTO -
CRADLE OF CIVILIZATION.
TORONTO IS WHERE THEY HAVE
THAT POUTINE CRAP
THAT LUNCHBOX
LOVES SO MUCH.
REALLY SIR,
IN FRONT OF EVERYBODY.
JASON MEWES:
YO, YO LISTEN...
HE CHOSE A TORONTO PREMIERE
OVER L.A. PREMIERE
BASED ON FOOD.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
TANYA KIM:
(GIGGLING)
TORONTO IS WHERE
WE CAST THE FLICK;
WE SHOT THE FLICK.
KEVIN SMITH IS BEING
INTERVIEWED RIGHT THERE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
HE'S SAYING?
THAT TONIGHT WILL BE
THE GREATEST,
MOST MAGICAL
MOVIE PREMIERE EVER?
IT BETTER BE!
IT'S NOT EVERY NIGHT
WE GET TO HAVE
OUR PROFESSIONAL
ACTING DEBUT.
YEAH,
OR HAVE MY MUSIC FEATURED
IN BIG,
HOLLYWOOD MOVIE.
WHICH IS WHY WE'RE ALL
GOING FIRST CLASS TONIGHT.
I'M TALKING STRETCH LIMOS...
YOU GUYS GOT A LIMO?
DIBS ON STICKING MY HEAD
OUT THE SUN ROOF.
I AM COMING,
RIGHT PAIGE?
I'M SORRY, HON,
THEY ONLY GAVE ME
TWO TICKETS...
AND I'M TAKING HAZEL.
PLEASE, AS IF WE WERE
GOING TO BRING HER.
OUR LIMO'S
A SKANK-FREE ZONE.
DID YOU JUST SKANKIFY
MY FRIEND?
FRIEND?
MORE LIKE PET PROJECT.
JEALOUS MUCH?
NO.
I JUST DON'T GET WHY
YOU HANG OUT WITH HER.
FUNNY, I WAS JUST ASKING MYSELF
THE SAME THING ABOUT YOU.
ENJOY THE LIMO.
I'LL SEE YOU GUYS
AT THE MOVIE.
ALEX!
WAIT!
"YOU WANNA GO TO THE PREMIERE?"
YOU SAID THAT.
THAT'S AN INVITATION.
IT WAS REALLY MORE
OF AN OBSERVATION.
LIKE, "YOU WANNA GO
TO THE PREMIERE?"
I THOUGHT YOU WERE SERIOUS.
WHATEVER.
I'M OUTTA HERE.
I'M NOT STANDING
FOR YOUR WHOLE
I'M ALEX,
I'M-GONNA-IGNORE-
EVERYONE-FOR-A-WEEK ACT.
SO I WANTED TO GO TO A PREMIERE
ONCE IN MY LIFE.
CRUCIFY ME.
PETER:
GRAB A BOOK OR SOMETHING.
PEOPLE SEE US,
THEY'LL DEFINITELY
START TO WONDER.
PETER:
WHO CARES?
I HAVE TICKETS TO THE PARTY
OF THE YEAR.
THANK YOU, MOM.
(SIGHS)
I'M WARNING YOU.
MAJOR DEVASTATION
IF YOU LET ME DOWN.
WHAT IF I LET YOU
DOWN EASY?
I ALREADY HAVE A DATE...
WITH MY STEP-DAD.
MOM HAS TO STAY HOME
WITH MY LITTLE BROTHER.
THING IS,
MANNY'S IN THE MOVIE.
SHE'S GONNA BE THERE
SO...
YEAH. NO TALKING,
NO TOUCHING,
NO LOOKING
AT EACH OTHER.
I KNOW THE DRILL.
JUST BEING UNDER THE SAME ROOF
AS YOU TONIGHT
IS GONNA BE
ENOUGH FOR ME.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
(SIGHS)
KEVIN. JASON.
I'D LIKE YOU BOTH
TO MEET
ONE OF DEGRASSI'S
FINEST TEACHERS,
ARCHIE SIMPSON.
KEVIN:
RIGHT ON, SIR.
WOW. WOW.
I'M SUCH A BIG FAN.
YOU KNOW,
"JAY AND SILENT BOB
STRIKE BACK"
IS ONE OF
MY FAVOURITE MOVIES.
KEVIN:
THANKS MAN.
MR. SMITH?
KEVIN?
KEV.
AS I LIVE AND BREATHE,
PAIGE MICHALTON!
HOW ARE YOU?
UH...MICHALCHUK.
MICHALCHUK. YOU KNOW WHAT?
MY BAD.
WE JUST ALWAYS CALLED YOU
THE BUSTED LEG GIRL SO...
NOT ANYMORE.
THESE WILL BE THE LEAST
BROKENEST GAMS
ON YOUR RED CARPET!
I'M SORRY,
DID YOU JUST SAY GAMS?
WHAT 21ST CENTURY TEENAGER
STILL USES THE TERM GAMS?
THE KIND WHO NEEDS
ONE MORE TICKET
TO THE PREMIERE TONIGHT.
COULD YOU SPARE A TEENSY WEENSY
EXTRA GOLDEN TICKET, MR. SMITH?
PLEASE?
FOR MY FRIEND?
GOD, YOU'RE WORKING ME HARD,
AREN'T YOU?
JUST LIKE A WOMAN.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I HAPPEN TO HAVE
ONE OF THOSE
TEENSY WEENSY TICKETS
RIGHT HERE
AND IT COULD BE YOURS IF...
YOU SAY "ABOUT".
MR. SMITH...
COME ON,
YOU KNOW I LOVE IT.
LET ME HEAR IT.
ABOOT.
MMM. I MELT.
THAT'S JUST SO CUTE.
YOU EARNED THIS.
JUST DON'T LET ME SEE IT
UP ON EBAY,
OR ELSE I'M GOING TO CUT
YOU OUT OF THE SEQUEL, TOO.
I CAN'T THANK...
UM "TOO"?
YEAH.
PAIGE, UH...
WE HAD TO TRIM YOUR PART DOWN
A LITTLE BIT.
SO...
AND WHEN I SAY
A LITTLE BIT I MEAN...
COMPLETELY.
WAS I THAT BAD?!
AND UNAWARE
OF MY BADNESS?
NO, NO, HON.
YOU WERE GREAT.
BUT IT'S JUST IN THE COURSE
OF CUTTING A MOVIE
STUFF, YOU KNOW,
HITS THE EDITING ROOM FLOOR.
WHEN I WAS DOING
"JERSEY GIRL",
I CUT J-LO OUT OF HALF
THE MOVE.
AFFLECK, I WANTED
TO CUT HIM OUT ENTIRELY
BUT THEN THAT JUST WOULD'VE
LEFT THAT LITTLE KID,
YOU KNOW?
I DIDN'T SEE
"JERSEY GIRL".
REALLY.
WELL NOW I'M REALLY GLAD
THAT I CUT YOU OUT OF MY MOVIE.
I'M JUST KIDDING.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
PLEASE TELL ME YOU'RE STILL
GOING TO COME TO THE PREMIERE.
YEAH.
GOOD.
MARCO:
EVERYONE'S GOING TO BE THERE.
WHO DO YOU THINK'S
GOING TO BE THERE?
CRAIG:
YOU THINK SO?
DO YOU THINK ALANIS
IS GOING TO BE THERE?
HERE.
AND BRING A GUEST.
KEVIN CUT ME OUT
OF THE MOVIE.
HENCE, I'M NOT GOING.
SO WHAT, YOU'RE JUST
GONNA SIT AT HOME?
I WAS THINKING OF LYING,
ACTUALLY...
IN BED,
WITH ICE CREAM.
UH-UH.
YOU'RE GOING.
THIS ISN'T DEBATABLE.
PAIGE, IT'S NOT LIKE ACTRESS
IS PART OF YOUR TEN-YEAR-PLAN.
NEITHER IS HUMILIATION.
ME AND YOU ARE HITTING
THAT RED CARPET TONIGHT,
AND WE'RE GONNA MAKE KEVIN
SO REGRET CUTTING YOU
OUT OF THAT FILM
'CAUSE WE ARE GOING
TO LOOK HOT.
AND I DON'T MEAN UP-DO,
PEARLS, PINK PROM DRESS HOT.
I MEAN "HOT" HOT.
(ROCK MUSIC BEGINS)
♪♪♪
AND YOU CUT HER
OUT OF THE MOVIE.
JACKASS.
SIMPSON:
HEY, JUST IN CASE
YOU DIDN'T KNOW,
YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL
TONIGHT, EM.
FEMALE ANNOUNCER:
THIS ACTRESS WAS 19
WHEN SHE GOT
HER FIRST NOMINATION
FOR BEST ACTRESS
IN A FEATURE FILM.
WHO WAS SHE?
SO THIS IS THE PART
WHEN EVERYONE GETS TO SEE ME
CUT FROM THE MOVIE.
THIS IS THE PART WHERE
YOU SIT BACK AND ENJOY
BEING HERE WITH ME.
(MOVIE MUSIC BEGINS)
YOU BOYS ARE
TOO BLOODY STUPID
TO MAKE THE GRADE DOWN
IN THE STATES
AND YOUR LAST HOPE
IS THE SCHOOL SYSTEM
OF THE GREAT WHITE NORTH,
EH?
YOU WANT TO GET OOT
OF GRADE 12?
YOU BETTER START
LEARNING
WHAT THE METRIC SYSTEM'S
ALL ABOOT!
AUDIENCE:
(CHUCKLING)
JASON:
I'VE GOT THREE
WORDS FOR YOU:
GOT TO...
SIR!
THERE WILL BE NO MORE
CUSS WORDS OUT OT YOU
YOU POTTY-MOUTHED,
MALLRAT.
YOU'RE GONNA LEARN
THE DUAL LANGUAGES
OF MY HOME A NATIVE LAND,
AND YOU'RE GONNA SAVOUR
MY POUTINE!
'CAUSE YOU'RE IN CANADA NOW,
EH?
(CHUCKLING)
JAY, WHEN I WAS BORN,
STAR WARS HAD ALREADY BEEN OUT
ON VIDEO FOR TEN WHOLE YEARS.
YOU'RE TOO OLD.
EVEN THOUGH THERE'S LAWS
TO PREVENT IT,
I'M GOING TO MARRY APPOLONIA.
SHE'S THE SUGAR
IN MY MAPLE;
CHEESE IN MY POUTINE;
THE BACK IN MY BACON.
THE "ICK"
IN PATHETIC.
(APPLAUSE)
ALEX:
WHO KNEW MANNY COULD
ACTUALLY ACT?
AND CRAIG'S SONG?
FULL-ON ROCKED.
PAIGE:
YOU'RE SOUNDING
SUSPICIOUSLY UPBEAT.
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE OKAY?
ALEX:
IT'S A HOLLYWOOD PREMIERE!
SUE ME FOR GETTING
CAUGHT UP IN IT.
WELL, THE ONLY THING
I'M CATCHING
IS A CAB RIDE HOME
FOR MY HOT DATE
WITH BEN AND JERRY.
ALEX:
WHAT KIND OF FRIEND
WOULD I BE
IF I LET YOU BAIL
ON THE HOTTEST PARTY EVER?
THIS IS THE AFTER PARTY?
THIS IS
THE KIDDIE VERSION.
THE REAL PARTY
IS THROUGH THOSE DOORS.
AND IT'S INVITATION-ONLY,
STRICTLY VIP.
ALEX:
AND SO ABOUT TO BE CRASHED.
YOU REALLY THINK
HE'S GONNA LET YOU IN?
TOBY:
I'M A CLOSE,
PERSONAL FRIEND OF KEVIN,
AND IF HE FINDS OUT
THAT YOU DIDN'T LET US IN?
YOU'RE GOING TO BE
IN BIG TROUBLE, PAL.
HUGE!
UH...
I CAN MOVE MYSELF.
THANKS.
HEY. YOU WERE GREAT
IN THE MOVIE.
YEAH.
ALL FIVE LINES.
WELL, THEY WERE
A GREAT FIVE LINES.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
IT'S VODKA.
I'LL ONLY POUR HALF.
DON'T.
IF YOU GET CAUGHT,
YOU'LL BE STUCK
IN DETENTION FOR WEEKS
AND THEN I'LL NEVER
GET TO SEE YOU.
WELL, YOU CAN
SEE ME TONIGHT.
MAYBE SOME PLACE QUIET
AND SECLUDED?
THEATRE LOBBY.
30 MINUTES.
MANNY!
HEY...
EMMA:
YOU WERE AMAZING!
REALLY?
YOU THINK SO?
DID YOU STAY UNTIL THE END
TO HEAR CRAIG'S SONG?
EMMA:
OF COURSE!
LET'S TOAST TO DEGRASSI'S
CELEBRITY COUPLE!
I DID MAKEUP ON THE MOVIE.
DO YOU MIND IF I CUT THROUGH?
NICE TRY, GIRLIE.
SORRY I'M LATE.
SOME JERK BLOCKED ME IN
AT THE STRIP CLUB, AGAIN.
THE SIGN CLEARLY SAYS
"EMPLOYEE PARKING ONLY".
OH, SWEETIE,
I HOPE YOU DIDN'T
TIRE YOURSELF OUT AT WORK.
YOU PROMISED ME
SOME HOT DANCING.
ALL RIGHT,
IN YOU GO.
MARCO:
WHAT?!
PAIGE:
I CAN'T BELIEVE THE BOUNCER
ACTUALLY FELL FOR THAT!
ARE YOU KIDDING?
WE'RE A COUPLE
OF HOT CHICKS.
OF COURSE HE WAS GONNA
FALL FOR THAT.
JAY:
LADIES.
EW, VIP DOES NOT STAND
FOR VASTLY ICKY POSER.
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
THAT'S MY BOY MICKEY
RIGHT THERE. HEY.
HE WORKED SECURITY
ON THE MOVIE.
WELL, I SAW YOUR LITTLE
GIRL-ON-GIRL PDA.
IS THAT WHY YOU DUMPED ME?
ALEX:
RIGHT.
IT HAD NOTHING TO DO
WITH YOU HOOKING UP
WITH EVERY SKANK
IN THE RAVINE.
AH... AND YOU'RE TRYING
TO GET BACK AT ME
BY HOOKING UP
WITH EVERY SKANK HERE.
YOU DO NOT CALL HER THAT,
EVER.
PAIGE, WOULD YOU LIKE
TO DANCE WITH ME?
LOVE TO.
REMIND ME TO TELL YOU
HOW MUCH I LIKE
YOUR NAUGHTY SIDE.
CONSIDER YOURSELF
REMINDED.
(VACUUM STARTS)
LET'S GO.
(SOUND OF SOMEONE KISSING)
THERE'S SOMEBODY
IN HERE WITH US.
♪♪♪
THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE!
THEY'RE UPSTAGING US
AT OUR OWN PREMIERE,
THESE CHICKS.
WHY AREN'T YOU AND I
OUT THERE,
DOING SOME KINDA EROTICALLY
CHARGED DANCE ROUTINE?
WE CAN, MAN.
LET'S DO IT!
IT WAS A RHETORICAL
QUESTION.
DUDE, DON'T CALL 'EM
RHETORICAL,
THAT'S MEAN.
YOU'RE RHETORICAL.
I NEED TO GO IN THERE
AND FACE THEM.
PETER:
DON'T.
HE'S MARRIED
TO MY MOTHER
AND HE'S IN THE THEATRE
NECKING WITH YOURS.
RUNNING IN THERE
WON'T FIX ANYTHING.
HOW WOULD YOU KNOW?
I JUST DO, OKAY?
YOU DON'T WANT TO DO ANYTHING
TILL YOU'VE CALMED DOWN.
YOU'LL REGRET IT.
BELIEVE ME.
I HAVE TO GO.
EVER FEEL DRUNK
WITHOUT DRINKING?
IS THAT WHY YOUR
SHOES WENT AWOL?
THEY WERE PINCHY.
I'M GONNA GET
SOME WATER.
I'LL GO GET YOU SOME.
HI!
SO, THIS NEW LESBIAN THING
YOU GOT GOING ON...
I LIKE TO WATCH.
I LIKE TO PUNCH.
DREAM ON.
LEXI...
LEXI, COME ON.
WHY WEREN'T YOU
THIS ADVENTUROUS
WHILE WE WERE DATING,
HUH?
WE COULD'VE HAD FUN.
YOU'RE DISGUSTING.
OH, AND YOU?
PUTTING ON A SHOW
FOR EVERYONE?
(CHUCKLES)
YOU KNOW,
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
TONIGHT IS ABOUT YOU,
ANYWAYS?
IT'S NOT.
IT'S ABOUT HER.
HERE.
THANK YOU.
LET ME WALK
YOU HOME.
BUT MY SHOES!
BAREFOOT SUITS YOU.
AND BESIDES,
MY PLACE IS ON THE WAY.
MY MOM AND HER BOYFRIEND
ARE HOME
SO JUST WAIT
BY THE DOOR.
OH, BUT I'M THIRSTY.
CAN'T I JUST GET
A DRINK OF WATER?
NO.
I'M GRABBING SHOES
AND THEN WE'RE OUTTA HERE,
IMMEDIATELY.
EMILY:
LEXI?
HEY.
WHO'S YOUR FRIEND?
ALEX:
NEVERMIND, MOM.
JUST GRABBING SHOES.
HI, MS. NUNEZ.
I'M PAIGE.
PAIGE...
THE PAIGE?
I FEEL LIKE I'M IN
THE PRESENCE OF ROYALTY.
YOU KNOW THAT LEXI
NEVER STOPS TALKING
ABOUT YOU!
PAIGE:
REALLY? LITTLE OL' ME?
MOM, WHERE'S CHAD?
OH, HE PASSED OUT
HOURS AGO.
COME SIT.
CAN I GET YOU SOMETHING,
DARLING?
PAIGE:
YEAH. DIET ANYTHING, PLEASE.
ALEX:
PAIGE, WE HAVE TO GO.
WOULD YOU HOLD
YOUR HORSES, LEXI,
AND JUST LET THE GIRL
SIT AWHILE!
BE A GOOD HOSTESS
AND GET HER A DRINK, EH.
LOOKS LIKE THE PARTY'S JUST
GETTING STARTED, MS. NUNEZ.
PLEASE,
CALL ME EMILY.
EMILY.
OKAY.
SO WHAT WAS LEXI LIKE
AS A GIRL?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I CAN'T REMEMBER.
(LAUGHING)
I'M KIDDING.
LEX, I'M KIDDING.
I'M JUST KIDDING,
HON.
EMMA,
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I'M MAKING TEA
AGAIN.
AND CRYING AGAIN.
I LEFT SOMETHING
IN THE THEATRE,
SO I WENT BACK IN
TO GET IT
AND THAT'S WHEN I SAW
YOU AND HER.
MS. HATZILAKOS.
WHAT?
WE-WE WERE JUST TALKING.
SNAKE,
I SAW YOU KISS HER.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
IT JUST SORT OF HAPPENED,
YOU KNOW.
IT WAS SUCH A MISTAKE.
SO YOU STICK YOUR TONGUE
DOWN THE PRINCIPAL'S THROAT
BY ACCIDENT?
EMMA, QUIET PLEASE.
YOU GONNA WAKE YOUR MOM.
BUT WHY?
DID YOU THINK
IT WOULD BE FUN?
DID YOU GET TO THE PARTY
AND WANT TO ACT LIKE
A TEENAGER AGAIN?
JUST GIVE ME A REASON, DAD.
PLEASE.
HAVE YOU EVER DONE SOMETHING
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO
WITH SOMEONE YOU WEREN'T
SUPPOSED TO BE WITH?
EMMA, I'M SO ASHAMED.
I WON'T BLAME YOU
IF YOU NEVER WANT
TO SPEAK TO ME AGAIN.
IT'S NOT ABOUT ME.
IT'S ABOUT MOM,
AND WHETHER I'M GONNA
TELL HER WHAT I SAW.
YOUR MOM GO TO BED?
ALEX:
YEAH.
SHE SAID TO SAY GOODNIGHT.
SHE'S NICE.
LIKE MOTHER,
LIKE DAUGHTER.
TONIGHT WAS GOOD.
YOU'RE MY LUCKY CHARM.
PAIGE?
ABOUT BEFORE...
WHEN WE WERE DANCING?
WHAT ABOUT IT?
WE WERE JUST HAVING FUN.
NO BIG DEAL,
RIGHT?
EMILY:
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
YOU SPENT IT ALL?!
CHAD:
I MEAN I SPENT IT ALL!
EMILY:
WHAT? HOW COULD YOU
BE SO STUPID, CHAD?!
I'M WALKING YOU
HOME NOW. GO!
CHAD:
DON'T EVER CALL ME STUPID!
EMILY:
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
CHAD:
THAT'S IT,
I'M OUT OF HERE!
CHAD, NO!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?!
ALEX:
WILL YOU STOP IT?!
WILL YOU HOLD STILL?
I'M TRYING TO HELP.
BEING HERE
IN YOUR ROOM,
THIS HELPS.
IT'S QUIET.
NO SCREAMING,
NO SMASHING.
NOBODY SHOULD HAVE TO DEAL
WITH DRAMA
OF THE SHOVED-OVER-
THE-END TABLE VARIETY,
DAY IN, DAY OUT.
EVEN ME?
ESPECIALLY YOU.
PAIGE,
I'M IN TROUBLE.
THIS ISN'T RELATED
TO ANY TABLE COLLISIONS
THAT HAPPENED TONIGHT.
IT'S A DIFFERENT
KIND OF TROUBLE.
UM...
OKAY, UH...
SPEAKING OF TROUBLE UH...
OR NOT TROUBLE UM...
UH YOU...
YOU SHOULD TAKE MY BED,
AND I'M GONNA-
I'M GONNA SLEEP DOWNSTAIRS
ON THE COUCH.
PAIGE?
NIGHTY-NIGHT THEN!