MARCO:
OKAY, SO...
THEN THE RED LIGHTS,
THEY COME UP,
HITTING DARCY
STAGE LEFT.
GOT IT.
RED LIGHTS,
PAIGE LEFT.
RED LIGHT,
DARCY LEF-
I'M SORRY.
MY-MY MIND IS JUST
PREOCCUPIED THIS MORNING.
WHAT? HOT DATE
WITH DARCY LAST NIGHT,
AFTER THAT BIZARRE
YET STRANGELY MOVING
RE-VIRGINIZING CEREMONY?
DEPENDS.
WOULD YOU DEFINE "HOT DATE"
AS BRUTAL FIGHT
AND BREAK UP?
NO, I WOULDN'T.
YOU OKAY?
LAST NIGHT,
AFTER THE BREAK UP...
I KISSED SOMEBODY.
SOMEBODY WHO WASN'T DARCY.
HEY, GUYS.
HEY STAGE.
PAIGE.
UH HON, I'D THINK YOU'D
KNOW MY NAME BY NOW.
I MEAN, REALLY.
SPINNER:
OF COURSE I KNOW
YOUR NAME, PAIGE.
I KNOW TONS ABOUT YOU.
I KNOW YOUR BIRTHDAY,
I KNOW YOUR FAVOURITE FOOD,
I KNOW- OOPH!
(HARD IMPACT)
TAKE IT FROM SOMEONE
WHO KNOWS, SPIN.
TOKING BEFORE SCHOOL
ENDS IN TRAGEDY.
HEY! IT WASN'T YOU
AND PAIGE, WAS IT?
SPINNER:
DARCY?
TAKE ME BACK.
I'M SORRY FOR BEING
SUCH A JEALOUS FREAK,
BUT I'M OVER IT.
MALE STUDENT:
(WHISTLES) WOO HOO!
JUST CONSIDER IT.
CONSIDER ME.
(EXHALES)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
HAZEL:
SO IF YOU AND ALEX WANT TO,
A BUNCH OF GIRLS
ARE GOING FOR FONDUE.
NICE OF YOU TO ASK,
BUT UH, ALEX ISN'T
SO "FOND-UE" OF ME.
WE BROKE UP.
PAIGE...
IT'S OKAY.
I MEAN,
I CARE ABOUT HER TONS,
BUT WE WERE
SO NOT RIGHT.
BESIDES,
LAST NIGHT, I UM...
I MIGHT'VE MADE OUT
WITH SPINNER...
A LITTLE BIT.
SPINNER?
BUT I JUST GOT USED TO YOU
BEING A LESBIAN!
THIS ISN'T ABOUT YOU,
IT'S ABOUT ME.
AND RIGHT NOW I'M ABOUT
BEING FREE TO DATE
WHO I WANT TO DATE -
GIRL OR BOY.
YEARBOOK, TOBY?
AND BTW,
WHAT YOU HEAR
AT YEARBOOK TABLE?
STAYS AT YEARBOOK TABLE.
JUST SO YOU KNOW,
I TOTALLY SUPPORT YOUR FREEDOM
TO DATE WHOMEVER.
AND BTW,
TOTALLY AVAILABLE.
(MOUTHS "CALL ME")
(LAUGHS)
JIMMY:
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME.
THE GHOST
OF ASHLEY KERWIN!
HOW YOU DOIN'?
I'M NO GHOST.
I'M THE REAL THING!
YOU LOOK GREAT.
SO YOU'RE HERE.
AH, DID YOU FINALLY
GET TIRED OF LONDON OR...?
I COULD NEVER GET TIRED
OF LONDON.
MM, YOU KNOW, BUT I GOT TIRED
OF MISSING HOME.
TRIED SOME SCHOOLS THERE,
BUT COULDN'T FIND ANYTHING
QUITE LIKE THIS.
YEAH, GUESS IT'S,
IT'S KINDA HARD TO FIND
A SCHOOL WITH...
SUCH A UNIQUE COMBO
OF SHOOTINGS
AND GONORRHEA OUTBREAKS.
(LAUGHS)
OKAY, YEAH, SOME BAD
STUFF'S HAPPENED HERE.
BUT THERE'S SOME GOOD
PEOPLE HERE TOO,
LIKE JIMMY BROOKS.
OH, WELL,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
BUT DON'T GET USED TO HIM
BECAUSE I'M GONNA BE
OUTTIE NEXT YEAR,
HOPEFULLY.
MM, THAT'S TOO BAD.
I WAS KINDA HOPING WE COULD
BE CLASSMATES AGAIN.
I WAS TALKING
TO MS. HATZILAKOS
ABOUT MAYBE COMING BACK
NEXT YEAR.
MS. KERWIN'S BACK
IN TOWN.
HEY!
HEY, JIMMY,
SHE'S ALL YOURS.
OKAY. UM, WE GOTTA
CATCH UP LATER.
OKAY?
SO, I HAVE TO CONGRATULATE YOU,
JIMMY.
YOU'VE PUT A LOT OF WORK
IN THIS YEAR.
WELL,
THANK YOU, MS. H.
LIKE COACH SAYS,
YOU KNOW, IT'S IMPORTANT
TO BE MOTIVATED
AND (SIGHS) I WAS
DEFINITELY MOTIVATED.
MM HMM.
JIMMY:
IT'S REALLY-
IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT FOR ME
TO GRADUATE THIS YEAR.
AND UH, I KNOW I MISSED
A LOT OF SCHOOL FOR PHYSIO,
BUT I FIGURED
THERE WAS SOME WAY
YOU COULD SWING THIS.
I'M SORRY, JIMMY.
YOU SIMPLY DON'T
HAVE THE CREDITS.
I CAN'T WORK MIRACLES.
SPINNER:
HEY, LOOKS LIKE YOU COULD
USE A HAND.
JIMMY:
I'M FINE, THANKS.
I SAID, I'M FINE.
THANK YOU.
JUST WANTED TO HELP,
MAN.
JIMMY:
YOU WANNA HELP ME?
WHY DON'T YOU TRANSFER
TO ANOTHER SCHOOL
SO I DON'T HAVE TO SEE
YOUR STUPID FACE NEXT YEAR.
THAT WOULD HELP -
A LITTLE BIT.
WHAT IS YOUR DAMAGE, MAN?
MY DAMAGE, MAN,
IS YOU, GAVIN!
MARCO:
HEY! WHOA! RELAX! CHILL!
CAN'T WE JUST GET THROUGH
THE REST OF THE YEAR
WITHOUT ANYMORE DRAMA?
ASK HIM THAT.
(SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER
AND P.A. SYSTEM)
ASHLEY:
(GIGGLING)
ELLIE:
ASH?
SOME BEST FRIEND!
YOU COULDN'T HAVE EMAILED?
WHAT AND RUIN
THE SURPRISE?
YOU LOOK AMAZING, EL.
LIKEWISE.
WHO ELSE GOT TO
SEE YOU SO FAR?
MOST OF THE OLD GANG:
JIMMY. PAIGE, HAZEL.
NO SIGN OF CRAIG,
THOUGH.
HE'S IN VANCOUVER.
RECORDING THE BIG SOLO
RECORD EXTRAVAGANZA,
REALLY? WOW.
I GUESS I KNEW HE WAS ALWAYS
DESTINED FOR GREATNESS.
ELLIE:
DON'T BE SO SURE.
HE'S DATING MANNY.
EW! THAT MAKES ME
VAGUELY ITCHY.
ME TOO!
OF COURSE IT COULD
JUST BE LABEL CHAFE,
NEW SHIRT AND ALL.
SO, HOW'S ALISTAIR,
AKA ALI,
AKA YOUR LONDON LAD?
AH, IT WAS GOOD,
AND THEN IT WAS BAD,
AND THEN IT WAS OVER.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
OH, I'M CRUSHING
ON SOMEONE, AS USUAL.
BUT UM,
IT'LL NEVER HAPPEN...
AS USUAL.
SPIN, THESE THINGS,
THEY'LL WORK THEMSELVES OUT.
DARCY:
HEY, SPIN.
CUP OF COFFEE TO GO?
I HEARD ABOUT
THE BIG FREAKSHOW
WITH JIMMY?
AND I'M SORRY,
'CAUSE I KNOW HOW MUCH
HE MEANS TO YOU.
WHATEVER.
I'M DONE WITH THAT GUY.
SPINNER,
THAT'S THE BIGGEST LIE.
I KNOW YOU WOULD GIVE
EVERYTHING YOU HAVE
JUST TO BE FRIENDS
WITH HIM AGAIN.
SO, DON'T GIVE UP.
HE'LL COME AROUND.
I KNOW IT.
LISTEN DARCE,
IF YOU'RE STILL COOL
WITH IT,
TODAY WE'RE BACK TOGETHER.
OH,
I BROUGHT YOU SOMETHING...
JUST IN CASE.
I'LL NEVER TAKE IT OFF.
OH SUGAR.
I HAVE TO GO PACK
FOR BIBLE CAMP,
BUT MAYBE AFTER
WE CAN CELEBRATE?
YOU GOT IT.
(DOOR CHIMES JINGLE)
OKAY,
NOW YOU HAVE TO TELL-
YEAH, I KNOW.
I GOTTA CALL PAIGE.
I'LL GO OVER THERE
AFTER WORK AND...
BREAK THE BAD NEWS.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
ASHLEY:
WHO KNEW YOU HAD SO MUCH
BEAUTY STORED UP INSIDE?
HAVE YOU SEEN
THE ULTRA-DISTURBING
VIOLENT HORROR STUFF?
ELLIE NASH,
MY BIGGEST FAN.
I SO AM
AND YOU KNOW IT.
OH, I'M LATE
FOR A MOVIE.
SEE YOU.
JIMMY:
BYE.
YOU TWO LOOK COZY.
WE'RE FRIENDS, ASH.
YEAH, BUT YOU WANT IT
TO BE MORE.
OKAY, SO MAYBE I DO,
BUT WHATEVER.
IT'S POINTLESS.
SHE'S NOT INTO ME.
WHAT MAKES YOU SO SURE?
WHAT'S TEN POUNDS,
METAL AND VINYL,
HAS TWO WHEELS?
YEAH, BUT UNTIL YOU MENTIONED IT
JUST NOW,
I COMPLETELY FORGOT
YOU WERE EVEN IN A CHAIR.
THAT'S BECAUSE
YOU'RE SITTING.
IT'LL BECOME MORE APPARENT
WHEN YOU STAND.
ALL RIGHT, BUT DON'T GET
TOO DOWN ON YOURSELF
'CAUSE YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE
WITH A CRUSH.
I THINK ELLIE'S CRUSHING
ON YOU TOO, ROMEO.
SHE PRETTY MUCH
TOLD ME SO.
(CHUCKLES)
(KNOCK AT THE DOOR)
YOU DECENT?
DYLAN LET ME IN.
PAIGE:
OH MY GOD, SPIN,
YOU HAVE TO LOOK
AT THIS OLD YEARBOOK
RIGHT THIS MINUTE!
OKAY, I-I THOUGHT
WE COULD TALK THOUGH?
SURE, HON. PLEASE,
JUST INDULGE ME FIRST,
AND FEAST YOUR EYES
ON THIS...
SPINNER:
CHECK IT OUT.
WE WERE COUPLE
OF THE YEAR.
UH, HOW COULD WE NOT BE?
WE WERE UNBELIEVABLY
SUPER ADORABLE.
BOTH:
(CHUCKLE)
SPINNER:
THERE WE ARE -
THE OLD GANG.
WE RAN AT THAT SCHOOL.
REMEMBER?
YOU EVER JUST WISH
YOU HAD A TIME MACHINE?
I JUST WANNA GO BACK,
YOU KNOW?
BEFORE IT ALL WENT...
ALL WENT TO CRAP.
PAIGE:
SPIN?
JUST SO YOU KNOW,
I NEVER BLAMED YOU
FOR WHAT HAPPENED...
WITH JIMMY.
DO YOU MEAN THAT?
PAIGE...
BOTH:
(LAUGHING)
JT:
THAT'S REALLY MATURE.
YEAH WELL,
IT'S STILL FUNNY.
IN HONOUR
OF OUR LAST CLASS, SIR,
WE GIVE YOU THIS -
A LITTLE MERCI GIFT.
(APPLAUSE)
WHAT?
COME ON, GUYS.
(GIGGLING)
SOMEONE'S IN
A GOOD MOOD.
I JUST HOPE WE CAN ALL
GET A LITTLE BIT
OF WHATEVER'S GOTTEN
INTO YOU, PAIGE.
I'M NOT SURE
THAT'S ADVISABLE, SIR.
SIMPSON:
OH GUYS,
THIS IS SO PERFECT.
YOU HAVE KNOW IDEA
HOW MUCH I LOVE KARAOKE.
I'LL DIG OUT MY ELVIS WIG,
FIRE UP THE MIC,
AND SEE IF I CAN'T
GET MYSELF
INTO SOME SORT OF COUNTY FAIR
ELVIS IMPERSONATOR CONTEST.
I'LL BE TALL LANKY ELVIS.
(EXHALES)
DARCY:
SPIN.
HERE YOU ARE!
I'VE BEEN CALLING YOU
FOR AGES!
OH. MY PHONE.
THE RINGER'S OFF.
WELL, WHERE WERE YOU
LAST NIGHT?
WE SAID WE WERE
GONNA CELEBRATE.
I KNOW,
I KNOW.
BUT I WAS...
I WAS ARRANGING
A GOING AWAY GIFT FOR YOU.
THAT'S SO SWEET.
BUT YOU KNOW, I WOULD'VE
EASILY TRADED THE GIFT
TO GET TO SEE YOU
LAST NIGHT.
BREAK A LEG OUT THERE,
OKAY?
JT:
WELCOME EVERYBODY
TO "HERBAL ESSENCES PRESENTS
50 YEARS OF DEGRASSI".
I AM YOUR HOST,
SIR PHILIP DEGRASSI,
AND I'M HIS LOVELY DAUGHTER,
CHARLOTTE.
AND TODAY
WE'RE TAKING YOU
ON A MAGICAL
HISTORY TOUR.
MANNY:
STARTING WITH 1968,
PLEASE WELCOME
TO THE STAGE,
DARCY EDWARDS
AND HER LOVE PARADE!
CROWD:
(APPLAUDS)
(1960'S MUSIC STARTS)
PAIGE!
I'VE BEEN LOOKING
EVERYWHERE FOR YOU.
ME TOO.
AH...
I WANTED TO SAY
MERCI. (LAUGHS)
FOR WHAT?
LAST NIGHT, DORKUS.
IT FELT LIKE
THE RIGHT WAY
TO END SCHOOL.
JUST DON'T FORGET ME,
OKAY?
I WASN'T PLANNING
ON IT.
I WAS- I WAS KINDA
HOPING THAT UM...
WHOA!
HON, YOU'RE...
YOU'RE NOT SERIOUS?
WE'RE BOTH MOVING ON.
BUT I WILL ALWAYS HAVE
THE BESTEST MEMORIES
OF MY FIRST
REAL BOYFRIEND -
YOU.
YOU-YOU USED ME
FOR MY BODY.
EMMA:
MANNY, THAT WAS AWESOME.
DON'T FORGET US
WHEN YOU'RE ON BROADWAY.
SHOW YOUR AGENT.
MAYBE IT'LL HELP
GET YOU THERE.
YOU TAPED IT?
YEAH. I USED MY POWERS
FOR GOOD THIS TIME.
THANKS.
JIMMY:
ELLIE, HI.
ELLIE:
WHAT'S UP?
YOU LOOK GREAT.
I MEAN,
YOU ALWAYS LOOK GREAT.
BUT TONIGHT,
YOU LOOK GREAT.
BOTH:
(CHUCKLE)
OH HEY,
I WAS JUST WONDERING,
HOW DO I LOOK?
COULD IT MAYBE BE GREAT?
(LAUGHS)
UM, LOOK YOU'VE BECOME
ONE OF MY BEST FRIENDS,
RIGHT?
AND...
YOU OPENED MY EYES
TO A LOT OF THINGS.
I WANTED TO KNOW
IF MAYBE WE COULD
TALK ABOUT TAKING IT
TO THE NEXT LEVEL?
BUT YOU DON'T.
JIMMY,
I'M-I'M SORRY. I-
DON'T BE.
IT'S NOT COMPLETELY
UNEXPECTED.
I'M GONNA GO,
OKAY?
ASHLEY:
EL, WHAT HAPPENED?
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
YOU WERE CRUSHING ON SOMEONE.
HE'S NOT THE GUY,
ASH.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
C'MON,
DANCE WITH ME.
YOU'VE BEEN A TOTAL WEIRDO
ALL NIGHT.
DARCY, I'M AN IDIOT.
WHAT'RE YOU TALKING
ABOUT, SPIN?
IT'S YOUR GIFT.
HEY, IT DIDN'T COME.
I'VE BEEN TEXTING BACK
AND FORTH WITH THE GUY
AND HE JUST BAILED,
THE JERK.
SEEING AS I HAVE TO WAIT
THE WHOLE SUMMER...
MAYBE YOU COULD GIVE ME
THE TEENSIEST OF HINTS?
GOOD THINGS COME
TO THOSE WHO WAIT.
I'M GONNA GET US
SOME DRINKS.
(SIGHS)
ASHLEY:
JIMMY! JIMMY, WAIT.
I'M SORRY!
PLEASE,
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
LOOK ASHLEY, IT'S FINE.
REALLY. OKAY?
NO. JIMMY. JIMMY!
IT'S NOT.
LOOK...
YOU'RE AN AMAZING GUY.
YOU DESERVE TO BE WITH
SOMEONE WHO ADORES YOU.
LOOK I'M GONNA LET YOU IN
ON A SECRET.
GIRLS DON'T DIG GUYS
IN WHEELCHAIRS.
YOU WERE SAYING?
(DANCE MUSIC)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
I WANTED TO KNOW
WHAT MY GIFT WAS.
DARCE, YOU DIDN'T
READ MY TEXTS?
(EXHALES)
SOME GIFT,
SPINNER.
SPECIAL.
YOU SUCK.
MARCO:
AND NOW,
AS WE HEAD OFF
IN EVERY DIRECTION,
LET US REMEMBER THE TIES
WE HAVE TO EACH OTHER
AND TO DEGRASSI.
BECAUSE THE BEST THING
ABOUT THE PAST
IS THAT IT'S JUST-
IT'S HUGE PART OF THE FUTURE,
SO...
TO THE FUTURE.
TO US.
WE DID IT GUYS!
(LAUGHS)
(APPLAUSE)
MS. HATZILAKOS:
THANK YOU, MARCO,
FOR A WONDERFUL SPEECH.
AND NOW,
WITHOUT FURTHER ADO,
I'D LIKE TO WELCOME
TO THE STAGE
DEGRASSI'S GRADUATING CLASS
OF 2006!
(APPLAUSE)
(CHEERING)
MS. HATZILAKOS:
HAZEL ADEN.
SCOTT ANDERSON.
SUSAN BROWN.
SO, THERE THEY GO,
OUR CLASS,
ONTO A BRIGHT FUTURE.
YOU SHOULD'VE BEEN UP
THERE, MAN.
IT'LL BE OUR TURN
NEXT YEAR, RIGHT?
I'M SORRY,
ARE WE ACTUALLY
HAVING A CONVERSATION?
MS. HATZILAKOS:
CHRIS HENDERSON...
LOOK UM...
I SPENT A LOT OF TIME
THIS YEAR
BLAMING PEOPLE -
YOU ESPECIALLY -
AND UM,
THAT WAS WRONG
AND I'M SORRY.
JIMMY, I DO-
IT'S COOL. I KNOW.
(CHUCKLES)
I GOTTA GO.
(CLEARS THROAT)
ALL RIGHT.
PEACE.
JIMMY:
OH! (LAUGHS)
("YOUR EX-LOVER IS DEAD"
BY STARS IS PLAYING)
♪ ...IN THAT INSTANT
IT STARTED TO POUR ♪
♪ CAPTURED A TAXI
DESPITE ALL THE RAIN ♪
♪ WE DROVE IN SILENCE
ACROSS MOUNT CHAMPLAINE ♪
♪ AND ALL OF THAT TIME
YOU THOUGHT I WAS SAD... ♪
DARCY!
LISTEN, JUST ONE MINUTE,
PLEASE!
(IRRITATED SIGH)
LISTEN, WHAT I DID...
WHAT I DID WAS HORRIBLE.
BUT I SWEAR I WILL
MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
SPINNER,
YOU BROKE YOUR VOW.
I KNOW.
SO THAT'S WHY ALL I CAN DO
IS ASK -
BEG -
FOR YOUR FORGIVENESS.
I'M NOT SURE THAT I CAN.
NOT THIS TIME.
WE HAVE TO GO, DARCY.
DARCY, PLEASE.
I'M REALLY NOT SURE.
IF SHE TURNS AROUND TO LOOK
BEFORE SHE GETS ON,
I'LL BE OKAY.
♪ LIVE THROUGH THIS ♪
♪ AND YOU WON'T LOOK BACK ♪
MISS ME?
(ELATED BREATH)
YOU KNOW IT!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU CAME.
YEAH, LIKE I'D MISS THIS
FOR THE WORLD.
♪ ...AND I WANT TO SAY
SO I'LL BE BRAVE ♪
♪ YOU KNOW WHAT I WANTED ♪
♪ I GAVE WHAT I GAVE ♪
♪ I'M NOT SORRY I MET YOU ♪
♪ I'M NOT SORRY IT'S OVER ♪
♪ I'M NOT SORRY
THERE'S NOTHING TO SAY ♪