(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(MUFFLED THUMPS)
(LOUD BANG)
(ITEMS BOUNCE AND THUMP
ON FLOOR)
EMMA:
I THOUGHT YOU CRAWLED
IN SOMEBODY ELSE'S HOUSE
BY ACCIDENT.
(CRASH)
(SPLASH)
(MUFFLED SCREAM)
(QUIET LAUGH)
EMMA:
OH NO.
YOU LOOK LIKE A PRETZEL.
(LOUDLY) MY INSIDES
ARE KINDA PRETZEL-Y TOO,
LET ME TELL YOU.
SHHH!
AND I AM
SOAKING WET!
HOW AM I GOING TO WEAR THIS
TO SCHOOL TOMORROW?!
SHHH!
MY PARENTS
ARE SLEEPING.
I'LL LOAN YOU
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
BUT YOU NEED
TO TELL ME
WHY JENN SAW PETER
AND STINKING-DRUNK YOU
UPSTAIRS ALONE
AT 2:00 A.M.
I TOLD YOU
I LIKED HIM.
HEY, HEY, OKAY.
YOU TELL ME HE'S HANDS-OFF
AND HE'S HANDS-OFF.
THAT'S JUST THE LAW.
LIKE GIRLS SCOUT HONOUR.
SHUT UP!
MANNY:
I'M A SAILOR.
(LOUD CRASH AND SCREAM)
EMMA:
OH, MY GOD.
SIMPSON:
OH MANNY.
YOU CAN BE MY TASTE-TESTER
FOR MY FRIDGE-DUMP OMELETTE.
WE'VE GOT ZUCCHINI,
SAUSAGE,
THE CRUMBLY END OF A BIG OLD
HUNK OF BLUE CHEESE.
COLD CEREAL
IS OUR FRIEND.
NO, NO THANK YOU.
I'M FINE.
OH...
GUESS WHO JUST HUNG UP
FROM A CONVERSATION
WITH YOUR MOM?
GREAT.
WHO NEARLY WEPT
WHEN SHE HEARD
THAT YOU WERE HERE,
SAFE AND SOUND.
I HATE HER.
I HATE THEM.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best that I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
TELL ME YOU'RE AS HUNGOVER
AS I AM.
SURE.
I WASN'T DRINKING.
OH, GOOD.
THEN YOU REMEMBER
WHAT HAPPENED
BECAUSE I'M STILL
A LITTLE FOGGY.
YEAH,
I REMEMBER EVERYTHING.
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU
SHOWED ME YOUR...
YOU KNOW.
BUT YOU WERE SOBER.
WHY DIDN'T YOU TRY
AND STOP ME?
BECAUSE YOUR REQUEST
"LET'S MAKE A LITTLE MOVIE"
IMPLIED YOU DIDN'T
WANT ME TO.
WHY ARE YOU
BEING LIKE THIS?
I WANNA SEE YOU AGAIN.
PETER, MY BEST FRIEND
SINCE DAYCARE LIKES YOU
AND SHE'S REALLY LOVELY.
YEAH,
BUT SHE'S NOT YOU.
LAST NIGHT
WAS WHAT IT WAS
AND NOTHING MORE.
AND I'M GONNA TRUST YOU
THAT IT STAYS BETWEEN US.
FIRST CHANCE I GET
I'LL ERASE EVERYTHING.
IT'LL BE
OUR LITTLE SECRET.
MARCO:
SO YOU AND CRAIG
ARE BEST FRIENDS ALL SUMMER...
REGRETTABLY.
AND YOU DEVELOP
A CUTE LITTLE CRUSH.
MARCO...
AND HE SAYS A FEW
MEAN WORDS TO YOU-
TWO.
HE SAID TWO MEAN WORDS
AFTER I BUST MY KILT
TO THROW HIM A PARTY.
SO WHAT?
WE'RE NOT GOING TO HANG OUT?
NOT UNTIL HE APOLOGIZES.
OKAY.
LOOK, WE HAVE BAND PRACTICE
SCHEDULED FOR TOMORROW NIGHT.
DIDN'T CRAIG SAY HE'D NEVER
LET SPINNER BACK IN THE BAND?
HE HASN'T,
AND SPINNER ISN'T.
WHICH LEAVES US
WITHOUT A DRUMMER.
HEY...
I JUST STARTED
DRUMMING AGAIN.
I HAVEN'T DRUMMED
SINCE I WAS LIKE, TEN.
YEAH,
BUT YOU KNOW HOW TO DRUM -
AN IMMEDIATE IMPROVEMENT
OVER SPINNER -
AND YOU HAVE BEEN
IN A BAND BEFORE.
SO MAYBE IT'S TIME
YOU THINK ABOUT
JOINING A NEW ONE.
EMMA:
YOU TOLD HIM
I LIKED HIM?!
SORT OF.
SO, NOW, INSTEAD OF JUST BEING
TONGUE-TIED IN FRONT OF HIM,
I WILL ACTUALLY HAVE
TO BARF ON HIS SHOES.
NO, NO...
I... I THINK HE WAS
KIND OF INTO YOU.
I MEAN, I TOLD HIM THAT YOU-
YOU WERE LOVELY.
REALLY?
WELL, SORRY I WAS SNOTTY
EARLIER.
YOU ARE SO GOOD!
(WHISPERING)
MANNY?
YOUR MOTHER'S HERE
TO SEE YOU.
I COULDN'T COME HOME,
MOM.
NOT AFTER LAST NIGHT.
SO YOU DECIDED TO MAKE
YOUR FATHER'S TEMPER EVEN WORSE?
MANNY:
I'M THE ONE
WHO SHOULD BE ANGRY.
HE CALLED ME A SLUT.
UNTIL YOU SWEAR
TO DO WHAT HE SAYS,
AND GIVE UP ACTING,
YOUR FATHER'S TEMPER
WILL ONLY GET WORSE.
HE'LL GET MORE ANGRY.
I CAN'T.
I WON'T.
MRS. SANTOS:
THEN... YOU CAN STAY AT EMMA'S?
I'M SURE IT'S
NOT A PROBLEM.
SO I CAN'T COME HOME?
NOT YET.
NOT UNTIL YOU ARE READY.
MS. KWAN:
A SMART READER USES STRATEGIES
BEFORE SHE READS,
TO PREVIEW THE TEXT
AND TO ACTIVATE THEIR PRIOR
KNOWLEDGE OF THE TOPIC.
A SMART READER ALSO TRACKS
AND REPORTS IDEAS
AS THEY READ THEM.
SMART READERS ALSO KNOW
THAT READING PLAYS...
STOP STARING.
STOP BEING AN ASS.
DO YOU KNOW
HOW HUMILIATING IT WAS
TO FIND OUT IN PUBLIC
THAT MY GIRLFRIEND DUMPED ME
BY EMAIL?
OH...
OH, YOU'RE FORGETTING
ON YOUR BIRTHDAY.
THAT'S A PRETTY GOOD
DETAIL, TOO.
ASHLEY WANTED TO TELL YOU
HERSELF.
SHE WANTED TO WAIT
TILL THE TIME WAS RIGHT.
SHE WAS... CONCERNED.
THAT I'D GO OFF MY MEDS
AND GO ALL CRAZY.
I'M FINE.
YOU KNOW I'M FINE.
WE HUNG OUT
ALL SUMMER.
AND I DON'T NEED YOU
PROTECTING ME.
ALL THIS ANGER
IS FOR ASHLEY.
BUY A TICKET,
GO TO LONDON
AND FREAK ON HER
THERE.
(BELL RINGS)
LOOKING FOR THIS?
SO WHEN ARE WE GOING OUT?
THIS ISN'T FUNNY ANYMORE.
YOU DIDN'T ANSWER
MY QUESTION.
WHEN ARE WE GOING OUT?
PETER, I AM NEVER GOING
TO GO OUT WITH YOU!
I DON'T LIKE YOU.
TO TELL THE TRUTH,
I THINK YOU'RE A FREAK.
JUST...
JUST I NEED-
I NEED THE TAPE BACK, OKAY?
NEVER TELL THE SHOPKEEPER
YOU'RE DESPERATE
TO BUY HIS MERCHANDISE.
'CAUSE NOW
MY PRICE JUST WENT UP.
WHAT?
PETER:
THERE'S A NEW CAMERA I WANT.
HDV 10 ADI.
RUNS ABOUT THREE THOUSAND.
I DON'T HAVE
THAT KIND OF MONEY.
YOU LIE.
PLASTIC SURGERY AIN'T COVERED
BY HEALTH CARE, HONEY.
BUT... MY CREDIT CARD
AND MY BANK CARD
ARE BOTH WITH MY FATHER.
WELL, I'M SURE YOU'LL
THINK OF SOMETHING.
OR MAYBE I'LL HAVE TO START
SELLING TICKETS
TO OUR LITTLE MOVIE.
MANNY ON TAPE:
I'M GOING TO BE AN ACTRESS -
AN ACADEMY AWARD
WINNING ACTRESS!
AND YOU CAN SELL THIS
FOR A MILLION DOLLARS
BECAUSE I AM GOING
TO BE FAMOUS!
MARCO:
HEY! HEY EL!
SORRY,
NEW FRIENDS.
PAIGE:
I WOULDN'T GET INTO KINDERGARTEN
WITH MY RESUME.
UM... CAN I SIT HERE?
UH, SURE, HON.
HAZEL:
YOU HAVE PLENTY
OF EXTRA-CURRICS
TO PUT ON YOUR UNIVERSITY APP.
PAIGE:
YES. SPIRIT SQUAD,
SPIRIT SQUAD,
AND MORE SPIRIT SQUAD?
DOES THAT SOUND
WELL-ROUNDED TO YOU?
HELL HATH NO FURY.
I SAID YOU COULD SIT HERE,
NOT SPOUT KOOKY DARK-GIRL
CLICHES AT ME.
I'M TALKING ABOUT OUR BAND -
HELL HATH NO FURY.
WHY DON'T WE
START IT UP AGAIN?
ON TOP OF HELMING
SPIRIT SQUAD,
WE'RE A LITTLE
BOOKED UP RIGHT NOW.
YOU WANNA BE
AN AD EXECUTIVE, RIGHT?
DON'T YOU THINK YOUR RESUME
COULD USE SOMETHING CREATIVE?
SEE, HAZEL?
THAT IS HELPFUL.
SHE IS A HELPFUL
FRIEND-PERSON.
MANNY:
SO I NEED MY MONEY BACK.
MY PARENTS WON'T LET ME
DO THE SURGERY.
DR. ANDRAS:
I'M AWARE OF THAT.
THE PROCEDURE'S
BEEN CANCELLED.
GREAT.
THEN ABOUT MY MONEY...
UH...
IT'S TAKEN CARE OF.
WE'VE ALREADY REFUNDED
YOUR CREDIT CARD.
NO.
I DON'T KEEP THAT CARD.
MY PARENTS DO.
I NEED CASH.
I'M SORRY,
THAT'S' NOT HOW IT WORKS.
MANNY:
IT'S MY MONEY, DR. ANDRAS.
I'M NOT MOVING.
I CAN ALWAYS CALL
SECURITY.
EM?
(GROANS)
WHATEVER HAPPENS
TOMORROW
REMEMBER I LOVE YOU,
AND I'M ALWAYS GOING
TO BE YOUR FRIEND, 'KAY?
ARE WE GOING
TO SCHOOL TOMORROW
OR ARE WE SHIPPING
OFF TO IRAQ?
GO TO SLEEP.
HEY...
LOOK,
I DON'T HAVE YOUR MONEY.
SO I'LL JUST GO OUT
WITH YOU, OKAY?
YOU CALLED ME A FREAK,
MANNY.
SO, NO THANK YOU.
THAT OFFER'S EXPIRED.
SO...
NOW OUR LITTLE MOVIE'S
GOING TO BE RELEASED
IN SELECT THEATRES.
MANNY ON VIDEO:
...FOR A MILLION DOLLARS
BECAUSE I AM GOING
TO BE FAMOUS!
WHY ARE YOU LIKE THIS?
WHY ARE YOU TRYING
TO HURT ME
FOR NO REASON?
YOU ASKED ME
TO PUT THE CAMERA ON
AFTER I TOLD YOU
TO GO HOME.
YOU TOOK ADVANTAGE
OF ME!
YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHAT I THINK?
I THINK YOU'RE SO DESPERATE
FOR MALE ATTENTION
YOU'LL DO ANYTHING FOR IT.
YOU'RE A BIG,
FAT ATTENTION WHORE.
SHUT UP!
AN ATTENTION WHORE
WITH A BAD TEMPER.
THAT'S NOT ME.
MOST GIRLS DON'T
WHIP THEIR BOOBS OUT
TO GUYS THEY'VE KNOWN
FIVE MINUTES.
I'M SO GLAD MY DAD
GOT ME THIS MODEL.
SUCH A GENEROUS GUY.
CAN YOU BELIEVE I CAN EMAIL IT
RIGHT FROM HERE?
PETER! PETER!
THAT WASN'T-
YOU DIDN'T!
PETER!
YOU'RE GONNA BE
A BIG STAR, MANNY.
AND I GET TO SAY
I KNEW YOU WHEN.
(CHUCKLING)
(LAUGHING)
TOBY:
ISN'T THAT HILARIOUS?!
JT:
OH, MY GOODNESS.
MANNY:
HEY GUYS.
WHATCHA WATCHING?
OKAY, HERE.
LET'S CHECK THIS OUT,
READY?
IT'S A MONKEY SMELLING
HIS OWN BUTT.
IT'S CLASSIC!
(LAUGHING)
I'M GOING TO BE AN ACTRESS...
JIMMY:
HEY MAN,
DID YOU CHECK YOUR EMAIL?
NO.
CHECK IT.
CHECK THE ONE THAT SAYS
"DEGRASSI GIRLS GONE WILD".
MANNY ON TAPE:
...AN ACADEMY AWARD
WINNING ACTRESS.
AND YOU CAN SELL THIS
FOR A MILLION DOLLARS!
(VOICE OVERLAPS
AS MORE PEOPLE WATCH VIDEO)
JIMMY:
MANNY SANTOS,
MY HOW YOU'VE GROWN.
SHUT UP, MAN.
THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
MANNY:
HEY GUYS,
THANKS FOR COMING OUT.
WE'RE GOING TO START
WITH SOMETHING SIMPLE,
JUST TO SEE IF YOU CAN MOVE.
(GIRLS GIGGLING)
YOU'RE LATE.
OKAY, SMALL-GIRLS-WITH-
THE-GRACE-OF-OBESE-CAMELS.
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
GUESS YOU HAVEN'T SEEN
"DEGRASSI GIRLS GONE WILD"?
THERE'S A VIDEO,
OF MANNY,
DOING SOMETHING
SHE SHOULDN'T BE DOING.
YOU MEAN...?
MANNY:
NO! NO.
IT'S NOT THAT BAD.
IT'S JUST...
LIFT-YOUR-SHIRT-FOR-THE-CAMERA
KIND OF BAD.
YOU OBVIOUSLY CAN'T BE ON
SPIRIT SQUAD THIS YEAR.
PAIGE!
YOU'RE DISMISSED.
FIRED.
WHATEVER.
(GIRLS GIGGLING)
EM...
YOU THINK I DON'T RECOGNIZE
WHAT YOU WERE WEARING.
OR THE BACKGROUND?
I KNOW WHO YOU DID
THAT WITH.
EMMA, I DIDN'T...
I HAVE TO EXPLAIN.
DON'T BOTHER.
BUT EMMA...
I HATE YOU.
ELLIE:
GUYS, I WROTE IT IN PHYSICS.
BUT IT'S NOT ABOUT VECTORS.
IT'S OUR NEW SONG.
PAIGE:
WE DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS.
ELLIE:
I THOUGHT YOU NEEDED MORE
EXTRA-CURRICULARS.
HAZEL:
WE SIGNED UP FOR YEARBOOK,
GIRLS ATHLETIC ASSOCIATION,
AND PROM COMMITTEE
THIS MORNING.
PAIGE:
PLUS WE HAVE A TOPLESS
CHEERLEADER CRISIS.
HAVE YOU NOT SEEN
THE MANNY SANTOS
MOVIE OF THE WEEK?
ELLIE:
I'VE SEEN IT.
BUT I DON'T GET WHY IT MEANS
YOU HAVE TO QUIT THE BAND.
SWEETIE, WE WERE NEVER
REALLY IN THE BAND.
THAT WAS JUST A LITTLE
ELLIE NASH FANTASY.
WE'RE DEALING
WITH REALITY HERE.
THIS IS SERIOUS!
WHY DON'T YOU JOIN
CRAIG'S BAND.
I HEAR THEY'RE LOOKING
FOR A DRUMMER.
MS. KWAN:
GOOD AFTERNOON, CLASS.
OUR GOAL TODAY,
IS TO HELP YOU DEVELOP...
(STUDENTS TALKING)
MOM?
DAD?
WHAT DOES SHE WANT?
ASK HER, JOSEPH.
AND LISTEN TO WHAT
SHE TELLS YOU.
DAD...
I HAD A GREAT TIME
LAST SUMMER.
I GOT TO BE IN A MOVIE,
AND IN FRONT
OF THE CAMERA.
AND FOR THE FIRST TIME
IN MY LIFE
I FELT GOOD.
LIKE I MATTERED,
LIKE I WASN'T A JOKE.
PLEASE DON'T TAKE THAT
AWAY FROM ME.
WE DID NOT COME
TO THIS COUNTRY
SO YOU COULD BECOME
SOME ACTRESS.
IT'S NOT THE JOB
FOR A DECENT GIRL.
IT IS TOO!
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT!
ENOUGH!
YOU WILL DO WHAT I SAY!
I CAN'T.
YOU CAN'T ASK ME!
YOU TELL HER.
YOU TELL THAT GIRL
THIS IS NO LONGER
HER HOME.
JOSEPH!
JOSEPH:
TELL HER!
(CRAIG PLAYING GUITAR)
CRAIG:
YOU HERE TO SEE MARCO?
HE'S NOT HERE YET.
I'M HERE TO SEE YOU.
(STARTS PLAYING GUITAR AGAIN)
CRAIG!
WE HUNG OUT ALL SUMMER
AND I KNOW YOU'RE OKAY NOW.
AND IT WAS SO...
SO STUPID OF ME
TO TRY AND PROTECT YOU.
I SHOULD'VE JUST TOLD YOU.
SORRY.
COOL.
THAT'S IT?
CRAIG:
THAT'S IT.
I... (SIGHS)
I CAN FEEL THEM, YOU KNOW.
YOUR EYES BURNING A HOLE
IN MY BACK.
I'M SORRY... TOO.
I OVERREACTED, OKAY?
SO... THERE.
BETTER?
NOT REALLY.
SO WHAT DO WE DO?
WELL...
I HEARD YOU'RE
IN-BETWEEN DRUMMERS.
YOU HEARD RIGHT.
KNOW ANY?
I HAPPEN TO BE
IN-BETWEEN BANDS.
MAYBE I SHOULD SIT IN?
I GOTTA WARN YOU, EL.
WE SUCK - HUGE.
OLDEST RULE OF MUSIC,
CRAIG.
A BAND'S ONLY AS GOOD
AS ITS DRUMMER.
(DRUMMING)
OKAY,
YOU'LL FIT IN FINE.
EM, JUST HEAR ME OUT.
HERE ARE THE CLOTHES
THAT YOU LENT ME.
I KNOW I HAVE OTHER STUFF
OF YOURS TOO, BUT...
YOU PROBABLY LOST IT ALL.
BUT I GOT KICKED OUT.
I DON'T KNOW FOR HOW LONG.
MAYBE FOR GOOD.
EM, I SCREWED UP...
SO BAD.
I LOST MY FAMILY,
MY REPUTATION,
AND MY BEST FRIEND.
JUST WAIT.
MANNY, IT'S HARD
TO WATCH YOU SOMETIMES.
YOU HAVE EVERYTHING
GOING FOR YOU
AND YOU JUST...
YOU KEEP SCREWING IT UP
PRETTY SPECTACULARLY.
IT'D BE EASIER
IF I WAS YOU, EM.
SKINNY, BLONDE...
MANNY,
THAT IS A BUNCH OF CRAP
AND YOU KNOW IT.
THAT IS NOT
WHAT THIS IS ABOUT.
(SOMEONE WHISTLES)
(STUDENTS MAKE INDISTINCT
COMMENTS ABOUT MANNY)
MANNY...
WE HAVE TO DO THIS.
GUYS:
(WHISTLING)
LOOK,
JUST SO YOU KNOW,
I DIDN'T SEND IT
TO THE WHOLE WORLD.
I JUST SHOWED IT
TO A COUPLE OF FRIENDS.
REMIND ME
TO THANK YOU.
HATZILAKOS:
PETER.
I'M TALKING TO FRIENDS, MOM.
LATER.
DON'T USE THAT TONE OF VOICE
WITH ME HERE.
THIS IS MY SCHOOL,
I AM YOUR PRINCIPAL.
IN MY OFFICE.
NOW.
(SIGHS)
I'M SO ASHAMED,
I CANNOT EVEN LOOK AT YOU.
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
HOW COULD YOU DO
SOMETHING SO HEARTLESS?
DID YOU KNOW
HE'S HATZILAKOS' SON?
NO.
HE DIDN'T TELL ME.
I DON'T THINK
HE TOLD ANYONE.
I WONDER WHO
HIS FATHER IS?
SATAN PROBABLY.
(WHISTLES)
MANNY, I KNOW YOU'RE GOING
THROUGH HELL RIGHT NOW
AND I DON'T WANT
TO ADD TO IT,
BUT YOU AND I NEED
SOME GROUND RULES.
I THOUGHT WE WENT OVER
GROUND RULES
WITH MR. SIMPSON:
NOTHING BELOW AN "A",
NO ACTING WORK
BEYOND THE DRAMA CLUB,
NO PLASTIC SURGERY...
I KNOW.
I DON'T MEAN
THAT STUFF.
I MEAN
BETWEEN YOU AND ME.
NO MORE LIES EVER,
OKAY?
THERE WILL BE NOTHING
BETWEEN US.
OKAY.
PROMISE.
EMMA:
SO YOU READY TO FACE
YOUR FIRST CLASS?
NOT EVEN REMOTELY.