JIMMY:
SHOW YOUR STUFF.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S GO.
GO BACK.
GO BACK UP TOP.
DEREK:
OKAY, COME ON.
OW.
TAKING IT EASY ON ME.
DOES THIS LOOK EASY
OR PAINFUL?
JIMMY:
SO GET UP.
DEREK:
OKAY, LET'S GO.
JIMMY:
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S IT.
LOOK AT THAT.
HE'S GOT A LOT OF POTENTIAL,
BUT...
(MUFFLED COMMENT)
THERE YOU GO.
SO HOW DID I DO?
GOOD ENOUGH
TO MAKE THE TRYOUTS?
WELL, TO BE HONEST,
YOU'RE STILL A LITTLE
AWKWARD IN YOUR CHAIR.
BUT THE NATIONAL WHEELCHAIR
SPORTS ASSOCIATION
LIKES A COMPETITIVE EDGE,
AND THAT YOU'VE GOT.
TRYOUTS ARE WEDNESDAY.
OH... THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
PROUD OF YOU, SON.
SO UH, I SHOULD BOOK
MY TICKET TO CHINA,
SAY UH... 2008?
LET'S GET PAST WEDNESDAY.
VERY GOOD, JIMMY.
VERY GOOD.
KEEP PLAYING WITH DEREK?
DEREK:
YUP.
WORK ON YOUR
CHAIR MANEUVERING.
HE DID SAY
YOU WERE A LITTLE AWKWARD.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
CRAIG:
JIMMY, YOU'RE NOT SERIOUS.
YOU CAN'T QUIT THE BAND.
CAN SOMEBODY BE HAPPY
ABOUT THIS?
THIS IS ME,
JIMMY THE ATHLETE.
I'M BACK.
WHAT CAN I SAY?
WE'LL MISS YOU
IN THE BAND BUT...
GOOD LUCK.
THANK YOU.
I APPRECIATE IT.
MARCO:
YEAH. GOOD LUCK.
THANK YOU.
I'M HAPPY FOR YOU.
WELCOME BACK,
JIMMY BROOKS.
SO, DO YOU THINK
YOU'LL MAKE THE TEAM?
LIBERTY, HOLD UP!
YOU'RE STARTING
TO SHOW.
PEOPLE BELIEVE WHAT
THEY WANT TO BELIEVE.
OKAY?
AND NO ONE WANTS
TO BELIEVE
THAT THEIR STUDENT
COUNCIL PRESIDENT
IS IN HER THIRD
TRIMESTER.
HER THIRD TRI-WHAT?
YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING,
DO YOU?
HAVE YOU DONE
ANY RESEARCH?
YEAH, I HAVE,
OKAY?
TONS.
OKAY, I'M LYING.
BUT THE THING IS...
EVERY TIME I LOOK
AT THOSE BOOKS,
I JUST GET KIND OF
FLUSTERED.
THEY FREAK ME OUT.
WHY AM I NOT
SURPRISED?
DANNY:
HEADS UP!
(BABY CRIES)
DANNY,
ARE YOU INSANE?
I'M NOT THE ONE
WHO MISSED A FLYING BABY.
WHAT IS THIS?
THE DIGITAL BABY.
SHHH. SHHH.
FAMILY PLANNING PROJECT.
I'M MR. MOM FOR A WEEK.
WHY ARE YOU TAKING
FAMILY PLANNING?
WHY DOES ANYONE TAKE IT?
'CAUSE IT'S A BIRD COURSE.
PLUS,
THE CLASS IS FULL
OF FLY MAMMIES
AND ONE DUDE -
ME.
I LIKE THOSE ODDS.
WHAT ARE YOU DRAWING?
IT'S NOTHING.
PEN'S HITTING PAPER
AND LEAVING A SERIES OF MARKS.
DEDUCTION SAYS
YOU'RE DRAWING.
MY DAD SAID HE'D GET ME
A NEW WHEELCHAIR
IF I MAKE
THE PARALYMPIC TEAM -
HAND-MADE,
DESIGNED BY ME.
ELLIE:
WHAT'S THIS?
I KNEW YOU COULD GET CREATIVE
WITH A GUITAR SLIDE,
BUT THIS IS
A WHOLE DIFFERENT...
AND DISTURBING SIDE OF YOU.
IT'S REALLY JUST SOMETHING
I STARTED IN THE HOSPITAL
TO PASS THE TIME.
IT KINDA MAKES ME CHILL.
THESE ARE REALLY GOOD.
I DON'T THINK YOU KNOW
HOW GOOD.
MR. BROOKS:
WORK ON YOUR CHAIR MANEUVERING.
HE DID SAY
YOU WERE A LITTLE AWKWARD.
(GUNSHOT)
AHHHH!
CRAIG:
JIMMY!
ELLIE:
THESE ARE REALLY GOOD.
I DON'T THING YOU KNOW
HOW GOOD.
MR. BROOKS:
JIM?
YOU OKAY?
YEAH,
I'M GOOD TO GO.
COULD'VE FOOLED ME.
DAD, I'M FINE.
I JUST...
I JUST KEEP LOSING FOCUS,
AND I DON'T FEEL THE FLOW
LIKE I USED TO.
MR. BROOKS:
THAT'S JUST STRESS TALKING.
MAKING THIS TEAM IS
THE BE-ALL-AND-END-ALL FOR YOU.
SO OF COURSE YOU
FEEL STRESSED OUT.
IT'S NATURAL, SON.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU KNOW THAT 90 PERCENT
OF BEING A CHAMPION IS MENTAL.
DO WE NEED TO GET YOU
A SPORTS PSYCHOLOGIST
BEFORE THE TRYOUT?
YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT
LETTING ME DOWN?
I'M NOT.
LOOK,
STOP WORRYING ABOUT ME.
I'M GONNA DO THIS.
OKAY.
THAT'S MY BOY.
(BABY'S HEAD THUDS
AGAINST THE DOOR)
LIBERTY, YOUR TIME WAS UP
20 MINUTES AGO!
LIBERTY:
GO AWAY. I'M SICK.
YEAH?
WELL, I'M SICK TOO.
SICK OF WAITING FOR YOU
TO GET YOUR SORRY BUTT
OUT OF THE BATHROOM
EVERY MORNING.
(TOILET FLUSHES)
(BABY CRIES)
WHAT IS THAT SMELL?
BODY SPRAY.
THE AD SAID IT'LL ATTRACT
THE FLY MAMMIES
LIKE A SEX MAGNET.
YEAH, WELL,
IT'S TURNING MY STOMACH.
WAIT.
I KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON.
YOU'RE IN HERE BLOWING
CHUNKS EVERY MORNING
LIKE IT'S GOING OUT
OF STYLE.
YOU'RE BULIMIC!
YEAH,
I'M BULIMIC.
BRILLIANT DEDUCTION.
WELL, IF YOU'RE GONNA
BINGE AND PURGE,
DO IT SOMEWHERE ELSE.
NOT THAT IT'S WORKING,
TUBBO.
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
IT'S AN ART EXHIBIT
DOWNTOWN.
I'M NOT REALLY THE ART EXHIBIT
TYPE OF GUY.
BUT THIS IS HORROR COMIC ART
FROM THE 50S:
COOL, DARK, DISTURBED.
RIGHT UP YOUR ALLEY.
SOUNDS LIKE.
BUT I GOT TRYOUTS
AT 6:00 P.M..
OH, TOO BAD.
IT'S THE LAST DAY
OF THE EXHIBIT.
LOOK...
ELLIE, I GOT A LOT
ON MY MIND.
ALL THE MORE REASON
TO GO SOMEPLACE ELSE.
IN YOUR MIND,
I MEAN,
BUT WHATEV.
LIBERTY,
WE NEED TO TALK.
NOT NOW.
MY STOMACH
IS DOING CARTWHEELS.
I FEEL HORRID.
JT:
IF YOU KEEP ACTING LIKE
YOU HAVE SOMETHING TO HIDE,
PEOPLE ARE GONNA
START TO WONDER.
LIBERTY:
I GET MORNING SICKNESS.
AND THE AMOUNT OF TIME
I SPEND IN THE BATHROOM-
DANNY:
NO WAY.
LIBERTY:
IT'S ALREADY MAKING
SOME PEOPLE WONDER.
YOU THINK THIS HAS BEEN EASY?
DANNY:
NO WAY!
JT, I WANT TO TALK WITH YOU!
YOU GOT MY SISTER PREGNANT?!
I'M GOING TO KILL YOU!
LIBERTY:
DANNY, STOP IT!
DANNY, GET OFF HIM!
JT:
AHH! CAN'T BREATH!
LIBERTY:
DANNY, STOP IT!
GET OFF HIM!
STOP IT!
LIBERTY, HOW COULD
YOU LET THIS IDIOT
DO THAT TO YOU?!
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
I WAS SPEAKING
TO MY SISTER.
DO MOM AND DAD EVEN KNOW?
DANNY, I BEG YOU,
PLEASE, DO NOT TELL.
LIKE THAT WORK IN THERE
WAS SICK.
THAT'S WHAT I LIVE FOR.
ELLIE:
IS IT OKAY TO BE
SCARED RIGHT NOW?
SO? SHOULD WE GO?
DON'T YOU HAVE TO
MENTALLY PREPARE?
GET IN YOUR BASKETBALL
ZONEY-ZONE?
IT'S A LITTLE CROWDED
IN THERE RIGHT NOW
AND THIS IS QUIET.
IT'S GOOD.
AND...
THIS IS A BOX.
YOU KNOW, I THINK
THEY HAVE LESSONS HERE.
JIMMY:
IN PROPER BOX PLACEMENT?
NO.
LIFE DRAWINGS,
STILL-LIFES,
LANDSCAPES.
YOU MIGHT LIKE IT.
I JUST DRAW STUFF
I IMAGINE.
STUFF I SEE
WHEN I CLOSE MY EYES.
IT'S LIKE I HAVE A PEN
IN MY HAND
AND EVERYTHING
JUST GOES "SHHHHH".
AND THEN I CAN SAY
EVERYTHING I WANT TO SAY -
EVERYTHING I NEED
TO SAY -
RIGHT THERE ON THAT
PIECE OF PAPER.
YOU'RE SOUNDING SUSPICIOUSLY
LIKE AN ARTIST.
AN ARTIST?
DOES THAT SOUND LIKE
JIMMY BROOKS TO YOU?
ELLIE:
I DON'T KNOW,
DOES IT?
TED:
GALLERY IS CLOSING, KIDS.
IT'S 5 P.M. ALREADY?
TED:
IT'S FIVE AFTER SIX.
♪♪♪
(KIDS YELLING ENCOURAGEMENT
BACK AND FORTH)
DAD!
COACH.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
YOU'RE 30 MINUTES LATE?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH,
I WAS PRACTICING...
PREPARING MENTALLY.
I LOST TRACK OF TIME.
I'M SORRY.
SHOWING UP LATE
FOR TRYOUTS
MAKES US THINK
YOU DON'T WANT THE SPOT.
NO, I WANT TO PLAY, SIR.
I DO.
IT'S TOO LATE.
WE'RE DONE.
MR. BROOKS:
COACH MORRIS,
THIS'LL NEVER HAPPEN AGAIN.
PLEASE LET US TRY OUT.
I PERSONALLY ENSURE
THAT JIMMY WILL BE HERE,
ON TIME,
READY TO GO.
OKAY, LOOK,
I'LL MAKE AN EXCEPTION FOR YOU.
BE HERE TOMORROW.
I'LL GET YOU A SPOT,
OKAY?
THANK YOU, COACH.
I WON'T LET YOU DOWN.
YEAH.
YOU NEITHER, DAD.
I PROMISE.
WOW.
OKAY, SEE?
NOW YOU'RE TEMPTING ME.
I MISS THIS SHOT
AND YOUR LEXUS WEARS A DENT.
MR. BROOKS:
DON'T MISS THE SHOT...
OR DON'T TAKE IT.
UNTIL YOU'RE SITTING IN THIS.
JIMMY:
IT'S AWESOME.
BUT WHAT HAPPENED TO ME
DESIGNING MY OWN?
JIM, THIS IS THE TOP
OF THE LINE.
THE LEXUS.
YOU GOT TO HAVE THE BEST
IF YOU'RE GONNA BE A CHAMPION.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY.
YOU WEREN'T SUPPOSED TO GET IT
UNTIL AFTER YOU MADE THE TEAM.
BUT AFTER YOUR LITTLE
STUNT YESTERDAY?
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT NEED
THE INCENTIVE.
BY SHOWING UP LATE,
YOUR DISCIPLINE WAS QUESTIONED.
YOU SHOW UP TONIGHT IN THIS,
THEY'LL TAKE YOU SERIOUSLY.
WE'LL ALL TAKE YOU
SERIOUSLY.
DANNY?
STILL NOT TALKING
TO EITHER OF YOU.
I BARELY SLEPT LAST NIGHT,
OKAY?
I HAD NIGHTMARES
WITH PITCHFORKS
AND TORCHES.
AND BABIES?
DANIEL,
THIS IS SERIOUS.
YOU DIDN'T TELL
MOM OR DAD, RIGHT?
IF I DID,
YOU'D KNOW.
BECAUSE YOU'D BOTH
BE DEAD RIGHT NOW.
PRECISELY WHY THIS NEEDS
TO REMAIN OUR SECRET.
DO WE HAVE YOUR WORD?
JT:
DANNY,
YOU CAN'T TELL ANYONE.
OH YES I CAN, IDIOT.
BUT I WON'T.
SO LONG AS YOU HELP ME
AND THE KID GET AN "A".
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU DON'T NEED
THE PRACTICE, DAD.
SEE,
I'M NOT GETTING THE FIT.
DEREK:
HEY, JIM?
SOMEONE TO SEE YOU.
I WANTED TO APOLOGIZE.
THERE IS NOTHING
TO APOLOGIZE FOR.
I MADE YOU
MISS YOUR TRYOUT.
I'M GETTING ANOTHER CHANCE.
AND BESIDES,
I HAD FUN WITH YOU.
I'M GOING
TO THE GALLERY TODAY.
TO SIGN UP
FOR LIFE-DRAWING CLASSES.
I CAN PUT YOUR NAME DOWN TOO.
UH...
ELLIE:
HEY, YOU SHOWED TALENT.
THIS IS ME
ENCOURAGING IT.
THIS IS ME THANKING YOU,
BUT... NO.
OKAY.
DEREK:
SO... CAN I ASK HER OUT?
JUST THROW ME
THE DAMN BALL.
AHHHH!
YOU OKAY?!
(GROANS)
(BABIES CRY)
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M SKIPPING BIO FOR THIS.
JUST SUPPORT ITS NECK,
MORON,
AND STOP COMPLAINING.
IF YOU'D KEPT THE DIME-STACK
IN YOUR PANTS,
YOU WOULDN'T BE
IN THIS SITUATION.
WHATEVER.
WHY WON'T THIS THING
STOP CRYING?
BURP IT.
I AM NOT BURPING
A DOLL.
HMMM...
SENSORS INSIDE DETECT
NO BURPING,
I GET A BAD GRADE,
EVERYONE FINDS OUT
YOUR SECRET.
YOU'RE JUST LOVING THIS,
AREN'T YOU?
THANK YOU.
DOES IT HURT?
I'LL LIVE.
WE'RE IN THE NURSE'S
OFFICE.
SO?
SO NOTHING.
JUST NOT IN THE MOOD.
I SPOKE TO YOUR DAD.
HE'S WORRIED.
AND AFTER TALKING TO HIM?
SO AM I.
HE SAID YOU MISSED
YOUR TRYOUTS LAST NIGHT
BECAUSE YOU WERE
AT THE ART GALLERY
WITH ELLIE NASH.
I JUST NEEDED TO FOCUS
AND IT WAS QUIET.
HAZEL:
SO IS THE LIBRARY.
I LIKE ART.
MAYBE I LIKE ART, TOO.
DO YOU, REALLY?
NO, I DON'T.
I DON'T GET ART AT ALL.
BUT IF YOU WERE FREAKED OUT
OR LOSING IT?
I WOULD'VE HOPED
I'D BE THE ONE YOU'D GO TO.
NOT ELLIE.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR HAND?
IT'S A LITTLE SPRAIN.
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
LOOK DAD, I GOTTA TALK TO YOU
ABOUT THIS NEW CHAIR.
IT'S NOT RIDING
LIKE MY OLD ONE.
IT RIDES BETTER,
I'M SURE.
IT'S THE SAME MODEL
THE TEAM PLAYS IN.
YEAH, DAD,
THIS ISN'T HELPING ME.
WELL,
HOW CAN I HELP YOU?
I JUST WANT YOU
TO WIN, SON.
I WANT YOU TO FEEL GOOD
ABOUT YOURSELF.
I WANT YOU TO BE
YOU AGAIN.
DAD, I CAN'T.
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
I'M IN A WHEELCHAIR,
OKAY?
I AM NEVER
WALKING AGAIN.
I KNOW, SON.
NO YOU DON'T.
'CAUSE YOU KEEP TRYING
TO BRING THIS OLD JIMMY BACK -
THE STAR PLAYER,
THE ATHLETE.
THAT JIMMY IS GONE.
THAT JIMMY GOT SHOT.
JIMMY, YOU'RE UNDER A LOT
OF PRESSURE RIGHT NOW.
YOU THINK?
AND WHERE'S THAT PRESSURE
COMING FROM, DAD?
FROM ME?
HAVE YOU EVER ASKED ME
JUST ONCE,
IF I WANT THIS?
COACH MORRIS:
JIMMY, YOU READY?
YEAH,
I'M READY.
DANNY:
THE BABY'S CRYING.
JT:
THANKS, YODA.
I NOTICED.
DANNY:
WELL, MAKE HIM STOP
OR GIVE HIM BACK TO ME.
YOU'RE GONNA MAKE ME FAIL!
JT:
NO, I WON'T.
YOU WILL.
FACE IT, JT.
YOU SUCK!
I DON'T SUCK!
I JUST NEED A LITTLE
MORE PRACTICE!
YEAH,
A LIFETIME'S WORTH.
GIVE ME THE BABY BACK!
(BABY CRYING)
BOTH:
NO!
NICE WORK, GENIUS.
COACH MORRIS:
HEY, YOU OKAY TO START
WITH FREETHROWS?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOUR HAND?
LOOK, I MEAN NO DISRESPECT
AT ALL, COACH.
BUT...
ALL THIS JUST ISN'T FOR ME.
SO YOU WASTED MY TIME?
AND I'M SORRY FOR THAT, SIR.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
LET'S JUST GO HOME.
WHAT ABOUT THE TEAM?
DAD, STOP.
THIS IS MY LIFE NOT YOURS.
WE GOT A LOT OF STUFF
TO TALK ABOUT.
I GOT AN "INCOMPLETE".
THANKS, JT.
YOU WERE THE ONE
WHO BLACKMAILED ME, OKAY,
INTO SCAMMING
A GOOD GRADE!
NO, I BLACKMAILED YOU
BECAUSE YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE A BABY, IDIOT!
SHHH.
YOU NEED TO LEARN
THIS STUFF.
I JUST THOUGHT
I COULD HELP.
LIBERTY:
THAT IS THE DUMBEST THING
I'VE HEARD
COME OUT OF YOUR MOUTH.
OKAY, I'VE BEEN DEALING
WITH THIS ON MY OWN,
FOR MONTHS.
I HAVEN'T NEEDED
ANY HELP SO FAR
AND I DON'T NOW.
YOU'RE WRONG,
LIBERTY, OKAY?
WE'RE BOTH TOTALLY
CLUELESS HERE.
SPEAK FOR YOURSELF.
YOU'RE SIX MONTHS PREGNANT
AND YOU HAVEN'T EVEN SEEN
A DOCTOR YET.
THAT'S NOT GOOD.
I'M STUDENT COUNCIL
PRESIDENT, OKAY?
I CAN'T BE PREGNANT.
I JUST... CAN'T.
THIS ISN'T JUST ABOUT YOU,
RIGHT?
IT'S ABOUT YOU
AND THIS BABY AND ME.
AND ME.
HEY, I'M THE UNCLE HERE,
OKAY?
WE'LL GO TO MS. SAUVE,
TOMORROW.
SHE'LL TELL US
WHAT TO DO.
I'M SORRY I DIDN'T CALL YOU
LAST NIGHT.
I WAS HAVING A LONG TALK
WITH MY DAD
ABOUT A LOT OF STUFF.
YOU COULD'VE EMAILED.
I JUST WANTED TO KNOW
IF YOU MADE THE TEAM.
IT'S OKAY.
YOU'VE BEEN UNDER
A LOT OF STRESS.
YOU CAN TRY AGAIN?
THAT'S THE THING...
I DON'T WANT TO.
EVERYTHING I'VE BEEN
THROUGH THIS PAST YEAR -
ALL THE PHYSIO,
THE THERAPY, THE TRAINING -
IT'S ALL BEEN TO GET BACK
TO HOW I WAS
BEFORE I GOT SHOT.
AND YOU ARE.
YOU ARE BACK.
NO. I'M NOT.
I'VE CHANGED.
AND I GOTTA MAKE
SOME CHANGES TOO.
HAZEL:
NO. YOU'RE WRONG.
YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED.
'CAUSE WHEN I LOOK IN YOUR EYES
I STILL SEE YOU.
I STILL SEE
THE SAME OLD JIMMY.
HAZEL,
IT'S COMPLICATED.
THEN EXPLAIN IT TO ME.
I DON'T KNOW IF I CAN.
HAZEL:
JUST TRY.
OKAY.
I'LL TRY.