(WATER SPLASHES)
AH! SON OF A-
FRUIT SALAD!
MANNY:
UM, MR. SIMPSON,
CAN YOU KEEP IT DOWN?
IT'S LONG DISTANCE
WITH CRAIG.
YOU HAVEN'T LET ME
BRUSH YOUR HAIR
SINCE YOU WERE TEN.
I WISH I WAS TEN.
YOU DON'T HAVE
A TIME MACHINE, DO YOU?
I'M AFRAID I DON'T,
KIDDO.
WHEN DID IT ALL GET
SO COMPLICATED.
HEY, SERIOUS MCMOPEY,
DO YOU KNOW HOW BORING
LIFE WOULD BE
IF IT WERE SIMPLE.
RIGHT?
HELLO?
ARE YOU THERE?
I'M HERE, MOM.
I'M JUST WORRIED
ABOUT EXAMS AND STUFF, OKAY.
OKAY.
EMMA:
WHERE ARE WE GOING?
PETER:
OH, JUST FOLLOW ME.
I'M SORRY I CAN'T
SEE YOU AT SCHOOL.
SO UH, THIS IS MY WAY
OF MAKING IT UP TO YOU.
I BRING YOU
ALL THE COMFORT FOODS:
POTATO SALAD,
UH...
FRIED CHICKEN,
CHOCOLATE CAKE.
YOU FEELIN' OKAY?
YOU LOOK KINDA SICK.
YEAH. I'M FINE,
I JUST...
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'D DO THIS FOR ME.
IT'S SO...
SEXY.
WHO KNEW POTATO SALAD
WAS SUCH AN APHRODISIAC?
SHUT UP!
LEAVE IT.
I WASN'T HUNGRY ANYWAY.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
MR. ELLIS:
OKAY, HEADS UP, EVERYBODY.
TODAY WE GOT LIBERTY
TALKING FROGS.
IT WILL BE MOST FASCINATING,
I'M SURE.
ALL RIGHT, TAKE IT AWAY,
LIBERTY.
LIBERTY:
OF COURSE, MR ELLIS.
I'LL BEGIN WITH THE FEMALE
REPRODUCTIVE SYSTEM.
AH, HINT HINT?
THIS JUST MIGHT BE
ON YOUR YEAR END TEST.
LIBERTY:
UP HERE WE HAVE
THE GALLBLADDER.
THEN WAY DOWN
AT THE BOTTOM...
OW! MANNY.
YOU'RE FALLING ASLEEP
DURING CLASS.
AND BY THE WAY,
YOUR HANDS ARE COLDER
THAN MY NANA'S...
AT HER FUNERAL.
I HAVE POOR CIRCULATION.
(IRRITATED EXHALE)
WHY DID YOU DO THAT?
BECAUSE YOU'VE BEEN WEIRD
AND DISTANT FOR WEEKS,
AND I'M GETTING TIRED
OF IT.
WELL, I'M TIRED OF YOU
BEING NEEDY MCNEEDERSONS
ALL THE TIME.
SORRY I HAVE A LIFE;
SORRY I'VE GOT STUFF GOING ON
THAT YOU WOULDN'T UNDERSTAND.
LIKE WHAT?
LIKE- (SIGHS) NOTHING.
JUST DROP IT.
WHOA. ARE YOU GETTING
YOUR ATTITUDE
FROM THESE THINGS?
PROTEIN BARS.
THEY'RE ALL YOU EAT, LATELY.
ARE THEY EVEN SAFE?
I GET THEM AT
A HEALTH FOOD STORE.
MR. ELLIS:
MISS NELSON?
UM YEAH, SORRY SIR.
MR. ELLIS:
I HOPE YOU ARE BACK THERE
WHISPERING
ABOUT ENDOCRINE GLANDS?
ABSOLUTELY.
GLAND CENTRAL OVER HERE.
MR. ELLIS:
GOOD.
BECAUSE IF YOU DON'T ACE
YOUR YEAR END EXAM,
I'LL BE SEEING YOU
IN SUMMER SCHOOL.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
OH MY GOD.
WILL SOMEONE PLEASE SEND
HEATHER SINCLAIR A MEMO
THAT BELLY SHIRTS
ARE OUT?
AS IF THEY WERE
EVER A GOOD IDEA
FOR MISS TELETUBBY,
ANYWAYS.
(CHUCKLES) ALEX,
YOU'RE LIKE...
THE VINEGARY DRESSING
ON THE DULL SALAD
OF MY LIFE.
AND HEARING
THE WORD DULL,
HAZEL MAGICALLY APPEARS.
HI, HON.
HEY, PAIGE.
ANYTHING EXCITING
IN YOUR MAILBOX?
IT'S VERY LONELY,
FILLED ONLY WITH THE SOUND
OF MY INCREASING PANIC.
ALEX:
GOSH, IF I DON'T GET
INTO THE UNIVERSITY
OR SORORITY OF MY CHOICE,
I'LL JUST DIE.
SEE YOU IN BIO.
HOPE THE LESSON'S
ON BECOMING INTERESTING
ON THE CELLULAR LEVEL
'CAUSE HAZEL
REALLY NEEDS IT.
EVERYTHING'S ALWAYS A GAME
TO YOU.
KEEPS LIFE INTERESTING.
WELL, SOME THINGS DO
ACTUALLY MATTER.
SOME PEOPLE MATTER,
AT LEAST TO ME.
HAZEL'S ONE OF THEM
AND...
YOU NEED TO BE
NICER TO HER.
BETWEEN STUDYING
AND PLANNING
THE END OF THE YEAR
EXTRAVAGANZA,
I BARELY HAVE TIME
TO BREATH.
HOW 'BOUT YOU?
HOW'S THE ENVIRONMENTAL CLUB?
MM, KINDA LOST INTEREST.
WHAT?
YOU'RE TELLING ME
YOU DON'T CARE ABOUT
THOSE POOR,
STARVING DOLPHINS
IN THE RAIN FOREST?
THEY'RE NOT STARVING,
THEY'RE NOT IN
THE RAIN FOREST
AND YES,
I STILL CARE.
I'M JUST FOCUSED
ON OTHER STUFF.
LIKE WHAT?
JOGGING?
AND OTHER STUFF.
HEY, EMMA.
MANNY.
THIS BRENDON,
ONE OF THE KIDS
THAT I TUTOR.
I'LL MEET YOU BACK HERE
AT 3:30 P.M.?
I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU TUTORED.
WELL, MY MOM ASKED
AND I THOUGHT WHY NOT?
EVERYONE NEEDS
A HELPING HAND.
HOW NICE OF YOU.
SO, WHAT'S YOUR FAVOURITE
THING TO TEACH?
GRAMMAR?
COMPOSITION?
GETTING GIRLS DRUNK
AND FILMING THEM
WITH THEIR TOPS OFF?
THAT ONE'S NOT
IN THE CURRICULUM.
DIDN'T THINK SO.
QUIT THE HERO ACT,
PETER.
YOU'RE NOT FOOLING ANYONE.
WE ALL KNOW
YOU'RE SCUM.
EM,
WE'RE GONNA BE LATE
FOR GYM.
TOBY:
WE CAN'T JUST FILL
THE YEARBOOK
WITH PICTURES OF YOU TWO,
YOU KNOW.
YOU'VE GOT TO REPRESENT
THE WHOLE SCHOOL.
PAIGE AND I
WERE THE SCHOOL.
YEAH...
THERE'S A CONVINCING
ARGUMENT.
SORRY ALEX,
YOU ACTUALLY HAVE
TO PARTICIPATE
TO GET IN THE YEARBOOK.
(FAKE SIGH) AND THE VICIOUS
INSULT CLUB, DOESN'T COUNT?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
I THINK WE SHOULD
HANG OUT.
UH, THE SARCASM ASSOCIATION
DOESN'T GET YOU
INTO THE YEARBOOK EITHER.
WE DON'T HAVE TO BE
BEST FRIENDS...
OR EVEN FRIENDS.
I'LL SETTLE FOR ACQUAINTANCES.
ACQUAINTANCES WHO DON'T
KILL EACH OTHER.
SO, WHAT DO YOU SAY?
WHY DON'T WE ALL GO OUT,
GET LOADED,
AND GET INTO SOME TROUBLE?
I COULD DO UP
SOME FAKE I.D.'S?
TAKE YOU LADIES
ON A PUB CRAWL.
NICE TRY.
HAZEL:
OR...
WE COULD GO SHOPPING -
YOU, ME AND PAIGE -
AT THE MALL?
THERE'S A BIG SALE ON.
YOU'RE REALLY GONNA MAKE ME
WORK FOR THIS,
AREN'T YOU?
YOU BET.
SEE YOU AT 4:30.
LET ME GUESS...
YOU WENT TO VISIT
SHAQUILLE O'NEAL
AND ALL YOU GOT
WAS HIS RUNNING SUIT.
SHAQ IS GINORMOUS.
UH, YEAH,
AND THAT'S THE JOKE.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
'KAY GIRLS,
AS YOU CAN SEE,
WE'RE ROTATING STATIONS.
SO LET'S GROUP UP.
DARCY:
EMMA, IT'S LIKE
A GABILLION DEGREES IN HERE.
EMMA:
I'M KINDA COLD IS ALL.
CHANTAY:
YOU'RE KINDA WHACKED IS ALL.
OH NO! I THINK I SEE
AN EXTRA OUNCE
OVER HERE
ON YOUR RIGHT CHEEK!
CALL WEIGHT WATCHERS!
911!
YOU THINK IT'S FUN TO LAUGH
AT THE TUB OF LARD?
IT'S NOT!
I KNOW WHAT'S WRONG,
SO YOU CAN STOP
POINTING IT OUT!
YOU'RE SO NOT FAT, EMMA.
WE WERE JUST JOKING.
ARE YOU OKAY?
OF COURSE.
I'M FINE.
I JUST DON'T WANNA
BE HERE TODAY.
ARMSTRONG:
EMMA?
HAZEL:
I'M HAVING A FASHION
FLASH FORWARD.
PAIGE:
CUTE. A SASSY MIX
OF CONSERVATIVE COLOUR
AND EDGY MILITARY.
IT'S GREY.
PAIGE HATES GREY.
WHAT ABOUT... THIS?
HAZEL:
NO OFFENSE,
BUT I DON'T THINK YOU'RE READY
FOR THE BIG LEAGUES.
CAN YOU EVEN AFFORD
THOSE CLOTHES?
HAZEL.
I'M SORRY,
BUT FASHION ISN'T EXACTLY
WHAT ALEX'S TYPE DOES WELL.
(ANGRY HUFF)
MY "TYPE"?
LESBIAN, YOU MEAN?
NO -
THE STYLE-IMPAIRED.
LADIES, PLEASE, JUST CHILL.
HAZEL, THIS SHRUNKEN BLAZER?
IT SO HAS YOUR NAME ON IT.
THINK IT MIGHT BE
A LITTLE TOO SHRUNKEN
FOR HAZEL'S BODY TYPE.
GIMMIE.
YOU IN A BLAZER?
SPARE ME.
DO I DETECT JEALOUSY?
TELL ME, HOW LONG HAVE YOU
WANTED TO KISS PAIGE?
GROSS. THAT'S YOUR THING,
NOT MINE.
GUYS, STOP IT!
YOU'RE EMBARRASSING ME.
HAZEL:
AND BTW?
PAIGE USED TO BE STRAIGHT
UNTIL YOU CAME ALONG
AND TURNED HER GAY!
(LAUGHING)
WHAT?!
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M SORRY.
I'M THROUGH PLAYING NICE.
COULDN'T PULL IT OFF
FOR VERY LONG, HUH?
BIG SURPRISE.
(HANGERS CLANGING TOGETHER)
SHE STARTED IT!
NO, I DIDN'T!
PAIGE!
PAIGE.
(LOW CHATTER)
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
EMMA:
GOING TOO FAST FOR YOU,
GRAMPS?
I'LL SLOW DOWN
SO YOU DON'T HAVE
TO TRAIL BEHIND.
AW! BUT I LIKE TRAILING
BEHIND YOU.
THAT WAY I GET TO
ENJOY THE VIEW.
SORRY. SORRY. SORRY.
AWE, YOUR JOGGING BREATH
IS FINE.
NO. I MEAN THIS - US.
JUST WHEN I THOUGHT
WE WERE FINALLY
GETTING SOMEWHERE.
I WANNA GO OUT WITH YOU,
PETER,
I REALLY DO BUT-
IT'S MANNY.
WEBMASTER OF THE "PETER STONE
MUST DIE" WEBSITE.
WHY DOES SHE STILL
HATE ME SO MUCH?
FORGIVENESS IS NOT
MANNY'S FORTE.
BELIEVE ME, SHE'S LIKE
THE FIVE-TIME WINNER
OF THE GOLDEN GRUDGE.
WELL THEN...
THEN WHY DOES SHE
HAVE TO KNOW?
IT COULD BE
OUR LITTLE SECRET.
NO,
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND!
THIS IS ALL CONFUSING
AND MESSY
AND COMPLICATED
AND I CAN'T DO IT ANYMORE,
OKAY?
SORRY.
WELL, ME TOO.
THIS SUCKS!
YOU THINK YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
THAT'S UNHAPPY?
WELL, JOIN THE CLUB,
PETER!
I'VE GOT A HUGE PILE OF WORRIES
OVER HERE BY MYSELF, OKAY?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
NO!
I HAVE TO GO.
MANNY:
HERE. EAT THIS.
EMMA:
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR YOUR
"GIRL, INTERRUPTED" TODAY.
I FOUND YOUR FOOD DIARY.
YOU'RE NOT EATING.
AND THOSE PROTEIN BARS,
THEY'RE PROPS.
YOU'RE HIDING THEM.
IT'S NOT TRUE.
YOU'RE MAKING IT UP.
(READING)
"I HAVEN'T LOST WEIGHT
IN THREE DAYS.
I RUN TWICE AS MUCH
AND STILL NOTHING."
STOP IT.
MANNY: (READING)
"I CAN'T EAT.
MY BODY MAKES ME SICK.
IT'S REBELLING AGAINST ME,
JUST LIKE EVERYONE ELSE."
GIVE THAT BACK!
I BET SPIKE WOULD LOVE
TO READ THIS.
EMMA:
MANNY! NO!
I'M DATING PETER.
WHAT?
EMMA:
YOU HEARD ME.
I'M DATING PETER.
THAT'S WHY I'M LIKE THIS.
I CAN'T EAT.
I CAN'T SLEEP.
I'M STRESSED 24/7
BECAUSE I'M SO SCARED
OF YOU FINDING OUT!
NOW YOU KNOW.
TAKE YOUR STUPID DIARY.
I DON'T CARE ANYMORE.
YOU DO WHATEVER YOU WANT,
'CAUSE WE'RE THROUGH!
I'M SLEEPING
ON THE COUCH
AND TOMORROW, WE CAN TALK
ABOUT ME GOING HOME.
FINE.
GOT YOUR MESSAGES.
WHAT'S THE BIG NEWS?
WHY DON'T I SHOW YOU.
COME ON.
I TOLD MANNY EVERYTHING.
WE'RE LEGIT.
AND SHE'S OKAY WITH IT?
WELL THAT'S SORT OF
THE PROBLEM.
AND SPEAK OF THE DEVIL...
WELL,
LOOK AT THE HAPPY COUPLE.
MANNY, SAVE THE DRAMA
FOR YOUR NEXT AUDITION.
WE'RE NOT INTERESTED.
MANNY:
FINE.
I JUST WANT WISH PETER
GOOD LUCK.
THANKS, I GUESS.
MANNY:
YOU'RE GONNA NEED IT.
MAYBE YOU CAN KEEP TRACK
OF WHETHER OR NOT
SHE'S EATING,
'CAUSE I'M DONE.
WHAT IS SHE
TALKING ABOUT?
I DON'T KNOW, PETER.
SHE'S COMPLETELY CRAZY.
COME ON, WE HAVE SOME FLAUNTING
TO DO.
YOUR FAVOURITE.
I WENT AND PICKED IT UP
AFTER SECURITY LET US GO.
I'M NOT TALKING TO YOU.
I HAD TO GO ALL THE WAY
TO MISSISSAUGA TO GET IT -
ON TRANSIT.
UH, HOW MUCH?
CASHIER:
$2.16.
I'M SORRY, OKAY?
BUT SHE PUSHED MY BUTTONS
RIGHT IN.
$2.20.
CASHIER:
HERE'S YOUR CHANGE.
I TRIED.
THAT'S GOTTA COUNT
FOR SOMETHING.
HAVE A GOOD DAY.
THANKS.
I JUST CARE ABOUT YOU.
GREAT JOB SHOWING IT.
PETER:
TO US.
COMPLETELY OFFICIAL
FOR ALL THE WORLD TO SEE.
YAY US.
CAN WE GET S-
KETCHUP.
WE NEED KETCHUP.
WHOA.
THAT IS IMPRESSIVE.
WHAT CAN I SAY,
I'M A HEALTHY, GROWING GIRL.
PETER:
SOMETHING'S MISSING HERE.
YOU'RE SO MYSTERIOUS.
I JUST THOUGHT
WITH US COMING OUT
THERE'D BE LIKE A
MARCHING BAND
OR SOMETHING.
MAYBE A BLIMP
WITH OUR NAME ON IT.
HEY, NOT FEELING
SO HUGGABLE RIGHT NOW.
EMMA, YOU'VE GOT FRIES
IN YOUR POCKET.
IT'S JUST A LITTLE SNACK
FOR LATER.
COLD FRENCH FRIES
FROM YOUR POCKET?
THAT'S A LITTLE WEIRD.
NOT REALLY.
HAVEN'T YOU SEEN
"NAPOLEON DYNAMITE"?
COME ON.
I'M JUST LIKE
A LITTLE SQUIRREL.
SURE.
I GOTTA GET TO CLASS.
SEE YA.
PAIGE ISN'T TALKING
TO ME.
ME NEITHER.
WELL, I HAPPEN TO BE
UPSET ABOUT IT.
SO DO I.
I DO HAVE FEELINGS,
YOU KNOW.
AND WHEN PAIGE
GETS UPSET-
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
SHE'S THE STUBBORNEST PERSON
I EVER KNEW.
OH, ME TOO!
AND IF YOU REALLY
WANT TO KNOW
HOW BAD A FREEZE-OUT
CAN GET?
PHONE ASHLEY KERWIN UP.
WE COULD TRY PLAYING
NICE, AGAIN.
"AGAIN?"
WE COULD TRY PLAYING NICE
PERIOD.
IF WE GO FOR HOT BEVERAGES,
PROMISE NOT TO SCALD ME?
JUST AS LONG
AS YOU PROMISE
TO LEAVE YOUR CYANIDE
AT HOME.
(BELL RINGS)
MANNY:
SO, YOU ALL HAVE YOUR SCHEDULES?
NEXT MEETING'S TUESDAY.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
TO SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
GOOD FOR YOU, PETER.
LEARNING TO READ
IS VERY IMPORTANT.
HIDING FOOD, BAGGY CLOTHES,
MOOD SWINGS, PARANOIA.
THOSE ARE ALL POSSIBLE SYMPTOMS
OF ANOREXIA-NERVOSA.
I'LL TALK TO HER MOM.
NO, WE'LL TALK
TO HER MOM.
HATE ME ALL YOU WANT,
EMMA'S MY GIRLFRIEND.
YOU CAN'T STOP ME
FROM HELPING HER.
DON'T EVEN TRY.
SO...
(CLEARS THROAT UNCOMFORTABLY)
WHAT IS THIS?
PAIGE-LIKERS CLUB.
ALEX IS TRYING
TO GET INTO THE YEARBOOK.
AND THE FIGHTING
BEGINS WHEN?
WE'VE SIGNED
A PEACE TREATY.
WE ALSO BOUGHT YOU
A TREAT.
WE EVEN WENT DUTCH
TO PAY FOR IT.
SO YOU KNOW,
YOU GUYS MADE ME REALLY MAD.
AND I REFUSE TO BE
THE MONKEY IN THE MIDDLE.
ALEX:
THAT'S FINE.
AS LONG AS YOU'RE
A TALKING MONKEY,
'CAUSE WE'RE A LITTLE STUCK
FOR CONVERSATION.
PAIGE:
OKAY...
LET'S AH, START WITH
HOW MANY CALORIES
ARE IN THIS BEVERAGE.
I ALWAYS ORDER NO WHIP.
TOLD YOU SO, ALEX.
PAIGE DOESN'T EAT SWEETS.
THAT'S A LIE.
SHUT UP!
YOU HAD THREE PIECES
OF CHOCOLATE CHEESECAKE
LAST WEEKEND!
IT WAS OUR TWO MONTH
ANNIVERSARY!
(LAUGHING)
OOPS! MY SPOON SLIPPED.
OOPS!
SO DID MINE!
(LAUGHING)
NO YOU DIDN'T!
(GIGGLING AND LAUGHING)
WHAT'S GOING ON?
SPIKE:
COME SIT DOWN HERE, HONEY.
MANNY AND PETER
CAME HERE
BECAUSE THEY'RE WORRIED
ABOUT YOU.
SIMPSON:
AND IT'S NOT JUST THEM.
YOUR TEACHERS TOLD ME
YOU'RE HAVING TROUBLE AT SCHOOL.
THEY'RE LYING.
NO, THEY'RE NOT.
EMMA...
WE WANT YOU TO GO
TALK TO SOMEONE -
A THERAPIST -
ABOUT WHY YOU'RE NOT EATING.
I AM EATING.
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG!
YOU'RE HIDING FOOD.
YOU'VE GOT MAJOR
PSYCHO MOOD SWINGS.
YOU'RE JUST NOT YOU.
WE'RE WORRIED.
(TEARING UP)
YOU GUYS ALL SO PERFECT.
YOU TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF DRUNK GIRLS.
YOU ARE THE DRUNK GIRL.
AND LAST TIME I CHECKED,
YOU WERE MAKING OUT
WITH HIS MOTHER.
EMMA,
YOU NEED TO CALM DOWN.
NO, I NEED TO
GET OUT OF HERE.
MANNY:
YOU CAN'T GO, EMMA.
PLEASE.
WE NEED TO GET YOU HELP.
YOU DID THIS!
YOU TOLD THEM!
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT,
MANNY!
(CRYING AND HYPERVENTILATING)
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?!
THAT'S MY STUFF!
I'M KICKING YOUR SORRY BUTT OUT,
MANNY,
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
MANNY:
PLEASE, STOP IT!
EMMA, PLEASE!
PLEASE STOP.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
MY FRIEND, MANNY!
I CAN'T EVEN
TRUST YOU ANYMORE!
I AM! THAT'S WHY
I'M TRYING TO HELP YOU!
(SHORT TIGHT BREATHS)
I CAN'T BREATH.
MY CHEST.
MANNY,
SOMETHING'S HAPPENING-
SIMPSON:
WHOA! EMMA!
P-PETER!
PETER, CALL 911! NOW!
EMMA, JUST LOOK AT US,
OKAY?
SPIKE:
ARCHIE...
NICE, LADIES.
ANOTHER NIGHT IN
THE SECURITY OFFICE.
(LAUGHING) THINK OF IT
AS MALL DETENTION.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE DIVED
OVER THE COUNTER
FOR THAT WHIPPED CREAM
CANISTER.
IF ONLY
THOSE GERMAN TOURISTS
HADN'T GOTTEN IN THE WAY.
(LAUGHING)
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU
THINK THIS IS FUNNY.
IT'S PATHETIC.
SAYS THE GIRL WHO WAS
THROWING- (LAUGHING)
BISCOTTI BOMBS.
ALL:
(LAUGHING)
(BURST INTO LAUGHTER)
EW!
(MONITOR BEEPS)
SPIKE:
THE DOCTOR SAID
YOU HAD A PANIC ATTACK.
EMMA:
'KAY, SO I'M FINE.
MUST'VE BEEN A REACTION
TO ONE OF THOSE
PROTEIN BARS.
THAT'S THE LAST TIME
I EAT ONE OF THOSE
NASTY THINGS-
EMMA!
YOU'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
BUT IT WAS JUST
A PANIC ATTACK.
BROUGHT ON BY STARVATION.
A PSYCHIATRIST IS COMING
TO TALK TO YOU.
AND SHE MIGHT
DIAGNOSE YOU...
AS ANOREXIC.
I WANNA GO HOME.
HONEY, YOU CAN'T.
(WHISPERS)
YOU CAN'T.
EM, YOU HAVE TO STOP.
YOU HAVE TO STOP
OR YOU'RE GONNA DIE.
YOU CAN'T DO THAT TO ME.
NO ONE'S GONNA DIE,
OKAY?
OKAY.
I'M GONNA TRY TO BEAT THIS,
MANNY.
I'M GONNA TRY TO BEAT THIS.