MIA:
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR,
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT!
OKAY, TEAM, BIG NEWS!
FIRST,
YOU HAVE A BIG FAN.
UM...
PRACTICE IS CLOSED.
I'LL LEAVE
AS SOON AS YOU SAY
YOU'LL GO SEE PINK FLOYD
WITH ME
THIS FRIDAY NIGHT.
TICKETS ARE $125 EACH...
BUT THEY'RE WORTH IT.
BETTER BE.
OR ELSE A SECOND DATE...
OUT OF THE QUESTION.
I'LL TAKE THAT
AS A "YES."
(CHUCKLES)
LIFE IS GOOD
FOR HOLLY J.
LIFE IS GREAT!
FOR ALL POWER SQUADDERS!
WE MADE THE FLORIDA CHEERBURST
CHEERLEADING COMPETITION!
I TOLD YOU IF WE WORKED
HARD ENOUGH...
WOW! FIRST TIME!
BEST CAPTAIN EVER!
I'M GONNA NEED YOUR CHECKS
TOMORROW.
$350 BIG ONES.
WOW, UH...
THAT'S A LOT OF MONEY.
WE'RE WORTH IT.
DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE TAKING UP
SCRAP-BOOKING AGAIN.
NO, HONEY.
I'VE GOT SOME BAD NEWS.
WE SHOULD'VE TOLD YOU
SOONER,
BUT WE THOUGHT THINGS
WOULD GET BETTER.
CUT TO THE CHASE,
MOM.
YOUR FATHER MADE
SOME RISKY INVESTMENTS.
SO...?
SO, WE'RE TRYING
TO SAVE THE HOUSE.
BUT THINGS ARE GOING
TO HAVE TO CHANGE.
HAND OVER
YOUR CREDIT CARD.
HOLLY J:
BUT, MOM, I NEED MONEY.
THE POWER SQUAD'S
GOING ON A TRIP!
I HAVE A DATE!
I'M SORRY, HONEY.
I ALREADY CUT UP MINE.
HOLLY J:
YOU CAN'T JUST GO
CHANGING EVERYTHING!
YOU'RE RUINING MY LIFE!
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Oh! Oh! Oh! ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
HOLLY J:
I'VE WORKED REALLY HARD
ON POWER SQUAD THIS YEAR.
NOW YOU'RE TELLING ME
I CAN'T GO TO CHEERBURST!
THAT'S NOT FAIR!
MAYBE THERE'S SOME SORT
OF FINANCIAL AID.
PLEASE.
I CAN SEE THE ANTI GRAPEVINE
HEADLINE NOW.
MEET HOLLY J.,
DEGRASSI'S NEWEST CHARITY CASE.
IT'S NOT EASY
ON ANY OF US.
YOUR FATHER EXPECTS ME
TO GET A JOB!
WHAT COULD I POSSIBLY DO
AFTER ALL THESE YEARS?
I DON'T KNOW.
PERSONAL SHOPPER?
YOU'LL HAVE TO GIVE UP
THE CONCERT.
WE'LL SEE ABOUT THE TRIP.
HERE.
DON'T FORGET YOUR LUNCH.
HOLLY J:
(EXASPERATED BREATH)
PICK ME UP AT FIVE?
THEY'RE TAKING BACK
THE CAR TODAY;
YOU'LL HAVE
TO TAKE THE BUS.
HEY! COME ON.
DID I HEAR YOUR MOM SAY
THAT YOU'RE TAKING
THE BUS NOW?
UH, YEAH, I INSISTED!
IT'S NEVER TOO LATE
TO GO GREEN.
BUT YOU HATE
THE BUS.
PEOPLE CHANGE.
AND DON'T GET DISTRACTED.
WE HAVE A COMPETITION
TO WIN!
YOU'RE RIGHT.
PETER:
ENTERTAINMENT SCOOP'S
REALLY DOING A PIECE ON YOU?
CRAZY RIGHT?
THE SHEP OKAYED THEM
COMING TO THE SCHOOL
AND EVERYTHING.
I CAN'T THINK
OF ANYONE
MORE DESERVING
OF THE ATTENTION.
DAWES:
DON'T HESITATE TO TAKE
YOUR PASTELS HOME TONIGHT,
THEY'RE DUE THURSDAY,
AND PLEASE MAKE SURE THAT
THESE WORKSTATIONS ARE CLEAN
WHEN YOU LEAVE.
THANK YOU!
GISELLE MAKES $40 MILLION
A YEAR.
WONDER HOW MUCH MIA
IS BANKING?
UGH.
BLUE:
TWO TICKETS TO PINK FLOYD!
WAITED SIX HOURS.
I HOPE YOU CAN SCALP THEM,
BECAUSE...
I CAN'T COME
TO THE CONCERT.
WHY?
EMERGENCY POWER SQUAD
PRACTICE.
SINCE WHEN?
IF UM... YOU DON'T WANNA
GO WITH ME, JUST SAY.
I DON'T WANNA GO
WITH YOU.
GREAT.
GLAD I FOUND THIS OUT
AFTER I WAITED SIX HOURS
IN THE RAIN.
SEE YA AROUND.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU'RE NOT BULIMIC
OR ANYTHING?
I'M HUNGRY.
I THOUGHT IT MIGHT BE NICE
TO EAT IN PEACE FOR ONCE
WITHOUT MINDLESS CHATTER
LIKE YOURS.
OKAY WITH YOU?
WHATEVER.
NEVER MIND.
MIA:
...BECAUSE YOU WANNA DANCE.
PETER:
DANCE?
COME ON, DANCE WITH ME.
PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE.
WASN'T EXACTLY THE PLAN,
BUT...
IF IT MAKES YOU HAPPY.
IT DOES.
OKAY.
IT DEFINITELY DOES.
(DOOR OPENS)
MOM!
PETER!
MS. HATZILAKOS!
MIA.
HI, HOW ARE YOU?
UH, WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
THERE WAS A LAST MINUTE
SEAT SALE,
SO I THOUGHT I'D COME
AND SURPRISE YOU.
YOU MEAN CHECK UP ON ME.
DO I GET A HUG?
HUH?
(ELATED LAUGH)
I'LL GET YOU THE BED.
HOW LONG'RE YOU HERE FOR?
OH, NOT LONG.
I WAS ONLY ABLE
TO GET GIA'S CAREGIVER
TO STAY A COUPLE OF NIGHTS.
DO YOU HAVE CLEAN SHEETS?
UH... MAYBE.
WELL, LOOKS LIKE I DIDN'T COME
A MINUTE TOO SOON, HUH, MIA?
REALLY DON'T KNOW HOW
YOU LIVE IN THIS PLACE.
(TRAFFIC WHIRS BY)
(HALF LAUGHS) NO.
I'M CAPTAIN OF THE DEGRASSI
POWER SQUAD,
PRESIDENT OF THE DEGRASSI
STUDENT COUNCIL,
AND I HAVE EXTENSIVE
RETAIL EXPERIENCE.
RETAIL?
I'M AN EXPERT SHOPPER.
(HALF LAUGHS)
YEAH, UM...
I'M NOT SURE YOU'RE A GOOD FIT
FOR THE DOT.
I NEED THIS JOB.
WHY? DADDY WON'T SPRING
FOR SOME CHANNEL BAG?
IT'S CHANEL.
AND NO.
MY UNIVERSITY APPLICATIONS
ADVISOR
TOLD ME I NEEDED
JOB EXPERIENCE.
I'M GONNA REGRET THIS...
(RELUCTANT BREATH)
BUT I NEED SOMEBODY,
SO, UM...
YOU'RE ON PROBATION UNTIL
YOU PROVE YOURSELF. OKAY?
HMM.
HOW HARD CAN IT BE?
YOU DO IT.
(ELECTRIC GUITAR PLAYS)
♪ LET'S SKIP HOMEROOM
I WANNA SEE YOUR BEDROOM ♪
♪ LET'S GET SEXY,
FORGET WHAT YOUR DADDY SAID ♪
♪ I'M NOT INTO STUDYING
OR GETTING GOOD GRADES ♪
♪ I JUST WANNA PARTY
AND MAYBE GET L... ♪
(MUSIC FADES AWAY)
GUYS?
DUDE, THE PRINCIPAL'S
WATCHING.
WELL, DEAL WITH IT!
WE GOT A LOT OF SONGS
TO GET THROUGH.
IT'S GETTING LATE.
SHOULDN'T YOU BOYS
BE GOING HOME?
WE PRACTICE HERE
SO THAT PARENTS DON'T BUG US.
DON'T USE THAT TONE WITH ME.
PETER:
I WASN'T USING A TONE.
ARE WE DONE?
ALL RIGHT, COME ON, GUYS!
♪ I'M NOT INTO STUDYING
OR GETTING GOOD GRADES ♪
♪ I JUST WANNA PARTY
AND MAYBE GET L... ♪
BRUCE:
WHERE, WHERE'RE THE FRIES
I ORDERED?
FRYING!
HEY! MY MILKSHAKE?!
WILL COME WITH THE FRIES.
(DOOR OPENS, CHIMES JINGLE)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
BEHIND THE COUNTER?
I'M JUST WORKING ON
MY RESUME FOR UNIVERSITY.
IF YOU DON'T HAVE A JOB YET,
YOU BETTER GET ON IT.
YOU SHOULDA COME WITH US
TO GET BIKINIS FOR FLORIDA.
LOOK.
MIA MADE A CALL,
WE WENT STRAIGHT
TO THE DESIGNERS!
I CAN GO WITH YOU TOMORROW
IF YOU WANT.
MY CREDIT CARD
IS MAXED OUT.
MIA SAYS SHE CAN GET US INTO
ALL THESE COOL FASHION EVENTS!
HOW NEAT IS THAT?
BRUCE:
YO!
FRENCH FRIES!
DEREK:
MY MILKSHAKE!
SPINNER:
HOLLY J, GET TO IT.
BRUCE:
IT'S OIL AND GREASE.
OH... OOH.
THANKS.
FANTASTIC.
(SPITS)
UGH! THIS SUCKS.
YOU GAVE ME SOME NO-FAT
POWER SQUAD MILKSHAKE
BY MISTAKE.
YEAH?
WELL IT GOES JUST RIGHT
WITH YOUR FULL-FAT HEAD.
CUSTOMERS:
OHHH! (LAUGHING)
(IN DISBELIEF)
OH!
SPINNER:
GUYS, I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY.
MILKSHAKE,
FRIES ON THE HOUSE.
HERE. HERE.
HOLLY J! WORD!
PLEASE.
DEREK IS A JERK,
BUT YOU CAN'T DO THAT!
THE CUSTOMER'S ALWAYS RIGHT.
OKAY?
LOOK, MAYBE YOU'RE A LOSER
WHO LIKES THE IDEA
OF CLEANING UP AFTER MORONS
FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
NOT ME!
WELL, IF YOU'RE TOO GOOD
FOR IT,
GIMME YOUR APRON.
YOU'RE FIRED. GET OUT.
WORKS FOR ME!
(DOOR CHIMES JINGLE)
(TEARY BREATHS)
MS. HATZILAKOS:
YOU DON'T NEED TO SNEAK.
I'M AWAKE.
(SIGHS)
SO, WHAT WERE YOU DOING
OUT SO LATE?
I THOUGHT I'D GIVE YOU
SOME SPACE.
WELL, I'D LIKE YOU
TO COME BACK
TO REGINA WITH ME
AFTER THIS SEMESTER.
NO WAY!
YOU NEED SOMEONE HERE
TO KEEP THINGS UNDER CONTROL.
THEY ARE!
I'M GETTING BETTER GRADES,
I HAVE MORE FRIENDS,
I'M HAPPIER.
THAT'S GREAT.
BUT IT'S NOT THE SAME THING
AS LIVING WITH A PARENT.
IT'S BETTER!
EVERYTHING WORKS GREAT
WHEN YOU'RE FAR AWAY!
MAYBE WE JUST NEED
TO SLEEP ON IT.
YOU'RE IN MY BED.
(BEDROOM DOOR CLOSES)
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
INTERVIEWER:
DEGRASSI MAY BE
A REGULAR HIGH SCHOOL,
BUT BRAND NEW T-BOMBZ GIRL
MIA JONES
IS ANYTHING
BUT A REGULAR STUDENT.
YOUR TEAMMATES MUST BE
SO PROUD OF YOU.
MIA:
THEY'RE GREAT.
HEY.
HEY, HAVE YOU DONE
A MIA INTERVIEW YET?
I DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR TRASH TV.
OH, BUT IT'S SO COOL
THAT OUR MIA'S THIS BIG MODEL.
GUESS WHAT?
SHE'S STILL DEFINITELY
COMING TO FLORIDA.
OH YEAH?
TURNS OUT I CAN'T GO.
YOU'RE MISSING CHEERBURST!
WHY?
IT'S MY FAMILY...
CHANTAY:
HEY!
FAMILY WEDDING.
I COMPLETELY FORGOT
IT'S THE SAME WEEKEND.
HOLLY J ISN'T COMING
TO FLORIDA!
BUT YOU'RE THE CAPTAIN!
YOU HAVE TO LEAD THE TEAM!
YOU'LL HAVE TO LIMP THROUGH
WITHOUT ME, I GUESS.
MAYBE MIA?
INTERVIEWER:
FAVOURITE FOOD?
GOOD IDEA!
GRILLED CHEESE.
DEFINITELY.
ALSO ONE OF MY FAVES.
P.A. ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION, STUDENTS.
WOULD MACKENZIE PALASTINE
PLEASE REPORT TO THE OFFICE.
THANK YOU.
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
I'M SORRY ABOUT WHAT I SAID
IN THE WASHROOM.
IT'S OKAY.
IT'S JUST THIS MIA WORSHIP
IS REALLY GETTING TO ME.
IT'S LIKE AN ALL MIA
ALL THE TIME CHANNEL!
I KNOW.
WEREN'T YOU FRIENDS?
LEIA:
NOT REALLY.
I WENT TO ONE PARTY WITH HER;
THAT WAS ENOUGH FOR ME.
EVERY TIME
I LOOK AT THESE POSTERS
I THINK ABOUT WHAT SHE DID
TO GET UP THERE.
WHAT'D SHE DO?
MIA:
YEAH, OF COURSE.
ALLI:
CAN I GET YOUR AUTOGRAPH, MIA?
I THINK YOUR STYLE IS AWESOME.
CHANTAY:
DON'T WORRY ABOUT MISSING
THE FLORIDA TRIP.
WE ASKED MIA IF SHE'D BE
ACTING CAPTAIN DOWN THERE
AND SHE SAID YES.
MMM.
YOU BRING YOUR LUNCH NOW?
I FORGOT SOMETHING.
I GOTTA GO.
INTERVIEWER:
I THINK WE NEED
LIKE ONE MORE PERSON -
MAYBE A COUPLE MORE -
I JUST NEED SOMETHING ELSE.
DO YOU HAVE
ENOUGH TAPE LEFT?
CAMERAMAN: YEAH.
INTERVIEWER: OKAY, GOOD.
UM...
YOU'RE DOING A PIECE
ON MIA JONES, RIGHT?
REPORTER:
YEAH. THE FRESH-FACED STAR.
SHE SURE LANDED THE SWEET LIFE,
HUH?
MAYBE NOT SO FRESH.
SOUNDS INTERESTING.
DO TELL.
(TV SHOW THEME MUSIC PLAYS)
REPORTER:
RUNWAYS, PHOTOSHOOTS,
SIZZLIN' SPORTS CELEBS!
BRAND NEW T-BOMBZ GIRL
MIA JONES
IS ANYTHING
BUT A REGULAR STUDENT.
THERE'S EVEN TALK
THAT SHE MIGHT DO
A HAUTE COUTURE SHOW
AT PARIS FASHION WEEK.
FROM OBSCURITY TO STARDOM
IN JUST A FEW MONTHS,
MIA'S RISE TO FAME
HAS BEEN QUICK.
BUT WHAT EXACTLY IS THE PRICE
OF SUCH INSTANT STARDOM?
ALL I KNOW IS THAT PEOPLE
ARE SAYING
THAT MIA LIKES TO HANG OUT
AT WILD SEX PARTIES.
I GUESS IF YOU HAVE A KID
AT THIRTEEN,
SLEEPING AROUND TO GET A JOB
ISN'T A BIG DEAL.
STILL, IT SEEMS SAD FOR SOMEONE
TO GO SO FAR
FOR A LITTLE FAME.
REPORTER:
MIA JONES, ANOTHER YOUNG GIRL
POISED ON THE BRINK
OF CELEBRITY,
TO BE FOREVER HAUNTED
BY THE RUMOURS
OF HARD PARTYING
AND SCANDALOUS SEX!
WE'VE SEEN THIS
RISE TO FAME BEFORE
AND IT USUALLY
DOESN'T END WELL.
SO WHAT'S NEXT FOR MIA JONES?
A SEX TAPE?
REHAB?
WE CAN ONLY HOPE
MIA'S PATH TO FAME
DOESN'T LEAD DOWN THIS ROAD.
I SHOULD PROBABLY GO.
PETER:
NO, NO, NO.
DON'T LEAVE.
IT'S OKAY.
NO ONE'S GONNA BELIEVE IT.
BUT...
PART OF WHAT HOLLY J SAID,
PART OF IT'S TRUE.
THAT DOESN'T MATTER.
I MADE SOME BIG MISTAKES...
I'M REALLY SORRY
YOU HAD TO FIND OUT LIKE THIS.
IT'S IN THE PAST.
I DON'T CARE.
I LIKE YOU
FOR WHO YOU ARE NOW;
THAT'S WHAT COUNTS.
(RELIEVED BREATH)
YOU'RE AMAZING.
DO YOU KNOW THAT?
MRS. SINCLAIR:
I GOT SOMETHING FOR YOU.
AH! AN EVICTION NOTICE?
WHAT, DO WE HAVE TO RENT OUT
MY BEDROOM NOW?
MRS. SINCLAIR:
NO.
SOME GOOD NEWS FOR A CHANGE.
FROM HEATHER.
SHE SAID NO CHEERLEADING
COMPETITION WOULD BE COMPLETE
WITHOUT A SINCLAIR.
(STUNNED BREATH)
I HEARD.
IS MIA OKAY?
YEAH.
I'M GONNA GO CHECK
ON THE TENANTS,
MAYBE PICK SOMETHING UP
FOR SUPPER.
WHATEVER.
YOU KNOW YOU WERE VERY,
UM...
KIND...
MATURE WITH MIA.
MIA'S LUCKY TO HAVE
SOMEONE LIKE YOU TO TALK TO.
THANKS, I GUESS.
I REALLY MISS YOU.
YOU KNOW,
IT'S BEEN REALLY HARD
TAKING CARE OF GIAGIA.
I AM SO PROUD OF YOU
AND HOW YOU'RE TURNING OUT.
(DOOR OPENS)
P.A. ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION STUDENTS...
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
BRUCE:
SO...
DO ALL MODELS DO THAT STUFF?
MIA:
GET A LIFE, BRUCE.
BRUCE:
I'D, I'D LOVE TO...
GET A LIFE...
WHERE MODELS LIKE YOU
DO WHATEVER IT IS YOU DO
AT THOSE PARTIES.
I GUESS THEY SAW
THE STORY TOO, HUH?
I GUESS YOU GUYS
ALL HAVE
WAY TOO MUCH TIME
ON YOUR HANDS.
BRUCE:
(SMARMY CHUCKLE)
I GUESS SO.
MIA:
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT!
ANYA AND CHANTAY:
ONE CENT! TWO CENTS!
THREE CENTS! A DOLLAR!
ALL FOR DEGRASSI,
STAND UP AND HOLLER!
HOLLY J:
UM... (CLAPS TWICE)
OKAY, TEAM.
BIG NEWS.
I'M COMING TO THE CHEERBURST
AFTER ALL.
I'VE DECIDED THIS TEAM
IS MORE IMPORTANT
THAN MY COUSIN'S WEDDING.
SORRY. ONLY TEAM PLAYERS
ON THIS TRIP.
NO ONE'S MORE DEDICATED
TO THIS TEAM THAN ME.
CHANTAY:
YOU'RE SO DEDICATED
YOU'LL SELL OUT
ONE OF YOUR TEAMMATES
ON NATIONAL TV?
ALL I DID WAS SAY
WHAT I HEARD.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT HAPPENED.
I MADE A MISTAKE
AND MY TEAMMATES
UNDERSTAND THAT.
ANYA:
AND WHAT YOU SAID WAS MEAN
AND HURTFUL.
CHANTAY:
AND YOUR TEAMMATES
DON'T UNDERSTAND THAT.
ANYA:
ALL IN FAVOUR OF VOTING HOLLY J
OFF THE POWER SQUAD?
YOU GUYS HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT'S GOING ON WITH ME.
YOU CAN'T DO THIS.
WE CAN AND WE HAVE.
SO, IT'S NOT ENOUGH
TO BE THE BIG MODEL,
NOW YOU'VE GOTTA TURN EVERYONE
AGAINST ME TOO?
NO, HOLLY J,
LIFE HANDS YOU STUFF
AND ALL YOU GET TO CHOOSE
IS WHAT YOU'LL DO
WITH WHAT YOU GET.
HM. SO NOW YOU'RE THE TOP MODEL
AND DR. PHIL!
GOOD LUCK WINNING ANYTHING
IN FLORIDA WITHOUT ME.
JUST THE GUY
I WANTED TO SEE.
WHY?
TURNS OUT I'M FREE
FRIDAY NIGHT AFTER ALL.
OH?
NO EMERGENCY POWER SQUAD
PRACTICE?
NO.
THINGS CHANGED.
YOU KNOW, MISS HOLLY J,
I FINALLY FIGURED YOU OUT.
YOU DID?
YEAH.
YOU'RE THE KIND OF GIRL
WHO EXPECTS EVERYTHING
HANDED TO HER
ON A SILVER PLATTER.
AND I'M NOT INTERESTED
IN A GIRL LIKE THAT.
I GOT YOUR MESSAGE.
WHY DIDN'T YOU WANT ME
TO PICK ANYTHING UP...
FOR DINNER?
MAYBE YOU SHOULD'VE.
I TOTALLY BURNT THE MEATLOAF.
(DISBELIEVING GASP)
YOU COOKED?
I NEVER ONCE ASKED
HOW GIAGIA WAS DOING.
HOW YOU WERE DOING,
TAKING CARE OF HER.
ANYTHING ABOUT YOUR LIFE
AT ALL.
SO YOU MADE MEATLOAF?
I COOKED YOU DINNER.
TO TRY TO APOLOGIZE
FOR BEING SUCH A JERK.
YOU KNOW, I DIDN'T COME HERE
TO SPY ON YOU.
I JUST...
I MISSED YOU.
AND BEING ALONE
WAS HARD AT FIRST,
BUT NOW I LIKE IT.
WELL...
YOU'VE DONE A GOOD JOB.
I CAN SEE WHY
YOU DON'T WANNA MOVE.
BUT LET'S NOT GO SO LONG
WITHOUT SEEING EACH OTHER.
DEFINITELY.
(DOOR CHIME JINGLES)
(CAFE MUSIC PLAYS,
LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
CAN I HAVE MY JOB BACK?
(LAUGHS)
NOW WHY WOULD I DO THAT?
BECAUSE I NEED THE MONEY.
BEFORE IT WAS FOR YOUR
UNIVERSITY APPLICATIONS.
GET YOUR STORY STRAIGHT,
HUH?
THE TRUTH IS THAT...
I NEEDED THIS JOB TO PAY
FOR OUR POWER SQUAD TRIP
TO FLORIDA.
AND YOU CAN'T WEASEL IT
OUT OF DADDY?
"DADDY" IS BROKE.
AND I GOT KICKED OFF
THE POWER SQUAD.
OUCH.
WHY'D YOU GET KICKED OFF?
I TOLD A REPORTER
SOME BAD GOSSIP ABOUT MIA.
WHOA.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHY I DID IT, REALLY.
I DO.
I STOLE MY BEST FRIEND'S
MP3 PLAYER ONCE.
WHY?
BECAUSE HE HAD ALL THE STUFF
AND I DIDN'T.
SEE?!
LIFE IS SO UNFAIR!
LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
YOU GOT BOTH PARENTS?
YEAH.
MY DAD DIED ON ME.
OH.
I'M SORRY.
THANKS.
YOU HAVE BALL CANCER?
OF COURSE NOT.
WELL, I DID.
AND IF I COULD GET
THROUGH ALL THAT,
YOU CAN GET THROUGH THIS.
RIGHT?
YEAH.
(SNIFFLES)
CONNOR:
UM, EXCUSE ME.
CAN WE GET SOME SERVICE,
PLEASE?
ALL RIGHT, SPECS,
WHAT CAN I GET YOU?
AND IT BETTER NOT JUST BE
TWO WATERS.