SAV:
WELL, IT'S BEEN SIX MONTHS,
RIGHT?
SO, I'M THINKING...
WHOA!
ABOUT TIME, DUDE!
DOES ANYA KNOW?
OH, OKAY, OKAY.
I'M A SKILLED
MOTH COLLECTOR,
AND NOW THAT WE'LL BE
AWAY FROM STREET LAMPS,
I'LL GET BETTER RESULTS.
HEY, KID.
UM, MY NAME
IS CONNOR.
HEY, CONNOR,
SHUT UP.
BUT I WAS JUST TELLING HIM
ABOUT MY MOTH COLLECTION.
DON'T MAKE ME
POUND YOU.
I GET TO GO!
WHY?
IT'S AN EDUCATIONAL
OPPORTUNITY.
AND I TOLD DAD
YOU'D KEEP AN EYE ON ME.
THE THING IS THAT...
THERE MIGHT BE
DIFFERNT ACTIVITIES
FOR DIFFERENT GRADES.
I MIGHT NOT BE ABLE TO...
BUT YOUR TOP PRIORITY
WILL BE TO LOOK AFTER
YOUR SISTER.
WON'T IT?
YES, FATHER.
GOOD.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh! ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
I THOUGHT YOU HATED
CAMPING.
I DO.
BUGS, COLD, WET.
SO... WHY?
BECAUSE I'M GOING
CATCH SOMETHING
AND IT WON'T BE BUGS.
YOU LIKE SOMEONE.
WHO?
I'LL LET YOU KNOW
IF THINGS WORKOUT,
BUT SAV CAN'T KNOW.
WHY NOT?
HE'S GOT A WHOLE DIFFERENT
SET OF RULES THAN I DO.
BUT YOUR PARENTS
LET YOU COME ON THE TRIP.
ONLY BECAUSE I SOLD EVERYONE
AT FAMILY DINNER
WITH THE WHOLE
"EDUCATIONAL VALUE."
FAMILY DINNER?
(HALF LAUGHS)
WHO WAS THERE?
AH, YOU KNOW, EVERYONE;
AUNTS, UNCLES, COUSINS.
SO BORING!
COME ON,
EVERYONE'S WAITING.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE,
WELCOME TO THE DEGRASSI ECOLOGY
AWARENESS TRIP.
WOO-HOO!
NOW, YOU ALL HAVE
TO FILL OUT THESE FORMS
TO ASSESS YOUR CARBON FOOTPRINT
ON THE PLANET.
UM, WHERE IS ALLI
AND ANYA?
UH, THEY'LL BE
RIGHT BACK.
HI.
I'M ALLI.
WHAT ARE YOU READING?
A BOOK.
THAT'S A JOKE,
RIGHT?
THAT WOULD BE CORRECT.
YOU READY TO CELEBRATE
OUR SIX MONTH?
THAT'S HANDY.
NOW WE CAN SAY WE WENT OUT
FOR EXACTLY SIX MONTHS.
I, I DON'T FOLLOW.
YOUR LAST FAMILY GATHERING
DIDN'T INCLUDE ME.
ALLI...
DIDN'T MEAN TO SPILL
THE BEANS.
WE'RE DONE.
DO THEY GIVE REFUNDS
ON CONDOMS?
(SCHOOL BUS WHIRS)
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
DR. POLLOCK:
MAKE SURE YOU READ YOUR
ASSIGNMENT GUIDELINES CLOSELY.
THEY CAN BE FOUND ONLINE
ON THE CLASS WEBSITE.
AND LET MR. SILVERMAN,
YOUR T.A.,
KNOW IF YOU HAVE ANY TROUBLE
LOGGING IN.
PLEASE SETTLE DOWN, EVERYONE.
TAKE YOUR SEATS.
OH.
THANKS.
CAN'T HAVE THE ROOMIE
GOING HUNGRY.
YOU'RE THE BEST.
DR. POLLOCK:
NOW, I WANT YOU TO PICK
A PARTNER
AND YOU WILL WORK
THROUGH A PERSONALITY
COMPATIBILITY TEST.
HE'S TAKEN.
DR. POLLOCK:
AND THEN GIVE A NON-CLINICAL
PSYCHOLOGICAL REPORT, OKAY?
NOW, IF SOMEBODY
CAN HIT THE LIGHTS?
UH, LET'S GET STARTED.
REPORTER:
ENVIRONMENTAL GROUP'S
EXPANDED THEIR PROGRAMMING
AND LOCAL VOLUNTEERS
HAVE JOINED...
EMMA:
I'M FREEZING.
ARE YOU GUYS COLD?
SHHH!
HOW'S THAT?
GOOD. THANKS.
SO GRAB YOUR BELONGINGS,
SET UP YOUR CAMP,
AND THEN WE'LL START
OUR GAME OF SURVIVAL.
OKAY, NOW REMEMBER,
YOU'RE GONNA BE DIVIDED
INTO HERBIVORES,
OMNIVORES,
AND CARNIVORES.
AND THE ONLY WAY YOU CAN WIN
IS TO BE ALIVE AT THE END
OF THE GAME, ALL RIGHT?
(HUM OF CHATTER)
YOU GONNA FREEZE ME OUT
THIS WHOLE TRIP?
I WANTED TO INVITE YOU.
BUT MY UNCLE JUST
LOST HIS JOB...
(EXHALES)
IT DIDN'T REALLY SEEM
LIKE THE BEST TIME.
I, I WROTE A SONG FOR YOU.
I'LL SING IT TO YOU,
IF YOU LET ME.
A SONG?
I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU TOO.
(LAUGHS)
LET'S NEVER BREAK UP AGAIN,
OKAY?
♪ Have you ever wondered, Baby ♪
♪ How life could be ♪
♪ Spend some time
in some far off places ♪
♪ Spend some time with me ♪
NOW, THERE'S WATER
AND FOOD STATIONS
HIDDEN IN THE WOODS
THAT YOU MUST FIND TO FULFILL
YOUR ANIMAL'S NEEDS, OKAY?
NOW, I'LL BE HERE IF YOU
OR YOUR ANIMAL NEEDS HELP.
BE RIGHT HERE
AT BASE CAMP.
♪ ...that you think about it ♪
SAV:
SO, TONIGHT.
OUT IN THE WOODS,
KIND OF ROMANTIC, HUH?
ANYA:
OH, LOOK,
ANOTHER WATER STATION.
NOW WE ONLY HAVE TO FIND
ONE MORE.
SAV:
SIX MONTHS...
THAT'S A LONG TIME.
WHEN PEOPLE HAVE CARED
FOR EACH OTHER FOR THAT LONG...
THERE YOU GUYS ARE!
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
WITH YOUR FRIENDS?
ANYA:
OH, COME ON, SAV.
YOU KNOW, IT'S ACTUALLY
A FUN GAME, ALLI.
LOOK.
YOU'RE AN OMNIVORE
AND YOU CAN TAG
SAV AND I
AND GET TWO LIFE TAGS.
UM, DID YOU MARK YOUR CARD
WITH THIS WATER STATION?
(EXHALES)
SO, EM,
YOU KNOW HOW WE HAVE THAT
NO ROOMMATE DATING POLICY?
YOU CAN'T DATE KELLY.
WE'LL BE DISCREET!
IT'S NOT A QUESTION
OF DISCRETION.
GREAT.
YOU LIKE HIM TOO.
WELL... YEAH.
AND HE'S MADE IT CLEAR
THAT HE'S INTERESTED TOO.
I DON'T KNOW, HON,
HE'S BEEN SENDING ME
SOME PRETTY STRONG SIGNALS.
COME ON, YOU'VE GOT
THE HISTORY SYMPOSIUM GUY
AND THE LIBRARY
VENDING MACHINE GUY.
KELLY IS THE FIRST DECENT GUY
THAT I'VE MET HERE.
YOU ALWAYS GO
FOR THE GUYS I LIKE.
(SCOFFS) EXCUSE ME?
UH, CRAIG?
UH, WE WERE TWELVE.
WHAT ABOUT DAMIEN?
YOU DATED DAMIEN
FOR FIVE MINUTES.
AND THEN YOU WENT OUT WITH JAY
AFTER ME.
UH, I DON'T KNOW
HOW TO PUT THIS, BUT...
I DON'T THINK YOU ACTUALLY
"WENT OUT" WITH JAY.
MANNY!
LOOK, THIS IS STUPID.
WE AGREED THAT
NO ONE GETS KELLY.
I GUESS.
BUT AREN'T YOU CURIOUS
WHO HE'D GO FOR?
NO.
WELL, OUR COMPATIBILITY
ASSIGNMENT
COULD TELL US.
WELL, JUST FOR FUN,
OF COURSE.
OH, OF COURSE.
CONNER:
WAIT 'TIL YOU SEE!
THE WHITE SHEET
ALMOST LOOKS BLACK
BECAUSE SO MANY MOTHS
AND OTHER INSECTS LAND ON IT.
STILL BORING YOUR FRIENDS
TO DEATH?
GETTING SOME SPOTTED MOTHS
FOR MY SPOTTED MOTH TRAY.
(NET TEARS)
OR NOT.
LISTEN, KID, I'M DOING YOU
A FAVOUR, ALL RIGHT?
NOBODY WANTS TO HEAR YOU TALK
ABOUT SPOTTED MOTHS ANY MORE.
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE
DONE THAT.
OH, I'M SCARED.
I'M SCARED.
PERSONALLY, I, UH,
I HATE SPOTTED MOTHS.
WANNA GO FOR A WALK?
OKAY, LET'S SEE,
UM...
"I HAVE A VERY RELAXED
PERSONALITY."
FROM "VERY TRUE"
TO "VERY UNTRUE."
"VERY TRUE,"
I WOULD SAY.
SERIOUSLY?
I HAVE A VERY RELAXED
PERSONALITY;
KELLY HAS A VERY RELAXED
PERSONALITY.
YOU...
DON'T LET ME EAT
A WAFFLE
IF YOU THINK IT'LL COST US
THE BEST SEATS IN CLASS.
"I TEND TO MAINTAIN MY SPACES
IN AN ORDERLY WAY."
MY CORNER, NEAT;
KELLY'S NEATER.
YOURS LOOKS LIKE
A THRIFT STORE THREW UP.
OH!
HERE'S A "VERY TRUE" FOR YOU.
"I AM A DOMINEERING PERSON."
ME?!
OKAY, UM...
MANNY AND EMMA:
"I AM ATTRACTED
TO UNAVAILABLE PEOPLE!"
LOOKS LIKE IT'S A DRAW.
HMM.
CHANTAY:
HOTDOG?
NO, I'M GOOD.
COME ON, I HEARD
THAT YOU AND ANYA
WERE MAKING OUT
IN THE WOODS.
THAT SHOULD'VE GIVEN YOU
AN APPETITE.
MY DAD PACKED ME
AND MY SISTER SOME FOOD.
FUNNY THAT YOU TOO ARE THE ONES
GETTING ALL THE ACTION.
WHAT?
WORD IS
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY BHANDARI
WHO'S BEEN BUSY
IN THE WOODS.
I GOTTA GO.
WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN UP TO?
JOHNNY BROKE CONNOR'S NET,
BUT WE'RE LOOKING FOR MOTHS
AND OTHER NOCTURNAL FAUNA.
HAVE YOU HEARD
YOUR NEW NICKNAME?
NO.
BACKWOODS BHANDARI.
THEY THINK YOU HOOKED UP
WITH JOHNNY!
THAT'S AWESOME.
YOU WANT THEM
TO CALL YOU THAT?
AH, IT'S COOLER THAN
"SAV'S LITTLE SISTER"
OR "NINER GEEK."
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU BETTER GO TO YOUR TENT.
WHY?
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING!
YOU'RE SUCH A HYPOCRITE.
I SAW THAT PACK OF CONDOMS
YOU BROUGHT.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
AND YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT
WHAT PEOPLE MIGHT THINK
ABOUT ME.
GO TO YOUR TENT, NOW!
SO UNFAIR!
ANYA:
HE'S JUST WORRIED ABOUT
HIS LITTLE SISTER.
IT'S WHAT BIG BROTHERS DO.
ALLI:
NO, HE'S WORRIED ABOUT
OUR FAMILY'S REPUTATION.
WELL, IT'S 'CAUSE
HE CARES ABOUT YOU.
MAYBE, BUT HE SOUNDS
JUST LIKE MY DAD.
IS THAT SO TERRIBLE?
IT'S HARD TO EXPLAIN.
YOU'D GET IT
IF YOU EVER MET MY FATHER.
YEAH, WISH I COULD.
ME TOO.
FAMILY DINNERS WOULD BE
WAY LESS BORING
WITH YOU THERE.
THANKS.
SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK
IT WOULD TAKE...
FOR SAV TO INTRODUCE ME
TO YOUR PARENTS?
YOU BEING MUSLIM.
(LAUGHS)
(FIRE CRACKLES, RAIN PATTERS,
GUITAR PLAYS)
SAV:
♪ I LOVE TO WATCH YOU CHEER ♪
♪ IT'S BEEN THAT WAY
FOR HALF A YEAR ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE WE BELONG ♪
♪ SO I WROTE THIS SONG,
YEAH ♪
♪ FOR MY ONE... ♪
♪ MY ONLY... ♪
♪ ANYA ♪
(PLAYS FINAL NOTES)
DUDE...
YOU MAKE PETER SEEM LIKE
AN AWESOME SONGWRITER.
YOU THINK SHE'LL LIKE IT?
SADLY, YES.
(PATTING AGAINST TENT ENTRANCE)
HI, ANYA.
HEY, GUYS, WHY DON'T YOU COME
TO CHANTAY'S TENT PARTY?
IT'LL BE AWESOME.
OR NOT.
HAPPY ANNIVERSARY.
HAPPY ANNIVERSARY
TO YOU, TOO.
CAN I PLAY YOU
MY "ANYA" SONG?
OF COURSE.
OH! UM, BUT FIRST,
I HAVE AN ANNIVERSARY PRESENT
FOR YOU.
UM, IT'S KIND OF SPECIAL.
YEAH?
I WANT TO BECOME
A MUSLIM.
FOR YOU.
YOU DON'T...
YOU DON'T LIKE THE IDEA?
'COURSE I DO.
IT'S JUST...
I'M SURPRISED.
UH, YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THAT
FOR ME.
WELL, IT'S BECAUSE I LOVE YOU.
UM...
UH...
YOU THOUGHT
WE'D HAVE SEX?
I JUST THOUGHT IT WAS
A POSSIBILITY, MAYBE.
BUT WE DON'T HAVE TO
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO.
BUT... WHAT IF I DO?
REALLY?
YEAH.
(GIGGLES)
(EXHALES)
(SCRATCHING ON TENT ENTRANCE)
I THINK YOU HAVE
THE WRONG TENT.
NOPE.
SO...
WHERE ARE
YOUR LITTLE FRIENDS?
THEY WENT TO COLLECT
NOCTURNAL SPECIMENS.
YAWN.
(HALF LAUGHS)
UH HUH.
THOUGHT MAYBE YOU MIGHT BE DOING
SOMETHING INTERESTING.
BUT I'M NOT...
SO MAYBE YOU SHOULD GO.
I DON'T MIND,
YOU READ YOUR BOOK.
I'LL, I'LL JUST HANG OUT.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA GIVE UP,
ARE YOU?
NO.
OKAY.
CRAZY EIGHTS?
POKER.
(SLIGHTLY TAKEN ABACK)
POKER, IT IS.
THAT WAS MY BEST NET.
I'M GONNA GET THAT BOY GOOD.
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO BE,
YOUR POKER FACE?
YOU KNOW I'M NOT SUPPOSED
TO TELL
YOU HAVE A KILLER HAND.
MAYBE I'M JUST HAPPY
TO BE SPENDING TIME WITH YOU.
(CHUCKLES)
SNAKE!
(SCREAMS)
ANYA:
WHAT WAS THAT?
SAV:
NOTHING. NOTHING.
ANYA:
WELL, SHOULDN'T WE CHECK IT OUT?
SAV:
NO, I'M SURE IT'S FINE.
IT'S ALL GOOD.
ALLI:
(TERRIFIED SCREAMS)
WATCH OUT!
THAT WAS ALLI!
BUT...
(EXHALES)
STUDENT:
NEED HELP?!
IT'S A GARTER SNAKE.
TOTALLY HARMLESS.
YEAH, MAN, I KNOW.
JUST THOUGHT IT WAS
A MISSISSAUGA RATTLER.
(TENT ZIPPER UNZIPS)
SAV:
WHAT WERE YOU AND JOHNNY DOING?
ALLI:
PLAYING POKER.
(FREAKING)
YOU WERE ALONE IN A TENT
WITH A BOY?!
(TENT ZIPPER UNZIPS)
SIMPSON:
WH-WHAT IS GOING ON?!
EVERYONE,
GO BACK TO YOUR TENTS!
THE TENTS YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE IN, ALL RIGHT?
GO BACK!
NOW, EVERYONE, GO!
FASTER! FASTER! FASTER!
COME ON!
(STUDENT CHATTER)
LIBERTY:
KELLY AND I DISCOVERED
WE ARE COMPATIBLE AS FRIENDS
OR ROOMMATES
BECAUSE WE ARE BOTH ORGANIZED
AND LIKE HIGH LEVELS
OF EXCITEMENT.
KELLY:
BUT FOUND THAT WE WOULD BE
COMPLETELY INCOMPATIBLE AS MATES
BECAUSE WE HAVE
VERY DIFFERENT GOALS.
DR. POLLOCK:
THANK YOU.
THAT WAS EXCELLENT WORK.
NELSON AND SANTOS?
UM... (CLEARS THROAT)
I'M AFRAID WE'RE NOT READY
FOR OUR PRESENTATION.
I SEE.
AND WHY WOULD THAT BE?
WELL...
WE GOT CAUGHT UP IN SOME
SUPPLEMENTARY RESEARCH.
I SEE.
SUPPLEMENTARY RESEARCH?
HE'S FAILED US.
BOYS ON THE LEFT.
GIRLS ON THE RIGHT.
SORRY, I CAN'T TRUST YOU
AFTER LAST NIGHT.
YOU ARE NOT GOING TO TELL DAD.
SAV:
GIVE ME ONE REASON NOT TO.
WE WERE JUST
PLAYING CARDS.
WHO CARES
WHAT YOU WERE DOING?
YOU KNOW
WHAT EVERYONE THINKS.
WHAT ABOUT YOU AND ANYA?
WHAT WERE YOU DOING?
YOU HAD YOUR SHIRT OFF.
WELL, WE'RE NOT TALKING
ABOUT ME AND ANYA.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT YOU.
I'M NOT AN IMPURE GIRL!
SAV:
PEOPLE ARE GOING THINK YOU ARE.
THEY'LL SAY YOU'RE NOT
GOOD ENOUGH FOR THEIR FAMILY.
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
(SARCASTIC TONE)
YES, RIGHT,
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT I WANT.
WE LOST A WHOLE LETTER GRADE.
NOW WE HAVE TO WORK
JUST AS HARD
AND THE BEST
WE CAN HOPE FOR IS A "B."
WHAT'S THAT?
IS THAT THE SOUND
OF A VERY RELAXED PERSONALITY?
SERIOUSLY, THIS IS BAD.
WE'RE HERE FOR SCHOOL.
WE SHOULD NEVER HAVE GONE DOWN
THE KELLY ROAD.
WHAT?
HE'S SO CUTE,
AND WE HAVE TO LIVE
WITH HIM.
THAT'S A LOT OF TENSION,
RIGHT?
MANNY!
WHAT WOULD BE THE HARM
IN ASKING HIM?
FOR FUN,
OF COURSE.
MANNY, NO.
AND IF HE HAPPENS TO LIKE
ONE OF US...
THEN WE CAN MAKE
A MATURE DECISION
ON HOW TO PROCEED.
LOOK, IF YOU'RE UNCOMFORTABLE
WITH THAT,
I CAN JUST TELL HIM
I LIKE HIM.
NOT IF I TELL HIM FIRST!
(MANNY AND EMMA GIGGLE)
KELLY:
UH... (STAMMERS)
GUYS?!
THE SOCK ON THE DOOR?
OH...
WE SHOULD GO.
THE SOCK.
YEAH.
LOOK AT THIS.
(GASPS)
MANNY AND EMMA:
(LAUGH)
(LOW HUM OF STUDENT CHATTER)
SAV:
HEY, I'LL CALL YOU TONIGHT.
I WOULDN'T HAVE THOUGHT
YOU'D HAVE ANYTHING TO SAY
TO AN IMPURE GIRL.
I WASN'T TALKING ABOUT YOU.
WELL, YOU COULD HAVE BEEN.
I WAS ALONE IN A TENT,
WITH A BOY.
JUST LIKE ALLI.
IT'S NOT THE SAME THOUGH.
SURE IT IS.
WE WANTED TO BE TOGETHER
AND NOW, ACCORDING TO YOUR
DOUBLE STANDARD,
I'M NOT GOOD ENOUGH FOR YOU
OR YOUR FAMILY.
HEY.
WE DON'T GET IT.
THE SOCIOLOGICAL PSYCHOLOGICAL
MEASURES CHAPTER?
ME NEITHER.
NO, YOU.
MANNY:
I MEAN...
YOU WALK AROUND HERE
FLIRTING WITH US
AND THEN WE FIND YOU
MAKING OUT WITH GWYNETH.
WHAT?
WELL, YOU'RE ALWAYS
SO COMFORTING.
AND THOUGHTFUL.
LIKE, WHAT'S THAT ABOUT?
BEING A GOOD ROOMMATE.
SO, YOU'RE NOT INTO
EITHER ONE OF US LIKE THAT?
WE'RE ROOMMATES -
NO DATING.
WASN'T THAT THE DEAL?
YOU'RE NOT ANSWERING
THE QUESTION.
TO BE HONEST,
YOU'RE A LITTLE SCARY
RIGHT NOW.
YOU'RE BOTH FANTASTIC.
AND... YES, IF IT WASN'T FOR
THE NO ROOMMATE DATING RULE,
I WOULD DEFINITELY BE
INTO ONE OF YOU.
(HALF LAUGHS)
I'M GONNA GO STUDY
AT THE LIBRARY.
I'LL TRY TO BE A LITTLE LESS...
COMFORTING AND THOUGHTFUL
WHEN I GET BACK.
DEFINITELY INTO ONE OF US?
WHICH ONE?
WE CAN'T GO THERE.
NOPE.
(STUDENT CHATTER)
I TEXTED HER TWENTY TIMES
SINCE WE GOT BACK.
NOTHING.
SHE'LL BE HERE ANY SECOND
SAYING "OH SAV,
LET'S NEVER
BREAK UP AGAIN."
YOU SEE?
I'M SORRY
IF I PRESSURED YOU.
WE CAN WAIT
AS LONG AS YOU WANT.
I JUST WANNA HANG OUT
WITH YOU.
AND I NEVER GOT
TO PLAY YOU MY SONG.
WOMEN ARE EQUAL TO MEN.
WELL, YEAH.
SO, IF WHAT I DID
WAS BAD,
THEN YOU WERE JUST AS WRONG
TO BE WITH ME.
I, I DON'T THINK
YOU'RE BAD.
(STAMMERS)
I'M SORRY.
I JUST MEANT...
IT'S GOT EVERYTHING
YOU EVER GAVE ME IN IT.
THE CDS,
THE STUDZ T-SHIRT,
THE POEM,
THE BRACELET,
AND...STICKERS.