FOOTBALL PLAYERS:
(ROWDY SHOUTING)
HOLLY J:
EIGHT, NINE...
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(GRUNTING)
DANNY:
HUT!
PLAYER 2:
GET IT!
SHEPPARD:
FOOTBALL.
NOT FOOT-FALL, LADIES.
LET'S GO.
WHAT?
I WANNA SEE
YOU DO IT.
SMILE.
IT'S NOT SCOWL-LEADING.
HOLLY J:
NO. SORRY.
COME ON, IZZY,
WORK WITH ME HERE.
WE'RE LATE AND MOMMY REALLY,
REALLY WANTS THIS.
OKAY? COME ON.
SHEPPARD:
GUYS, I JUST WANNA SAY
THANK YOU
FOR SPENDING YOUR FINAL WEEKEND
OF THE SUMMER
GETTING INTO FIGHTING FORM.
PLAYERS:
(CHEER, WHISTLE AND APPLAUD)
YOU ARE THE NEW ELITE,
AND WE'LL MAKE SURE
THE REST OF THE SCHOOL
KNOWS THAT
AT TOMORROW'S FASHION SHOW.
PLAYERS:
(CHEER, WHISTLE AND APPLAUD)
IS IT TOO LATE
TO TRY OUT?
BEING ON TIME
WOULDN'T HAVE HELPED
WITH THAT PSYCHO WITCH
IN CHARGE.
YOU'RE RUNNING
THE SPIRIT SQUAD?
WE'VE REBRANDED IT,
MAMA MIA.
THIS YEAR,
IT'S THE POWER SQUAD.
WHO DIED
AND MADE YOU QUEEN?
WHEN HATZIE BAILED,
THE SHEP SWOOPED IN
AND HE'S ALWAYS HAD
A SOFT SPOT FOR ME.
PRINCIPAL SHEPPARD
FROM LAKEHURST?
OKAY, LOOK,
I'M SORRY I'M LATE,
BUT AT LEAST GIVE ME
A SHOT.
'KAY, WE'VE DONE
THIS DANCE BEFORE.
YOU MAKE THE TEAM
AND THEN ABANDON US
AS SOON AS THE KID
NEEDS A COOKIE.
NO, NO, THIS YEAR'S
GONNA BE DIFFERENT.
REALLY? 'CAUSE FROM
WHERE I'M STANDING,
IT LOOKS EXACTLY
THE SAME.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Oh! Oh! Oh! ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
STUDENTS:
(CHATTER)
SPIKE:
EM, I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE AT UNIVERSITY.
MOM! I'M EIGHTEEN!
SHE MEANS
WE'RE GOING TO MISS YOU.
I WILL MISS YOU, TOO.
BUT I CAN'T,
UNLESS YOU GET OUT OF HERE.
BE SAFE.
EMMA:
BYE.
BYE, GIRLS.
SPIKE:
(RELUCTANT SIGH)
STUDENTS:
(HUM OF CHATTER)
ALL:
(RELIEVED BREATH,
EXCITED SQUEALS)
LET'S GO!
OH MY GOD!
MANNY:
I CAN'T BELIEVE
WE'RE ACTUALLY HERE!
EMMA:
SMITHDALE GIRLS, TOGETHER!
VICKIE:
ARE YOU MANUELA?
UH, YEAH,
THAT'S ME.
I'M VICKIE,
YOUR FROSH LEADER.
YOU'RE ON MY FLOOR!
AWESOME.
HOW 'BOUT ME, EMMA,
HER ROOMMATE?
NOPE.
I THINK THIRD FLOOR JULIE
MIGHT HAVE SOME EMMAS,
ARE YOU LIBERTY?
'CAUSE I'VE GOT A LIBERTY!
WELCOME TO FLOOR FIVE!
(EXCITED LAUGH)
WAIT. I'M SUPPOSED TO BE
WITH MANNY.
THERE MUST'VE BEEN
A MISTAKE.
OH WELL.
MANUELA, LIBERTY,
COME MEET YOUR FLOORMATES.
UM, WE'LL STILL BE UNDER
THE SAME ROOF.
BELLA.
GO DRAW MOMMY A PICTURE,
OKAY?
(SIGHS)
HOLLY J IS THE DEVIL!
SHE RUNS EVERY CLUB
IN SCHOOL
AND SHE'S 100 PERCENT
COMMITTED
TO KEEPING ME OUT OF
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF THEM.
AH, YOUR CHANCE'LL COME,
SWEETIE.
YES, IT WILL,
AND WHEN IT DOES
24-HOUR-MOMMY-DUTY WILL STOP ME
FROM TAKING IT.
I LOVE BELLA,
BUT I JUST...
I WANNA BE A NORMAL
HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT.
OKAY,
I'VE BEEN THINKING.
I'M WORKING
FROM HOME NOW
AND BELLA'S
IN PRE-KINDERGARTEN...
I'M GONNA HELP YOU OUT.
REALLY?
ON ONE CONDITION.
YOU MAKE THIS YOUR YEAR.
DONE!
ANNA:
(CHUCKLES)
♪♪♪
SAV:
YOU CAN'T WEAR THAT.
♪♪♪
ANYA:
HEY, GOOD SUMMER?
THE BEST.
THIS IS MY SISTER,
CLARE.
SHE'S IN GRADE NINE.
UH, THE GIFTED CLASS.
SAV:
ALLI'S IN THAT CLASS TOO.
ALLI:
YOU SWORE YOU WOULDN'T
TELL ANYBODY!
SIMPSON:
HEY, GUYS!
UH, THIS IS MY GODSON,
CONNOR.
HE'S GONNA BE BOARDING
WITH ME THIS YEAR
SO HE CAN ATTEND
THE GIFTED PROGRAM.
SO UH, MAYBE YOU GUYS CAN
NAVIGATE REGISTRATION TOGETHER
AND I'LL SEE YOU GUYS
IN HOMEROOM.
OKAY? BYE.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
MRS. SMITH:
LOCKER ASSIGNMENT'S
ON THE BACK.
NEXT!
SHEPPARD:
WELCOME BACK, DEGRASSI.
IT'S THE SHEP HERE TO TELL YOU
WE'RE GONNA START THE YEAR OFF
RIGHT -
NO CLASSES.
JUST REGISTRATION
AND A FASHION SHOW
TO INTRODUCE YOU
TO OUR NEW FOOTBALL TEAM
AND SOME OF OUR FAVOURITE GIRLS.
THIS IS A PRINCIPAL
I CAN GET BEHIND.
SHEPPARD:
...EXCITED I AM TO BE
STARTING UP A FOOTBALL TEAM...
HOLLY J:
HEY! IT TOOK ME WEEKS
TO CONVINCE MY NEIGHBOUR'S
SISTER-IN-LAW'S COUSIN
TO SCOUT OUR FASHION SHOW,
AND IN ONE MINUTE
YOU RUIN EVERYTHING.
WHY?
I'M A FOOTBALL PLAYER,
NOT A MODEL.
AND WHAT IF YOU HAD A FRIEND
BY YOUR SIDE?
POSSIBLY.
OVER MY DEAD BODY.
THEN DEFINITELY.
FINE.
GYM. AT LUNCH.
DON'T BE LATE.
I'VE GOTTA JET
TO PRACTICE.
OH HEY, THANKS.
THE PLEASURE...
IS ALL MINE.
(CELL PHONE RINGING,
HUM OF CHATTER)
HE'S GOT IT BAD.
DANNY? NO.
HE'S JUST A FRIEND.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
HE WAS PRACTICALLY
DROOLING.
I'M MIA.
LEIA.
OR AS HOLLY J PUT IT:
"AN UNWELCOME ADDITION
TO DEGRASSI."
IT TAKES A WHILE FOR HER
TO WARM UP TO NEW PEOPLE.
I'VE KNOWN HER
THREE YEARS
AND I'M STILL WAITING.
(RELUCTANT)
HEY...
DO YOU WANNA GRAB LUNCH
BEFORE THE SHOW?
AFTER FOUR YEARS
AT BALLET SCHOOL,
A FRIEND WHO EATS
WOULD BE A THRILL.
(CHUCKLES)
FOR ME, JUST A FRIEND
WOULD BE ENOUGH.
SHEPPARD:
UH... HOW DO I TURN
THIS THING OFF?
UM...
(OVERLAPPING SHOUTS
OF ENCOURAGEMENT)
GIRL:
WE'RE ALMOST THERE!
(LAUGHING)
VICKIE:
NICE JOB, FLOOR FIVE!
TIME FOR THE CAMPUS-WIDE
SCAVENGER HUNT!
MANNY! MANNY!
I HAVE THE BEST NEWS!
MANNY:
OH UM, ME TOO!
EMMA, THIS IS GWYNETH,
MY NEW ROOMMATE.
WE'RE BOTH IN DRAMA
AND WE BOTH LOVE FEIST
AND DAVID MAMET!
MANUELA'S TOLD ME
ALL ABOUT YOU!
OH. HI.
SO I JUST TALKED TO HOUSING
AND THEY FIXED THE MISTAKE!
WE'RE ROOMIES AGAIN!
(DIN OF CHATTER)
DARCY:
NO CLASSES?
FASHION SHOWS AND FOOTBALL?
JANE:
WHEN WILL YOUR MOM COME BACK
TO SAVE US FROM "THE SHEP?"
IF SHE COMES BACK,
I LOSE MY PAD.
MM, IT'S A SMALL PRICE TO PAY
FOR MY SANITY.
LADIES AND GENTS,
WHEN I SAID WE'RE GONNA
START THE YEAR OFF RIGHT,
I MEANT IT!
STUDENTS:
(CHEER AND APPLAUD)
WOW.
THANK YOU!
SHEPPARD:
...FIRST ANNUAL
FOOTBALL FASHION SHOW!
I KNOW HOW WE CAN
REALLY WOW THEM.
STUDENTS:
(CHEER AND APPLAUD)
SHEPPARD:
LET ME INTRODUCE
OUR NEW RUNNING BACK,
RILEY STAVROS.
ON HIS ARM,
HOLLY J SINCLAIR,
CAPTAIN OF OUR POWER SQUAD -
A HOT LITTLE NUMBER!
NEXT UP,
FULL BACK SAV BHANDARI.
ON HIS ARM,
ANYA MACPHERSON.
COME ON, GIVE IT UP
FOR THOSE TWO LOVEBIRDS, HUH?
AND FINALLY, IF EVERYONE COULD
PUT THEIR HANDS TOGETHER
FOR OUR TEAM CAPTAIN, QB,
DANNY VAN ZANDT!
(WILD CHEERS)
WHOO!
WITH MIA JONES.
STUDENTS:
(WILD CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
(WHISTLING AND CHEERING)
(WILD CHEERS)
WHAT'S UP?
I'M LATE FOR THE SORORITY'S
MAKE-YOUR-OWN PAD THAI.
WE ARE YOUR NEW ROOMMATES!
WHAT IS SHE TALKING ABOUT?
WE'RE ROOMING HERE NOW -
EMMA ARRANGED IT ALL -
THE THREE OF US
AND SOME GIRL NAMED KELLY.
BUT MY ROOMMATE
AND I HAD PLANS.
ME TOO.
WELL, WE HAD PLANS, MANNY.
REMEMBER?
WELL, IT IS A CHANCE
TO MEET NEW PEOPLE.
UGH, GOD FORBID
I HOLD "MANUELA" BACK
FROM HER AMAZING
NEW FRIENDS.
KELLY:
YOU GIRLS
THE WELCOMING COMMITTEE?
I'M KELLY.
UH, WE WERE EXPECTING
SOMEONE
A LITTLE BIT MORE
ESTROGEN-Y.
I'LL SORT IT OUT
WITH HOUSING.
YOU'LL BE BACK
TO YOUR OLD ROOMS
AND YOUR NEW LIVES
IN NO TIME.
HOUSING SAID THIS WAS
THE LAST ROOM AVAILABLE.
HI.
WAY TO GRANDSTAND,
BABY MOMMA!
SORRY YOU DIDN'T THINK OF IT
YOURSELF?
JANICE:
NICE ENTRANCE.
JANICE PEARSON.
I'M HOLLY J. SINCLAIR.
I SPOKE TO YOU
ON THE PHONE.
I'D LIKE TO HAVE A CHAT WITH YOU
ABOUT MODELING.
IF YOU'RE INTERESTED,
CALL ME.
(LAUGH OF DISBELIEF)
SOMEBODY PINCH ME.
OW.
(HALF LAUGHS)
(DISSATISFIED SIGH)
AHHH...
(LOW DIN OF CHATTER)
WOW!
I LOOK...
PERFECT.
FOR YOU.
GET USED TO WALKING
IN THEM.
REALLY?
THANKS.
THANK ME BY BOOKING
A BIG JOB.
WE'VE SCHEDULED
SOME GO-SEES FOR YOU
OVER THE NEXT FEW DAYS.
LET'S SEE IF WE CAN'T
MAKE A MODEL OUT OF YOU.
(TRAFFIC WHIRS)
MOMMY,
WHO'S YOUR BEST FRIEND?
YOU ARE, SWEETIE.
NO. I'M TOO LITTLE.
WHO'S YOUR BIG BEST FRIEND?
MOMMY DOESN'T HAVE
A BIG BEST FRIEND RIGHT NOW.
WHY?
BECAUSE...
BECAUSE WHY?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT EVERYTHING'S
GONNA CHANGE.
'CAUSE MOMMY'S GONNA BE
A MODEL NOW.
THEN YOU'LL HAVE
A BEST FRIEND?
YEAH.
THEN EVERYONE'S GONNA
WANNA BE MY FRIEND.
BUT IT'S TIME FOR YOU
TO GO TO SLEEP NOW, 'KAY?
(KISS)
♪♪♪
♪ Get your hands up ♪
♪ From the moment that
she walked in the room ♪
♪ Like Cinderella goin'
boom-boom-boom ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ The girl was on fire ♪
HEY.
YOU LOOK AMAZING.
CHANTAY:
WE'VE GOT TO POST A PHOTO
OF YOUR NEW LOOK
ON THE ANTI-GRAPEVINE.
(SHEEPISH CHUCKLE)
I LOVE YOUR HAIR.
THANKS. THE GUY WHO DID IT
DID BEYONCE'S!
WHATEVER CHANCE YOU HAD
WITH HER - GONE.
CHANTAY:
DID THEY MENTION PARIS YET?
NEW YORK?
MIA:
WELL, MY AGENT SAID
THAT IF I GO OVERSEAS,
IT'LL BE MILAN FIRST!
BUT UM, HERE IN TOWN
I GOT A COUPLE GO-SEES.
"GO-SEES."
WOW, YOU'RE A REAL MODEL.
YOU SHOULD SIT WITH US
IN CLASS.
WE WANNA HEAR EVERYTHING.
ANYA:
YOUR SHOES ARE SO HOT.
WHERE'D YOU GET THEM?
♪ She said
I just want your love ♪
♪ So throw your hands up ♪
♪♪♪
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
TOMORROW WE'LL DELVE DEEPER
INTO DNA.
CHANTAY:
OKAY, DISH.
ANYA:
HOW WERE THE GO-SEES?
CHANTAY:
WAS THERE A CASTING COUCH?
I HEAR THAT'S HOW IT WORKS
SOMETIMES.
HOLLY J:
HERE'S THE REAL QUESTION.
DID YOU BOOK ANY JOBS YET?
MIA:
UH, NO.
NOT YET.
HUH.
WELL YOU CAN FILL US IN
ON THE GREAT FASHION WORLD
AT LUNCH...
LIKE WHEN WE'LL ACTUALLY
SEE YOU DO A SHOOT.
UNLESS YOU WANNA GRAB
A HOT DOG AT THE PARK;
PRACTICE GOT CANCELLED.
GO FOR IT.
MAYBE THERE'LL BE LESS
COMPETITION
AS A PLUS SIZE MODEL?
REMIND ME,
WHEN IS YOUR NEXT GO-SEE?
WHERE'S EMMA?
UH, PROBABLY REGISTERING ME
FOR POLI-SCI
SO WE CAN BE IN
ALL THE SAME CLASSES.
HMM.
WHA... UH...
(AWKWARD STAMMER)
(HALF LAUGHS)
THANK YOU.
COURTESY OF
THE RUSSELL HALL CAF.
APOLOGY BREAKFASTS
FOR MY ROOMIES.
I'LL GET ALL I NEED
AT THE PSI ALPHA ZETA
CHARITY FLAPJACK STACK-OFF.
BUT THANKS.
KELLY:
I'M OUT TOO.
THANKS FOR THE HASH BROWN,
HOME FRY.
MANNY:
THE UH, FROSH WEEK
DRAMALYMPICS START IN 10.
I GOTTA MEET GWYN.
BYE.
(HUM OF CHATTER)
HOLLY J'S JUST JEALOUS,
YOU KNOW?
MAYBE SHE'S RIGHT.
FOUR GO-SEES AND NO JOBS?
MAYBE I'M NOT CUT OUT
TO BE A MODEL.
A GIRL LIKE YOU?
IMPOSSIBLE.
(FLATTERED HALF LAUGH,
CELL PHONE RINGS)
OH.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
ANOTHER GO-SEE.
TOM BLAKE IS LOOKING
FOR THE NEW FACE OF T-BOMBZ!
ALL STAR QUARTERBACK
TOM BLAKE?
YEAH!
THE BEST QB IN THE LEAGUE!
AND HIS T-BOMBZ KICKS
ARE SWEET.
YOU CAN DO IT.
JUST GO AND BE
YOUR HOT SELF.
AND WHETHER YOU GET IT
OR NOT,
I'LL STILL BE
YOUR BIGGEST FAN.
THANK YOU.
FOR LUCK.
ALTHOUGH...
YOU WON'T NEED IT.
(WHACK)
BIANCA:
KICK IT RIGHT,
T-BOMBZ!
I WISH SHE WASN'T UP
FOR THIS TOO.
SHE GETS A LOT OF WORK.
GUESS WHY.
BIANCA KNOWS HOW TO MAKE
THE CLIENTS HAPPY...
IN EVERY WAY.
YOU MEAN...
JANICE:
MIA?
THEY'RE READY FOR YOU.
HEY, COME ON,
IT'S OKAY.
ALL RIGHT?
MIA:
KICKING IT RIGHT,
T-BOMBZ!
(AWKWARD CHUCKLE)
MAN AND MIA: OH!
(OBJECTS CLATTER)
I'M-I'M SO SORRY.
OH...
ALL RIGHT.
SECOND TIME'S THE CHARM, OKAY?
HERE WE GO...
MIA:
(GRUNTS)
(SHEEPISH LAUGH)
KICK IT RIGHT,
T-BOMBZ!
SHE'S A NATURAL.
DID I HURT YOU?
ARE YOU OKAY?
TOM:
OH NO, NOT AT ALL.
HEY, GOOD LUCK.
THAT LOOKED GREAT.
WHAT DO WE GOT,
LIKE FOUR GIRLS LEFT?
WE CAN JUST MOVE 'EM THROUGH.
I'M SORRY, I DIDN'T MEAN
TO MESS UP.
LET'S SEE HOW
THIS AUDITION GOES
AND THEN WE'LL TAKE IT
FROM THERE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
THERE ARE LOTS
OF PRETTY GIRLS OUT THERE
WHO DON'T HAVE WHAT IT TAKES
TO BE A MODEL.
(HUFFS)
THIS STUFF IS JUVENILE.
(KNOCK AT THE DOOR)
OKAY.
I LOVE YOU TOO, MOM.
WHAT'S UP, EMS?
DID YOU RUN INTO A PACK
OF WILD SHARPIES?
HUMANITIES GRAFFITI PICNIC.
SHOULDN'T YOU BE
PAINTING THE TOWN RED?
ACTUALLY?
I'M GONNA GO HOME
'TIL ALL THE EXCITEMENT
DIES DOWN.
FROSH WEEK ISN'T MY STYLE.
WHY NOT?
TOO MUCH FUN?
TOO MUCH FUN FOR ME
BY MYSELF.
I CAME HERE FROM THE YUKON
WITHOUT A SINGLE FRIEND.
YOU JUST GOTTA DIVE IN
AND TRY IT OUT.
(COCKS WATER-GUN)
THE BEACH BATTLE'S STARTING
AND WE'RE SHORT A SOLDIER.
(BLOWS)
WHERE DO I REPORT FOR DUTY?
(GIGGLES)
(HUM OF CHATTER)
CAN I HAVE
YOUR AUTOGRAPH?
IT'S NOT WORTH MUCH YET.
BUT IT WILL BE
ONCE YOU'RE THE T-BOMBZ GIRL.
AND WHEN YOU ARE,
MAYBE YOU COULD GET ME
TOM BLAKE'S AUTOGRAPH.
ARE YOU USING ME
TO GET TO TOM?
BUSTED.
(BELL RINGS)
PRACTICE CALLS.
AH...
SEE YOU TOMORROW?
(EXHALES)
I HAVE A PHILOSOPHICAL
QUESTION.
IF A BABY MOMMA
GETS A MODELING AGENT
BUT NEVER GETS ANY WORK,
IS SHE STILL A MODEL
OR JUST A POSEUR?
IF YOU'RE NOT GOOD ENOUGH
TO GET A GIG SOON,
THE NEW BOY,
THE NEW FRIENDS,
THE NEW LIFE WILL GO POOF.
(PAPER CRINKLES)
(CELL PHONE BUTTONS DIAL)
(PLAYFUL SQUEALS
AND SHOUTS)
EMMA:
THANKS FOR DRAGGING ME
OUT HERE.
YOU WERE RIGHT
ABOUT DIVING IN.
SEE?
IT'S JUST GOOD CLEAN FUN.
EMMA:
LOOK.
LET'S AMBUSH THEM.
LIBERTY AND MANNY:
(SCREAM)
LIBERTY:
OH MY GOD! WHOA!
WHOA! TRUCE!
WE CAME TO FIND YOU.
WE WERE WRONG TO SAY
WE DIDN'T WANNA LIVE
WITH OUR OLDEST FRIEND.
LIBERTY:
SO, WE THOUGHT WE COULD DISCUSS
THE DETAILS OVER...
DINNER IN THE CAF?
ACTUALLY, I MET SOME PRETTY
COOL PEOPLE OUT HERE.
WE'RE GONNA GO
GRAB A BITE.
I'LL SEE YOU GIRLS
AROUND?
MANNY:
(SQUEALS)
(LAUGHS)
OH...
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(DOORS WHIR SHUT)
(PREPARATORY BREATH)
SO CAN I GET YOU ANYTHING?
YOU WANT A DRINK?
UH, NO, I'M OKAY.
ACTUALLY, NO,
MAYBE A WATER.
I-I'M FINE.
NEVER MIND. HEH.
(FORCED EXHALE)
THIS IS BEAUTIFUL.
YEAH, YOU KNOW,
IT'S JUST A PLACE
TO HANG MY HAT
WHEN I'M IN THE CITY.
SO...
WHAT DID YOU WANNA TALK
ABOUT?
I WANTED TO GET
YOUR AUTOGRAPH.
FOR A FRIEND.
REALLY?
AN AUTOGRAPH?
AND I WAS HOPING
WE COULD...
HANG OUT SOME MORE.
AH... HEH, YEAH.
I'M SORRY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I-I SHOULDN'T HAVE COME.
TOM:
NO, NO, HEY-HEY-HEY.
A BEAUTIFUL GIRL
WANTS TO MAKE A HOUSE CALL,
WHO AM I TO COMPLAIN?
LOOK, DO YOU WANNA SPEND
SOME TIME WITH ME?
LIKE I SAID,
YOU ARE A GORGEOUS GIRL.
BUT ONLY IF YOU WANT TO.
I KNOW.
AND I DO.
I WANT TO.
IS THAT OKAY?
YEAH.
DEFINITELY.