(KIDS SCREAMING WILDLY)
PANTHERS RULE!
JANE:
TWO TOUCHDOWNS.
OVER A 150 RUSHING YARDS.
DANNY:
YO, YOU OWNED THAT GAME.
THAT SECOND TOUCH DOWN?
MAGIC.
WE DESTROYED THEM.
ABOUT TIME.
YOU LOOKED AMAZING
OUT THERE.
(MOCKING ANYA)
YOU LOOKED AMAZING.
DAMN RIGHT.
SHEP:
ALL RIGHT! YEAH!
OKAY EVERYBODY,
LISTEN UP.
PLAYER OF THE GAME...
RILEY STAVROS!
STUDENTS:
(CHEERING AND WHISTLING)
GOOD GAME, COACH.
GREAT GAME.
I'M FLOORED.
YOU'VE REALLY IMPROVED,
BUDDY.
WELL, I'VE BEEN TRAINING HARD.
AND IT SHOWS.
KEEP IT UP.
THANKS COACH.
TOO BAD YOU DIDN'T HAVE A GIRL
TO CELEBRATE WITH, HUH?
YEAH, I'VE GOT GIRLS.
JUST DON'T KNOW
WHICH ONE TO CHOOSE.
LOOKS LIKE DEREK'S SINGLE.
MATCH MADE IN HEAVEN,
BROTHER. HEH-HEH.
HERE.
KEEP IT.
GREAT GAME.
WHOA!
(CACOPHONY OF CHEERING FADES
AND BECOMES MUTED)
(GRUNTED EXHALE)
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Oh! Oh! Oh! ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
(COMPUTER KEYS CLACK,
LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
WHAT ARE YOU ORDERING?
TANNING OIL?
UM... NOTHING.
DIDN'T LOOK LIKE NOTHING.
YOU WON'T SAY ANYTHING
TO ANYONE?
PETER:
NO, I SWEAR.
I'VE BEEN TAKING
THESE PILLS...
PETER:
WHAT, LIKE PRESCRIPTION?
RILEY:
THEY'RE PERFORMANCE ENHANCERS.
THEY HELP BUILD MUSCLE,
LIKE, CRAZY FAST.
SO, STEROIDS?
SORT OF.
THEY'RE SAME ONES
PROFESSIONAL ATHLETES USE.
YEAH, BUT DON'T THEY
GIVE YOU, LIKE, BOOBS
AND MAKE YOU ALL PARANOID
AND STUFF?
HEH. NO, MAN.
ALL THEY DO IS IMPROVE MY GAME.
IT'S ALL GOOD.
(COMPUTER KEYS CLACK)
LEIA AND DEREK:
(CHUCKLING)
DEREK:
NO, BUT... YOU, UM...
WE CAN GO FOR A WALK,
UH, WE CAN GO
TO A MOVIE AFTER...
YOU CAN PICK WHAT YOU WANT.
NEVER MIND THE WALK.
LEIA:
I... I DON'T KNOW.
UM...
I'VE GOT TO GET TO CLASS.
(DIN OF CHATTER)
HOW DID YOU
GET TO BE SO COOL?
IS IT THE VESTS?
'CAUSE I CAN GET A VEST.
NO.
JUST STOP BEING AN IDIOT.
OH, GREAT ADVICE.
THANKS.
'KAY LISTEN, I KNOW
WE HAVEN'T BEEN TIGHT LATELY,
BUT... REALLY,
I NEED A FAVOUR...
NO. NO WAY.
PLEASE, PLEASE HOOK ME UP
WITH LEIA.
SHE'LL NEVER
HANG OUT WITH YOU.
WHY?!
SHE HANGS OUT WITH YOU.
AND YOU AND I
ARE VERY DIFFERENT.
COME ON!
YOU GUYS ARE FRIENDS,
I LIKE HER...
IT'S PERFECT!
AND ONCE SHE GETS TO KNOW ME,
YOU KNOW...
ARE YOU EVER GONNA
GIVE THIS UP?
NO. NEVER. JAMAIS.
NUNCA!
FINE!
I'LL SEE WHAT I CAN DO.
THANKS, BROSY!
CHILL AFTER SCHOOL?
I SAID I'LL SEE
WHAT I CAN DO ABOUT LEIA.
(INCOMING MESSAGE BEEPS)
(COMPUTER KEYS CLACK)
(MESSAGE BEEPS)
(KEYS CLACK)
(MONITOR BEEPS)
(MOUSE CLICKS)
(MESSAGE BEEPS)
(KEYS CLACK)
(LAPTOP SNAPS SHUT)
RILEY:
HEY, ANYA?
THE STAR PANTHER.
EVERYONE'S STILL TALKING
ABOUT HOW WELL YOU PLAYED.
AND YOU TOO.
YOUR CHEERING AND STUFF?
IT WAS... LOUD.
THANKS.
BY LOUD I MEAN, GREAT.
HEH.
WELL, IT'S EASY BEING
ON THE POWER SQUAD
WHEN THERE'S SOMETHING
WORTH CHEERING FOR.
UM... I WAS THINKING.
WANNA GRAB COFFEE
AT THE DOT, TOGETHER.
AFTER SCHOOL?
I MADE PLANS WITH THE HILLS.
BUT I AM GETTING
A LITTLE LC'D OUT,
SO... YEAH.
I'D LIKE THAT.
(PLEASED HALF LAUGH)
DANNY:
I'M PRETTY SURE COFFEE'S
NOT MEANT TO BE CHUGGED.
I NEED IT.
I'VE BEEN COMING IN EARLY
TO DANCE.
SWEET.
YOU GONNA PERFORM SOMETIME?
NUH-UHN.
ON A PERFORMANCE DETOX
POST BALLET SCHOOL.
BUT I STILL NEED TO DANCE,
LIKE, EVERY DAY.
JUST FOR ME.
HOW WOULD YOU FEEL ABOUT
GOING ON A DATE WITH DEREK?
WHY WOULD I GO OUT
WITH SOMEONE I DON'T LIKE?
PLEASE. AS A FAVOUR,
SO I CAN TELL HIM I TRIED.
WORST CASE?
YOU'LL KNOW FOR SURE
THAT YOU DON'T LIKE HIM.
OKAY.
I'LL GO OUT WITH HIM, ONCE.
BUT ON ONE CONDITION.
YOU SHOW UP DURING THE DATE
TO SAVE ME.
DEAL.
SAV:
(EXHALES FORCEFULLY)
FOUR SETS OF 15.
WORKS BICEPS
AND CORE.
(GRUNTS) YEAH,
WHAT'VE YOU BEEN EATING?
AND CAN I HAVE SOME?
IT'S NOTHING
TO DO WITH FOOD.
BRUCE:
AND LIFTING DOUBLE WHAT YOU
STARTED WITH THIS YEAR, BRO?
THAT'S WHACK.
YEAH,
WHAT'S YOUR SECRET?
MY SECRET?
IS ACTION.
LIKE HOOKING UP WITH HOT
CHEERLEADERS LIKE ANYA.
OH, THAT A BOY!
GUYS:
(LAUGHTER)
ATTA BOY!
WHAT? NEED A SPOT?
NO. I DON'T.
AND A GENERAL RULE
AMONG ALL GUYS?
IS THAT YOU DON'T HOOKUP
WITH YOUR TEAMMATES EX.
YEAH, WELL,
I COULDN'T HELP IT.
SHE SEEMED TO LIKE ME.
THAT'S WEAK, MAN.
DUDES DON'T DO THAT.
STILL GOT SOMETHING TO SAY?
YEAH,
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
RILEY:
(EXHALING FORCEFULLY)
ANYA:
COME ON. IT'S FUN.
IF YOU COULD BE
ANY KIND OF BREAD,
WHAT WOULD YOU BE?
RILEY:
WHAT? I HAVE NO CLUE.
I'LL GO FIRST.
I WOULD BE...
A POP TART!
A POP TART?!
DOES THAT EVEN COUNT
AS A BREAD?
YOU'RE WAY TOO CUTE
WHEN YOU LAUGH.
CAN I GET YOU
A BLOCK OF CHEESE
TO GO WITH YOUR HUMONGOUS
MEAT HEAD?
RILEY:
IT'S CALLED A COMPLIMENT.
YOU'VE PROBABLY
NEVER HEARD ONE BEFORE.
OKAY. SO I GUESS THAT'S
A STRAWBERRY MILKSHAKE FOR ANYA
AND A BRAIN FOR RILEY.
ANYTHING ELSE?
ANYA:
MIA, PETER!
HEY!
COME SIT.
OH, WE WERE JUST TALKING ABOUT
WHAT KIND OF CARB WE WOULD BE.
AH, RILEY'S SUCH A PANINI!
(HALF LAUGHS)
I'M GONNA RUN
TO THE RESTROOM.
GET ME WHAT I USUALLY GET?
ANYA:
OH, WAIT FOR ME.
SO THE STEROIDS
ARE MAKING YOU BUFF
AND STRAIGHT?
I'M ON A DATE WITH ANYA.
AND I LIKE HER.
A LOT.
ARE YOU SURE?
REMEMBER...
FORGET IT.
IT'S KINDA HARD TO FORGET,
DUDE.
YOU TRIED TO KISS ME.
IT WAS A WEIRD MISTAKE.
IT'S DONE.
PETER:
YOU COULD BE CONFUSED OR...
GET OVER IT.
(CLACK OF POOL BALLS)
DEREK:
MAY I SHOW YOU
HOW TO HOLD THE STICK?
WHY, AM I DOING SOMETHING
WRONG?
SMOOTH MOVE.
BUT IT ONLY WORKS IN MOVIES.
SOME ROOM?
PLEASE.
DEREK:
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
(CLACK OF POOL BALLS)
YES!
DEREK:
WOW!
AH! YOU INTO THIS SONG?
OVERPLAYED.
CAN'T STAND IT ANYMORE.
YEAH.
YEAH, ME NEITHER.
(CLACK OF POOL BALLS)
SO, HOW ABOUT YOU SHOW ME
SOME DANCE MOVES.
YOU'RE A DANCER,
RIGHT?
BALLET SCHOOL.
AND I'M SORTA SHY
ABOUT DANCING.
(HALF LAUGHS)
CAN'T BE AS SHY AS DANNY.
NO ONE CAN BE SHYER
THAN DANNY.
YEAH, LIKE WHEN HE GETS
FLUSTERED AROUND GIRLS,
HE DOES THIS LIKE,
HEAD SHAKE THING, YOU KNOW.
HE'S SO CUTE
WHEN HE DOES THAT!
HO-OH, SO THAT'S HOW
HE GETS THE GIRLS, HUH?
YEAH. AND 'CAUSE
HE'S A QUALITY GUY.
WAIT. WAIT, ARE WE TALKING
ABOUT THE SAME DANNY?
YOU KNOW, LIKE,
SIX-ONE,
QUARTERBACK,
COOL STYLE,
SOMETIMES LOOKS LIKE HE'S ABOUT
TO BUST INTO THE MOONWALK?
(LAUGHS)
ALL RIGHT.
YOU READY?
THIS IS IT.
(PATRONS CHATTER AND LAUGH,
CAR HORN HONKS)
ANYA:
OH, UH, THAT'S MY MOM.
RILEY:
SO, WE STILL ON FOR TOMORROW,
RIGHT, POP TART?
ANYA:
DEFINITELY, PANINI.
(RILEY'S PHONE RINGS)
(PHONE BEEPS)
(CAR WHIRS AWAY)
SOCCERSTUD1717:
RILEY?
RILEY.
(PANTING)
(EXHALING FORCEFULLY)
(DIN OF CHATTER)
(MUTED CHATTER AND LAUGHTER)
(SCHOLL BELL RINGS)
KWAN:
I ASSUME YOU'VE ALL DONE
YOUR READINGS.
RILEY,
YOU'LL BE LEADING
THE DISCUSSION
ON THE DIFFERENCES
BETWEEN DUNSTAN RAMSAY
AND PERCY BOYD.
WHEN YOU'RE READY.
PETER: (WHISPERING)
YEAH.
...SHEP.
(INAUDIBLE WHISPER)
THE FIRST DIFFERENCE
IS THAT PERCY...
IS MATERIALISTIC
AND, UH, DUNNY
IS MORE SPIRITUAL.
KWAN:
PLEASE ILLUSTRATE.
(LAUGHING)
WHAT ABOUT AT THE BEGINNING,
WHEN THEY'RE TOBOGGANING?
KWAN:
GO ON.
THEIR SLEDS SORT OF...
KWAN:
RILEY!
(SHOCKED MURMURS)
PRINCIPAL SHEPPARD'S OFFICE.
NOW!
RILEY:
BUT MISS, THEY WERE-
KWAN:
I SAID NOW.
WE DON'T TOLERATE VIOLENCE
HERE.
(OBJECTS CLATTER)
SO HOW DID YOU MESS UP?
I UH...
SET DEREK UP WITH LEIA
BEFORE I REALIZED
I WAS INTO HER.
(SYMPATHETIC BREATH)
I EVEN SAW
ONE OF THEIR DATES...
LAUGHING -
HAVING A BLAST.
SHE'S BEEN "DEREK'D".
I NEVER THOUGHT
SHE'D LIKE A GUY LIKE HIM.
HE'S SO... ANNOYING.
SORRY TO BREAK IT TO YOU,
BUT YOU USED TO BE HIM.
KEY WORDS, MAN:
USED TO.
NOT ANYMORE.
I DON'T WANNA BE ASSOCIATED
WITH THAT GUY.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST TELL HER
HOW YOU FEEL, THEN?
AGH...
I CAN'T DO THAT TO DEREK.
BUT IF YOU THINK
HE'S SUCH A JERK...?
WOULDN'T BE RIGHT.
HEY, THROWING AN ERASER
AT MY HEAD?
NOT COOL, MAN.
I WASN'T EVEN LAUGHING AT YOU.
YOU GOT 'ROID RAGE.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TAKING ABOUT.
I GOOGLED IT, DUDE.
STEROIDS CAUSE, LIKE,
SERIOUS PERMANENT LIVER DAMAGE,
THEY STUNT YOUR GROWTH.
AND LOOK-
BACK OFF!
IT'S MY BODY.
AND I'LL DO WHAT I WANT.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
WHY DIDN'T YOU SHOW
LAST NIGHT?
BUSY WITH FOOTBALL STUFF.
BUT WE HAD A DEAL.
SORRY.
THAT'S OKAY, TURNS OUT
I DIDN'T NEED SAVING.
DEREK'S A FUN GUY.
GREAT.
I'M CROWNING YOU
THE KING OF MIXED MESSAGES.
I SAID YES
TO THE DATE WITH DEREK
BECAUSE I THOUGHT
YOU'D BE THERE.
(SIGHS)
BUT DEREK REALLY LIKES YOU.
SO IT'S DONE.
ANYA:
HM. LOOK!
SHE DREW LITTLE FOOTBALLS
ON THE ONES FOR YOU.
AND POM POMS FOR ME.
RILEY:
MY MOM WENT ALL OUT.
ANYA:
MM-HM.
ANYA AND RILEY:
(LAUGH)
AND THESE SANDWICHES
DIDN'T MAKE THEMSELVES.
(HALF LAUGHS)
'KAY, MY MOM MADE THEM TOO.
SHE GOT EXCITED THAT I WAS
TAKING A CHEERLEADER OUT
ON A DATE.
(DOG BARKS IN THE DISTANCE)
BETTER?
MUCH.
(HALF LAUGHS)
THIS IS PERFECT.
(KISS)
I... JUST REMEMBERED,
I GOTTA BE SOMEWHERE
IN HALF AN HOUR.
SOME GROUP PROJECT.
(DOG BARKS)
(CLEAR THROAT)
SHOULD I WALK YOU HOME?
NO, I'LL JUST CALL MY MOM
TO PICK ME UP.
SORRY.
NO...
(BUSHES RUSTLE)
NOT RUNNING AWAY
THIS TIME?
YOU LOOK THE SAME.
YOU KNOW,
MINUS THE BRACES.
AND THE BABY FAT.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHY I'M HERE.
WHAT, YOU...
DIDN'T COME TO APOLOGIZE
FOR THE TIME YOU
TOILET PAPERED MY CABIN?
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
YEAH, YOU TOO.
I SHOULD GO.
LOOK, RILEY,
JUST WAIT OKAY.
I WAS JUST AS NERVOUS...
MY FIRST TIME
WITH A GUY.
BUT IF YOU...
IF YOU JUST RELAX.
I PROMISE EVERYTHING'S
GONNA BE FINE, OKAY?
(TENSE BREATHS)
♪ I can't the breath
in the space ♪
♪ That's filled
with your sound ♪
♪ Can't call a spade a spade
in this town ♪
♪ Dug a hole
now I can't get out ♪
♪ I can't I figure it
I can't I figure it out ♪
♪ Out... ♪
♪ Keep your head up high ♪
♪ Keep mine
deep in the ground ♪
♪ Hide away the love
that I found ♪
♪ Built a wall
now I can't get 'round ♪
♪ I can't figure it
I can't figure it out ♪
RILEY:
SORRY I PEACE'D OUT LIKE THAT.
I REALLY HAD TO GET
THAT GROUP PROJECT DONE.
UH HUH.
OKAY, UM...
YESTERDAY WAS WEIRD.
WAS IT?
WE HAD A GOOD TIME.
I KNOW I HAD TO GO.
BUT WE HAD FUN, RIGHT?
THE KISS...
IT DIDN'T FEEL RIGHT.
WE WERE JUST NERVOUS
OR SOMETHING.
NO. THERE'S A REASON.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I DON'T THINK
I'M OVER SAV YET.
HE'S THE ONLY GUY
I'VE EVER KISSED-
YEAH, I GOTCHA.
NO, BUT I STILL
WANNA BE FRIENDS.
I'M NOT JUST SAYING THAT.
I MEAN IT.
I CAN BE OKAY WITH THAT.
REALLY?
THAT'S AMAZING!
BECAUSE MOST GUYS WOULD BE
TOO TOUGH TO STAY FRIENDS.
WELL, YOU'RE REALLY COOL
HANGING OUT WITH.
(LAUGHS)
ALL RIGHT...
OH, AND I'LL BE CHEERING
FOR YOU AT THE GAME LATER.
GO PANTHERS GO!
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
KWAN: (READING)
"IF YOU DON'T HURRY UP AND LET
LIFE KNOW WHAT YOU WANT,
LIFE WILL DAMNED SOON SHOW YOU
WHAT YOU'LL GET."
NOW, PARTNER UP
AND WRITE A BRIEF PARAGRAPH,
AND HOW THIS QUOTATION RELATES
TO THE NOVEL'S THEMES.
GO FOR HER.
WHAT?
I SAW YOU WATCHING LEIA.
SHE'S ALL YOUR'S.
WHAT ABOUT YOU AND LEIA?
DON'T YOU-
YOU TRIED
TO HOOK A BROTHER UP.
THAT MEANS MORE THAN GETTING
THE GIRL.
KWAN:
DEREK, DANNY,
PLEASE FOCUS
ON YOUR ASSIGNMENT.
(HUFFS) NOTHING EVER CHANGES
WITH YOU TWO.
OKAY...
BEGIN.
SHEP: (BLOWS WHISTLE)
OKAY, LISTEN UP!
AS THE GREAT LOMBARDI SAID:
"SHOW ME A GOOD LOSER,
AND I'LL SHOW YOU A LOSER."
BREAK!
WE LEAVE IN FIVE.
SO, LET'S BE WINNERS!
LET ME HEAR IT.
(RILED UP CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
HEY,
YOU PUMPED FOR ANOTHER WIN?
YEAH, DEFINITELY.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH. FINE.
OKAY.
(RILEY'S PHONE RINGS)
(PHONE BEEPS ON)
WHO'S THAT?
RILEY:
IT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
WELL, IF IT'S ANYA
TEXTING YOU?
THEN IT IS MY BUSINESS.
I'M PRETTY SURE
SHE DUMPED YOU, MAN.
SHOW ME WHAT SHE WROTE.
GET OUT OF MY FACE, MAN!
SAV:
WE WERE TOGETHER SIX MONTHS!
MEANS MORE THAN SOME STUPID
GAY PICNIC!
(BONE CRUNCHES)
(STUDENTS GASP, SHOCKED)
ANYA:
SAV!
(WHACK OF HARD PUNCHES)
RILEY:
GET OFF HIM, MAN.
PETER:
HEY! HEY!
TEAMMATES!
MIA:
(GASPS)
OH MY GOD.
SHEP:
GET THE NURSE.
DEREK:
CHILL.
HOW'S SAV?
TOOK A WHILE FOR HIS NOSE
TO STOP BLEEDING.
BUT HE'LL SURVIVE.
SURPRISINGLY TOUGH FOR A GUY
WHO USED TO COLLECT STICKERS.
(CHUCKLES)
AND THE GAME?
WE LOST.
THINGS ARE BACK TO NORMAL.
WHATEVER THAT MEANS
AROUND HERE.
SO, DEREK AND I TALKED...
LET ME UM,
CLARIFY SOMETHING.
I DON'T WANNA DATE HIM.
I KNOW.
HE TOLD ME.
(KISS)
HOMEWORK FOR THE NEXT WEEK.
BEING SUSPENDED SUCKS,
I KNOW.
HOW'S SAV?
I DIDN'T MEAN TO DO THAT.
HE'S FINE.
ANYA MUST HATE ME.
NOT GONNA LIE.
SHE'S PISSED, MAN.
I MESSED UP.
EVER SINCE I WAS A LITTLE KID,
I ALWAYS WANTED TO BE
THE STAR ATHLETE.
WITH LOTS OF FRIENDS
AND A HOT GIRLFRIEND.
WHAT ABOUT THE STEROIDS?
I'M DONE WITH THEM.
I THOUGHT THEY WOULD
CHANGE THINGS...
YOU REALLY THOUGHT STEROIDS
WOULD MAKE YOU STRAIGHT?
I DON'T WANNA BE LIKE THIS.
DUDE...
YOU CAN STILL BE
A STAR ATHLETE.
HAVE LOTS OF FRIENDS.
THIS DOESN'T CHANGE THAT.
(DEEP BREATH)