(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
SHEP: (OVER PA)
GOOD MORNING, DEGRASSI.
IT GIVES ME GREAT PRIDE
TO ANNOUNCE
THAT YOURS TRULY
WILL BE RECEIVING
THE PRINCIPAL OF THE YEAR AWARD
THIS WEEK.
GREAT. CONNOR'S FOUND
ANOTHER WAY
TO MAKE US LOOK LIKE FREAKS.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO STOP
THE FLICKER
OF FLUORESCENT LIGHTS
FROM BOTHERING ME.
I STAND CORRECTED.
SHEP:
OKAY, EVERYBODY,
LISTEN UP.
WHICH ONE OF YOU GEEKS
WANTS FRIDAY OFF?
NICE. YOU TWO.
OKAY, SO WHAT I NEED
IS QUOTES ABOUT ME, ON VIDEO,
FOR THE AWARD CEREMONY.
OKAY?
(SHEP GRUNTS,
KIDS LAUGH)
THIS THING'S A HAZARD.
BUT IT STOPS THE LIGHT
FROM BOTHERING ME.
IF SUCH A SERIOUS PROBLEM,
YOU MUST HAVE
A DOCTOR'S NOTE, RIGHT?
NO?
WELL, THEN TRY AND BE
A LITTLE MORE NORMAL,
WOULD YA, DUDE?
I THINK YOU SHOULD
LET CONNOR KEEP HIS LAMP.
HE NEEDS IT.
SORRY,
CAN'T GIVE ONE STUDENT
PREFERENTIAL TREATMENT.
UNLESS HE'S
A FOOTBALL PLAYER.
SHEP:
OOH.
YOU'RE ENTITLED
TO YOUR OPINION -
IN DETENTION.
YOU CAN'T GIVE ME A DETENTION
FOR HAVING A POINT OF VIEW.
SURE I CAN.
I'M THE PRINCIPAL.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Oh! Oh! Oh! ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(LOW HUM OF STUDENT CHATTER)
CLARE:
"BE MORE NORMAL."
IS THAT THE TYPE OF ADVICE
THE PRINCIPAL OF THE YEAR
SHOULD GIVE HIS STUDENTS?
ALLI:
CUT!
THIS VIDEO IS TO SHOW
WHY THE SHEP
DESERVES PRINCIPAL
OF THE YEAR.
HE DOESN'T.
ARE YOU STILL ON
ABOUT THE LAMP?
IT'S NOT ABOUT THE LAMP.
IT'S ABOUT TOLERANCE
OF INDIVIDUAL DIFFERENCES.
WHAT'RE YOU GONNA DO?
PROTEST?
YOU'RE NOT GONNA PROTEST
ARE YOU?
HELLO.
OOH... NICE CAMERA.
BRUCE:
YEAH, I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR ONE
JUST LIKE THIS.
KC:
HEY. MAYBE YOU SHOULD
BUY YOUR OWN.
BRUCE:
(LAUGHS)
WHATEVER.
WE WANNA TAKE ON SHEPPARD...
WE DO IT AS A GROUP.
BECAUSE ONE DETENTION
WASN'T ENOUGH?
(CAR WHIRS AWAY)
SOMEONE'S HAPPY
TO SEE YOU.
YEAH, EVER SINCE I GOT PUNCHED
IN THE NOSE,
SHE'S BEEN SO SWEET TO ME.
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN
WHY YOU TWO BROKE UP?
SOMETHING ABOUT FAITH
AND FAMILY
TRUMPING YOUR RELATIONSHIP.
IS THERE ROOM
FOR ONE MORE?
I CAN'T BELIEVE RILEY
ONLY GOT THREE DAYS SUSPENSION
FOR PUNCHING YOU.
PRINCIPAL OF THE YEAR
CAN'T LOSE HIS STAR
RUNNING-BACK
FOR THE BIG GAME.
ANYA:
BUT SAV'S NOSE
STILL LOOKS AWFUL.
I KINDA THOUGHT
IT MADE ME LOOK TOUGH.
TOUGH?
REALLY?
THE BOY'S NEVER EVEN BEATEN ME
IN ARM-WRESTLING.
I LET YOU WIN.
MM-HMM.
REMATCH.
MOVIE DATE WITH LEIA.
GOTTA RUN.
GO.
(FISTS THUD ON TABLE)
YOU DIDN'T REALLY THINK
YOU WERE TOUGHER THAN ME?
YOU DID!
(LAUGHS)
I'LL SHOW YOU WHO'S TOUGH.
(PLAYFUL PUNCHES)
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
UH... WELL...
YOU CARED SO MUCH
WHEN I GOT HURT,
I THOUGHT...
THAT I STILL LOVE YOU?
I DO.
IT DOESN'T MEAN
I WANNA GET BACK TOGETHER.
IS THIS ABOUT
THE CAMPING TRIP?
'CAUSE I KNOW
I WAS A JERK.
WHO WAS TRYING TO DO
WHAT HIS FAMILY WANTED.
WHICH YOU ALWAYS DO.
THE ONLY PROBLEM?
YOUR FAMILY
DOESN'T WANT ME.
WE DON'T KNOW THAT.
BECAUSE YOU DON'T
HAVE THE GUTS
TO TELL THEM ABOUT ME,
AND I'M PRETTY SURE
YOU NEVER WILL.
ALLI:
YOUR LITTLE PLAN
IS ABOUT TO GET US
INTO REALLY BIG TROUBLE.
SHEP:
'KAY, SO, UH, YEAH,
HOW'S MY VIDEO COMING ALONG?
WHAT DID I SAY YESTERDAY?
THAT YOU COULDN'T MAKE
AN EXCEPTION FOR ONE STUDENT.
NOW YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
WHAT?
NO, NO. TAKE THOSE LAMPS
OFF YOUR DESK.
NOT UNLESS CONNOR
CAN KEEP HIS.
SHEP:
WHAT, YOU WANNA NEGOTIATE?
OKAY, WHAT DO YA GOT TO OFFER?
THAT'S RIGHT.
NOTHING.
SO TAKE THE LAMPS
OFF THE DESK, EVERYONE.
'KAY, FINE.
DETENTIONS ALL AROUND.
BE SURE TO THANK
MISS EDWARDS FOR THAT.
NICE ONE,
ST. CLARE.
(HUM OF CHATTER)
I TELL MY PARENTS
ABOUT ANYA,
IT'S OVER.
IF I DON'T...
YOU DRESS HOW YOU WANT.
YOU PLAY IN A BAND.
FROM WHAT I'VE SEEN,
YOUR PARENTS
ARE PRETTY OPEN-MINDED.
YEAH, ABOUT MOST THINGS.
BUT...
DATING IS HARRAM...
LIKE FORBIDDEN.
AND DATING A NON-MUSLIM
IS LIKE SUPER HARRAM.
SO YOU HAVE TO CHOOSE,
ANYA OR FAMILY?
TOO BAD I LOVE THEM BOTH.
(RAPID TAPPING)
WE COULD INVOLVE
THE SCHOOL BOARD.
(HUSHED SPEECH)
LET'S SERVE THIS DETENTION
BEFORE YOU GET US
ANOTHER ONE.
(PERINO'S CELL PHONE RINGS)
(BEEPS CELL PHONE ON)
PERINO:
BE BACK IN A MOMENT.
BEHAVE.
(TAPPING)
STOP IT, CONNOR.
I SAID STOP TAPPING
THAT PENCIL.
LEAVE HIM ALONE, ALLI.
NOT UNTIL HE GIVES ME
THE PENCIL.
GET AWAY FROM ME!
(SPITS)
(HUFFS)
YOU FREAK!
GIVE ME BACK MY PENCIL!
(PENCIL SNAPS)
(EASEL CLATTERS)
ALLI:
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?!
PERINO:
HEY!
WHO'S RESPONSIBLE
FOR THIS?
I TOLD HER
TO GET OUT OF MY WAY.
OH,
THAT'S A COMPELLING STORY.
I'M SURE THE SHEP
WILL BE MOVED TO TEARS.
YOU KNOW WHAT HE'S LIKE.
WHY COULDN'T YOU
JUST LEAVE HIM ALONE?!
KC:
ALLI'S OKAY.
NOT THAT YOU WOULD CARE.
WHAT'S THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
HE'S YOUR FRIEND,
I GET THAT,
BUT YOU CAN'T DEFEND HIM
PUSHING ALLI.
HAVE EVER HAD YOUR FACE
PUSHED INTO A PUDDLE OF MUD
WHILE PEOPLE STOOD AROUND
AND LAUGHED?
THEN YOU WOULDN'T
UNDERSTAND.
CONNOR:
I AM NOT APOLOGIZING TO ALLI!
I TOLD HER
TO GET OUT OF MY WAY!
(DOORS OPEN)
CONNOR'S A GOOD KID.
OKAY?
IF WE COULD JUST WAIT
FOR THE TEST RESULTS.
MMM...
I'D STILL EXPEL HIM.
I MEAN,
THE KID'S A LOOSE CANNON
AND THIS IS NOT
HIS FIRST INCIDENT.
I'M SORRY,
MY DECISION'S FINAL.
(VEHICLE WHIRS BY)
OKAY, SO,
THERE'S THIS GIRL AT SCHOOL.
(MIMICKING FATHER)
YOU'RE GROUNDED.
FOR LIFE.
THIS IS SERIOUS, ALLI.
WHAT'S SERIOUS?
UH, DAD, UH...
THERE'S SOMETHING
I WANNA TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
THAT DOESN'T INVOLVE ALLI.
GO ON, SON.
UH...
BEFORE YOU MARRIED MOM,
WERE YOU EVER INTERESTED
IN OTHER GIRLS?
(LAUGHS)
YOU MEAN WAS I 17 ONCE?
YES.
OKAY, UM, BUT YOU NEVER
DATED ANY OF THEM,
RIGHT?
NO PROPER GIRL
WOULD BE ALLOWED.
IN INDIA.
BUT IT'S DIFFERENT HERE.
I MEAN, EVERYONE DATES.
AND THERE'S THIS GIRL
THAT I LIKE - ANYA.
I LIKE HER A LOT.
PLEASE SAY SOMETHING.
WELL, IF YOU'RE SERIOUS
ABOUT THIS GIRL,
WE SHOULD MEET HER.
WHY DON'T YOU INVITE HER
OVER TO DINNER?
SERIOUSLY?!
DAD, YOU'RE THE BEST.
(CHUCKLES)
YOU CAN'T GO HOME.
NOT YET!
IF I'M NOT IN GIFTED
AT DEGRASSI,
MY PARENTS WON'T LET ME STAY.
BUT WE'RE NOT DONE
FIGHTING THIS.
WE HAVEN'T GONE
TO THE SCHOOL BOARD...
OR THE MEDIA.
YOU JUST HAVE TO APOLOGIZE
FOR PUSHING ALLI.
SHE TOOK MY PENCIL!
I'M A FREAK, OKAY?!
EVERYONE THINKS SO!
SHEP, ALLI, KC.
EVEN MR. SIMPSON.
THAT'S WHY HE KEEPS
TAKING ME FOR TESTS.
TESTS?
WHAT TYPE OF TESTS?
ALL YOUR CLOTHES,
THEY'RE THE SAME.
CONNOR:
YOU WEAR THE SAME THING
EVERY DAY.
BUT I HAVE OTHER CLOTHES
AT HOME.
YOU THINK I'M A FREAK TOO!
GET OUT!
GET OUT! GET OUT!
GET OUT! NOW!
(OBJECTS CLATTER)
(HUM OF CHATTER)
HOLLY J:
SHEP CAN SPOT A LEADER.
HE DIDN'T MAKE ME RUN
FOR SCHOOL PRESIDENT,
HE JUST APPOINTED ME.
PRETTY SURE
THAT'S NOT A GOOD THING.
WE'LL JUST CUT AROUND
THE "APPOINTED" PART.
CONNOR GETS EXPELLED;
CLARE GETS A NEW WARDROBE.
LEAVE IT ALONE, ALLI.
ARE YOU OKAY?
CONNOR WAS JUST SO...
WEIRD?
I WENT OVER LAST NIGHT
AND HE HAD SOME SORT
OF MELTDOWN.
THERE'S SOMETHING WRONG
WITH HIM.
SIMPSON:
CLARE.
CAN I SPEAK TO YOU
FOR A MOMENT?
SINCE YOU'RE HIS FRIEND,
CONNOR WANTED ME
TO TELL YOU.
HE'S BEEN DIAGNOSED
WITH ASPERGER'S SYNDROME.
ASPERGER'S SYNDROME?
IT MEANS HIS BRAIN
IS WIRED DIFFERENTLY.
SOCIAL RULES
THAT WE ALL KNOW,
HE HAS TO LEARN.
BUT THERE'S SOME SORT OF CURE,
RIGHT?
LIKE MEDICATION
OR SOMETHING?
NO.
BUT WITH COUNSELLING
HE CAN LIVE A NORMAL LIFE.
HE'S REALLY SCARED;
HE COULD USE A FRIEND
RIGHT NOW.
I SHOULD GET STARTED
ON MY ASSIGNMENT.
MS. DAWES:
"ROMEO AND JULIET":
AN EPIC LOVE STORY
OR THE TALE OF TWO
HORMONE-ADDLED TEENAGERS?
WHAT IS THIS ARTIST'S
INTERPRETATION?
AND MORE IMPORTANTLY,
WHAT WOULD YOUR
INTERPRETATION BE?
I WANT EACH OF YOU
TO CREATE A PIECE
THAT REPRESENTS
SHAKESPEARE'S PLAY...
YOU'RE MAKING THIS HARDER.
JUST OPEN IT.
MS. DAWES:
...WATER COLOURS,
PASTELS, PENCILS,
THE CHOICE IS YOURS.
TAKE YOUR TIME
WITH THIS ASSIGNMENT.
AM I MISSING SOMETHING?
YOU'LL NEED IT,
FOR WHEN YOU COME TO MY HOUSE
FOR DINNER TONIGHT.
YOU TOLD YOUR PARENTS
ABOUT US.
YEAH. AND THEY WANNA
MEET YOU TONIGHT.
(ELATED BREATH)
I LOVE YOU.
THANK YOU.
MS. DAWES:
OKAY?
OH, LOVE.
ENJOY IT WHILE YOU'RE YOUNG
AND BEAUTIFUL.
KIDS:
(SNICKERING)
(LAWNMOWER ENGINE RUMBLES)
(DOOR OPENS AND SHUTS)
(KNOCKS THREE TIMES)
MR. SIMPSON LET ME IN.
IS THAT AN X-23 MODEL?
YEAH,
BUT I REPLACED
THE ELECTRIC MOTOR
WITH A HYDRAULIC SYSTEM.
TO GIVE IT MORE POWER.
SMART.
I DIDN'T THINK YOU'D VISIT
BEFORE I LEFT.
I GUESS I NEEDED SOME TIME
TO DIGEST YOUR NEWS.
THEY SAY THAT EINSTEIN
MIGHT'VE HAD ASPERGERS.
HE USED TO WEAR
THE SAME OUTFIT EVERYDAY
JUST LIKE YOU.
MR. SIMPSON TOLD ME
I'M REALLY SMART.
YOU ARE.
BUT HE SAID THAT
NOT EVERYONE IS INTERESTED
IN WHAT I'M INTERESTED IN.
SO I HAVE TO BE CAREFUL
NOT TO BORE PEOPLE
ABOUT ROBOTS AND MOTHS
AND STUFF.
WELL, YOU DON'T BORE ME.
SO YOU DON'T THINK
I'M A FREAK?
NO.
I THINK THAT YOU BELONG
IN THE GIFTED PROGRAM
AT DEGRASSI.
ISN'T THE BURFI ANYA MADE
DELICIOUS?
MIGHT EVEN RIVAL
YOUR MOTHER'S.
I'M JUST SO EXCITED
TO MEET YOU BOTH.
AND WE'RE HAPPY
TO HAVE THE CHANCE
TO TALK TO BOTH OF YOU,
TOGETHER.
WE'RE HAPPY SAV HAS A FRIEND
AS LOVELY AS YOU.
BUT YOU NEED TO KNOW,
SAV'S FUTURE
WILL BE WITH SOMEONE...
MORE LIKE HIM.
MA!
MRS. BHANDARI:
NONE OF THIS SHOULD COME
AS A SURPRISE TO YOU, SAVTAJ.
YOU LET ANYA
COME FOR DINNER.
IT'S IMPORTANT
ANYA HEAR THE TRUTH.
NEITHER OF YOU SHOULD BE
IN A RELATIONSHIP
THAT HAS NO FUTURE.
ANYA:
UM, I CAN BECOME MUSLIM.
I'VE BEEN READING THE QUR'AN
AND EVERYTHING.
IT'S NOT JUST ABOUT RELIGION.
WHEN YOU LEAVE YOUR HOME,
IT'S EASY TO LOSE YOUR ROOTS.
IT'S UP TO OUR CHILDREN
TO MAINTAIN THEM
WITH INDIAN SPOUSES.
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
YOU WERE 17 ONCE.
MR. BHANDARI:
I'M SORRY, SAV.
BUT YOUR MOTHER AND I ARE UNITED
ON THIS FRONT.
I APPRECIATE YOUR HONESTY,
AND I THINK I SHOULD GO.
ENJOY THE BURFI.
UH...
I'LL WALK YOU OUT.
UH, THAT'S OKAY.
CHANTAY:
A NEW FOOTBALL TEAM,
A REVAMPED POWER SQUAD...
SINCE PRINCIPAL SHEPPARD
JOINED DEGRASSI,
SPIRIT HAS BEEN
AT AN ALL-TIME HIGH.
YAY SHEP!
WOW.
GREAT JOB, KIDS.
NOW, LET'S SHOOT
MY INTRO
AND WE'RE DONE.
RIGHT HERE?
KC: SURE.
SHEP: OKAY.
(CAMERA BUTTON CLICKS,
RECORD BUTTON BEEPS ON)
ACTION.
PRINCIPAL OF THE YEAR?
WOW. I CAN'T TELL YOU
WHAT AN HONOUR THIS IS FOR ME.
YOU NEED TO LET CONNOR
COME BACK TO DEGRASSI.
(SCOFFS) THE ONLY THING
I NEED TO DO
IS FINISH THIS VIDEO,
OKAY?
CLARE:
KIDS WITH ASPERGERS
CAN DO WELL
AT REGULAR SCHOOLS.
IF YOU KICK HIM OUT,
HE'LL...
DEGRASSI'S BETTER OFF
WITH ONE LESS OF YOU WEIRDOS.
(SNICKERS)
ONE LESS OF US WEIRDOS?
SHOULD WE JUST KICK OUT
EVERYONE WHO'S NOT A JOCK?
DON'T TEASE ME.
YOU'RE A TERRIBLE
PRINCIPAL!
AND YOU'RE A LITTLE BITCH.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
FORGET MY INTRO.
I'LL DO IT LIVE.
ARE YOU TRYING
TO GET EXPELLED?
IF THAT MAN RUNS THE SCHOOL,
I DON'T CARE.
WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE SHOW THE SCHOOL
THE REAL PRINCIPAL
OF THE YEAR?
(HIP HOP SONG BEGINS)
♪ Hey! Come on! ♪
(MUSIC PLAYS,
LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
SIMPSON:
GUYS, GUYS. EVERYONE,
PLEASE TAKE YOUR SEATS.
CEREMONY'S ABOUT TO BEGIN.
(EVERYONE APPLAUDS)
SHEP:
THANK YOU,
SCHOOL BOARD PRESIDENT,
TRUSTEES,
TEACHERS AND STUDENTS,
THIS AWARD IS TRULY AN HONOUR.
EVERY DAY,
I TRY AND MAKE DEGRASSI
THE KIND OF SCHOOL
I'D LIKE TO ATTEND.
AND I THINK I'M DOING
AN OKAY JOB
BECAUSE SOME STUDENTS ASKED
TO PUT TOGETHER
A TRIBUTE VIDEO FOR ME.
PLEASE. WATCH.
CLARE: (ON VIDEO)
KIDS WITH ASPERGERS
CAN DO WELL
AT REGULAR SCHOOLS.
IF YOU KICK...
SHEP:
DEGRASSI WILL BE BETTER OFF
WITH ONE LESS OF YOU WEIRDOS.
CLARE:
ONE LESS OF US...
TURN THAT OFF, PLEASE.
I SAID TURN IT OFF!
CLARE: (ON VIDEO)
...EVERYONE WHO'S NOT A JOCK?
SHEP: (ON VIDEO)
DON'T TEASE ME.
CLARE: (ON VIDEO)
YOU'RE A TERRIBLE PRINCIPAL!
SHEP: (ON VIDEO)
AND YOU'RE A LITTLE BITCH.
(STUNNED GASPS AND MURMURS
THROUGHOUT GYM)
STILL THINK HE DESERVES
PRINCIPAL OF THE YEAR?
SOMEONE WHO THINKS THAT
DEGRASSI'D BE BETTER OFF
WITHOUT KIDS
WHO ARE A LITTLE DIFFERENT?
KC:
BECAUSE WE DON'T.
YOU KNOW WHY.
(LOW MURMURING THROUGHOUT GYM)
SHEP:
WAIT A MINUTE.
HEY!
STOP NOW AND YOU WON'T FACE
DISCIPLINARY ACTION.
I MEAN IT.
WHAT IS THIS,
A JOKE?!
NO MORE SHEP!
STUDENTS: (CHANT)
NO MORE SHEP! NO MORE SHEP!
NO MORE SHEP!
SCHOOL BOARD PRESIDENT:
I'M THE PRESIDENT
OF THE SCHOOL BOARD
AND I UNDERSTAND THAT
YOU'RE THE STUDENT
RESPONSIBLE FOR THIS.
YES, I AM.
CARE TO EXPLAIN?
WELL...
IT ALL STARTED
WITH A DESK LAMP...
(PAPER RUSTLES)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
PA ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION, STUDENTS.
IT'S PIZZA DAY IN THE CAF...
FOR WHAT IT'S WORTH,
I'M SORRY.
HOW COULD YOU EVEN
PUT ME IN THAT SITUATION?
I... (SIGHS)
WANTED TO BELIEVE
THAT MY PARENTS
WOULD BE OKAY WITH YOU,
WITH US.
YOU DIDN'T EVEN STAND UP
FOR ME.
I DID. I...
I JUST MIGHT'VE DONE IT
A LITTLE TOO LATE.
WHAT'RE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I TOLD MY PARENTS
THAT I WOULDN'T
STOP SEEING YOU.
YOU DID?
YEAH, UM...
THEY WERE UPSET...
BUT IT'S MY LIFE
AND I WANT YOU IN IT.
THIS ISN'T GONNA BE EASY.
I KNOW.
BUT UH...
I LOVE YOU
AND I'M PRETTY SURE
MY PARENTS WILL TOO.
WELL, I'M GONNA MAKE THEM
LOVE ME.
BOTH:
(CHUCKLE SOFTLY)
SO I'LL BE ACTING PRINCIPAL
FOR THE NEXT MONTH,
WHILE PRINCIPAL SHEPPARD
ATTENDS A VERY IMPORTANT...
WORKSHOP.
HE'S NOT GETTING FIRED?
MY DAD SAID
IT'S ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE
FOR TEACHERS
TO GET FIRED.
EVEN A BAD ONE.
AND I HEARD
THE "IMPORTANT WORKSHOP"
IS REALLY
SENSITIVITY TRAINING.
ARE WE REALLY BACK TO THAT
FOR GOOD?
I CHANGED
FOR THE WRONG REASONS.
I THINK SHE LOOKS NICE.
SIMPSON:
CAN CLARE EDWARDS,
ALLI BHANDARI AND KC GUTHRIE
PLEASE COME TO THE MI ROOM?
YOU'RE BACK!
I GOT A DESK LAMP,
AND IT'S SAFETY-PROOFED.
THE SCHOOL BOARD INSISTED
THAT CONNOR COME BACK.
HE'LL HAVE SESSIONS
WITH A COUNSELOR
WHERE HE'LL LEARN
NEW TECHNIQUES
ON HOW TO DEAL WITH
SOCIAL SITUATIONS.
LIKE KNOWING
WHEN TO APOLOGIZE.
I'M SORRY I PUSHED YOU.
ME TOO.
KC:
SO... HOW DOES IT FEEL?
YOU KNOW...
TO HAVE ASPERGERS?
RELIEVED...
TO KNOW IT'S NOT MY FAULT
THAT I'M THE WAY THAT I AM
AND THAT THERE ARE OTHER PEOPLE
JUST LIKE ME.
AND I'M NOT JUST
SOME WEIRDO ANYMORE.
HEY, WE'RE ALL WEIRD.
AT LEAST YOU HAVE
AN EXCUSE.