(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
(PHONE BEEPS)
DRIVING EXAMINER:
THAT'S IT FOR TODAY.
WE CAN'T WAIT ANY LONGER.
PLEASE? MY BROTHER
SHOULD BE HERE ANY MINUTE.
REALLY.
(WHIR OF APPROACHING CAR)
OH, UH, THERE'S MY RIDE.
DRIVING EXAMINER:
IT'S ABOUT TIME.
(CAR STEREO PLAYS LOUDLY)
JANE:
TROUBLE GETTING OFF THE COUCH?
THOUGHT YOU'RE BOYFRIEND
WITH ONE NUT
WOULD HELP YOU OUT.
UNFORTUNATELY,
HE WAS AT WORK.
SO I THOUGHT I'D ASK
MY UNEMPLOYED
DROP-OUT BROTHER
FOR ONE FAVOUR.
(CLEAR THROAT)
JANE:
(HUFFS)
(HIP HOP PLAYS LOUDLY)
GREAT.
THANK YOU FOR WAITING.
HEY, MOM.
MY DRIVERS TEST.
I GOT IT!
AH!
YOU GOT IT!
(GUSHING)
OH!
I AM SO PROUD OF YOU!
AND ON YOUR FIRST TRY!
YEAH.
NO THANKS TO LUCAS THOUGH.
HE WAS LATE.
I ALMOST MISSED THE TEST.
(SIGHS)
I'M SORRY, SWEETIE.
I JUST, UH...
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO
ABOUT HIM ANYMORE.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE HE WILL
PULL HIMSELF TOGETHER
IF IZZY'S AROUND.
EVELYN:
(EXASPERATED SIGH)
YEAH...
MAYBE.
SOMETHING'S GOTTA CHANGE.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Oh! Oh! Oh! ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
I DON'T KNOW...
WHAT COLOUR DO YOU THINK
THAT WE SHOULD MAKE THE CAR?
BLUE, AND GREEN, AND PINK.
OKAY...
LUCAS,
YOU WANNA COME OVER HERE
AND HELP IZZY AND I
DECORATE JANE'S CAKE?
ISABELLA:
DADDY?
WHEN IS AUNTIE JANE
GONNA GET HERE?
OH, SOON, HONEY.
AND THEN WE CAN
GIVE HER THIS CAKE
FOR PASSING HER TEST.
YOU THINK
SHE'S GONNA LIKE IT?
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
DANNY:
YOU WATCHED FOUR SEASONS
OF "LOST"
JUST BECAUSE I LIKE IT.
LEIA:
THE THINGS I DO
TO GET CLOSER TO YOU.
LIKE, HAVING LUNCH
WITH MY FRIENDS?
I KNOW IT'S AWKWARD 'CAUSE
OF THE WHOLE MIA SITUATION,
BUT I JUST WANT THEM TO KNOW
HOW AWESOME MY GIRLFRIEND IS.
AND I DON'T WANNA
LET YOU DOWN,
BUT I HAVE CHOIR AT LUNCH.
MAYBE WE CAN GET A COFFEE
THIS WEEKEND?
DEAL.
I GOTTA GET TO CLASS.
LATER.
SAV:
ALL RIGHT, MY LITTLE DANNY'S
GROWING UP.
FINALLY GOT A GIRLFRIEND
OF HIS OWN.
WHICH MEANS I'M NO LONGER
THE FIFTH WHEEL
TO YOU AND PETER.
SO, YOU GUYS IN LOVE?
WELL, NOT LIKE YOU
AND ANYA...
YET.
BUT I LIKE HER.
A LOT.
PETER:
DUDES.
BEST NIGHT EVER,
EH, SAV?
POWER SQUAD DINNER
AT MICKEY-D'S.
YEAH, A BUNCH OF SKINNY GIRLS
TRYING TO BEAT THE MCNUGGET
EATING RECORD.
IT'S CRAZY.
MUST BE NICE THAT
YOUR GIRLFRIENDS ARE BFF'S.
YOU THINK MAYBE LEIA
AND I COULD JOIN SOMETIME?
PETER:
UH... I'M NOT SURE
THEY ALL GET ALONG.
DANNY:
BECAUSE THEY DON'T HANG OUT.
WHAT IF WE ALL DID SOMETHING?
TONIGHT.
SAV:
WELL...
ANYA'S STAYING OVER
AT MIA'S HOUSE.
MAYBE THEY COULD INVITE LEIA.
PETER:
AND I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
COUPLE WHITE LIES
TO YOUR PARENTS AND VOILA!
MAKE A SLEEPOVER PARTY
AT MY PLACE.
YOU GUYS ARE GONNA
LOVE LEIA.
TRUST ME,
SHE'S AWESOME.
PETER:
LATER, DUDE.
HE'S BACK SO SOON?
AFTER WHAT HE SAID TO CLARE?
DANNY:
I HEARD SENSITIVITY TRAINING
REALLY AFFECTED HIM.
(SKEPTICAL HUFF)
WHAT?
PEOPLE CAN CHANGE.
SIMPSON:
OKAY, BEFORE WE START
OUR THRILLING LESSON
ON SEARCH ENGINE ALGORITHMS,
I WANNA WELCOME BACK
THE SHEP.
(STUDENTS APPLAUD SPORADICALLY)
SHEP:
THANKS. I JUST WANNA SAY HI,
EVERYONE.
ALUMNI WEEK
IS ABOUT TOGETHERNESS.
AND, UH...
(CLEARS THROAT)
SECOND CHANCES.
SO, UH,
IF YOU HAD A PARENT
OR SIBLING
WHO WENT TO DEGRASSI,
GET THEM TO JOIN
THE ALUMNI FOOTBALL TEAM.
SHEP:
THE MORE, THE MERRIER,
AM I RIGHT?
CAUGHT LIBERTY STUDYING
PASSING PLAYS YESTERDAY.
SHE'S CRAZY DETERMINED
TO BE BETTER THAN ME
AT EVERYTHING.
HOW WOULD YOU FEEL
IF YOUR BROTHER ONE-UP'D YOU?
THAT WOULDN'T BE
SUCH A BAD THING RIGHT NOW.
HM.
OKAY, I THINK I KNOW
HOW TO HELP LUCAS.
ACTUALLY, I HAD AN IDEA.
NO, NO, LISTEN,
THIS'LL BE GREAT.
HE CAN PLAY
ON THE DEGRASSI ALUMNI TEAM
FOR ALUMNI WEEK.
YOU KNOW,
GET SOME FRESH AIR,
MAKE SOME CONTACTS,
MAYBE GET A JOB.
SPIN'S HEAD COACH,
SO HE CAN PLAY
WHATEVER POSITION HE WANTS.
I MEAN, IT'S...
IT'S SOMETHING, RIGHT?
YEAH, THAT'S GREAT, JANE.
I WAS THINKING LUCAS
NEEDS SOME DAD TIME.
SO I'VE INVITED YOUR FATHER
FOR DINNER.
WHY?
EVELYN:
WELL, THEY REALLY HAVEN'T
SPOKEN IN SIX MONTHS.
AND I JUST...
I THOUGHT IT MIGHT HELP.
WHY DOES CARLO
NEED TO COME HERE?
CAN'T THEY JUST
GO OUT SOMEWHERE?
EVELYN:
ALL RIGHT, LET'S JUST, UM...
LET'S THINK OF THIS AS...
FAMILY TIME.
(HUFFS)
IT WOULD BE NICE FOR LUCAS
TO HAVE HIS DAD
AND HIS DAUGHTER TOGETHER.
FINE.
BUT IT'S NOT CHRISTMAS EVE,
SO DON'T EXPECT ME
TO TALK TO HIM.
SO, EVERYTHING'S SET
FOR TONIGHT.
SAV AND I ARE WORKING ON
"ALUMNI WEEK" STUFF AT PETER'S-
AND THE GIRLS ARE DOING
AN ALL-NIGHT
ENGLISH PROJECT
AT ANYA'S."
YOUR PARENTS
DIDN'T BUY IT.
YEAH, THEY DID.
IT'S JUST...
WHAT, YOU DON'T WANNA
HANG OUT WITH MY FRIENDS?
OF COURSE I DO.
OKAY, FINE.
THE TRUTH IS,
I'M A LITTLE FREAKED.
LATELY SAV'S BEEN...
COMING ON TO ME.
COMING ON TO YOU?
WHAT?!
NO BIGGIE.
OBVIOUSLY HE'S HUNG UP ON ANYA.
HE'S JUST FLIRTY AND STUFF.
MAKES ME... UNCOMFORTABLE.
MAYBE I SHOULD MAKE HIM
UNCOMFORTABLE.
NO.
DON'T SAY I SAID ANYTHING.
IT'S FINE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
SINCE IT MEANS SO MUCH TO YOU,
I'LL COME.
GREAT.
WE'LL ALL HAVE A BLAST.
(SILVERWARE CLINKS)
KNIFE FACES INWARDS?
CORRECT.
DID MOM TELL YOU?
YEAH. IT'S COOL.
DAD BEING AROUND.
I JUST WANNA REMEMBER
THEY THAT IT WAS.
(HALF LAUGH)
THE WAY IT WAS.
DAD, LEFT.
WE WERE MISERABLE FOR YEARS,
NOW WE HAVE THE CHANCE
TO BE A FAMILY.
REMEMBER THAT.
(VAN ZIPS BY)
WELCOME TO THE PARTY.
BETTER LATE THEN NEVER,
I GUESS.
TO MAKE UP FOR IT?
YOU GUYS WANNA
GET LOST TONIGHT?
YEAH, SWEET.
LET'S WATCH THE EPISODE
WHERE THE OTHERS KIDNAP WALT.
LEIA, WHO'S YOUR FAVOURITE
OTHER?
UH... I MUST HAVE SKIPPED
THAT DISC.
GUESS WE SHOULD WATCH IT?
OR... WE COULD DO
SOMETHING SOCIAL.
WE DIDN'T ALL
SNEAK OVER HERE
TO SIT IN FRONT
OF THE TELEVISION, DID WE?
WHAT ABOUT TRUTH OR DARE?
(SNAPS FINGERS)
YEAH!
OKAY, MY TURN.
LEIA? TRUTH OR DARE.
DARE?
ANYA:
I DARE YOU... TO...
WEAR YOUR BRA ON THE OUTSIDE
OF YOUR SHIRT
THE WHOLE NIGHT.
(LAUGHTER)
UM... I DON'T THINK SO.
ANYA:
OKAY.
WELL, I WILL.
(CHUCKLING)
LUCAS:
HOW MANY MEATBALLS DO YOU WANT?
ISABELLA:
TWO.
LUCAS:
AND WHAT DO WE SAY?
ISABELLA: PLEASE.
LUCAS: GOOD GIRL.
CARLO:
MAN, SHE'S GROWN UP SO MUCH.
LOOKS LIKE
YOU'RE A GOOD DAD.
EVELYN:
HE IS.
WHEN HE'S NOT PLAYING
VIDEO GAMES.
ALTHOUGH, HE WAS THINKING
OF PLAYING IN THE DEGRASSI
ALUMNI GAME.
BOTH MY KIDS ON THE GRIDIRON?
CAN'T WAIT TO WATCH THAT.
I'VE GOT A MEETING
ABOUT IT TONIGHT.
RIGHT, JANE?
YEAH.
AND HOW'VE YOU BEEN,
JANE?
FINE.
SHE'S DOING GREAT.
MOSTLY A'S.
FOOTBALL, OF COURSE.
OH, AND...
SHE JUST GOT HER LICENCE!
THAT'S WONDERFUL.
DO YOU KNOW IT TOOK YOUR MOM
THREE TRIES TO PASS THAT TEST.
CARLO!
YES, AND I FINALLY PASSED
WITH YOUR DAD'S LESSONS.
WE'D THROW YOU KIDS
IN THE BACKSEAT.
I REMEMBER.
I MADE US STOP
FOR CHEESEBURGERS.
CARLO AND LUCAS:
(LAUGH)
EVELYN:
JANE ALWAYS FELL ASLEEP
IN THE BACK SEAT.
WE'D PUT HER
IN HER PAJAMAS.
I REMEMBER THAT.
THE...
THE YELLOW ONES
THAT DAD GOT ME?
I HATED THOSE.
EVELYN:
NO...
NO, NONNA GOT YOU THOSE
FOR YOUR BIRTHDAY.
UM... (CLEARS THROAT)
EXCUSE ME.
ARE YOU OKAY?
JANE:
YEAH.
YOUNG JANE:
(GIGGLING)
CARLO:
(MIMICKING PLANE WHIRRING)
YOUNG JANE:
(GIGGLES)
CARLO:
BE A GOOD GIRL, JANIE-BEAR.
(DOOR CHIMES JINGLE)
SPINNER: HEY!
JANE: HI.
(DOOR CHIMES JINGLING)
AND HOW'S INDIANA JANE
AND THE LUCAS CRUSADE GOING?
GREAT. HE'S COMING
TO YOUR ALUMNI MEETING.
HE WANTS TO BE A COACH,
ACTUALLY.
YOU KNOW,
I'M PROUD OF YOU, DUDE.
YOU'RE HELPING YOUR BROTHER
EVEN THOUGH HE'S A LOSER.
AND YOU GOT YOUR LICENCE.
THAT'S PRETTY SWEET.
SPIN, WHAT'S YOUR, UH...
EARLIEST MEMORY?
(HALF LAUGHS)
I WAS FOUR.
AND I DIDN'T INVITE JIMMY
TO MY BIRTHDAY PARTY.
AND HE DIDN'T TALK TO ME
FOR A YEAR.
YEAH.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
ANYTHING BEFORE EIGHT
IS KIND OF FOGGY.
EIGHT'S KIND OF OLD,
ISN'T IT?
YEAH, UH...
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I NEED TO CELEBRATE
GETTING MY LICENCE!
ARE YOU IN?
COACH'S MEETING IN TEN.
CLOSED EARLY FOR IT.
REMEMBER?
RIGHT.
I MIGHT STICK AROUND.
AS LONG AS YOU DON'T
SCOPE OUR SECRETS.
I'LL FLUSH THEM
FROM MY MEMORY.
(MUSIC BEGINS TO PLAY)
♪ You love, love
people that love you ♪
♪ You hear the music
they move to ♪
♪ You give into
the fall through ♪
♪ But you don't know ♪
♪ You don't know
you don't know ♪
You... ♪
(APPLAUSE AND CHEERS)
I TOLD YOU I HAD
THE CRAZY-LEGS.
ALL RIGHT, MIA,
TRUTH OR DARE?
TRUTH.
WHO'S THE COOLEST
FAMOUS PERSON
YOU'VE EVER MET?
(THINKING)
I...
MET TIMBALAND
DURING FASHION WEEK.
AND HE SAID
I HAD BEAUTIFUL EYES.
YOUR TURN.
TRUTH OR DARE.
TRUTH.
ASK HER THE SAME QUESTION.
OKAY. WHO'S THE COOLEST
FAMOUS PERSON YOU'VE MET?
LEIA:
UH... MY DAD
IS A MUSIC PRODUCER, RIGHT?
SO I BASICALLY GREW UP
WITH FALL OUT BOY.
PETE IS LIKE MY BIG BRO.
(AMAZED BREATH)
YOU'RE PALS
WITH PETE WENTZ?
BACK IN GRADE SCHOOL?
HE'D EVEN PLAY ME LULLABIES
ON HIS GUITAR.
THAT'S SO COOL!
SPINNER:
OKAY... SO I'M QB.
JAY. RUNNING BACK?
JANE:
JAY? IF HE HAS TO WALK A BLOCK
HE'LL DRIVE.
FORGET RUNNING.
(LAUGHS)
SPINNER:
WHICH LEAVES MOST OF THE OTHER
POSITIONS STILL OPEN.
WE GOT FULLBACK, KICKER...
YEAH, AND I'LL PLAY.
JAY:
ALL RIGHT.
ROUND OF DRINKS FOR
THE BEST TEAM OF THE WEEKEND.
AND...
THE OTHER TEAM'S SPY.
HEY, HEY, HEY.
CAN YOU AND YOUR LITTLE FRIEND
MAKE ME ANOTHER
SPECIAL DRINK, PLEASE?
TO BAD YOU DIDN'T BRING
THIS JANE TO DINNER.
DAD WOULDN'T THINK I'M THE ONLY
LOSER IN THE FAMILY.
YOU-YOUR DAD?
JANE:
YUP, YUP-YUP-YUP.
FAMILY DINNER.
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
(INEBRIATED, BUFFOONISH
LAUGHTER)
SPINNER:
OKAY, OKAY.
YOU'RE DRUNK.
LET ME TAKE YOU HOME, OKAY.
NO, I'M NOT DRUNK.
IT'S YOUR MEETING MAN, STAY.
I'LL... I'LL WALK HER.
OKAY.
(GIGGLES)
OW.
PEACE.
AHHH...
SEEMS YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY DUDE
WHO'S GIRL HAS FAMOUS HOOK-UPS.
WHAT, YOU MEAN HER
FALL OUT BOYFRIEND?
MAYBE STUDZ
CAN OPEN FOR THEM!
SURE,
IN IMAGINARY-PALOOZA.
SHE DOESN'T REALLY KNOW 'EM,
MAN.
YEAH SHE DOES,
THROUGH HER DAD.
YEAH,
BIG TIME PRODUCER.
PETE WENTZ PLAYS BASS.
NOT GUITAR.
(MIMICS BASS TUNE
AND CHUCKLES)
SOME LULLABY.
I'M SURE HE KNOWS
HOW TO PLAY GUITAR, TOO.
AND PLUS, THEY DIDN'T EVEN
RELEASE AN ALBUM 'TIL 02.
DID LEIA NEED TO BE
SUNG TO SLEEP
WHEN SHE WAS IN FIFTH GRADE?
DUDE, WHY WOULD SHE LIE?
I'M JUST WATCHING YOUR BACK,
MAN.
YOU SHOULD ASK HER?
WHILE YOU'RE AT IT?
SEE IF SHE CAN GET US
INTO THIS SHOW.
IT'S BEEN SOLD OUT FOR WEEKS.
(SIGHS)
HEY, GUYS.
PARENTALS!
(EXHALES)
EVELYN:
HAS SHE BEEN DRINKING?
YEAH.
SHE'S A MESS.
I'M CHECKING OUT.
EVELYN:
THANKS FOR GETTING HER HOME
SAFE.
A SLEEP OVER?
THAT'S COZY.
NO, I WAS JUST LEAVING.
THANKS FOR JOINING US
FOR DINNER, DAD.
IT'S ALWAYS SO NICE
TO SEE YOU.
JANE.
GOOD NIGHT.
THIS IS SO NOT LIKE HER.
USUALLY IT'S, UH,
IT'S LUCAS...
CARLO:
NO, IT'S MY FAULT.
I DIDN'T KNOW
SHE WAS STILL SO MAD AT ME.
SHE EVER TELL YOU WHY?
EVELYN:
SHE WAS FIVE YEARS OLD
WHEN YOU LEFT.
IT'S BOUND TO LEAVE SOME SCARS.
(HUM OF STUDENTS CHATTER)
HEY, GOOD LOOKIN'.
THOUGHT YOU MIGHT
NEED A PICK ME UP
AFTER ALL YOUR HARD WORK
LAST NIGHT.
ON MY ENGLISH ASSIGNMENT?
I CAN'T BELIEVE MY PARENTS
FELL FOR THAT.
AND THE SLEEP OVER
WAS A HUGE SUCCESS.
MY FRIENDS LOVE YOU.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I WAS AFRAID OF.
THEY ALL WANT TO HANG OUT
AGAIN.
TONIGHT?
REALLY?
YEAH, AND THEY'D LOVE
TO SEE THIS SHOW.
THINK YOU CAN GET US IN?
YOU'RE PALS WITH PETE,
RIGHT?
OH YEAH, TOTALLY.
TELL THE GANG
TO GET THEIR ROCK SOCKS ON.
SEARCH ENGINES
DON'T PUBLICLY SHARE
HOW THEIR RANKING ALGORITHMS
WORK.
IT'S A BIT OF A TRADE SECRET
THEY HOLD CLOSE TO THEIR CHEST.
FOR EXAMPLE...
CARLO:
I DIDN'T KNOW
SHE WAS STILL SO MAD AT ME.
SHE EVER TELL YOU WHY?
EVELYN:
SHE WAS FIVE YEARS OLD
WHEN YOU LEFT.
IT'S BOUND TO LEAVE SOME SCARS.
SIMPSON:
JANE.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
UM, I JUST-
I FEEL KINDA DIZZY.
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU GO DOWN TO
THE NURSE'S OFFICE, ALL RIGHT?
(CRIES)
MAN:
CHECK. ONE TWO...
CHECK.
(DIN OF CHATTER)
DO YOU THINK MY FRIENDS
AND I COULD SNEAK IN?
I'M FRIENDS WITH PETE.
(HUFFS IN DISBELIEF)
GUY'S GOT A LOT OF FRIENDS
TONIGHT.
ARE YOU ON THE LIST?
NO, BUT WE GO WAY BACK.
WAY BACK TO A FEW MINUTES AGO
WHEN YOU CONCOCTED
THAT LITTLE LIE?
NO.
HE'S BEING KIND
OF UNREASONABLE.
MAYBE NEXT TIME?
REALLY SORRY.
TELL HIM ABOUT YOUR DAD.
OH YEAH?
WHO'S YOUR DADDY?
A RECORD PRODUCER.
DAVID CHANG.
MADE THE LAST AEROSMITH RECORD.
NEVER HEARD OF HIM.
NOW LEAVE.
I'M SORRY, DUDES.
GUY DOESN'T KNOW
HOW IMPORTANT LEIA'S DAD IS.
YEAH,
PROBABLY BECAUSE HE'S NOT.
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY?
SAV:
DANNY...
I THINK IT'S PRETTY CLEAR.
YOU'RE JUST JEALOUS
BECAUSE YOU WANT HER
AND I HAVE HER.
I KNOW YOU'VE BEEN
HITTING ON HER.
COME ON, DUDE.
DID SHE TELL YOU THAT?
CAN'T BELIEVE SHE DRAGGED US
ALL DOWN HERE.
WE'RE GOING TO MY PLACE
TO WATCH LOST.
YOU'RE INVITED.
BUT NO LIAR LEIA.
(DOOR SHUTS)
EVELYN:
AWWW.
THAT WAS YOUR FOURTH BIRTHDAY.
I DON'T REMEMBER IT.
YEAH, YOUR DAD BOUGHT YOU
THAT DOLL.
UH... HANNAH.
AH, YOU TOOK HER EVERYWHERE.
YOU MADE A LITTLE COZY ROOM
IN THE BACK OF YOUR CLOSET.
PUT HER TO SLEEP THERE
EVERY NIGHT.
HM.
DID HE AND I GET ALONG
WHEN I WAS A KID?
ARE YOU KIDDING?!
YOU WERE CRAZY ABOUT YOUR DAD.
I WORKED ALL THE TIME.
YOU SPENT MOST OF YOUR TIME
WITH HIM.
HE PUT ME TO BED EVERY NIGHT.
JANE, I...
YOU KNOW, I WISH THAT
I COULDA BEEN THERE MORE.
IT'S HARD BALANCING A CAREER
AND A FAMILY.
HAVING HIM BACK HERE?
IT SEEMS...
IT SEEMS TO WORK.
LUCAS IS BETTER.
IT'S LIKE, UH, IT'S LIKE
WE GET A SECOND CHANCE.
WOULD YOU BE OKAY
IF HE WERE AROUND MORE?
WE'D LIKE TO TRY AGAIN.
SEE IF WE CAN
GET IT RIGHT THIS TIME.
I'M ONLY HERE
FOR SIX MORE MONTHS.
SO YOU'RE DAD'S AN ENGINEER,
AND YOU DON'T KNOW
"FALLOUT BOY".
I COULDN'T EVEN
NAME ONE OF THEIR SONGS.
I'M SO SORRY.
WHY SAY ALL THAT STUFF THEN?
AND TAKE US TO THE SHOW?
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S JUST YOUR FRIENDS
ARE SO COOL.
I MEAN, MIA'S A MODEL.
AND SHE ALREADY
DISSED ME ONCE.
YOU WEREN'T THE ONLY ONE.
BUT I GOT OVER IT.
I WANTED THEM TO LIKE ME.
SO YOU'D LIKE ME.
I LIKED YOU
BEFORE THE STORIES.
DANNY, EVERYBODY LIES.
WE ALL LIED
SO WE COULD STAY AT PETER'S.
PEOPLE LIED
DURING TRUTH OR DARE...
BUT IF WE'RE GONNA
STAY TOGETHER,
YOU CAN'T LIE TO ME.
I PROMISE,
I WON'T EVER LIE TO YOU
AGAIN.
ONE THING THAT'S NOT A LIE?
I REALLY, REALLY LIKE YOU.
I LIKE YOU, TOO.
YOU WANNA GET OUT OF HERE?
YOU'VE GOT SOME FALL OUT BOY
MUSIC TO LEARN.
♪ Going counterclockwise ♪
♪ To look into your eyes ♪
(KNOCK AT THE DOOR)
COME IN.
UM, YOUR MOM TOLD ME
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT
WITH ME HANGING AROUND MORE.
THANKS.
MEANS A LOT TO ME.
HAVING ANOTHER CHANCE TO...
TO GET IT RIGHT.
OKAY.
'NIGHT, JANIE-BEAR.
BE A GOOD GIRL,
OKAY, JANIE-BEAR?
(EQUIPMENT CLATTERS)
.