("Chances" by Jill Barber plays)
♪♪♪
♪ Chances ♪
♪ What are the chances? ♪
♪ The chances
that I'd find you ♪
(STUDENTS LAUGH)
♪ Stealing glances ♪
DAWES:
THANK YOU, BLUE.
ALWAYS INTRIGUING
WHEN A WORK OF ART
ALSO SERVES A UTILITARIAN END.
(CHUCKLES)
(BELL RINGS)
PA ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION, DEGRASSI.
ALL STUDENTS INTERESTED IN...
BLUE:
SO?
UH...
I CAN'T GO TO THE DANCE
WITH YOU.
I'M SORRY,
I HAVE TO WORK THAT NIGHT.
OKAY. UM...
MAYBE NEXT TIME?
YEAH. MAYBE.
CHANTAY:
TOO ROMANTIC?
TOO HOT?
TOO AWESOME?
MAYBE SOME OTHER GUY?
I GUESS SO.
HE GOES TO ANOTHER SCHOOL.
WILL WE MEET HIM
AT THE DANCE?
NO. IT'S COMPLICATED.
UNSOLICITED ADVICE:
IF YOU'RE PICKING THIS GUY
OVER BLUE,
YOU MUST BE CRAZY
ABOUT HIM.
SO GO FOR IT.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Oh! Oh! Oh! ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
BYE.
HOLLY J:
HEY.
UH, ARE YOU GOING
TO THE DOT TONIGHT?
JANE:
NO. I'M BABYSITTING IZZY.
WHY?
NO REASON.
(CAR WHIRS BY)
DID ANYONE BORROW
MY PEN?
YOU THINK I DID IT?
YOU'RE SITTING NEXT TO ME.
AND I'M THE ONLY ONE
WITH A CRIMINAL RECORD.
WHY ARE YOU STILL BEING
SUCH AN IDIOT?
NOW I'M A THIEF
AND AN IDIOT?
CONNOR:
HEY. YOU GUYS UP FOR RISK
TONIGHT?
NOT IF HE'S COMING.
NOT IF SHE'S COMING.
YOU'RE STILL COMING OVER,
RIGHT?
I HAVE TO BUY
THE PERFECT DRESS
FOR THE DANCE,
SO, UM... NO.
CONNOR:
BUT IT'S THURSDAY.
ON THURSDAYS, YOU GUYS COME OVER
AND PLAY RISK.
I LIKE RISK.
OBVIOUSLY.
IT'S THE BEST GAME EVER.
WHY WON'T CLARE AND KC
STOP FIGHTING?
THEY'RE IN LIKE
WITH EACH OTHER.
AND...
SINCE YOU TOLD CLARE
ABOUT KC'S CRIMINAL PAST,
EVERYTHING'S BEEN
TOTALLY AWKWARD.
SO... WHAT DO WE DO?
YOU FIX IT.
(HUM OF CHATTER)
I DON'T EVEN TALK TO DARCY
ANYMORE.
I'VE NEVER BEEN AS HAPPY
WITH ANYONE
AS I AM WITH YOU.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO BELIEVE THAT?
BECAUSE IT'S TRUE.
(SIGHS)
I'M ALWAYS GONNA WONDER
WHAT WOULD HAVE HAPPENED
IF DARCY HAD STAYED.
WELL, WHAT CAN I DO
TO CHANGE THAT?
NOTHING.
IT'S THE LAST THURSDAY
BEFORE I GO HOME
FOR WINTER BREAK.
SORRY, MAN.
I'M NOT IN THE MOOD
FOR CLARE'S
PATRONIZING ATTITUDE.
SHE WON'T BE THERE.
SHE CAN'T COME.
REALLY?
CONNOR:
YEAH. COME ON.
IT'S THURSDAY.
WE ALWAYS PLAY RISK
ON THURSDAY.
ALL RIGHT,
I'M IN.
ANTI-GRAPEVINE REPORT.
"WHAT DOT EMPLOYEE
WITH AN INTEREST IN ART
TURNED DOWN A DATE
WITH ONE OF THE HOTTEST GUYS
AT DEGRASSI?
AND FOR WHO?"
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU READ THAT STUFF.
YEAH.
HE'S NICE,
NOT LIKE YOU.
THANK YOU.
WHY ARE YOU PUSHING ME
TO GO OUT WITH HIM?
EHN. I ADMIRE THE GUY.
HE SEES THROUGH ALL
THE ANNOYING STUFF
TO THE KINDA COOL J
UNDERNEATH.
(HALF LAUGHS,
DOOR CHIMES JINGLE)
MIGHT AS WELL TAKE A TABLE
OR TWO,
SINCE I'M HERE.
YEAH. WHY ARE YOU HERE
WHEN YOU DON'T HAVE A SHIFT?
'CAUSE I CAN'T LIVE
WITHOUT YOU.
KNEW IT.
(POP MUSIC PLAYS
WITHIN THE DOT)
(CAR HORNS BEEP)
SPINNER:
(PLEASED CHUCKLE)
SUCKERED YOU INTO WORKING
A WHOLE SHIFT.
YOU SEE, IT'S DANGEROUS
TO COME AROUND HERE.
YEAH. YEAH.
YOU OWE ME HALF YOUR TIPS.
IT'S ALL ABOUT MONEY
WITH YOU.
SO, YOU WANT TO GIVE ME
A RIDE HOME?
YEAH. SURE.
(DOOR CHIMES JINGLE)
UH, HELLO?
CAN YOU READ?
WE'RE CLOSED.
THE DOOR WAS OPEN.
HOLLY J:
THAT'S BECAUSE I HAVEN'T
LOCKED IT YET.
GIMME A BURGER.
THE GRILL'S BEEN CLEANED...
BECAUSE WE'RE CLOSED.
YEAH,
MAYBE JUST ONE BURGER.
NO!
NO, I WANT TO GET HOME.
LOOK, I KNOW THIS DEADBEAT
FROM LAKEHURST.
HE'S A TOTAL LOSER.
GO ON. SCOOT.
(HUFFS)
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
"SCOOT?!"
SPINNER:
WHOA! DUDE! DUDE!
CHRIS:
GIMME THE CASH YOU GOT -
IN THE REGISTER
AND THE SAFE. NOW!
NOW!
(DOOR CLOSES)
OKAY. SINCE ALLI AND KC
AREN'T HERE,
WE CAN TAKE THEIR COUNTRIES.
I'LL TAKE ALLI'S
AND YOU CAN HAVE KC'S.
THAT'S VERY GENEROUS OF YOU,
CONNOR.
YOU REALIZE KC'S WINNING?
YEAH. THAT'S OKAY.
I'LL GO GET US
SOME SNACKS.
WHAT?
IT'S JUST... YOU'RE BEING
A REALLY GOOD HOST.
IT'S NICE.
(MONEY RUSTLES)
SPINNER:
HERE.
NOW THE SAFE.
OPEN THE SAFE!
THERE'S NOT GONNA BE
THAT MUCH MONEY IN THERE ANYWAY.
(SAFE KEYPAD BEEPS)
WHOA! DON'T SHOOT.
THIS GUY'S TRYIN'
TO MESS WITH ME.
NO. HE'S JUST TRYING
TO BE A STUPID HERO.
THE SAFE.
(MONEY RUSTLES)
(LOUD KNOCK AT THE DOOR)
JUST GO OUT THE BACK.
THEY'LL LEAVE
IF YOU DON'T ANSWER, MAN.
CHRIS:
NO, NO, NO.
THEY KNOW SOMEONE'S HERE.
(KNOCKING CONTINUES)
ANSWER IT.
NO MORE TRICKS!
OR I WILL SHOOT YOU BOTH.
LET'S GO!
(FORCED CALMING BREATHS)
(DOOR CHIMES JINGLE)
YOU SHOULD GO.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE
UNTIL YOU ADMIT
THERE'S SOMETHING BETWEEN US.
THE MANAGER DOESN'T ALLOW
PEOPLE IN
WHEN WE'RE CLOSING.
WHAT IS YOUR PROBLEM,
HOLLY J?
YOU.
OKAY.
I WON'T BOTHER YOU AGAIN.
HAVE A NICE LIFE.
HOLLY J:
OKAY.
(DOOR OPENS)
(SIGHS)
CONNOR SAID
YOU WEREN'T COMING.
(DOOR CLOSES)
CLARE AND KC:
CONNOR!
CONNOR:
YOU TWO STAY DOWN THERE
UNTIL YOU FIX IT!
(EXHALES)
OKAY. GOOD.
NOW I'M GONNA GO
OUT THE BACK
AND NOBODY GETS HURT.
OPEN IT!
NOW, YOU BOTH
KEEP YOUR MOUTHS SHUT
AND I WON'T HAVE
TO COME BACK.
WE WILL. WE WILL.
I KNOW WHO YOU ARE,
HOLLY J.
(GUNSHOT POPS,
HOLLY J GASPS, STUNNED)
(PANICKED BREATHS)
SPIN!
OH GOD!
ARE YOU OKAY?
BOTH:
(QUICKENED BREATHS)
CHRIS:
I DIDN'T MEAN TO!
HEY, WHERE'RE YOU GOING?!
HOLLY J:
I NEED SOMETHING
TO STOP THE BLEEDING.
(FRANTIC BREATHS)
HOLLY J:
IT'S OKAY.
IT'S GOING TO BE OKAY.
(ROCKBAND PLAYS)
♪ TAKING CARE OF BUSINESS ♪
♪ EVERYDAY! ♪
DID MIA TELL ANYA
SHE'S FOR SURE
GOING TO THE DANCE?
MAN, YOU GOTTA GIVE UP
ON THAT.
MAN, I CAN'T.
(SAV'S PHONE RINGS)
AH. HOLD ON.
(PHONE RINGING)
WHAT?
OKAY. YEAH,
WE'LL CHECK IT OUT.
OKAY. ALLI SAYS SOMEONE SAW
A LOT OF COP CARS BY THE DOT.
ANYA AND MIA WERE GONNA GO THERE
AFTER SHOPPING.
(POLICE SIREN WAILS)
WHAT DID YOU DO?
DID YOU TELL THAT GUY SOMETHING?
NO.
SPINNER:
(WINCES) THEY PROBABLY HEARD
THE GUNSHOT, MAN.
SHE DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING.
CHRIS:
WHAT DO I DO NOW?
EVERYTHING IS SO MESSED UP!
(PAINED BREATHS,
POLICE SIRENS WAIL)
CLARE:
ARE YOU JUST GONNA SIT THERE
EATING COOKIES?
CAN'T YOU...
FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO BREAK OUT?
WHY? 'CAUSE I'M A CRIMINAL
MASTERMIND?
THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEAN!
YEAH, IT IS.
I KNOW THE WAY PEOPLE LIKE YOU
THINK ABOUT PEOPLE LIKE ME.
AND I'M SUPPOSED TO BE
THE JUDGMENTAL ONE?!
DID IT WORK?
IS IT FIXED?
(ASCENDING FOOTSTEPS)
(CHATTER OVER POLICE BAND RADIO)
NEGOTIATOR:
ANYONE MADE CONTACT?
POLICE OFFICER:
NOT YET.
(SIRENS WAIL,
LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
THIS IS OFFICER WILLIAMS
WITH THE EMERGENCY TASK FORCE.
WE WANNA RESOLVE
THIS PEACEFULLY.
BUT WE NEED TO TALK.
WE NEED TO MAKE SURE...
BLUE,
WHAT'S GOING ON, MAN?
BLUE:
SOMEONE'S IN THERE
WITH A GUN.
HE'S HOLDING HOLLY J HOSTAGE.
WHO ELSE IS IN THERE?
THEY DON'T KNOW.
(PHONE RINGS)
SPINNER:
(GASPING FOR BREATHH)
(PHONE RINGING)
(HUM OF CHATTER)
PETER:
WHY AREN'T YOU DOING ANYTHING?
POLICE OFFICER:
STEP BACK, PLEASE.
PETER:
HE SAID THERE'S AN EMPLOYEE
IN THERE.
WHO ELSE IS IN THERE?
POLICE OFFICER:
I TOLD YOU TO STEP BACK.
ANYA:
SAV! WHAT'S HAPPENING?
MIA:
PETER?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
PETER:
MIA.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
IN THERE.
(GRUNTS)
PETER...
I'M OKAY.
I THOUGHT I'D NEVER
SEE YOU AGAIN.
YOU'D NEVER KNOW
HOW I FEEL ABOUT YOU...
I LOVE YOU.
JANE:
HEY, UM, WHAT'S GOING ON?
PETER:
HOLLY J'S IN THERE.
AND SPINNER?
NO ONE KNOWS.
(PHONE RINGS,
HEAVY, AGITATED BREATHS)
HOLLY J:
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT -
YOU SHOOTING SPIN.
WE'LL TELL THEM THAT.
HOW DO I KNOW YOU WILL?
IT'S LIKE EVERY SINGLE THING
I DO GOES SO WRONG!
I KNOW WHAT THAT'S LIKE.
CHRIS:
(MOCKING LAUGH)
YEAH.
YOU KNOW, I REMEMBER YOU:
HOLLY J WITH THE FANCY HOUSE,
AND THE BIG CAR,
AND THE CHEERLEADER...
RICH SNOB!
NOT ANYMORE.
I GOT KICKED OFF THE SQUAD,
MY DAD LOST ALL HIS MONEY,
AND...
(SHAKY BREATHS)
AND I'M IN LOVE WITH THAT
IDIOT HERO GUY BACK THERE,
BUT HE'S CRAZY
ABOUT HIS GIRLFRIEND.
SO...
I TOTALLY GET IT.
I TOTALLY GET
WHAT IT'S LIKE...
WHEN THING'S ARE ALL WRONG.
LET'S JUST WALK OUT TOGETHER.
I'LL TELL THEM
WHAT REALLY HAPPENED.
IT'LL BE OKAY.
NEGOTIATOR:
WE WANNA HELP YOU OUT.
I'M GOING TO TRY THE PHONE
AGAIN.
(PHONE RINGS)
NO, IT'S TOO LATE.
THEY'RE GONNA STICK ME
IN PRISON.
WE'RE GONNA GO OUT TOGETHER
WITH YOU AS MY HOSTAGE.
IF WE GO OUT LIKE THIS...
THEY'LL SHOOT YOU.
LET'S JUST GO OUT TOGETHER...
WITHOUT THE GUN.
(BUZZ OF CONCERNED CHATTER,
SIRENS WAIL)
(DOOR CHIMES JINGLE)
GO! GO! GO! MOVE!
THERE'S SOMEONE INSIDE.
HE'S BEEN SHOT.
HE NEEDS HELP!
THE SHOOTING...
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
JANE:
SPINNER! SPINNER!
OH MY GOD!
ARE YOU OKAY?
S-SPINNER, I'M RIGHT...
I'M RIGHT HERE.
(CRYING)
HI. COME IN.
I'LL GO GET SOME COFFEE.
SPINNER:
OKAY.
YOU SURE YOU WANNA SPEND
YOUR SATURDAY AFTERNOON HERE?
(HALF LAUGHS)
I DON'T KNOW WHY
I BOUGHT YOU A PLANT;
YOU WON'T WATER IT.
IT'LL DIE IN A COUPLE DAYS.
(EXHALES)
YOU OKAY?
I WILL BE.
DOCTOR SAID MORE BLOOD LOSS
AND STUFF
WOULD NOT HAVE
WORKED OUT WELL.
SO...
YOU SAVED MY LIFE, J.
SO, UH...
CRAZY ABOUT THE IDIOT
HERO GUY, HUH?
YEAH. I WAS HOPING
YOU DIDN'T HEAR THAT;
THAT YOU WERE IN SHOCK
OR SOMETHING.
I HEARD EVERY WORD.
(SIGHS)
I'M... I'M FLATTERED.
BUT ME AND JANE...
I KNOW. I KNOW.
BUT...
YOU'RE THE ONLY PERSON
WHO KNOWS ME...
AND STILL THINKS I'M OKAY.
LOTS OF PEOPLE WOULD
IF YOU JUST GAVE THEM
THE CHANCE.
COME ON,
YOU CAN DO IT, J.
AFTER WHAT YOU DID
IN THE DOT,
YOU CAN DO ANYTHING.
(MUSIC PLAYS,
LIVELY CHATTER OF PARTYGOERS)
WHY IS HE SUCH AN IDIOT?
BECAUSE HE'S IN LIKE
WITH YOU.
I NEED YOUR HELP.
KC:
TELL ME AGAIN WHY YOU NEED
A BASKETBALL AT THE DANCE?
(DOOR CLOSES)
(HUFFS)
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
(BANGS DOOR,
RATTLES HANDLE)
HE DID IT AGAIN!
CONNOR!
NO.
THIS WAS ME.
I THINK I KNOW WHY WE FIGHT
ALL THE TIME.
YOU GOT IT ALL FIGURED OUT,
HUH?
YEAH.
WE FIGHT BECAUSE
WE'RE AFRAID IF WE STOP,
WE'LL... DO THIS.
♪ Their maps didn't match up ♪
OR... MAYBE I GOT IT
ALL WRONG.
NO.
YOU GOT IT RIGHT.
♪ She would say,
when will the ship roll in? ♪
♪ When will it sail away? ♪
♪ When will our timing
fall into perfect place ♪
♪ When will the stars
that shine ♪
♪ Shine me on my way ♪
♪ When will our ship roll in ♪
♪ Take me away ♪
DO YOU WANNA DANCE?
ME?
YEAH.
IT'S OKAY IF YOU DON'T.
CONNOR:
NO.
I DO.
I WANNA DANCE.
♪ Taking all our dreams
for granted ♪
♪ Wasting all the sunny days ♪
♪ I said the clouds
are changing ♪
♪ You said you feel the same ♪
♪ But it's you ♪
♪ That I'm after ♪
♪ Darling you ♪
♪ Help me sing ♪
♪ Into the mystery ♪
♪ Mmm mmm... ♪
♪ It's you that I came for ♪
♪ Hoping you'll set me free ♪
HEY, LOOK,
IT'S HOLLY J.
♪ Into the mystery ♪
(STUDENTS APPLAUD
AND CHEER FOR HOLLY J)
(PREPARATORY BREATH)
SO, YOUR PERFORMANCE
ART THING...
THE DANCING...
DOES THAT OFFER STILL STAND?
I GUESS IT DOES.
♪ When will my ship roll in ♪
♪ When will I sail away ♪
♪ When will my timing fall... ♪
WHEN WE WERE GONNA
GO OUT BEFORE...
♪ ...into perfect place ♪
MY FAMILY'S HAVING
SOME MONEY TROUBLE
AND I DIDN'T KNOW
HOW TO TELL YOU.
I'M SORRY TO HEAR THAT,
HOLLY.
♪ When will my ship roll in ♪
♪ Take me away ♪