TOM:
WHERE YOU GOING?
IT'S ONLY ELEVEN.
YEAH, I JUST, I'VE GOT
SO MUCH TO DO TOMORROW,
SO I'M GONNA GO NOW.
WELL, HEY,
DON'T FORGET YOUR AUTOGRAPH?
THE ONE FOR YOUR FRIEND?
RIGHT.
THANKS.
I HAD A GOOD TIME.
SO, I'LL SEE YOU
AT THE T-BOMBZ SHOOT?
YEAH, I'D BE SURPRISED
IF WE DIDN'T.
HEY, WAIT, WAIT.
WAIT.
WHAT'S THIS FOR?
IT'S FOR A TAXI.
CAN'T HAVE YOU WALKING HOME
AT THIS HOUR.
SOMEONE COULD TAKE
ADVANTAGE OF YOU.
THANKS.
SEE YOU AROUND.
COUNT ON IT.
(DOOR CLOSES)
MOMMY?
SHHH.
GO BACK TO SLEEP.
MOMMY'S GOING TO SLEEP TOO.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Oh! Oh! Oh! ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
WALTZING IN AT MIDNIGHT
ON A SCHOOL NIGHT
IS NOT ACCEPTABLE.
(SIGHS)
DOES THAT SEEM LIKE
A GOOD ANSWER?
I WAS WITH THE MODELING
PEOPLE, MOM.
YOU KNOW THAT'S IMPORTANT.
THAT DOESN'T MEAN
YOU CAN BE IRRESPONSIBLE.
YOU HAVE SCHOOL.
WE HAD A DEAL.
I KNOW, MOM, BUT...
I WAS SCARED THAT I WASN'T
GONNA GET THIS JOB AND...
I KNOW HOW MUCH
YOU WANT IT, BUT...
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
HELLO?
YEAH.
YEAH?
REALLY?
YEAH! FOR SURE.
OKAY.
YEAH, OKAY.
BYE.
(SNAPS PHONE SHUT)
I GOT IT!
I'M THE T-BOMBZ GIRL!
BOTH:
(EXCITED SQUEALS)
YOU WORKED SO HARD
FOR THIS.
YOU DESERVE IT!
OH, I'M PROUD OF YOU!
(CLEARS THROAT UNEASILY)
YEAH, I...
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
BOTH:
(LAUGHING)
CLARE:
ENIAC, WAS THE FIRST GENERAL
PURPOSE COMPUTING SYSTEM.
IN ENGLISH,
PLEASE.
DIDN'T YOU LEARN THAT
IN GRADE NINE?
HOW COULD OUR PARENTS
HAVE GIVEN BIRTH
TO SUCH
DIFFERENT CHILDREN?
CLARE:
YOU KNOW, SIBLINGS ONLY SHARE
ABOUT 50 PERCENT OF THEIR DNA.
DARCY:
WHICH WOULD EXPLAIN WHY
YOU'RE WEARING
A PRIVATE SCHOOL UNIFORM
AT A PUBLIC SCHOOL.
(BOOKS CLATTER)
SEE?
A GUY LIKE THAT
MIGHT ACTUALLY TALK TO YOU
IF YOU WEREN'T WEARING
THAT RIDICULOUS UNIFORM.
WELL, IT'S A GOOD THING
I'M HERE FOR SCHOOL
AND NOT FOR BOYS.
THAT GUY DIDN'T EVEN
KNOW ENOUGH
TO WEAR A HELMET.
STILL, YOU COULD AT LEAST LOOK
LIKE YOU GO TO DEGRASSI.
LOOK AT SAV'S SISTER.
I DON'T WANT YOU TO LOSE OUT
ON ANY OPPORTUNITIES,
JUST BECAUSE PEOPLE
THINK YOU'RE...
DIFFERENT.
HOW CAN YOU DRESS
LIKE THAT?
IF MOM AND DAD SEE YOU
IN THOSE SHOES,
THEY'LL KILL YOU.
AND ME!
SO THEY WON'T FIND OUT.
OTHERWISE, I'LL TELL THEM
ABOUT ANYA.
CONNOR:
...NOT MAGNESIUM.
WHO'S THAT GUY?
HE'S IN MY SEAT.
SOME NEW KID,
I GUESS.
CONNOR:
BUT WHY IS HE IN MY SEAT?
UM, EXCUSE ME,
IS THIS YOUR FIRST DAY?
IT IS.
KC.
CLARE.
UM...
I THINK YOU'RE IN
THE WRONG PLACE;
THIS CLASS
IS FOR GIFTED STUDENTS.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
OKAY...
FIRST OFF, I WOULD LIKE TO
INTRODUCE OUR NEWEST STUDENT.
KC, YOU WANNA STAND UP.
NOW HE'S JUST SETTLING IN,
SO UM...
CLARE, WHY DON'T YOU
SHOW HIM AROUND
AFTER CLASS, OKAY?
NOW, WITHOUT FURTHER ADO,
PRINCIPAL SHEPPARD,
TO SAY A FEW WORDS.
SHEPPARD:
IT'S "THE SHEP."
THERE'S NO DENYING IT,
YOU'RE DIFFERENT.
UM, WHAT "THE SHEP" MEANS
IS UH...
YOU'RE A UNIQUE CLASS
WITH UNIQUE SKILLS.
THAT SOME MIGHT
CONSIDER WEIRD.
SIMPSON:
INTELLECTUAL PURSUITS
CAN ENHANCE
THE EDUCATIONAL EXPERIENCE.
SHEPPARD:
RIGHT. YOU WANNA ENHANCE
YOUR EDUCATION...
ANYA:
SO, WE HEARD.
DISH.
HOLLY J:
GUESS YOU PULLED A FAST ONE
ON THEM.
DANNY:
IS TOM BLAKE AS CUTE
IN PERSON?
UH, SURE.
OH, AND UM...
THIS IS FOR YOU.
YOU'RE THE BEST,
YOU KNOW THAT RIGHT?
OKAY.
DANNY:
UH...
THANKS AGAIN.
OH, UH...
IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
JUST A JOB PERK.
THAT IS SWEET.
ISN'T IT COOL?
SO COOL.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I GOT IT.
SO, THESE ARE OUR LOCKERS.
UM, YOURS IS...
RIGHT HERE,
UH... NEXT TO MINE,
I GUESS.
YOU BETTER STICK AROUND.
I MIGHT HAVE TROUBLE
OPENING IT.
AND THAT WAY
IS THE LIBRARY
AND THE OTHER WAY,
THE CAFETERIA.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA TELL ME
WHERE MACHINE SHOP IS?
SPECIAL ED?
LOOK, I'M SORRY.
I JUST, I DIDN'T THINK
YOU'D BE SMART.
YOU JUST DON'T LOOK-
LIKE A PRIVATE SCHOOL
SNOB?
I AM NOT A SNOB.
THEN WHY DO YOU DRESS
LIKE THAT?
BECAUSE IT'S COMFORTABLE
AND I DON'T CARE
WHAT OTHER PEOPLE THINK
ABOUT ME.
EVERYONE CARES
WHAT OTHER PEOPLE THINK.
IT'S HUMAN NATURE.
CLARE:
WELL NOT ME,
AND THAT CONCLUDES OUR TOUR.
P.A. ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION PLEASE.
STUDENTS ARE REMINDED THAT
(UNCLEAR) IS STARTING NOW
IN THE CAFETERIA.
BRUCE:
THERE ONCE WAS A MAN
FROM NANTUCKET
WHO SAW A FLYING FISH
AND WANTED TO DUCK IT.
THE MAN ZIGGED,
THE FISH SAGGED;
THE MAN FELL IN THE LAKE
AND THE FISH ENDED UP
IN A BUCKET.
ANYA:
WHERE'S MY POEM, SAV?
IT'D GO LIKE:
DEAREST ANYA, I MISS YOU
WHEN YOU'RE GONEYA,
LOL.
LAST WEEK WAS A FREEBIE,
NINER.
TIME TO FIND
YOUR OWN FRIENDS.
CONNOR:
WE NEED FUEL, OXIDIZER,
COLOUR CHEMICALS,
BINDER...
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
WHICH HOLDS
THE PALLET TOGETHER,
AND A CHLORINE DONOR.
HE'S EXPLAINING FIREWORKS
TO ME.
KC:
EATING WITH THE BRAINS?
SOUNDS...
COMFORTABLE.
THAT'S RIGHT.
BECAUSE YOU DON'T CARE
WHAT ANYONE ELSE THINKS.
I TOLD YOU,
I DON'T.
HOW ABOUT THIS?
IF YOU REALLY DON'T CARE
WHAT ANYONE THINKS,
THEN GET UP THERE
AND DISPLAY A TALENT.
DEREK:
I CAN'T JUGGLE ALL DAY LONG,
PEOPLE.
IN FACT...
I CAN'T JUGGLE AT ALL!
SO, WHO'S THE NEXT VICTIM,
DEGRASSI?
HMM?
SOMEONE?
MINOR NINER.
ALL RIGHT!
HERE YOU GO.
IT'S ALL YOURS.
I'D LIKE TO PERFORM A HYMN.
♪ WHO SO BESET HIM ROUND ♪
♪ WITH DISMAL STORIES ♪
♪ DO BUT THEMSELVES CONFOUND ♪
♪ HIS STRENGTH THE MORE IS ♪
GUY:
BOOOO!
♪ ...SHALL STAY HIS MIGHT; ♪
♪ THOUGH HE WITH GIANTS FIGHT ♪
♪ HE WILL MAKE GOOD HIS RIGHT
TO BE... ♪
STUDENTS:
(MOCKING LAUGHTER
AND BOOING)
DEREK:
HEY... SO THAT WAS
A GREAT HYMN.
(SNICKERS)
LEIA:
WOW, THE T-BOMBZ GIRL?
IT'S ALL OVER THE BLOG.
YOU MUST BE EXCITED.
EXCITED AND NERVOUS.
ESPECIALLY FOR TONIGHT'S
PRESS CONFERENCE.
MY MOM AND BELLA
ARE GONNA BE THERE, BUT...
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'D BE GREAT TO HAVE A FRIEND,
IF YOU'RE FREE?
I'LL HAVE TO CHECK
WITH MY PEOPLE.
LEIA AND MIA:
(CHUCKLE)
BETTER NOT READ
ABOUT YOUR BAD BEHAVIOUR
IN THE TABLOIDS
TOMORROW.
IT'S OKAY, I'LL HAVE LEIA
TO KEEP ME IN LINE.
(TIRES SCREECH,
CAR ENGINE RUMBLES)
WOW!
(ENGINE RUMBLES)
HEY, T-BOMBZ GIRL!
THOUGHT YOU COULD USE A RIDE
TO THE STUDIO.
ENJOY THE RIDE!
I'LL MEET YOU THERE
TONIGHT.
HAVE FUN.
UH, SEE YOU TOMORROW?
UH, SURE.
OKAY.
(MUSIC BLASTS FROM CAR)
HI.
HEY.
(DOOR SHUTS)
(TIRES SCREECH,
ENGINE ROARS)
TOM:
PLEASE ALLOW ME
THE IMMENSE PLEASURE
OF INTRODUCING THE NEW FACE
OF T-BOMBZ...
MIA JONES!
ATTENDEES:
(CHEERING, CAMERAS SNAPPING)
♪♪♪
♪ Later Sunday morning ♪
♪ Jump inside your bed ♪
♪ The blues came
without warning... ♪
ISABELLA:
(GIGGLING)
ANNA:
(PRIDEFUL BREATH)
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU,
SWEETHEART!
WELL, HELLO.
YOU MUST BE MIA'S SISTER?
(HALF LAUGHS)
AND WHO'S THIS
LITTLE BEAUTY?
MIA:
THAT ONE REALLY IS MY SISTER.
TOM:
OKAY, MOM, YOU DON'T MIND
IF I STEAL CINDERELLA HERE
FOR A LITTLE SCHMOOZING,
DO YOU, MOM?
OH, IT'S A SCHOOL NIGHT.
MOM!
IT WOULD BE HELPFUL
FOR MIA
TO MEET THE T-BOMBZ
INVESTORS.
AND I WON'T LET HER
OUT OF MY SIGHT.
AND LEIA'S GONNA BE THERE.
OKAY,
BUT NOT TOO LATE.
OKAY. BYE.
ISABELLA:
(FUSSY MOAN)
(MOUTHS "I'M SORRY")
(HALF LAUGHS)
(LOW DIN OF CHATTER)
OH, WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN
ALL MY LIFE?
(GIGGLES)
BIANCA: CHEERS.
TOM: RIGHT. CHEERS.
TOM:
(SNORTED CHUCKLE)
LAME.
(WHISPERS)
WHO ARE THESE PEOPLE?
YEAH, THIS PARTY'S
GETTING BORING.
SEND THE LITTLE ONES
HOME,
I'LL MAKE THINGS
MORE INTERESTING.
TOM:
(CHUCKLES)
I BET YOU WILL.
(SMALL COUGH)
WE'RE UP FOR WHATEVER
YOU ARE.
REALLY?
THEN COME HERE.
JERRY:
OOH! OW!
(PATS LEG)
TOM:
(WHOOPS EXCITEDLY)
SEE?
OUR LITTLE MIA CAN PARTY
WITH THE BEST OF 'EM.
BIANCA:
(TITTERS)
WHAT DO SAY A FEW OF US
TAKE THIS TO THE OTHER ROOM?
JERRY? BIANCA?
YEAH?
JONES?
YOU CAN BRING YOUR FRIEND.
BIANCA:
IF SHE'S UP FOR IT.
(WITHDRAWING FOOTSTEPS)
WHAT,
BEDTIME ALREADY?
(MUTED BEAT OF MUSIC)
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
THIS ISN'T MY SCENE,
OKAY?
OKAY, IF YOU DON'T STAY,
I'LL LOOK BAD.
YOU DON'T REALLY NEED ME
FOR THAT.
LEIA, I THOUGHT YOU
WERE MY FRIEND.
WHICH IS WHY I'M TELLING YOU
IT'S TIME TO LEAVE.
(EXASPERATED SIGH)
LEIA:
HOW FAR ARE YOU GONNA GO
TO IMPRESS?
IT'S AT AN ADULT PARTY;
STUFF HAPPENS, OKAY?
AND FOR ME,
IT'S JUST PART OF THE JOB.
I HAVE TO STAY IN
WITH THIS CROWD.
BIANCA:
YOU LITTLE GIRLS COMING BACK
OR WHAT?
I HAVE TO GO BACK.
YOU DON'T GET IT.
I GUESS I DON'T.
(DOORS WHIR CLOSED)
(HEAVY SIGH)
(OFFICE PHONE RINGS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
OH.
MIA JONES.
THE T-BOMBZ GIRL!
SO WHAT CAN I DO YOU FOR?
I UH...
JUST THIS ONCE,
COULD I GET A LATE SLIP?
BEEN PARTYING ALL NIGHT,
HUH?
SURE.
BE OUR LITTLE SECRET.
DOES THAT WORK FOR HOMEWORK,
BY ANY CHANCE?
DOES NOW.
SAY "HI" TO TOM BLAKE
FOR ME!
THANK YOU,
PRINCIPAL SHEPPARD.
IT'S "THE SHEP."
OH.
(QUIET TITTER)
LET'S EXPLORE MY FAVORITE GAS,
HYDROGEN.
NICE OF YOU TO JOIN US,
MS. JONES.
CHANTAY:
HOW WAS THE PRESS RELEASE
THING?
DID YOU PARTY WITH TOM
ALL NIGHT LONG?
FINALLY HAVE YOUR FIRST
PHOTO SHOOT;
YOU SURE YOU'RE READY?
MIA:
I WAS BORN READY.
MR. BINCE:
WOULD YOU GIRLS LIKE
TO TAKE OVER FROM HERE?
PERHAPS YOU'D LIKE TO START
BY LISTING THE INERT GASES.
FINE.
LADY T-BOMBZ?
ASSIGNMENT FOR ME?
IF YOU FALL FAR BEHIND
THIS EARLY,
YOU WON'T CATCH UP.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE SAYING...
SO HOW WAS THE REST
OF YOUR NIGHT?
YOU'D KNOW
IF YOU HAD STAYED.
I'M NOT THE PARTIER
LIKE YOU.
IT WAS WORK,
NOT PLAY.
OH, YOU'RE LIKE
A BAD CLICHE -
SLEEPING YOUR WAY
TO THE TOP.
SHUT UP!
Y-YOU DID!
YOU SLEPT WITH TOM
TO GET THE JOB?!
(BELL RINGS)
BINCE:
TOMORROW WE'LL INTRODUCE
CHLORINE TO ACETYLENE
WITH EXPLOSIVE RESULTS!
JUDGE ALL YOU WANT.
OF COURSE, IT'LL BE LONELY
WITH NO ONE TO LISTEN.
LET'S GO.
CHANTAY:
WHAT'RE YOU WEARING?
DO YOU GET TO KEEP
YOUR CLOTHES?
ANYA:
DO YOU GET TO SPEND
MORE TIME WITH TOM?
P.A. ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION, STUDENTS.
A BRIEF REMINDER...
CONNOR:
UM, AREN'T WE GOING
TO THE CAFETERIA?
WE USUALLY EAT
IN THE CAFETERIA.
CLARE:
I THOUGHT WE'D TRY SOME PLACE
DIFFERENT, TODAY.
NICE PIPES YESTERDAY,
LITTLE EDWARDS.
BETWEEN THE VOICE
AND THE OUTFIT?
YOU COULD BE ON IDOL.
THE BLOOPER REEL,
AT LEAST.
I THINK WE SHOULD EAT
IN THE CAFETERIA.
CLARE:
UH, HEY, CONNOR?
UH, IS THERE ANY WAY TO MAKE
FIREWORKS BRIGHTER?
CONNOR:
WELL, YOU MAKE THEM BRIGHTER
BY ADDING COMPOUNDS
WITH MORE OXYGEN
AND...
YOU'RE IN MY SEAT.
SORRY.
HEH.
SO, UM, HOW DO YOU MAKE
OTHER EFFECTS?
CONNOR:
BY MIXING OTHER ADDITIVES:
TITANIUM MAKES SPARKS;
ZINC MAKES SMOKE CLOUDS;
CALCIUM DEEPENS COLOUR.
YOU CAN TRACE AMOUNTS OF METALS
THAT BURN AT HIGH TEMPERATURES
TO MAKE...
DANNY:
LEIA.
YOU'VE GOTTA HELP ME OUT.
MIA'S PLAYING ME HOT
AND COLD.
DO I HAVE A CHANCE?
WHAT'S HER GAME?
YOU DON'T WANT
TO KNOW.
BUT YOU'RE FRIENDS,
RIGHT?
WERE FRIENDS.
AND THE CAUSE OF THE SUDDEN
BREAK UP?
LET'S JUST SAY MIA'S
MORE ADVENTUROUS THAN I AM.
ADVENTUROUS, HOW?
SHE SLEPT WITH TOM BLAKE
TO GET THE JOB.
SO DO YOU HAVE
A CHANCE?
MAYBE.
DO YOU WANT IT?
THAT'S UP TO YOU.
MOORE'S LAW SAYS
THAT COMPUTING POWER DOUBLES
EVERY 18 MONTHS.
SO, WHERE WILL WE BE
IN TEN YEARS?
(KNOCK ON THE DOOR)
SHEPPARD:
HOWDY PARDNER.
NEED A WORD
WITH YOUR SPECIAL CLASS.
HI.
SOME OF YOU HAVE BEEN
EATING IN HERE.
NOW, THESE COMPUTERS
ARE EXPENSIVE
AND THEY DON'T LIKE MAYO.
SO PLEASE EAT ONLY IN
DESIGNATED LUNCH AREAS.
I SUGGEST THE CAF.
WITH ME?
OOH.
THAT'S IT.
'CAUSE IT'S GOT SUCH
GREAT ENTERTAINMENT.
HUH, CLARE?
CLASS:
(LAUGHS)
SIMPSON:
UM...
GUYS, SETTLE DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, SETTLE DOWN.
UM... WHERE WERE WE?
UM, LET'S KEEP OUR MIND
ON THE CLASS, ALL RIGHT?
CLARE.
WHAT, DIDN'T GET YOUR DIGS
IN CLASS?
ALLI WAS JOKING.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
I WAS UNTIL YOU HAD ME
MAKE A FOOL OF MYSELF.
I'M SORRY.
I WAS JUST TRYING TO PROVE
YOU CARE WHAT PEOPLE THINK.
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.
NOW I KNOW THEY THINK
I'M A DORK.
KC:
SO NOW IT'S BACK TO HANGING
ONLY WITH THE SMART KIDS?
STUDENTS:
(HUM OF OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
THEY GET ME,
OKAY?
THEY DON'T THINK
I'M WEIRD
OR... LAUGH AT ME.
SO IT'S NOT THAT YOU
DON'T CARE WHAT PEOPLE THINK?
MY SISTER DARCY
IS THE PRETTY
AND POPULAR ONE.
I'M GOOD AT BEING
THE SMART ONE.
YOU'RE SO MUCH MORE
THAN "THE SMART ONE."
JANICE:
A MOMENT WITH MY CLIENT, ANDRE.
YOUR FIRST SHOOT
AND YOU CAN BARELY
KEEP YOUR EYES OPEN?
I... (SIGHS)
WAS I WRONG TO TAKE
A CHANCE ON YOU?
I WAS OUT LATE.
WHEN YOU SHOULD HAVE BEEN
AT HOME RESTING
FOR THE BIG DAY.
BUT I THOUGHT THE SOCIAL STUFF
HELPED GET WORK?
SAYS WHO?
IT WAS CLEAR FROM THE MOMENT
YOU LEFT THE STUDIO
YOU WERE FIRST CHOICE;
IT WAS UNANIMOUS.
IT WAS? BUT...
YOU KNEW THAT DAY?
BUT TOM, HE-
YOU'RE NOT GETTING INFATUATED
WITH TOM, ARE YOU?
HIS WIFE
WOULD NOT APPROVE.
WIFE?
HE'S MARRIED?
TWO YEARS.
NOW, SMARTEN UP.
THE ONLY SCENE
THAT COUNTS WITH ME
IS THE ONE WE'RE SHOOTING
RIGHT NOW.
PHOTOGRAPHER:
CAN WE HAVE PRODUCT ON SET
PLEASE?
TOM:
HEY.
THERE YOU ARE.
THERE YOU ARE,
STRANGER.
SET DIRECTOR:
'KAY, WE NEED TO TURN OFF
THE LIGHTS...
TOM:
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE NICE TO ME
TODAY?
PHOTOGRAPHER:
WE'RE READY, GUYS.
AND HERE WE GO!
OKAY,
LOOK UP TO HIM.
DIRECTOR:
(INDISCERNIBLE DIRECTIONS)
♪ But where do you
draw the line? ♪
♪ 'Cause I've got no room
for mine ♪
♪ When is enough enough ♪
♪ How do you love that stuff ♪
♪ 'Cause if we are on the run ♪
♪ Is that when you
find your gun ♪
♪ Trying to guess... ♪
PHOTOGRAPHER:
AND THAT'S A WRAP, GUYS!
THANK YOU!
SO WHERE DO YOU WANNA
PARTY TONIGHT?
WILL YOUR WIFE
BE JOINING US?
(LAUGHS)
COME ON.
YOU CAME UP TO MY APARTMENT
ON YOUR OWN AND...
AND YOU DIDN'T TELL ME
THAT I ALREADY HAD THE JOB.
OH, SO WHAT?
YOU GONNA WALK AWAY
FROM THE CONTRACT?
(SNICKERS)
IT'S NO SKIN
OFF MY BACK.
NO.
I EARNED THIS CONTRACT
IN THE AUDITION.
FROM NOW ON,
THE JOB DESCRIPTION
WILL ONLY INCLUDE MODELING.
YOU USED ME.
WHO USED WHO?
YEAH.
(SHREWD CHUCKLE)
WHAT?
WE MISS ONE DAY
AND PEOPLE TAKE OUR TABLE.
THAT'S OUR TABLE.
WHERE ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO SIT?
DO YOU MIND
IF WE SIT HERE?
BE MY GUEST.
THIS IS NOT OUR TABLE.
ALLI:
(HALF LAUGHING)
BUT CLARE?
NO SINGING.
I PROMISE, I WILL NEVER SING
IN THE CAFETERIA AGAIN.
KC:
I LIKED IT.
STUDENTS:
(LAUGHING)
ANYA:
YOUR SKIN LOOKS AMAZING!
RILEY:
YOU'RE LOOKING GOOD.
DANNY.
DON'T YOU WANNA
COME SIT WITH US?
DEPENDS.
WHAT'S IN IT FOR YOU?
HEARD YOU ONLY HANG WITH GUYS
WHO CAN GET YOU AHEAD.
UH, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
DANNY.
DON'T WORRY,
LEIA AND I WON'T TELL
YOUR NEW FRIENDS.
MIA,
WE TOOK A VOTE.
YOU HAVE TO BE
ON THE POWER SQUAD.
AND I WAS THINKING,
POWER SQUAD MOVIE NIGHT
TONIGHT?
SURE.
SOUNDS GREAT.