POWER SQUAD:
ASK ME A QUESTION,
I'LL GIVE NO ANSWER.
I'LL JUST CLAW YOUR FACE OFF
'CAUSE I AM A PANTHER!
(CLAP TWICE)
ROAR!
THEY'VE GOTTA BE KIDDING.
SOMEONE'S BITTER
ABOUT BEING KICKED OFF
POWER SQUAD.
SOMEONE SHOULD SHUT
HER NINER MOUTH.
MAYBE YOU CAN USE
YOUR NEW FREE TIME TO...
FIND TRUE LOVE?
RELATIONSHIP ADVICE
FROM THE GIRL WHO SHOPS
IN JUNIOR MISS?
HEY,
I HAVE A BOYFRIEND.
WHO?
WE'RE KEEPING IT QUIET.
HOLLY J:
HMM, AN IMAGINARY BOYFRIEND.
CUTE.
JOHNNY DIMARCO.
YOU'RE SAYING YOU'RE DATING
JOHNNY DIMARCO?
ALLI:
YEAH.
LET'S SEE ABOUT THAT.
P.A. ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION DEGRASSI,
COULD ALL STUDENTS...
ALLI:
PLEASE DON'T SAY ANYTHING.
JOHNNY, BRUCE AND DEREK:
(LOW CHATTER)
HEARD YOU AND BACKWOODS
ARE AN ITEM.
BRUCE:
WHOA?
ISN'T THAT ILLEGAL?
(HALF LAUGHS)
I'M A SENIOR.
YOU SERIOUSLY THINK
I'M GOING TO DATE A NINER?
YOU HIGH?
GUESS I MUST BE.
DEREK:
(PATTING JOHNNY)
GRADE NINE, EH, BUDDY?
HOLLY J:
SORRY, HON.
NOW YOU CAN FIND
TRUE LOVE, TOO.
I'M GONNA KILL HER.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh! ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
ALLI:
JOHNNY, PLEASE.
YOU KNOW...
I TOLD YOU WE SHOULD
KEEP THIS QUIET
AND NOW YOU KNOW WHY.
I JUST WANT TO PROVE TO HER
THAT I HAVE AN AWESOME
BOYFRIEND.
NOW YOU DON'T.
YOU'RE NOT BREAKING UP
WITH ME!
I HAVE NO CHOICE NOW,
OKAY?
COULDN'T WE JUST KEEP
SNEAKING AROUND?
AS SOON AS THOSE GUYS SEE US
IN THE SAME ROOM TOGETHER,
IT'S GONNA BE
NON-STOP INSULTS...
FOR ME AND FOR YOU.
IT'S NOT GONNA WORK,
BACKWOODS.
I'M SORRY.
YOU RUINED EVERYTHING.
YEAH, IT MUST HAVE BEEN
A REALLY SOLID RELATIONSHIP
IF ONE COMMENT DESTROYS IT.
IT WAS.
IT WAS REALLY GOOD.
JUST BECAUSE YOU HAVE
NO FRIENDS,
NO BOYFRIEND,
AND YOU'RE KICKED OFF
THE POWER SQUAD,
DOESN'T MEAN YOU CAN BE
SO MEAN TO ME.
DO YOU REALLY THINK
I NEED A REASON
TO BE MEAN TO YOU?
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
SAV (SINGING):
♪ I LOVE TO WATCH
YOU CHEER ♪
♪ IT'S BEEN THAT WAY
FOR HALF A YEAR ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE WE BELONG ♪
♪ SO I WROTE THIS SONG,
YEAH! ♪
♪ FOR MY ONE... ♪
♪ MY ONLY... ♪
♪ ANYA ♪
(LOCK CLICKS,
DOOR OPENS)
DAD?
MR. STONE:
THANK GOD, YOU'RE HERE.
LISTEN...
PETER, I HAVE A COUPLE
OF TICKETS
TO THE HOCKEY GAME AND...
I'LL TELL THE GUYS.
PETE, PETE.
OH, THEY'RE NOT FOR ME?
MR. STONE:
MISSY'S IN VEGAS.
AND A BIG CLIENT'S
COME TO TOWN UNEXPECTEDLY.
WHICH MEANS...
I NEED YOU
TO LOOK AFTER ANGEL.
I DON'T SEE YOU
FOR MONTHS
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN
YOU WANT ME TO BABYSIT?
PETE, I AM DESPERATE.
THINK OF IT AS PAYBACK
FOR THIS SWEET PAD.
GOT HER?
I'LL MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
NEXT TIME I GET TICKETS,
IT'S YOU AND ME, PAL.
SOUNDS GOOD.
MR. STONE:
GOOD.
SPINNER:
SO, I GUESS,
BAND PRACTICE IS OVER?
PETER:
NO, BABIES LOVE MUSIC.
(PLAYS A LICK,
ANGEL CRIES)
YEAH, NOT THIS ONE.
(ANGEL CRIES)
STUDENTS:
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
HEY!
ISN'T THAT JOHNNY'S
GIRLFRIEND.
MAYBE I SHOULD GET
A NINER GIRLFRIEND;
I HEAR THEY'RE EAGER
TO PLEASE.
YOU KNOW, THEY WILL DO
JUST ABOUT ANYTHING
FOR A COOKIE.
ON SECOND THOUGHT,
DIAPERS ARE EXPENSIVE.
ANYA:
NICE, GUYS.
I HATE HER.
I HATE HOLLY J.
JOIN THE CLUB.
WE USED TO BE
BEST FRIENDS,
UNTIL SHE BURNED ME
ONE TOO MANY TIMES.
WE NEED TO DO
SOMETHING TO HER.
FIGHT BACK.
BELIEVE ME, I'VE TRIED.
SHE'S LIKE A COCKROACH.
SHE'LL SURVIVE ANYTHING.
SO, I'M JUST SUPPOSED
TO GRIN AND BEAR IT?
I CAN'T DO THAT.
I WON'T DO THAT.
I HATE HOLLY J.
I HATE HER SO MUCH.
CLARE:
THEN IGNORE HER.
(FRUSTRATED SIGH)
(KEYBOARD KEYS CLICK)
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
(MOUSE POINTER CLICKS,
KEYBOARD KEYS CLACK)
(MOUSE POINTER CLICKS)
DOES THAT MAKE YOU
FEEL BETTER?
YOU BET.
PETER:
MY SISTER JUST CRIED
AND CRIED AND CRIED
AND CRIED AND CRIED.
BABIES ARE EXHAUSTING.
I HAD NO IDEA.
NO, THIS IS DIFFERENT.
BELLA IS A SWEETHEART.
MY SISTER
IS THE DEVIL-CHILD.
WELL, SHE DOES SHARE
YOUR DNA.
DON'T LET HOW YOU FEEL
ABOUT YOUR DAD
AFFECT HOW YOU FEEL
ABOUT YOUR SISTER.
I SAW HIM LIKE...
ONCE A MONTH
WHEN I WAS A KID.
HALF THOSE TIMES,
I WAS IN HIS OFFICE
PLAYING WITH A STAPLER.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(CELL PHONE BUTTON BEEPS)
AGAIN?
HE'S LEAVING HER
WITH ME AGAIN.
NO WAY.
COME ON,
GIVE HER A CHANCE.
WITH A DAD LIKE YOURS,
SHE NEEDS HER BIG BROTHER.
I DON'T SPEAK BABY.
I COULD COACH YOU.
NANNY 911,
AT YOUR SERVICE.
OH...
ANY CHANCE THERE'S
A CUTE UNIFORM INVOLVED?
MIA AND PETER:
(PLAYFUL GIGGLES)
(STUDENT CHATTER)
HEY, HOLLY J.
I JUST JOINED
YOUR FAN CLUB.
LIKE THEY SAY, "SMALL THINGS
AMUSE SMALL MINDS."
SAW YOUR LITTLE GROUP.
CUTE.
LIKE I REALLY CARE WHAT YOU
AND TEN OTHER LOSERS THINK.
BUT I KNOW YOU'D CARE
THAT I SAW JOHNNY
HEADING INTO THE RAVINE
WITH MEGAN ROTHMAN.
PROBABLY HIS REAL
GIRLFRIEND.
YOU'RE LYING.
I DON'T DO THAT.
IT'S EMBARRASSING
TO BE CAUGHT IN A LIE.
I WASN'T LYING.
JOHNNY AND I WERE TOGETHER.
TELL IT TO SOMEONE WHO CARES,
LITTLE BHANDARI.
SEE?
YOU HURT HER FEELINGS.
IF IT'S GETTING TO HER,
THAT'S GREAT.
I NEED TO TAKE IT
TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
♪ If you think
you're on a roll ♪
♪ You're garbage
turns to gold ♪
♪ Tell everyone ♪
♪ You're going alone ♪
♪♪♪
♪ You're climbing out
your hole ♪
♪ And now you're in control ♪
♪ Tell everyone ♪
♪ You're going alone ♪
♪♪♪
You've broken every bone
you're made of
♪♪♪
FINALLY ASLEEP.
WHICH MEANS...
IT'S OUR, UH...
BEDTIME, TOO.
(ANGEL CRIES)
(GRUNTS) WHAT'S WRONG
WITH THAT THING?
SHE'S NOT A THING,
SHE'S A BABY
AND BABY'S CRY.
YEAH, WELL, THIS BABY
IS NOT MY RESPONSIBILITY.
I'M GONNA CALL MY DAD
RIGHT NOW
AND TELL HIM
TO PICK HER UP.
SO HE CAN PUT HER
IN A CORNER
AND LET HER PLAY
WITH A STAPLER?
NOT MY KID,
NOT MY PROBLEM.
SO, YOU'RE SAYING
YOU COULD NEVER...
TAKE CARE OF SOMEBODY ELSE'S
CHILD?
I DIDN'T MEAN BELLA.
NOT THIS TIME.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
(EXHALES)
I THINK I'LL GO.
AND, UH, IT'S PROBABLY
HER DIAPER
THAT NEEDS CHANGING.
I'M SURE YOU CAN
FIGURE IT OUT.
(DOOR OPENS)
(ANGEL CRIES HARDER,
DOOR SHUTS)
(LOW HUM OF STUDENT CHATTER)
CLARE:
SO...
YOU'D LIKE
TO STRANGLE HER?
NOT LITERALLY.
WELL, DO YOU REALLY
THINK IT'S OKAY
TO POST THAT ONLINE?
WHOSE SIDE ARE YOU ON?
WELL, I GET THAT
SHE HURT YOU.
DOESN'T MEAN YOU NEED
TO UP THE ANTE.
CHANTAY:
HEY, GIRL.
YOU SHOULD SIT WITH US.
WE'RE ALL OBSESSED
WITH YOUR FACERANGE GROUP.
OBVIOUSLY, YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
THAT FEELS THAT WAY.
YOU'VE GOT TO SEE
THE POST I ADDED.
WISH WE'D THOUGHT OF THIS
A LONG TIME AGO.
BRUCE:
YOU KNOW, I HATE...
HOLLY J.
DEREK:
YEAH, YOU COULD SAY
THAT AGAIN.
I HATE HOLLY J, TOO.
BRUCE AND DEREK:
(LAUGHING)
I HATE HOLLY J!
(STUDENTS JOIN CHANT)
LIKE I CARE
WHAT YOU LOSERS THINK!
♪ She pretends to be free ♪
♪ But she's locked
in her ivory towers ♪
♪ She's the most popular girl
in the world ♪
♪ In the world ♪
♪ Even the most popular girl
in the world ♪
♪ Has her own share
of problems ♪
MR. STONE:
I'M ON MY WAY BACK NOW.
YEAH. DON'T LET THEM START
THE MEETING WITHOUT ME, OKAY?
THAT'S IT.
(STRAINING) ALL RIGHT.
YEAH.
UH-HUNH.
(EXASPERATED BREATH)
OH! WHAT IS THE MATTER
WITH THIS?
PETE.
MM-MMM.
OH! LISTEN, I'M GONNA NEED YOU
TO LOOK AFTER ANGEL
THIS AFTERNOON.
WELL, IF YOU FOUND ME
A SITTING SERVICE,
WE WOULD BE HAVING
THIS CONVERSATION.
(ANGEL CRIES)
YOUR JOB IS TO ASSIST ME,
LISA.
AND TODAY I NEED YOUR ASSISTANCE
WITH MY DAUGHTER.
THANK YOU.
I'LL SEE YOU IN 20.
THANKS, PETE.
WAIT.
I'M ALREADY LATE,
PETE.
NO, I'LL TAKE HER.
MR. STONE:
NO, NO, THAT'S OKAY.
MY SECRETARY'S GONNA HANDLE IT.
I MEAN, HER.
YEAH, SHE SEEMED, UH...
REAL THRILLED ABOUT THAT,
TOO.
I'LL TAKE HER,
JUST PROMISE YOU WON'T
LEAVE HER WITH ME AGAIN,
OVERNIGHT?
I'LL PICK HER UP
RIGHT AFTER WORK.
I PROMISE.
(ANGEL CRIES)
PETER:
LOOKS LIKE IT'S JUST
ME AND YOU, KIDDO.
(VEHICLE WHIRS AWAY)
ALLI:
"WE RAN HER OUT OF THE CAF!
NEXT STEP, THE SCHOOL!"
THIS IS BETTER
THAN I EVER DREAMED.
BETTER?
YOU'RE DESTROYING
A PERSON'S LIFE.
HOLLY J IS NOT A PERSON.
SHE'S A WITCH OR A...
TROLL OR SOMETHING.
SHE DESERVES IT.
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
CLARE:
"WANT TO STRANGLE HER?
I'LL BRING THE ROPE."
THIS HAS GONE TOO FAR.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
MS. DAWES IS GONNA COVER
FOR A FEW MINUTES,
WHILE I TEND TO SOME
"ACTING PRINCIPAL DUTIES."
ALLI BHANDARI,
WILL YOU JOIN ME PLEASE?
MS. DAWES:
UH... OKAY,
MEDIA ISN'T MY FORTE,
SO, LET'S OPEN PHOTOSHOP
AND SEE IF WE CAN FIGURE OUT
HOW TO EXPLORE OURSELVES...
CREATIVELY.
UM, OUR ASSIGNMENT IS TO, UM...
DO A DIGITAL INTERPRETATION
OF A RENAISSANCE PAINTING.
ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION, STUDENTS,
WOULD ALL TUBA PLAYERS
PLEASE REPORT TO THE BAND ROOM
IMMEDIATELY.
THANK YOU.
(ANGEL FUSSES)
YOU BROUGHT A BABY
TO SCHOOL?
SHE'S TOO YOUNG
TO PLAY WITH STAPLERS.
SO YOU'RE TAKING
RESPONSIBILITY
FOR SOMEONE ELSE'S CHILD?
I DIDN'T MEAN BELLA.
I'M SORRY,
I WAS AN IDIOT.
AND ANGEL'S MY SISTER,
SO I WANNA TAKE
CARE OF HER.
WELL, FOR STARTERS,
SHE'S A BABY,
NOT A FOOTBALL.
AW.
(ANGEL STOPS FUSSING)
OH, SHE LIKES ME.
MIA:
(LAUGHS)
I DON'T WANT TO BE
MY FATHER.
NOT A CHANCE.
DID WE NOT RAISE YOU
IN A HOUSEHOLD
THAT VALUES RESPECT?
I DIDN'T DO
ANYTHING WRONG.
(SHOCKED GASP)
MRS. SINCLAIR SAYS
HOLLY J'S REFUSING
TO COME OUT OF HER ROOM
BECAUSE OF YOUR ATTACKS.
ALLI:
I DIDN'T WRITE ALL THIS.
SIMPSON:
NO, BUT YOU DID START
THE GROUP
AND YOU DID THREATEN
HOLLY J'S LIFE.
THAT WAS A JOKE,
OBVIOUSLY.
WHEN 411 PEOPLE
GET ON THE BANDWAGON,
IT'S VERY SERIOUS.
THIS IS UNCONSCIONABLE.
I AM ASHAMED.
I'M SUSPENDING ALLI.
THAT'S NOT FAIR!
SIMPSON:
AND WHEN SHE COMES BACK,
SHE'LL MAKE A SPEECH
TO THE SCHOOL
ABOUT WHY WHAT SHE DID
WAS WRONG.
THAT'S MORE THAN FAIR.
ALLI:
SO, EVEN IF YOU HATE
HOLLY J
DON'T USE FACERANGE
TO EXPRESS YOURSELF,
BECAUSE SHE'LL RAT YOU OUT.
SAV:
OH, YEAH, WELL...
I MEAN, THAT SOUNDS LIKE
YOU LEARNED YOUR LESSON.
DON'T YOU START IN
ON ME, TOO.
THE LAST THING I NEED
IS ANOTHER LECTURE.
DON'T WORRY,
I WASN'T GOING TO.
EVERYONE'S TOTALLY
OVERREACTING.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
DAD SO UPSET.
THEY'VE GROUNDED ME
FOR TWO WHOLE MONTHS
AND TAKEN AWAY MY COMPUTER.
LIKE THE SUSPENSION
WASN'T BAD ENOUGH.
THAT SUCKS.
ALLI:
WHATEVER.
I'M JUST GONNA TREAT IT LIKE
A LITTLE VACAY FROM SCHOOL.
AT LEAST NOW,
EVERYONE AT DEGRASSI
KNOWS WHO I AM.
IT WAS TOTALLY WORTH IT.
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
(PHONE BEEPS ON)
HELLO?
OH? OKAY, YEAH.
SURE...
I'LL LET HER KNOW.
OKAY, BYE.
HEY, THAT WAS DAD.
HE'S COMING HOME
BECAUSE...
THE SINCLAIRS CALLED
THE POLICE.
THEY WANT TO QUESTION YOU.
VERY FUNNY.
YOU'RE SERIOUS?
THE POLICE?
SAV:
YEAH.
(HEAVY BREATHS)
I CAN'T BELIEVE
SHE'S DOING THIS TO ME.
(VEHICLE WHIRS BY)
ALLI:
I COULDN'T KILL A FLY.
LOOK AT ME.
POLICE DETECTIVE:
BE THAT AS IT MAY,
THE SINCLAIRS ARE CONCERNED
AND WE'RE TAKING THIS
VERY SERIOUSLY.
SHOULDN'T YOU BE GOING
AFTER ACTUAL CRIMINALS?
UTTERING DEATH THREATS
IS AN ACTUAL CRIME.
MR. BHANDARI:
I ASSURE YOU,
ALLIAH IS REPENTANT.
WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
WE'RE GONNA GIVE
YOUR DAUGHTER A WARNING.
BUT THIS WILL STAY
ON HER JUVENILE RECORD.
I'M GETTING A RECORD?
POLICE DETECTIVE:
YES.
SO IF YOU'RE EVER CAUGHT
AT A PARTY
WITH UNDERAGE DRINKING,
IT'LL BE YOU WHO'S ARRESTED.
NOT YOUR FRIENDS,
YOU.
MR. BHANDARI:
DON'T WORRY, OFFICER.
SHE WILL NOT BE GOING
TO ANY PARTIES,
EVER.
I SUGGEST YOU WRITE
AN APOLOGY
TO MS. SINCLAIR
AND HER FAMILY.
MR. BHANDARI:
SHE WILL DO MUCH BETTER
THAN THAT.
ALLIAH WILL GO
AND APOLOGIZE IN PERSON.
THIS LITTLE PIGGIE
WENT TO THE DOT,
AND THIS LITTLE PIGGIE WENT,
"RAH, RAH, RAH"
ALL THE WAY
TO THE ROCK CONCERT.
(DOOR KNOB RATTLES,
DOOR OPENS)
YOU SAID RIGHT AFTER WORK.
SOMETHING CAME UP.
YEAH. OF COURSE,
I GET IT.
BUT, UH...
I PICKED THIS UP.
AS A...
KIND OF A THANK YOU
FOR ALL YOUR HELP
THIS WEEK.
THAT'S A BASS;
I PLAY GUITAR.
OH.
WELL, I CAN'T KEEP TRACK
OF EVERYTHING.
YEAH, KEEPING TRACK OF SOMETHING
I'VE BEEN DOING SINCE I WAS 10,
THAT'D BE CRAZY.
I SHOULD PROBABLY
HEAD OUT.
THAT'S WHAT
YOU DO BEST.
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED
TO MEAN?
YOU WERE A LOUSY FATHER
FOR ME,
SO DON'T BE FOR ANGEL.
NOW THAT'S NOT FAIR,
PETE.
I TRIED WITH YOU.
I REALLY DID.
BUT YOUR MOTHER...
NO. YOU KNOW WHAT?
JUST STOP.
THE TRUTH IS YOU DIDN'T
AND, AND THAT'S FINE.
BUT... I DON'T WANT MY SISTER
TO GO THROUGH THE SAME THINGS
I WENT THROUGH.
ANGEL:
(GURGLES)
CUSTOMERS:
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
UM, I ORDERED A BURGER TOO.
LIKE AN HOUR AGO.
BLAME HOLLY J.
SHE DIDN'T SHOW UP
FOR HER SHIFT TODAY.
(DOOR CHIMES JINGLE)
SAV SAID YOU'D BE HERE.
YOUR DAD LET YOU OUT?
YEAH. I HAVE TO GO
TO HOLLY J'S HOUSE
AND APOLOGIZE.
WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA SAY?
I CAN'T DO IT.
I'LL CHOKE ON AN APOLOGY.
SHE DID THIS
ALL ON PURPOSE.
YOU THINK HOLLY J
IS PRETENDING TO BE UPSET
TO GET YOU IN TROUBLE?
HOLLY J IS RUINING MY LIFE.
HOLLY J NEEDS TO HEAR YOU
SAY ALL THIS.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(KNOCKING)
(DOOR OPENS)
ANYA.
I DIDN'T THINK
YOU'D COME AFTER...
WHEN I SAW YOUR NAME
ON THAT GROUP,
I COULDN'T BELIEVE IT.
(UNCOMFORTABLE THROAT CLEAR)
UM...
YOUR MOM TOLD ME
YOU DIDN'T WANT ANY VISITORS,
BUT I CONVINCED HER.
UM...
I THINK THAT YOU GUYS
NEED TO TALK.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
GET OUT.
NOW.
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING
TO DO TO ME?
SUSPENSION AND NOW THE COPS?
WHY WOULD I CALL THE COPS?
ALLI:
BECAUSE YOU HATE ME
AND YOU WANT TO RUIN MY LIFE?
WELL,
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.
IF I WANTED TO RUIN
YOUR LIFE,
I'D CREATE
AN "I HATE ALLI GROUP,"
GET 400 PEOPLE TO JOIN
AND TALK ABOUT HOW MUCH THEY...
(WELLING UP)
HOW MUCH THEY HATE YOU
AND THAT THEY WANT YOU DEAD.
ALLI:
YOU JUST MADE ME SO MAD
AND... EVERYONE SAID
THERE WAS NOTHING I COULD DO.
I JUST WANTED YOU TO STOP.
WELL, YOU GOT YOUR WISH.
BECAUSE I'M NOT COMING
BACK TO DEGRASSI.
EVER.
JUST LEAVE.
MIA:
HEY.
SO,
WHAT'D YOUR DAD SAY?
UH, HE MUTTERED SOMETHING
ABOUT TRYING TO BE
A BETTER FATHER
AND THEN HE JUST TOOK OFF.
DO YOU THINK
YOU GOT THROUGH TO HIM?
I HOPE SO.
I HAD ONE REALLY AWESOME
ADULT IN MY LIFE:
MY MOM.
ANGEL? I'M NOT SURE
SHE HAS ANY.
COME ON,
SHE'S GOT YOU.
(GRUNTS)
MMM.
CLASS?
ALLI:
AND I WAS SO MAD
I DIDN'T THINK WHAT MY ACTIONS
MIGHT DO TO SOMEONE ELSE.
AND NOW THAT
I'VE SEEN THE EFFECT,
I'M REALLY, REALLY SORRY.
YOU SHOULD'VE SEEN
HOLLY J.
SO, HAVE YOU
FORGIVEN HER?
YEAH.
I THOUGHT ABOUT IT.
IF JOHNNY COULDN'T
STAND UP FOR ME,
HE DOESN'T DESERVE ME.
(STUDENT CHATTER)
UM, HOLLY J?
I'M SO SORRY FOR EVERYTHING.
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT LEAVING.
ANYA:
I CONVINCED HER TO GIVE
DEGRASSI ANOTHER CHANCE;
WE NEED HER HERE.
ALLI:
I GOT KICKED OFF FACERANGE.
THE GROUP IS GONE.
SO IT SHOULD BE KIND OF
BACK TO NORMAL AROUND HERE.
DEREK:
HEY, ALLI.
I, UH, BROUGHT SOME ROPE.
(DEREK PATS HOLLY J,
HOLLY J SIGHS)
YEAH,
BACK TO NORMAL.
ANYA:
COME ON.