(DIN OF CHATTER)
ROOMIES ARE GONE.
CAN'T WE GO BACK TO BED
AND CUDDLE A LITTLE LONGER?
ARE YOU SUGGESTING
WE SKIP WINDOVER'S
ROCKS FOR JOCKS LECTURE?
(TIGHT INHALE)
OKAY.
YOU'RE RIGHT, LET'S GO.
BECCA:
OH, KELLY!
HILARIOUS POINT IN CLASSICS
YESTERDAY.
ROME WAS TOTALLY THE STUDENT
APARTMENT VERSION OF ATHENS.
THE OTHER FLOORS'LL
BE SO JEALOUS.
BEST FLOOR OLYMPICS EVER!
HEY, KEL!
BLONDE EMMA.
HOW CAN SHE STILL BE
CALLING ME BLONDE EMMA?
VICKIE'S A PRETTY BUSY GIRL,
EM.
WHICH IS WHY
SHE HAS BESTOWED UPON US
THE HONOUR OF PLANNING
THE FLOOR OLYMPICS.
EMMA:
JUST YOU TWO?
WELL, YOU CAN HELP, TOO, EM.
SEE YOU GUYS IN CLASS.
KELLY!
GIRLFRIEND OF KELLY.
HEY, THANKS TO YOU,
NAILED THAT HISTORY PAPER
THE OTHER DAY.
C-PLUS!
THANKS, BROSEPH.
BOTH:
(WHISTLE AND MIMIC EXPLOSION)
NOW WE CAN PLAY FRISBEE
GUILT-FREE TOMORROW.
BOTH:
FRISBEEP, WHAT!
(LAUGH)
GIRLFRIEND OF KELLY?
I HAVE A NAME!
WHICH I'M SURE HE KNOWS.
HE'S A WEIRD DUDE.
I MEAN, THANK YOU CARD?
AND VICKIE ONLY KNOWS ME
AS "BLONDE EMMA".
WELL, IT CAN GET
PRETTY CONFUSING,
WHAT WITH SHORT EMMA
DOWN THE HALL
AND SPORTY EMMA UPSTAIRS...
KELLY!
I'M NOT EVEN BLONDE
ANYMORE.
I'VE BEEN HERE
FOR THREE MONTHS.
HOW CAN I PROVE THAT
I'VE GOT MORE TO OFFER
THAN CUTE HAIR
AND A CUTE BOYFRIEND?
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Oh! Oh! Oh! ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
EMMA:
MANNY'S GOT HER DRAMA POSSE,
LIBERTY'S GOT HER REZ COUNCIL
JOINER STUFF,
AND YOU?
WELL, EVERYONE LOVES YOU.
WELL, I LOVE YOU.
MAYBE YOU'VE JUST GOTTA
GET MORE INVOLVED.
YOU KNOW, CLUBS, TEAMS...
SOMETHING.
"A LITTLE SOMETHING
FOR ALL YOUR TROUBLES.
THANKS AGAIN, BROSY!"
AWWW...
CHECK IT.
YOU DON'T SMOKE, DO YOU?
SOMETIMES.
WITH DYSE AND BEX. YOU?
UM.
NOT REALLY MY THING.
WHAT?
YOU GET PARANOID, OR...
YOU DIDN'T GET THE HIGH SCHOOL
LECTURE?
SO YOU'VE NEVER TRIED IT?
LOOK. PEOPLE I'VE BEEN AROUND
THAT WERE ON POT
JUST SEEMED ANNOYING
AND GIGGLY.
I DON'T LIKE LOSING CONTROL
LIKE THAT.
WELL, MAYBE YOU SHOULD
OPEN YOURSELF UP
TO NEW EXPERIENCES.
(HUM OF CHATTER)
CLARE:
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE STILL
HAVE TO DO GYM IN HIGH SCHOOL.
WHEN WILL I USE A "LAY-UP"
IN REAL LIFE?
IT'S EASY. HERE.
PUT THE BALL UP
WITH BOTH HANDS,
THEN EXTEND YOUR RIGHT.
BEND YOUR KNEES
AND FOLLOW THROUGH.
(BALL THWUNKS THROUGH HOOP)
YOU'RE A GOOD TEACHER.
DID YOU PLAY AT YOUR
LAST SCHOOL OR SOMETHING?
CONNOR! YOUR TURN.
THINK FAST.
CONNOR:
OUCH!
THERE ARE STRANGE NOISES
COMING FROM THE STAGE.
COACH ARMSTRONG.
STRANGE NOISES
COMING FROM THE STAGE.
(SMALL, SHARP POPS)
GIRL:
(GIGGLES)
ARMSTRONG:
GET TO CLASS!
AND REESE?
CLEAN UP YOUR BEHAVIOUR,
OR NO BASKETBALL!
KC:
HEY, NEVER MIND THOSE IDIOTS.
OH, SORRY WE'RE NOT SMART
ENOUGH FOR GIFTED GYM.
DORKS.
ARMSTRONG:
KC. YOU GONNA TRY OUT
FOR THE TEAM, TOO?
I'LL TRY OUT.
(BALL CLANGS AGAINST BACKBOARD)
SURE THING, CONNOR.
YES!
ARMSTRONG:
KC?
UH, I'M NOT SURE I CAN.
I'LL HAVE TO CHECK AT HOME.
OKAY.
EVERYONE GATHER 'ROUND.
IN THE GRAND TRADITION
OF THE FLOOR OLYMPICS,
TEAMS OF TWO COMPETE AGAINST
EACH OTHER IN CRAZY GAMES
WHICH LIBERTY
WILL BE IN CHARGE OF.
(GRUNTS)
USING ONLY THESE ITEMS.
MANNY, WILL RUN
THE OPENING CEREMONIES.
LARA, YOU'LL MAKE MORE MEDALS;
KIKI, YOU'VE GOT NAME TAGS;
AND AARON,
YOU'RE IN CHARGE
OF REFRESHMENTS.
WHAT ABOUT ME?
BLONDE EMMA!
THAT'S ALL I'VE GOT,
SORRY.
BUT NO MATTER WHAT,
IT'S GONNA BE FUN.
(FORCED HALF LAUGH)
YEAH, FUN.
GUYS, I'M GONNA GO SEE
WHAT KELLY'S UP TO.
SURPRISE, SURPRISE.
(KNOCKS ON DOOR)
BECCA:
OH, HEY!
DO YOU KNOW
WHERE KELLY IS?
HE'S NOT HERE?
HE MUST STILL BE OUT
WITH DYSON.
ASK HER.
MAYBE SHE'S GOT SOME.
BECCA:
HEY.
DO YOU HAPPEN TO HAVE ANY...?
(DOOR OPENS)
(FORCED EXHALE)
HEY...
DO YOU WANNA, LIKE...
BLAZE?
(TRAFFIC WHIRS)
(TRAIN RATTLES ALONG TRACKS)
FIVE SECONDS ON THE CLOCK.
GUTHRIE DRIVES THE LANE.
LOOKS LEFT, FAKES RIGHT.
THREE, TWO...
STUDYING HARD?
THE SCHOOL CALLED.
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING,
I SWEAR.
I'VE BEEN HANGING OUT
WITH THE GOOD KIDS.
I COME STRAIGHT HOME
FROM SCHOOL...
YOU CAN TRY OUT FOR BASKETBALL
IF YOU WANT.
REALLY?
COACH ARMSTRONG SAID HE SEES
REAL POTENTIAL IN YOU.
SAID HE THINKS
YOU'RE A LEADER, HM.
I KNOW IT'S A BIG DEAL
TO SIGN OUT
FOR ALL THE GAMES
AND PRACTICES,
BUT I'LL BE SO GOOD.
YES. YES.
YOU'LL BE ON
YOUR BEST BEHAVIOUR.
BECAUSE IF YOU GO BACK
TO YOUR OLD WAYS?
I WON'T. I PROMISE.
YOU KNOW THE JUDGE'S
POSITION ON THIS:
ANY NEW VIOLENT INCIDENTS?
YOU FIND YOURSELF A NEW HOME
IN JUVIE.
YES!
(METAL DOOR SQUEAKS OPEN)
EMMA:
IS THAT IT?
GUYS, I DON'T FEEL ANYTHING.
I FEEL SOMETHING -
SICK!
EXCUSE ME.
OH NO.
AM I GONNA BE ILL?
NAH.
SHE ALWAYS SICK AT FIRST.
SHE'S A LIGHTWEIGHT.
EMMA:
AH, I DON'T THINK
IT'S WORKING FOR ME.
NO. MAYBE I DIDN'T
SMOKE ENOUGH.
OH! OH! DID I JUST
SAY THAT OUT LOUD?
OH MY GOSH.
AM I TALKING LIKE SO LOUD?
OH, I AM.
COME ON.
WE SHOULD GO BACK OUTSIDE.
WE'RE SO GONNA GET CAUGHT.
YOU'RE BEING PARANOID.
NO.
YES.
NO, I'M ECHOING.
NOT REALLY.
LISTEN:
ECHO! ECHO! ECHO!
ECHO...
WHO KNEW BLONDE EMMA
WAS SO FUNNY?
BE MY TEAMMATE
FOR THE FLOOR OLYMPICS.
IT'S TOTALLY LAME,
BUT WITH YOU, IT'D BE FUN.
YES!
BECCA:
EXCEPT,
YOU NEED A NEW NICKNAME.
BLAZE!
YEAH, BLAZE.
NICE!
(BALL PATTERS HEAVILY)
KIDS:
(SNICKERING)
ARMSTRONG:
OKAY, LET'S SEE
SOME GOOD D NOW.
(BALL PATTERS HEAVILY)
(KC THUDS DOWN HARD,
KIDS GASP)
REESE:
AW, GONNA FIGHT BACK,
BRAINIAC?
COME ON.
THAT WAS JUST A LOVE TAP.
ARMSTRONG:
OKAY, GUYS.
THAT'S ENOUGH. THAT'S ENOUGH.
(FRUSTRATED CRY)
(GYM DOOR CLOSES)
HEY.
ARE YOU AWAKE?
(SLEEPY MOAN)
MMMM...
SO...
I SORT OF BORROWED
YOUR JOINT LAST NIGHT.
WHERE DOES DYSON
GET HIS POT?
GOOD MORNING TO YOU, TOO.
(HALF LAUGHS)
I SMOKED IT WITH BECCA
AND SHE THOUGHT
I WAS HILARIOUS.
SO I'M THINKING,
GET SOME POT,
SHARE THE WEALTH
FOR THE FLOOR OLYMPICS.
AND SHOW EVERYBODY JUST
HOW INTERESTING I CAN BE.
BUT YOU CAN'T SMOKE IN REZ.
THEN NO SMOKING.
I'LL BAKE WEED BROWNIES.
THAT'S SOMETHING YOU CAN DO,
RIGHT?
I GUESS.
(MARCHING BAND MUSIC PLAYS,
LIVELY CHATTER OF STUDENTS)
LET THE GAMES BEGIN!
ALL:
(EXCITED APPLAUSE AND CHEERS)
BLAZE.
PERFECT.
LET THE GAMES BEGIN
INDEED.
MMM-MMM-MMM.
CHEERS.
MMM.
WEED BROWNIE.
YOU WANT ONE?
(EXCITED)
OH...
THE TASTIEST OF TREATS.
♪ I was so amazed ♪
♪ And wondered
what you heard ♪
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
♪ Well, I was so amazed ♪
♪ And wondered
what you heard ♪
♪ When you slip
from the window ♪
♪ And split your head
wide open ♪
♪ Could you hear the silence ♪
♪ That fell upon us there ♪
♪ I think we all prayed ♪
♪ Didn't want it that way ♪
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
♪ Well, I think we are afraid ♪
♪ 'Cause we didn't
want it that way ♪
(EXCITED CHEERS AND HOLLERS)
DYSON:
AND THE JUDGES SAY...
NINE!
NINE-POINT-FIVE.
EMMA:
AND... AVACADO.
BECCA: (LAUGHS)
YOU ARE THE FUNNIEST!
(LAUGHING)
THANK YOU.
♪ And I'll be upfront
with you ♪
(GIGGLING AND LAUGHTER)
PASSING OUT WEED BROWNIES?
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
WELL MOSTLY,
I WAS JUST LAUGHING.
LOOK, EVERYONE HAD
A GREAT TIME.
YOU'RE JUST JEALOUS
THAT I MADE IT HAPPEN.
JEALOUS?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
DON'T LISTEN TO SOBERTY.
WHAT YOU DID TONIGHT WAS RAD
IN A BIG-STYLE WAY, BLAZE.
(CHAIR AND TABLE GRIND)
KELLY AND EMMA:
(LAUGH)
NICE JOB, BLAZE.
EVERYONE KNOWS
WHO YOU ARE NOW.
YEAH. AND I GOT MY TEAMMATE
TO THANK FOR IT.
THANK-YOU SEXY BEXY?
OOH...
NOT SO SEXY BEXY.
YOU THINK SHE'S GONNA
BE ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, MAN.
SHE JUST NEEDS
TO SLEEP IT OFF.
YEAH. THERE YOU GO.
(STRETCHING GRUNT)
LET'S GO TO BED.
(STREETCARS RATTLE,
LOW HUM OF TRAFFIC)
BRANDON:
HEY, K,
YOU HAVE A GUEST.
HOW DID YOU FIND ME HERE?
WELL, I GOT YOUR NUMBER
OFF THE SIGN UP SHEET.
THEN, I DID A REVERSE
LOOK UP ON-LINE.
THEN I WALKED
TO THIS ADDRESS.
THEN THAT MAN LET ME IN.
BUT WHY?
YOU WERE WEIRD AT TRY-OUTS.
I WAS WORRIED.
THIS IS WHAT FRIENDS DO.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY.
NO MORE TRY-OUT WEIRDNESS.
I'M QUITTING.
WHAT?!
BECAUSE THAT REESE KID'S
A JERK?
IT'S NONE
OF YOUR BUSINESS WHY.
HAVE FUN TOMORROW.
AND CONNOR?
SWEAR YOU WON'T TELL ANYONE
WHERE I LIVE.
SWEAR.
OKAY, I WON'T.
BUT YOU CAN'T
QUIT BASKETBALL...
YOU'RE MY ONLY FRIEND
AT THE TRY-OUTS.
FINE, I'LL BE THERE.
JUST... GO.
(AMBULANCE SIRENS WAIL)
PARAMEDIC:
CAN YOU JUST GIVE US
SOME ROOM HERE, GUYS, PLEASE?
GIRL 1:
WHAT'S GOING ON?
GIRL 2:
SHE DIED.
GIRL 1:
DOES ANYONE KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED?
STUDENTS:
(OVERLAP OF CONCERNED CHATTER)
WHAT'S GOING ON?
IT'S BECCA.
I THOUGHT SHE JUST NEEDED
TO SLEEP IT OFF.
I GUESS WE WERE WRONG.
WHAT IF THE DRUGS WERE LACED?
I GAVE THEM TO HER.
IT'S- IT'S GONNA BE FINE.
(DIN OF CHATTER)
(CAR WHIRS BY)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
HOW DO YOU DO GYM
AND TRY-OUTS EVERYDAY?
MY ARMS ARE KILLING ME.
GUESS I'M A MODERN-DAY
HERCULES.
CHECK OUT MY SUPER-HUMAN
STRENGTH.
REESE:
HEY, BRAINIAC,
A LITTLE BIRDIE TOLD ME
WHAT A REAL BAD-ASS YOU ARE.
THAT YOU LIVE
IN THAT GROUP HOME...
FOUND OUT WHY, TOO.
YOU AND YOUR BUDS
STEAL A CAR?
KC:
SHUT UP!
HEY MAN, RESPECT.
WOULDN'T WANT YOU
TO TAKE OUT MY LEGS.
I NEED 'EM FOR BASKETBALL.
CONNOR IS SO DEAD.
REMEMBER, GUYS,
CHECK FOR MEDIC ALERT
BRACELETS.
BECCA WAS IN A DIABETIC COMA
THAT COULD'VE BEEN AVOIDED.
HER MOM SAID SHE HASN'T HAD
AN INSULIN PROBLEM IN YEARS.
WELL, IS SHE GONNA BE OKAY?
SHE'S CONSCIOUS,
BUT SHE'LL BE IN THE HOSPITAL
FOR A FEW DAYS
FOR TESTS AND OBSERVATION.
FROM WHAT I HEAR?
THE CULPRIT WAS MARIJUANA
BROWNIES.
IF SHE HADN'T INGESTED THEM,
SHE NEVER WOULD'VE FORGOTTEN
HER INSULIN.
REMEMBER, ANYONE CAUGHT
WITH ILLEGAL SUBSTANCES
IN THEIR ROOM
OR ON THEIR PERSON
WILL BE REMOVED
FROM RESIDENCE IMMEDIATELY.
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
OH MAN.
THAT'S HEAVY.
AH...
PROBABLY SHOULD DITCH
THE REST OF THE GOODS.
WELL, BECCA'S GONNA BE OKAY.
STILL.
IF WE WEREN'T STONED,
IT NEVER WOULDA HAPPENED.
(KC'S BAG THUMPS DOWN)
DID YOU TELL REESE
WHERE I LIVE?
WHAT? NO.
THEN, HOW DID HE KNOW?
I LOOKED THAT PLACE UP.
WHERE YOU LIVE?
YOU'VE GOTTA DO BAD STUFF
TO LIVE THERE.
I THOUGHT
IT WOULD SCARE REESE.
BUT YOU SWORE
YOU WOULDN'T TELL.
NOW EVERYONE KNOWS.
I THOUGHT IT WOULD HELP.
WHAT DOES IT MATTER
IF PEOPLE KNOW WHERE YOU LIVE?
I DON'T WANT THEM TO KNOW
WHY I LIVE THERE.
THEY'LL THINK
I'M A "BAD KID".
BUT YOU'RE NOT.
TELL THAT TO EVERYONE ELSE.
MY OLD SCHOOL.
MY FOSTER PARENTS.
THE JUDGE.
AND NOW THANKS TO YOU,
EVERYONE AT DEGRASSI.
I DON'T THINK THAT.
AND YOUR FRIENDS WON'T
EITHER.
WE KNOW YOU.
YOU SAY THAT NOW.
BUT WHEN PEOPLE FIND OUT?
THEY JUST WRITE ME OFF.
(DOOR OPENS)
HEY.
DID YOU HEAR ABOUT BECCA?
YEAH MAN, HARSH BUZZ.
I DITCHED MY STASH
AS SOON AS I HEARD THE NARCS
WERE DOING SEARCHES.
NARCS?
WELL, CAMPUS COPS.
LOOKING FOR BECCA'S HOOK UP.
THEY ROLLED MY ROOM.
DO YOU THINK THEY KNOW
ABOUT ME?
I DON'T KNOW, BLAZE.
BLAZE...
CRAP!
(PHONE BEEPS AND SPEED DIALS)
KELLY, ARE YOU IN THE ROOM?
KELLY:
EM, WHAT'S UP?
I DIDN'T GET RID OF IT.
THERE'S STILL BROWNIES
AND WEED IN THE ROOM.
THEY'RE DOING SEARCHES!
CAMPUS SECURITY:
THIS WAY?
KELLY:
UNGH!
VICKIE:
YOU NEED TO COME WITH ME.
SORRY, KEL.
EMMA:
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
MANNY:
KELLY'S STILL NOT BACK.
WE'RE ALL GETTING KICKED OUT.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO SLEEP
ON THE STREETS.
THERE GOES LAW SCHOOL.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU PUT US ALL AT RISK.
EMMA:
LOOK.
NO NOBODY'S SLEEPING
ON THE STREETS
OR GETTING KICKED OUT
OF LAW SCHOOL.
THIS IS MY FAULT.
I'LL TELL THEM.
PA ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION, STUDENTS,
THIS IS A REMINDER
THAT THE SOUTH SIDE
OF THE PARKING LOT
IS FOR TEACHERS ONLY,
ANY STUDENTS CARS
WILL BE TOWED.
(HUM OF CHATTER)
SO, HOW WAS THE LAST TRY-OUT?
KC:
DECENT.
I THINK I'LL MAKE IT.
DID YOU REALLY DO
WHAT REESE SAID?
MY FRIENDS AND I
FROM MY LAST SCHOOL...
WE USED TO FIND INTERESTING
WAYS TO PASS THE TIME.
LIKE STEALING CARS?
LIKE LOTS OF THINGS
YOU DON'T WANNA KNOW ABOUT.
WHY CAN'T YOU TALK TO ME
ABOUT THIS?
YOU HAD THIS IDEA OF ME.
THAT I'M A GOOD GUY.
I LIKED IT.
NOW CONNOR WENT
AND RUINED IT.
CONNOR:
HEY!
HEY, WE MADE THE TEAM!
BOTH OF US!
KC! YOU DIDN'T HIT HIM,
DID YOU?
NO, NO-NO-NO.
I TOOK AN ELBOW IN PRACTICE.
I JUST LOVE BASKETBALL.
CLARE:
KC, WAIT!
I'M SORRY.
YOU ARE A GOOD GUY.
AND I KNOW THAT.
DO YOU WANNA GO CELEBRATE
MAKING THE TEAM?
THANKS, BUT I PROBABLY
SHOULD GET RIGHT HOME.
KICKED OUT OF REZ.
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
I CAN GO BACK TO VICKIE
AND COME CLEAN.
I'M THE REASON
YOU GOT CAUGHT.
THEY FOUND THE DRUGS ON ME.
ZERO TOLERANCE.
WE'D BOTH GET KICKED OUT.
BESIDES, YOU AND YOUR GIRLS
BELONG TOGETHER.
YEAH...
IF THEY EVER FORGIVE ME.
HEY.
DO YOU FORGIVE ME?
(HEAVY EXHALE)
ON THE BRIGHT SIDE?
YOU CAN EXPLORE REZ LIFE
WITHOUT BEING MY APPENDAGE.
THIS ISN'T HOW I WANTED THAT
TO HAPPEN.
YEAH...
(SIGHS)
SEE YOU IN CLASS.
MM-HM.
(DIN OF CHATTER)
TOO BAD.
(HUM OF LIVELY CHATTER)