I CAN'T BELIEVE
THE BUS WAS STOLEN.
I HAD THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS
OF DESIGNER CLOTHES
IN THOSE BAGS.
PETER:
YEAH, THOSE WOULD COME IN HANDY
ON A ROAD TRIP.
MY STICKERS...
ALL GONE.
JAY:
WE'LL CHECK INTO A MOTEL
FOR THE NIGHT
AND WE'LL FIGURE OUT
WHAT TO DO.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
HELLO?
OH, HI.
YEAH, WE'RE CLOSE.
WE JUST RAN INTO A GLITCH.
YOU'RE KIDDING!
WELL...
WELL, THAT'S GREAT!
I'M NOT REALLY SURE
WHERE WE ARE RIGHT NOW,
BUT DON'T WORRY,
I CAN MAKE MY OWN WAY THERE.
THANKS. I PROMISE YOU,
I WON'T LET YOU DOWN THIS TIME.
OKAY.
WE GOTTA GO!
PETER:
THE BUS IS GONE,
REMEMBER?
MANNY:
YEAH, WELL,
PAIGE IS OFF THE MOVIE.
THAT WAS MEWES;
HE FIRED HER
AND HE WANTS ME
TO PLAY TRIXIE!
THAT'S GREAT, BOO.
BUT BE REASONABLE.
YOU'RE GONNA WALK
ALL THE WAY TO HOLLYWOOD?
WHATEVER IT TAKES!
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Oh! Oh! Oh! ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
MEWES:
I DON'T KNOW, SIR.
NONE OF THEM ARE MANNY.
AND MANNY'S LOST SOMEWHERE.
WHAT IF SHE DOESN'T MAKE IT?
YOU GOTTA FIND A TRIXIE
THAT WORKS FOR YOU, OKAY?
RIGHT IN HERE,
AND YOU KNOW WHO THAT IS.
I THINK YOU SHOULD
FOLLOW YOUR HEART.
I DON'T THINK YOU SHOULD
SELL OUT THIS QUICKLY.
TOOK ME YEARS, DUDE,
YEARS.
THAT'S TRUE.
THANKS, SIR.
KEVIN:
YEAH.
ROBBIE:
PAIGE TOLD ME WHAT HAPPENED.
NOW LET'S NOT OVERREACT.
YOU INSISTED I USE HER,
AND I TRIED.
BUT NOT ONLY
IS SHE A BAD ACTRESS,
SHE HAS A BAD ATTITUDE.
COME ON.
WORK WITH ME HERE.
PAIGE IS PREPARED
TO ACCEPT AN APOLOGY.
YOU NEED ME.
ROBBIE:
THIS LITTLE GIRL
IS CREATING SOME GOOD BUZZ.
AND DON'T FORGET...
WE OPTIONED YOUR STORY.
THE STUDIO OWNS
"MEWESICAL HIGH."
LOOK, I'M STILL DIRECTOR
AND I'M RECASTING.
I WANT MANNY SANTOS.
MANNY SANTOS?!
PLEASE!
YOU'RE KIDDING!
THAT GIRL WITH
THE TERRIBLE AUDITION TAPE?
YOU CAN'T HAVE MANNY.
YOU CAN HAVE PAIGE.
SHE'S NOT MY TRIXIE.
THEN YOU'RE FIRED.
FIRED? I QUIT!
DON'T WORRY,
HE DOESN'T MEAN IT.
KEVIN:
OH, I THINK HE DOES, HON.
I THINK HE DOES.
(CROWS CAW)
SO HOW LONG ARE YOU
GONNA STAY MAD AT ME?
UNTIL WE GET TO HOLLYWOOD.
YOU KNOW, WE'RE NOT GONNA WALK
ALL THE WAY THERE IN TIME!
ARE YOU INSANE?
YES, I'M INSANE!
WITH RAGE, TOWARDS YOU!
I HAVE TO GET THAT PART.
AND HOW COULD
I POSSIBLY KNOW
THAT SOMEONE WOULD WANNA
STEAL A SCHOOL BUS?
HOW COULD YOU POSSIBLY
NOT KNOW
THAT LEAVING THE KEYS
IN THE IGNITION
WAS A STUPID IDEA!
PETER:
GUYS!
JAY AND MANNY:
WHAT?!
LOOK OVER THERE!
I HAVE A FIX
FOR OUR PETITE PROBLEME;
A LIST OF REALLY GOOD
DIRECTORS.
ANY OF THEM WOULD BE PERFECT
FOR "MEWESICAL HIGH."
HOW CAN WE POSSIBLY MAKE
A MOVIE ABOUT MEWES' LIFE
WITHOUT MEWEWS?
BUT...
YOU SAID HE NEEDED ME.
YOU FIRED HIM.
IT WAS A BLUFF!
I THOUGHT HE'D CAVE
AND WE'D JUST MAKE
THE MOVIE.
BUT YOU PISSED HIM OFF,
AND NOW YOU'VE GOTTEN
YOURSELF A DIVA REP.
WHAT?!
YOU DIDN'T SEE PEREZ' BLOG
TODAY?
NO ONE WILL WORK
WITH YOU NOW.
I THOUGHT PEREZ LOVED ME?
THINGS CHANGE FAST
AROUND HERE.
YOU CAN KEEP THE HOUSE
FOR ONE MORE WEEK.
ENJOY THE POOL.
(LIGHTS CLICK OFF)
CRAIG:
HEY, I'LL STAY WITH ELLIE.
YOU BETTER GET GOING.
THANKS.
SEE YA.
(EXHALES)
I'M SORRY FOR ACTING LIKE
SUCH AN IDIOT LAST NIGHT.
SLEEP'S PROBABLY THE BEST THING
RIGHT NOW.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I WAS THINKING.
I WASN'T...
(HALF LAUGHS)
TRYING TO KILL MYSELF.
CRAIG:
I KNOW.
MARCO, UM...
HE TOLD ME ABOUT YOUR DAD.
I SHOULD PROBABLY GO SEE HIM,
RIGHT?
WHEN YOU'RE READY.
IT'S JUST...
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN ABLE
TO FIX THINGS.
YOU KNOW, LIKE...
MY MOM.
(TEARY BREATH)
AND THEN YOU.
MY DAD WATCHED
HIS SOLDIERS DIE.
HE'S GOT POST TRAUMATIC
STRESS DISORDER
AND...
I KNOW I CAN'T FIX THAT.
NO ONE EXPECTS YOU TO.
CRAIG:
LOOK, AFTER YOU SLEEP,
I'LL MAKE YOU SOME EGGS.
IF YOU SURVIVE THAT,
WE'LL TAKE THE NEXT STEP.
OKAY?
OKAY.
(HUM OF CHATTER)
YOU NEED TO PRINT
A RETRACTION.
DO I KNOW YOU?
PAIGE MICHALCHUK.
YOU WROTE THAT "MEWESICAL HIGH"
GOT CANCELLED
BECAUSE I WAS BEING A DIVA.
RIGHT, I REMEMBER NOW.
UNKNOWN GOES BACK
TO BEING UNKNOWN.
NO.
NO-NO-NO, PLEASE.
YOU HAVE TO HELP ME!
NO ONE WILL RETURN MY CALLS.
PEREZ:
THEN DO SOMETHING INTERESTING.
MAYBE THEN I'LL WRITE ABOUT IT.
AROUND HERE,
YOU'RE ONLY AS HOT
AS YOUR LATEST SCANDAL.
HERE. AN INVITE TO
THE PREMIERE OF PINK RIFLE.
KNOCK YOURSELF OUT.
BYE.
(EXHALES IN DISBELIEF)
YES!
MIA:
(HALF LAUGHS)
I KNEW THESE $300 LEGGINGS
WERE A GOOD INVESTMENT.
PETER:
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
AN OLD TRICK
THAT MY MOM TAUGHT ME.
OUR CAR WAS ALWAYS
BREAKING DOWN.
SHOULD LAST UNTIL
THE NEXT TOWN.
'KAY, TRY IT NOW.
(IGNITION TURNS,
ENGINE RUMBLES)
MIA FIXED THE BUS!
NOW WHO'S GLAD THE GIRLFRIEND
CAME ALONG?
I'M GOING TO L.A.
YOU COMING?
♪ Well, let's not be typical ♪
♪ And do this our own way ♪
♪ And we can fight
for what we know ♪
♪ And be there to get paid ♪
♪ Well, let's just be big
and bold ♪
I'M JUST TRYING
TO BE HELPFUL.
I NEED SOMETHING TO GET
MY FACE OUT THERE TODAY.
THIS IS MY LAST CHANCE!
I'M READY
FOR MY BRAZILIAN.
PAIGE:
THAT'S IT! THANK YOU!
WHAT?
A COMMANDO SHOT!
THAT'LL DO IT!
HAILEY:
GOOD ONE.
(LAUGHS)
MARCO:
THIS IS WHAT YOU WANNA BE
FAMOUS FOR?
FLASHING YOUR BUSINESS
ALL AROUND TOWN?
UH...
I DON'T KNOW, MARCO.
WHAT ARE YOU FAMOUS FOR?
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
NOTHING.
PAIGE AND HAILEY:
(LAUGH)
I WAS HAPPY FOR YOU
WHEN YOU GOT THIS GIG.
YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT,
HEY, YOU'D FINALLY GROW UP.
I WAS WRONG.
YOU KNOW WHAT WOULD BE
REALLY NICE?
IF YOU HAD THE GUTS TO ACTUALLY
DO SOMETHING WITH YOUR OWN LIFE
INSTEAD OF JUST WHINING
AND JUDGING EVERYONE ELSE.
WOW.
YOU ARE STILL THE SAME
INSECURE LITTLE GIRL
THAT YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN.
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
♪♪♪
♪ Wasting away
hanging on to a feeling ♪
HEY, MEWES! YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT WE'VE BEEN THROUGH.
BUT WE'RE IN L.A.
WHERE DO WE GO?
I AM SO READY FOR THIS!
NO...
NO... NO.
I CAME ALL THIS WAY.
LOOK! A PREMIERE!
DANNY: AWESOME! SEE ANY STARS?
MANNY: DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
MANNY:
THANKS FOR CALLING.
STOP THE BUS!
I JUST SAW BEN AFFLECK!
(GASPS)
STOP THE BUS,
MAN!
STOP THE BUS.
DANNY, PETER, SAV AND MIA:
(OVERLAPPING,
AWESTRUCK CHATTER)
BUT YOUR MOVIE...
JAY, STOP THE BUS.
(CROWD CHATTERS EXCITEDLY)
(BUZZ OF EXCITED CHATTER)
PAIGE:
YOU REALLY THINK
THE PHOTOGRAPHERS'LL CATCH THIS?
HAILEY:
SURE. THERE HASN'T BEEN A GOOD
"BUSINESS SHOT" IN DAYS.
(SIGHS) IT'S NO BIGGIE.
JUST REMEMBER:
HIKE UP YOUR SKIRT,
LOOK SURPRISED
AND SLIGHTLY NAUGHTY.
WHAT AM I DOING?
HAILEY:
BEING SMART.
THIS IS YOUR LAST
A-LIST INVITE, REMEMBER.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
BOTH:
(DEEP INHALES)
(DOOR OPENS, CAMERAS FLASH,
CROWD CHEERS)
PAIGE?
MANNY?!
OHHH!
OWWW!
(SHOCKED GASPS AND LAUGHTER)
PAIGE:
(PAINED GROAN)
OH MY LEG!
(PHOTOGRAPHERS CALL FOR HAILEY)
(PAIGE GRUNTS IN PAIN,
CROWD APPLAUDS)
PAIGE?
OW! MY LEG!
IT'LL BE OKAY.
(PAINED BREATHS)
OH MY LEG.
I SHOULD PROBABLY JUST GO.
SECURITY CAN TAKE AWHILE.
YEAH.
THANKS AGAIN
FOR ALL YOUR HELP.
YOU REALLY CAME THROUGH
FOR ME.
WE'LL CALL IT EVEN.
♪ I see it in the way
you would do ♪
♪ When no one else
could ever get through ♪
♪ Holding back
'til I come around ♪
♪ Time and time again
you wait for me to come and... ♪
♪ And did you really
look my way ♪
♪ 'Cause no one could've
seen this coming ♪
♪ I would never let you down ♪
♪ If was running backwards
in full time ♪
♪ So I can and I will ♪
♪ And you'll see
your hero come a-running ♪
♪ Over and over tonight ♪
♪ And I do wanna love you ♪
♪ If you see me running back ♪
♪ And I do wanna try ♪
♪ 'Cause if falling for you,
girl, is crazy... ♪
WE'LL ALWAYS HAVE L.A.,
RIGHT?
SOMEDAY MAYBE.
♪ ...this time ♪
♪ Me, I'm used to being tired
and bloody ♪
♪ But you believed
that I could be somebody ♪
♪ You put your world
on hold for me ♪
♪ Gave away to follow failure
through the fire ♪
♪ I need you to... ♪
SO MEET ME HALFWAY.
THE STUDIO IS REALLY HOT
ON YOUR STORY
AND YOU DIRECTING IT.
LOOK, THIS ISN'T JUST A MOVIE,
DUDE.
IT'S THE STORY OF MY LIFE.
AND YOU MESSING IT UP?
I'M NOT INTERESTED.
I NEED YOU!
I EVEN FOUND YOU
A NEW TRIXIE.
MEWES:
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME.
PAIGE:
YOU NEED TO GO TO THE WINDOW.
AND YOU WANNA BRING HER BACK,
TOO, MAN?
GIVE IT UP, SUITMAN!
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
GUYS, I'M NOT HERE ABOUT ME.
YOU JUST...
YOU NEED TO COME
TO THE WINDOW, NOW!
(MANNY SINGS, STUDZ PLAYS)
TRUST ME, ROBBIE,
YOU'RE GONNA WANNA SEE THIS.
MANNY:
♪ AND STANDING ON THE STAGE
IS WHERE I BELONG ♪
♪ OH! LIFE IS A SHOW ♪
♪ SKYDIVING ABOUT TO LET GO ♪
♪ WALKING THE WIRE
WITH NOTHING BELOW ♪
♪ DON'T YOU KNOW ♪
♪ 'CAUSE LIFE IS A SHOW ♪
♪ IN EVERY SHADE
OF THE RAINBOW ♪
THAT'S MY MANNY.
DID YOU DO THIS?
TRYING TO GET AT LEAST
ONE THING RIGHT.
LOOK, I'LL DO THE MOVIE
IF MY MANNY HERE IS TRIXIE.
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE BACK
IN BUSINESS, MEWES.
MEWES:
HEY, MANNY!
YOU'RE TRIXIE!
I... I GOT THE PART?!
YOU ARE THE PART!
(LAUGHS)
♪ LET'S GO!
GO! GO! GO! ♪
♪ LIFE IS SHOW ♪
♪ LIFE IS A SHOW ♪
♪ 'CAUSE LIFE IS A SHOW ♪
♪ LIFE IS A...
LIFE IS A LIE ♪
♪ I WANNA BE IN THE SHOW ♪
♪ LIFE IS A SHOW ♪
CROWD:
(CHEERING AND APPLAUDING)
YOUR COFFEE, MR. MEWES.
BLACK. FIVE SUGARS.
PERFECT.
THANKS, DUDE.
CAN I GET YOU
ANYTHING ELSE?
I GOT ME MY TRIXIE.
I GOT MY SHOT LIST.
IT'S ALL GOOD.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
MEWSEY HAS TRIED
ALL KINDS OF STUFF
TO WIN OVER TRIXIE.
BUT HERE'S WHERE HE LETS ALL
HIS NATURAL MEWESY GOODNESS
ALL HANG OUT!
SO MANNY? MICHAEL?
ACTION!
♪ LIVING ON THE WILD SIDE ♪
♪ EVERY NIGHT ♪
♪ HANGING OUT
WITH NOTHING TO DO ♪
♪ MEANT THE WORLD WAS RIGHT ♪
MANNY AND MICHAEL:
♪ AND I WAS HOPING
THAT I CAN CHANGE YOU ♪
♪ I'D BE THE ONE TO TAME YOU ♪
♪ BUT YOU NEVER GOT CLOSE ♪
♪ BABY, YOU DIDN'T KNOW, OH! ♪
♪ YOU WERE UNTOUCHABLE ♪
♪ IMPOSSIBLE ♪
♪ YOU WERE TOO COOL ♪
♪ TOO CRIMINAL TO BELIEVE ♪
♪ YOU WERE ALWAYS
ONE SATURDAY NIGHT ♪
♪ ALWAYS ONE SATURDAY NIGHT
AWAY FROM ME ♪
♪ SATURDAY NIGHT AWAY ♪
(CRYING)
HEY, DADDY.
(SOBBING)
(ELATED BREATH)
ELLIE.
HEY.
(SOBBING)
IT'S OKAY...
ELLIE:
(SOBBING)
MANNY:
♪ YOU THOUGHT YOU OWNED IT ♪
MICHAEL:
♪ BUT THAT WAS JUST AN ACT ♪
MANNY:
♪ I THOUGHT YOU WERE
ABOVE THAT ♪
WORK FOR YOU, DUDE?
YES, SIR. IT DOES.
BOTH:
♪ WOULD WE... ♪
♪ COULD WE... ♪
♪ COME BACK?!
YEAH! ♪
♪ UNTOUCHABLE! ♪
♪ IMPOSSIBLE! ♪
MANNY:
♪ YOU WERE TOO COOL ♪
MICHAEL:
♪ TOO BEAUTIFUL TO BELIEVE ♪
♪ YOU WERE ALWAYS
ONE SATURDAY NIGHT ♪
MANNY:
♪ YOU WERE ALWAYS
ONE SATURDAY NIGHT♪
♪ ALWAYS ONE
SATURDAY NIGHT ♪
BOTH:
♪ AWAY FROM ME ♪
(SIGHS)
SO I GUESS THIS IS...
GOODBYE.
YUP.
(SIGHS)
YOU KNOW,
I LOVE YOU.
I KNOW.
WELL, THIS BUS ISN'T GONNA GET
BACK TO DEGRASSI BY ITSELF.
I'M REALLY PROUD OF YOU.
WAIT.
I'LL BE BACK
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
I'LL BE WAITING FOR YOU,
BOO.
Manny:
♪ Everything that
knocks me down ♪
♪ Is making me strong ♪
♪ And standing on this stage
is where I belong ♪
♪ Oh, life is a show ♪
♪ Skydiving about to let go ♪
HEY, GUYS.
STUDZ RULE!
GUYS:
(CHEERING AND LAUGHING)
YEAH! STUDZ!
COURTESY OF MR. MEWES,
YOUR CALL TIME FOR TOMORROW:
6 A.M. SHARP.
♪ Life is a show ♪
♪ Skydiving about to let go ♪
GUYS:
BYE JAY!
♪ Walking the world
with nothing but love ♪
♪ Don't you know! ♪
♪ Don't you know? ♪
♪ 'cause life is a show ♪
♪ In every shade
of the rainbow... ♪