SHEP:
DEGRASSI, GET READY
TO GET YOUR GROOVE ON
AT THE SWEETHEART DANCE.
OH, AND UH...
SOME GRADE NINERS WILL BE
PARTICIPATING IN BOT WARS...
ANYA:
JANE!
SHEP:
...SO PLEASE DON'T MOCK THEM.
JANE!
DELIVERY FOR YOU.
FROM SPIN.
MM.
AT LEAST SOMEONE
HAS A SWEETHEART.
HAD A SWEETHEART.
(CLEANSING BREATHS)
LOVER'S QUARREL?
HE'S JUST... UGH!
YOU KNOW? UGH!
YEAH, HOPE YOU'RE MORE
ARTICULATE
WHEN YOU DELIVER YOUR SPEECH
THIS MORNING.
I HAVE TO FINISH IT FIRST.
I SPENT ALL NIGHT
TRYING TO WRITE
ABOUT BEING A GIRL
ON A GUY'S TEAM
AND ALL I COULD THINK ABOUT
WAS A GUY.
SO SPINNER LIED
ABOUT POLICE COLLEGE?
YEAH, AND THEN SHOWED UP
DRUNK AT MY HOUSE
AND WOKE UP MY MOM.
SERIOUSLY?
I LOVE SPIN,
BUT SOMETIMES...
SOMETIMES LOVE
JUST AIN'T ENOUGH?
SHEP:
OH.
THERE'S MY FAVOURITE
WIDE RECEIVER.
YOU WON'T FORGET TO MENTION ME
IN YOUR SPEECH, RIGHT?
IF YOU'D JUST LET ME ON THE TEAM
IN THE FIRST PLACE,
I'D HAVE NOTHING
TO TALK ABOUT.
CUTE.
DON'T SAY THAT.
SHEP AND DANNY:
(CHUCKLE)
WHAT AM I GONNA DO,
MAN?
SPINNER CAN WAIT.
YOUR SPEECH CAN'T.
I'LL HELP YOU WRITE IT
ON THE WAY TO THE SYMPOSIUM.
IT'LL ALL WORK OUT.
I PROMISE.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Oh! Oh! Oh! ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
HI.
SORRY WE'RE LATE.
SO, WE'LL JUST HEAD IN
AND UH, FIND OUR SEATS.
UH, NO YOU WON'T.
THE SYMPOSIUM'S
ALREADY STARTED.
NO LATE COMERS.
DO YOU REALLY WANNA BE
THE MORON THAT DOESN'T LET...
BARRY COHEN IN?
BARRY COHEN?
FROM SASKATCHEWAN?
I'VE READ YOUR BOOK.
MY-MY BOOK?
REALLY?
I THOUGHT YOU MISSED
YOUR FLIGHT.
BELIEVE ME,
BARRY COHEN WOULD DO ANYTHING
TO BE AT THIS SYMPOSIUM.
WELL...
I WILL LET THEM KNOW
YOU'RE HERE.
ANY WORDS OF ADVICE?
DON'T BE A BLOCKHEAD.
SOME OF US ARE STILL IN SCHOOL,
SO I GOTTA HEAD BACK.
(DEEP, PREPARATORY BREATH)
I WANTED TO PLAY FOOTBALL.
I DIDN'T WANNA BE A HERO.
BUT ANYONE WHO ACTIVELY PURSUES
THEIR GOALS IN LIFE
DESPITE OPPOSITION
BECOMES ONE.
SOMETIMES, UM, THINGS HAPPEN
AND YOU FIND THAT
YOU HAVE TO TAKE A STAND,
AND PEOPLE AROUND YOU
MAKE THAT POSSIBLE.
SOME FELLOW STUDENTS
LET ME KNOW
THAT THEY LOOKED UP TO ME...
CROWD:
(CHEERING WILDLY)
WELCOME TO BOT WARS:
HIGH SCHOOL EDITION.
READY FOR BATTLE?
CROWD:
(CHEERS AND WHISTLES)
OKAY, WE'RE DONE
UNLOADING THE ROBOT.
ARE YOU READY TO GO SHOW IT
TO THE JUDGES?
TOBY: ONCE YOUR BOT
HAS BEEN EVALUATED...
HEY.
HI.
TOBY:
SO ROBOTEERS,
LET'S GET INTO...
CLARE,
ARE YOU WITH US HERE?
CLARE AND I NEED A MOMENT
TO DISCUSS STRATEGY.
THOUGHT WE WEREN'T
LETTING HORMONES
GET IN THE WAY
OF BOT WARS?
IT'S COMPLICATED.
I'LL SIMPLIFY:
YOU LIKE KC.
KC LIKES YOU.
GO TO THE DANCE WITH HIM.
BUT CONNOR...
WILL GET OVER IT.
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
I REANALYZED
THE DANCE SITUATION
AND...
DECIDED THAT IT WOULDN'T BE
COMPLETELY HORRIBLE
TO GO WITH YOU.
YOU'RE ASSUMING
I STILL WANNA GO WITH YOU.
(HALF LAUGHS)
YOU'RE SO...
CHARMING?
JOHNNY DIMARCO
IS INTO ROBOTS?
I HAVE A BROTHER
IN THE COMPETITION.
SO YOU HAVE A NINER BROTHER
YOU'RE NOT EMBARRASSED
TO BE SEEN WITH?
IT'S JUST...
IT'S JUST WEIRD
TO LIKE A NINER.
YOU LIKE ME?
HEH.
ENOUGH TO GO
TO THE DANCE?
I DON'T DO DANCES,
AND I ESPECIALLY DON'T DO THEM
WITH THE NINERS.
WELL, I'M GOING
AND I'M GONNA LOOK HOT.
SO IF YOU SKIP OUT?
YOUR LOSS.
(HUM OF CHATTER)
AN ALL NIGHT
HORROR MARATHON?
INTERESTING CHOICE
FOR A FIRST DATE.
NEXT TO A ZOMBIE
OR A WEREWOLF,
I'M BOUND
TO LOOK GOOD.
SO...
THIS IS OUR ROOM.
AND MANNY AND LIBERTY
AGREED TO BE ELSEWHERE.
DO YOU ALWAYS INVITE GUYS IN
ON THE FIRST DATE?
WELL...
THERE'S A COUCH
IN THE COMMON ROOM.
OF COURSE,
IT WOULD BE RUDE
TO KICK YOU OUT
OF YOUR OWN ROOM.
GWYNETH:
KELLY.
GWYNETH?
CAN WE TALK?
YEAH.
YEAH,
LET'S GO GET A COFFEE.
I WILL BE...
RIGHT BACK.
I'LL BE WAITING.
JANE:
I WOULDN'T BE HERE TODAY,
IF ONE PERSON HADN'T PUSHED ME
TO SUCCEED.
MY COACH, PRINCIPAL SHEPPARD.
THANK YOU.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDS)
GIRL'S GOT
A SHORT-TERM MEMORY.
NO ONE'S PERFECT, DUDE.
JANE:
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE,
SPINNER?
I KNOW I MESSED UP
YESTERDAY.
BUT I LEARNED MY LESSON.
I AM NEVER EVER
GONNA LIE TO YOU AGAIN.
I PROMISE...
JASON:
NEXT UP, WE HAVE BARRY COHEN
DISCUSSING THE CHALLENGES
OF BEING A HIGH SCHOOL FARMER.
I THOUGHT WE HAD MISSED HIM,
BUT HE SHOWED.
BARRY?
UH, BARRY?
WE'RE WAITIN' ON YOU.
ATTENDEES:
(APPLAUDING)
(TRAFFIC WHIRS)
TOBY:
BATTLING IT OUT
WITH REIGNING CHAMPION,
GOVERNOR SIMCOE SYMBOTICS,
IS MY ALMA MATER,
DEGRASSI.
AUDIENCE:
(APPLAUDS AND CHEERS)
REMEMBER ALL THE RULES:
PUT YOUR BALL OVER THE BEAM
FOR 8 POINTS.
TEAM WITH THE MOST POINTS WINS.
LET'S SHOW EVERYONE
WHAT DEGRASSI'S MADE OF.
GOOD LUCK.
THANKS.
ALLI:
EW, CONNOR.
DON'T BE DISGUSTING.
BUT KC SQUEEZED
CLARE'S HAND.
SHE'S ALSO GOING
TO THE DANCE WITH HIM.
AND DON'T YOU DARE
ASK ME.
ARE YOU GOING TO THE DANCE
WITH KC?
NOT NOW, CONNOR.
THE MATCH
IS ABOUT TO START.
BUT I ASKED YOU,
AND I WAS YOUR FRIEND FIRST.
AND I'M WAY BETTER AT ROBOTS
THAN KC.
JUST...JUST GO BACK
TO YOUR SPOT.
WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT
AFTER THE ROUND.
CROWD:
(CHEERING AND APPLAUDING)
TOBY:
READY TEAMS?
FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO...
AND GO!
(GAME BUZZER BUZZES)
(ROBOTS WHIR)
KIDS:
(CHEER)
♪ Good enough for now ♪
♪ Having any other ♪
♪ Just good enough for now ♪
♪ Good enough for now ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
(ALARM BUZZES)
CROWD:
(CHEERS)
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM,
DUDE?
TOBY:
AND IT'S 32 TO NOTHING
FOR GOVERNOR SIMCOE.
EVEN IF THEY COULD BRING
THEIR ROBOTS BACK TO LIFE,
I DOUBT DEGRASSI
HAS A CHANCE HERE.
LET'S HOPE THEY DO BETTER
IN THE NEXT ROUND.
MAYBE KELLY GOT IN
AN ACCIDENT, OR...
HEY, WE WERE JUST
IN THE COFFEE SHOP TALKING
AND OOPS,
OUR TONGUES COLLIDED.
IT'S OBVIOUS THEIR BREAK UP
TURNED INTO A MAKE-UP.
I'M OFF.
TO WHERE?
HOME FOR THE WEEKEND.
I DON'T WANT TO BE HERE
WHEN KELLY AND GWYNETH
GET BACK.
(EXHALES FORCEFULLY)
COFFEE ISN'T SOMETHING
THAT WE FARM IN CANADA.
BUT MILK IS.
AND MILK IS USED IN COFFEE.
WE'RE SEEING A BIGGER
DEMAND FOR IT,
UH, IN URBAN MARKETS,
ESPECIALLY FROM COFFEE SHOPS.
(SCOFFS)
WHO THOUGHT SPINNER
COULD HANDLE HIMSELF
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS?
SPINNER:
...PRODUCTION IN CANADA.
THANK YOU.
ATTENDEES:
(APPLAUDING)
THANK YOU, BARRY,
FOR THAT COMPELLING TALE
OF LIFE ON A FARM.
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE
YOU'D LIKE TO SAY?
SPINNER:
YEAH.
JANE, YOU WANTED ME TO HAVE
A PLAN FOR THE FUTURE, RIGHT?
I DO.
WILL YOU MARRY ME?
ATTENDEES:
OOH! (WHISTLE)
(CHANTING) BARRY.
JANE AND BARRY.
ALL: (CHANT AND CLAP)
JANE AND BARRY,
JANE AND BARRY.
HOW COULD YOU DO THAT?!
TELL YOU I WANNA SPEND
THE REST OF MY LIFE WITH YOU?
GEE, I'M SORRY.
TODAY WAS IMPORTANT.
IT COULD'VE OPENED DOORS
FOR ME.
IF YOUR STUPID BOYFRIEND
HADN'T SCREWED IT UP AGAIN,
RIGHT?
I'M TALKING ABOUT
HOW IMPORTANT IT IS
FOR WOMEN TO SUCCEED
ON THEIR OWN
AND THEN YOU SWEEP IN
AND SAY LET'S GET HITCHED!
DID YOU EVEN LISTEN
TO MY SPEECH?
YEAH.
DIDN'T THANK ME.
FOR WHAT?
FOR RUINING MY BIG DAY?
YOU WANT TIME TO THINK?
TAKE ALL THE TIME
YOU WANT.
I AM DONE.
IT'S PROBABLY FOR THE BEST,
DUDE.
OKAY.
SHEP:
I HEARD I ALREADY GOT
MY SHOUT-OUT IN YOUR SPEECH,
HUH?
YOU NEED YOUR HEAD CHECKED.
I DIDN'T GET HIT
THAT HARD.
THEN HOW DO YOU EXPLAIN
THE MEMORY LOSS?
GIRL WANTS ON
THE FOOTBALL TEAM.
GUYS PLAY DIRTY
TO GET HER OFF.
PRINCIPAL TURNS
A BLIND EYE.
ONE GUY'S THERE FOR YOU
THROUGH IT ALL.
HE LIED TO ME
ABOUT POLICE COLLEGE,
AND PROPOSED TO ME
IN FRONT OF A HUNDRED PEOPLE.
YOU DON'T WANT TO MARRY HIM?
I GET THAT.
BUT GIVE THE DUDE HIS DUE -
YOU SHOULD'VE THANKED HIM.
SHEP:
OKAY, TEAM.
LISTEN UP.
GET YOURSELVES CLEANED UP
AND GET READY
TO GET YOUR DANCE ON.
AND REMEMBER, EVERY GIRL
LOVES A FOOTBALL PLAYER.
CROWD:
(CHEERING)
TOBY:
AFTER TEN HOURS OF BATTLING,
DEGRASSI HAS FOUGHT BACK
FOR A CHANCE AT THE PODIUM.
AND THINGS ARE GETTING TENSE
IN THE THIRD PLACE BATTLE.
ST. GEORGE AND DEGRASSI
ARE TRULY FIGHTING
TO THE DEATH.
25 SECONDS LEFT, FOLKS.
(ROBOTS WHIR)
SO YOU'RE REALLY NOT GOING
TO THE DANCE WITH KC?
YOU'RE ASKING ME
ABOUT THE DANCE?
NOW? WE'RE FIGHTING
FOR OUR LIVES HERE.
(ROBOTS WHIR)
SHOOT!
(GAME BUZZER BUZZES)
CROWD:
(CHEERING WILDLY)
TOBY:
THREE, TWO, ONE...
AND IT'S OVER!
DEGRASSI WINS THIRD PLACE.
WAY TO MAKE ME PROUD!
(CHEERING WILDLY)
PANTHRO: (ROBOT VOICE)
CLARE, WILL YOU GO TO THE DANCE
WITH CONNOR?
ALL: (CHANT AND CLAP)
DANCE! DANCE! DANCE! DANCE!
(NERVOUSLY)
OKAY.
(DOOR OPENS)
WHERE'S EMMA?
YOU GONNA BREAK IT
TO HER NICELY?
BREAK WHAT?
YOU AND GWYNETH,
BACK TOGETHER.
WE'RE NOT.
I JUST SPENT THE LAST 8 HOURS
TELLING HER THAT.
OKAY, WELL,
EM WAS IMAGINING
EVERYTHING BUT.
I WAS JUST TRYING TO BE
A GOOD GUY.
WELL,
YOU WEREN'T TO HER.
'KAY, YOU CAN'T HAVE
EVERYONE LIKE YOU
ALL THE TIME.
SOMETIMES YOU HAVE
TO CHOOSE
AND THIS TIME,
YOU CHOSE WRONG.
ANYA:
TICKET PLEASE.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE
I'M NOT THE ONLY ONE HERE
FORCED TO GO SOLO.
(SLOW MUSIC PLAYS)
♪ And say like any other ♪
♪ I can taste her warm kiss
of summer... ♪
AREN'T WE SUPPOSED TO DANCE?
THEORETICALLY, YES,
BUT...
OKAY.
♪ Brace yourself ♪
♪ Here come the angels ♪
BRUCE:
(LAUGHS) THAT...
IS HOW YOU SLOW DANCE, KIDS.
EXCUSE ME.
♪ Brace yourself ♪
♪ Here come the angels ♪
(MUSIC BECOMES MUTED)
(DOOR SHUTS)
HAVING FUN
WITH CONNOR?
HE'S...
I WANTED TO GO WITH YOU.
PROVE IT...
BY DANCING WITH ME.
♪ ...is this the last ride
with you ♪
♪ Brace yourself ♪
♪ Here come the angels ♪
CONNOR:
CLARE!
YOU'RE MY DATE TO THE DANCE!
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO DANCE
WITH ME.
CLARE:
CONNOR!
(DOOR OPENS,
FOOTSTEPS CLACK AS CLAIRE RUNS)
(GUITAR PLAYS)
KELLY: (SINGING)
♪ MY BONNIE LIES
OVER THE OCEAN ♪
♪ MY BONNIE LIES OVER THE SEA ♪
♪ MY BONNIE LIES
OVER THE OCEAN ♪
♪ OH, BRING BACK
MY EMMA TO ME ♪
I DIDN'T DATE YOU
'CAUSE I WAS TRYING
TO BE A GOOD GUY.
I'M DONE BEING A GOOD GUY.
YOU CAME ALL THIS WAY
TO TELL ME THAT.
NO.
I CAME TO KISS YOU.
(DOOR CRASHES OPEN)
DANCES SUCK!
I CAN'T FIND SPIN
ANYWHERE.
FOR SOME REASON,
I REALLY THOUGHT HE'D SHOW.
AND GIVE YOU
ANOTHER OPPORTUNITY
TO BREAK HIS HEART?
UNLIKELY.
WAIT, YOU DON'T KNOW
WHERE HE IS, DO YOU?
YES.
CARE TO SHARE THE WEALTH?
BEG.
EXCUSE ME?
IF YOU WANNA KNOW
WHERE SPINNER IS,
GET DOWN ON YOUR KNEES
AND BEG.
(BREATH OF DISBELIEF)
(AWKWARD HALF LAUGH)
(CLEARS THROAT
UNCOMFORTABLY)
(LAUGHS)
WILL YOU HELP ME
FIND SPINNER?
YEAH.
JAY:
MAN, YOU ARE GOING TO LOVE
MY UNCLE'S COTTAGE.
SPINNER:
ANYWHERE -
AS LONG AS IT'S FAR AWAY
FROM THAT STUPID
SWEETHEART DANCE.
(JAY'S CELL PHONE RINGS)
Y'ELLO?
AND HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO DO THAT?
AH. GOTCHA.
(PHONE BEEPS OFF)
WE HAVE TO GO
TO THE DANCE.
MANNY'S THERE.
NOW IT'S MY TURN
TO WIN BACK MY WOMAN.
AND I NEED A WINGMAN.
FINE.
BUT IF I SEE JANE,
I'M BAILING.
(ENGINE REVS,
TRUCK RUMBLES OFF)
(SLOW MUSIC PLAYS,
LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
MANNY?
MANNY!
EXCUSE ME!
WHERE ARE YOU, MANNY?
SPINNER:
YOU SURE SHE'S REALLY HERE?
THERE SHE IS.
JANE:
(TAPS MIC AND CLEARS THROAT)
UM...
YESTERDAY, I MADE A SPEECH.
I THANKED LOTS OF PEOPLE,
BUT I WAS TOO STUPID
TO RECOGNIZE SOMEONE
WHO SUPPORTED ME
THROUGH IT ALL.
YOU WERE RIGHT, SPIN.
I SHOULDA THANKED YOU.
I HOPE IT'S NOT TOO LATE
BECAUSE...
I LOVE YOU
AND I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'D DO WITHOUT YOU.
GIRL:
AWWWW...
STUDENTS:
(APPLAUDING)
CAN I HAVE THIS DANCE?
♪ Come on, slam me down ♪
♪ Through the table
to the ground ♪
♪ Say you'll go,
Say you'll lead ♪
♪ Nothing here for you
but me... ♪
YOU DO LIKE ME.
A LOT.
YOU'RE TRIPPIN'
BACKWOODS.
WHY ARE YOU SO AFRAID
TO ADMIT IT?
(EXCITED SQUEAL)
OH!
WAS THAT YOUR FIRST KISS?
THE NEXT ONE WON'T BE.
♪ Come away with me ♪
♪ Come away ♪
HAVE YOU GUYS
SEEN SAV?
NOPE.
♪ Come away with me ♪
♪ Come away ♪
♪ Radio over my head ♪
I'M NOT READY
FOR A RELATIONSHIP.
AND WHO ARE YOU NOT READY
TO HAVE THIS RELATIONSHIP WITH?
♪ Take my hand... ♪
QUITE THE SCHEMER, HOLLY J.
I AM IMPRESSED.
NAH.
I'M JUST A HOPELESS ROMANTIC.
JAY:
YEAH.
ME TOO.
I WISH SHE REALLY WAS HERE.
♪ Away with me ♪
♪ Come away ♪
I KEPT ASKING IF I COULD PICTURE
MY LIFE WITH YOU,
AND I SHOULD'VE BEEN ASKING
IF I COULD PICTURE IT
WITHOUT YOU.
SPINNER:
AND?
I COULDN'T.
BUT NO WEDDING
UNTIL AFTER UNIVERSITY.
WELL, IT MIGHT TAKE THAT LONG
FOR YOUR MOM TO FORGIVE ME, SO.
♪ Come away ♪