JACKET OR NO JACKET?
AREN'T YOU A SHOO-IN
FOR YOUR MOM'S SORORITY?
LIBERTY:
NO JACKET.
WELL, BEING LEGACY
DOESN'T GUARANTEE YOU A SPOT.
THEY HAVE TO LIKE ME.
THEY WILL.
BUT IT SHOULDN'T BE BECAUSE
OF YOUR OUTERWEAR CHOICE.
CUTE.
AND INCREDIBLY NAIVE.
WOULD YOU WEAR JEANS
AND A T-SHIRT
TO A JOB INTERVIEW?
YEAH.
EMMA:
REMIND ME WHY YOU EVEN WANT
TO JOIN A SORORITY?
I MEAN, WHAT'S WRONG
WITH BEING AN INDIVIDUAL?
IT'S ALL ABOUT CONNECTIONS.
NOW, IS MY INQUISITION
COMPLETE?
GOOD,
THEN WISH ME LUCK.
(HUM OF CHATTER)
DAKOTA:
ARE YOU PLANNING TO RUSH
PSI ALPHA ZETA?
IT'S MY MOTHER'S SORORITY.
AND IT'S A GOOD ONE.
BUT IT'S NOT THE ONLY ONE.
DAKOTA WESTON, PRESIDENT,
PI GAMMA PI.
LIBERTY VAN ZANDT.
VALEDICTORIAN.
SCHOOL PRESIDENT.
AND NATIONAL MERIT SCHOLAR.
WHICH MAKES YOU PI GAMMA PI
MATERIAL.
HOW DO YOU...
KNOW THAT?
THE DEAN IS PI GAMMA PI.
SHE KEEPS HER EYES OUT
FOR POTENTIAL RECRUITS.
WE ONLY ACCEPT THE CREAM.
IT'S YOUR CHOICE.
A SAFE BET,
OR COMPETE FOR A SPOT
TO JOIN THE BEST.
I REALLY HOPE TO SEE YOU
AT THE HOUSE TOMORROW.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Oh! Oh! Oh! ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
DAKOTA:
WELCOME TO YOUR FIRST
PLEDGE EVENT, LADIES.
IN THIS ROOM STAND THE LEADERS
OF TOMORROW.
WE COUNT BOTH M.P.S
AND NOBLE PRIZE WINNERS
AS ALUMNAE.
BUT FIRST,
PLEDGING IS LIKE DATING.
GIVES A CHANCE TO SEE
IF THE RELATIONSHIP WILL WORK
BEFORE WE COMMIT.
YOU CAN BREAK UP
WITH US TOO.
AND GIVE UP CRAZY CONNECTIONS
AND FRIENDS FOR LIFE?
PLEDGES:
(CHUCKLE)
DAKOTA:
MY FEELINGS EXACTLY.
IT'LL BE HARD TO LEAVE
THIS PLACE NEXT YEAR
FOR HARVARD LAW.
HARVARD LAW?
A PI GAMMA PI RUNS ADMISSIONS.
GET INVITED TO JOIN US
AND THOSE CONNECTIONS
ARE GUARANTEED.
BUT FIRST,
YOU MUST PROVE YOU BELONG.
(WHISPERS)
I SEE SOME THINGS
THAT DON'T BELONG.
DAKOTA:
NOW LET'S GO MEET SOME ALUMNAE.
(DIN OF CHATTER)
HOLLY J, YOU CAN'T
JUST DECLARE YOURSELF
STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT.
I DIDN'T.
THE SHEP DID.
BUT IT'S UNDEMOCRATIC.
OH MY GOD, YOU'RE RIGHT.
AND YET STRANGELY?
UNBOTHERED.
IF YOU DON'T
GO ALL CHE ON ME,
I MIGHT MAKE YOU SECRETARY.
NOW SCOOT, I HAVE A POWER SQUAD
TO BRING INTO LINE.
CHANTAY:
(INAUDIBLE WHISPERING)
CAN SOMEBODY PLEASE TELL ME
WHAT'S MORE IMPORTANT
THAN CITY FINALS?
ANYA'S FINALLY
SWIPED HER V-CARD.
SAYS WHO?
CHANTAY: EVERYONE.
AND IT EXPLAINS
WHY SHE ISN'T AT PRACTICE.
SHE AND SAV ARE PROBABLY
DOING IT RIGHT NOW.
ANYA SAID SHE WAS SICK.
CHANTAY:
PROBABLY JUST BED-RIDDEN.
AND NOW THAT
ANYA'S DONE THE DEED,
THE POWER SQUAD MIGHT FINALLY
BE VIRGIN-FREE.
(SCOFFS)
NOT A CHANCE.
UNLESS YOU'RE ONE?
I'M THE CAPTAIN
OF THE POWER SQUAD.
OKAY, GOSSIP'S NOT GONNA
GET US ANYWHERE.
TOE TOUCHES, PEOPLE.
EMMA:
HOW'S RUSH?
SPECIFICALLY,
HAVE YOU FOUND ME
A CUTE SORORITY GIRL?
NO, BUT I MET TWO M.P.S
AND A SUPREME COURT JUDGE.
ALL ALUMNAE.
IMAGINE ME.
IN SUPREME COURT!
DON'T GET TOO EXCITED.
I HEAR PI GAMMA PI
IS VERY SELECTIVE.
YOU DON'T THINK
I HAVE WHAT IT TAKES?
HEY GIRL.
COME ON, PI GAMMA PI
SITS AT THE FRONT.
WAIT, YOU'RE DITCHING US?
FOR THEM?
JUST UNTIL I MAKE THE CUT.
LIBERTY, THIS IS JULIE.
THOUGHT YOU TWO WOULD HAVE
A LOT IN COMMON.
ARE YOU A THREE-SPORT ATHLETE
FROM THE WEST COAST?
STAR ATHLETE.
STAR SCHOLAR.
YOU TWO MAKE ME FEEL
LIKE A MAJOR SLACKER.
DAKOTA:
OKAY, EVERYONE,
GRAB A SEAT ON THE FLOOR.
COME ON.
SO TODAY'S PLAN
IS TO GET MORE FAMILIAR
WITH EACH OTHER
BY SHARING THE TOUGHEST TIME
OF YOUR LIFE.
BECCA.
YOU'RE UP FISRT.
OKAY.
UM, IT WAS GRADE NINE.
HE HAD SEEMED
LIKE A REALLY NICE GUY.
UNTIL HE GAVE ME A MULLET.
NEVER WENT TO THAT
HAIRDRESSER AGAIN.
(LAUGHS)
I'VE HAD A PRETTY CHARMED LIFE.
DAKOTA:
WELL, WE CAN'T HOLD THAT
AGAINST YOU.
OKAY, LIBERTY,
YOUR TURN.
WELL, UH, THE TOUGHEST TIME
IN MY LIFE WOULD BE...
WHEN I HAD TO GIVE MY BABY
UP FOR ADOPTION.
OH MY GOD, UM...
WAS THE FATHER SUPPORTIVE?
HE DIED.
HE WAS STABBED.
I'M SO SORRY.
IN A GANG FIGHT?
NOT EXACTLY.
DAKOTA:
IT'S AMAZING,
YOU GREW UP LIKE THAT
AND END UP HERE.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE
THE PRIVILEGES WE DID,
BUT YOU OVERCAME THE ODDS.
IT WOULD BE GREAT TO HAVE
SOMEONE WITH YOUR PERSPECTIVE
IN PI GAMMA PI.
WE WOULD BE LUCKY
TO HAVE YOU.
(APPLAUSE OF COMMENDATION)
MS. KWAN:
GATHER YE ROSEBUDS
WHILE YE MAY,
OLD TIME'S STILL A-FLYING.
AND THIS SAME FLOWER
THAT SMILES TODAY
TOMORROW WILL BE DYING.
BLUE? WHAT IS ROBERT HERRICK
SAYING IN THIS POEM?
TOO MANY FLOWERS.
NOT ENOUGH TIME.
ACCORDING TO
THE ANTI-GRAPEVINE,
HE'S HAD MANY FLOWERS.
AND THEY'VE ALL BEEN
VERY HAPPY AFTERWARDS.
MS. KWAN:
CHANTAY, SOMETHING YOU'D LIKE
TO SHARE WITH THE CLASS?
CHANTAY:
NO, MISS KWAN.
MS. KWAN:
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
SINCE YOU HAVE SO MUCH TO SAY,
WHY DON'T YOU ILLUMINATE US
WITH YOUR INTERPRETATION
OF THE POEM.
(BELL RINGS)
SAVED BY THE BELL.
WE'LL RESUME OUR DISCUSSION
NEXT CLASS.
WAIT UP.
WHY? SO YOU CAN HANG
A SCARLET V ON MY CHEST?
(WHISPERS) BEING A VIRGIN
IS NOTHING TO BE ASHAMED OF.
WELL, TRY BEING THE ONLY ONE
ON THE POWER SQUAD.
LOSING YOUR VIRGINITY ISN'T
LIKE GETTING YOUR WISDOM TEETH
TAKEN OUT.
IT COMES WITH COMPLICATIONS.
WELL, UNLIKE YOU,
I'VE HEARD OF A CONDOM.
WHICH WON'T PROTECT YOU
FROM GETTING HURT.
TRUST ME.
THANKS FOR THE ADVICE,
JUNO.
(SIGHS)
HEY, GIRL.
I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU COULD HELP US OUT
WITH SOME HIP HOP MOVES
FOR TONIGHT'S LIP SYNC.
(HALF LAUGH) LIBERTY?
TEACH YOU TO DANCE?
LIBERTY:
I CAN TRY.
UH, SEE YOU LATER?
YEAH.
YOU THINK YOU CAN TEACH ME
TO CRUNK DOWN LOW FIRST?
SO THEY'RE MAKING
SOME ASSUMPTIONS...
IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
WHAT KIND OF ASSUMPTIONS?
THEY THINK I'M FROM AN
UNDERPRIVILEGED BACKGROUND.
YOU? MISS DAUGHTER
OF TWO LAWYERS
WITH A SWIMMING POOL
IN THE BACK YARD?
MAYBE THEY'RE JUST EXCITED
TO HAVE SOMEONE
WHO'S A LITTLE DIFFERENT.
THEY SHOULD BE EXCITED
TO HAVE A LIBERTY.
MS. DAWES:
OKAY, THIS SEMESTER
WE'LL BE EXPLORING LANDSCAPES
WITH THE MOST EXQUISITE HILLS
AND VALLEYS -
THE HUMAN BODY.
NAKED?
IN YOUR WATERCOLOUR DREAMS.
UNFORTUNATELY, NO.
THE BOARD OF EDUCATION
IS A BUNCH OF PRUDES.
OKAY, PARTNER UP, EVERYBODY.
COME SEE ME
IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS.
PARTNERS?
UH, NOT THIS TIME.
DO YOU WANNA BE PARTNERS?
HERE. AFTER SCHOOL.
TOMORROW.
UM, STUDENT PRESIDENT
HAS THE KEY.
THEN WHO'S GOING TO STOP YOU
FROM TAKING ADVANTAGE OF ME?
SEE YOU TOMORROW,
MISS HOLLY J.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
PARTYGOERS:
(CACOPHONY OF CHATTER)
NEVER THOUGHT THE LEADERS
OF TOMORROW PARTIED THIS HARD.
WORKED ON BAY STREET
LAST SUMMER.
THE INTERNS WHO PARTIED
UNTIL 3 AM WITH THE PARTNERS
WERE THE ONES
THAT GOT JOBS.
BECCA:
LIBERTY, YOU IN?
WE'RE DOING BODY SHOTS!
I'M GONNA SIT THIS ONE OUT.
DAKOTA:
LIBERTY.
SOME OF THE SISTERS
WORRY YOU WON'T FIT IN.
I KNOW THEY'RE WRONG.
BUT YOU NEED TO PROVE
YOU EXCEL
AT ALL ASPECTS
OF SORORITY LIFE.
INCLUDING THIS ONE.
BEN:
ALL RIGHT, SO WE JUST NEED
SOME VOLUNTEERS
FOR OUR FIRST COMPETITION.
ANY TAKERS?
I'M IN.
BEN:
ALL RIGHT, SO LIBERTY'S IN
FOR GAMMA GAMMA.
ANYONE ELSE?
GAMMA GAMMA?
YEAH, GET READY
TO SHED SOME CLOTHES.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
COME ON, LIBERTY!
WHAT! YOU CAN DO IT!
PARTYGOERS:
(PLAYFUL WHOOPS AND HOLLERS)
BEN:
ALL RIGHT, M GAMMA...
UH... FOUR!
DAKOTA:
(EXCITED SQUEAL)
NOW FOR YOUR PRIZE.
MM-HM.
IT'S FOR THE MAIN BEDROOM.
BEN:
BUT WHAT YOU DO THERE
IS UP TO YOU.
SHALL WE?
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYS)
YEAH.
(PLAYFUL WHOOPS AND HOLLERS)
(PLAYFUL WHOOPS AND HOLLERS,
HIP HOP PLAYS)
WOW, THIS IS A REALLY NICE
COMFORTER.
MUST BE LIKE THREE,
400 THREAD COUNT.
AND THE COLOUR?
IT'S, UH...
I'M NOT GONNA HOOK UP
WITH SOMEONE I JUST MET.
YEAH, I HAVE A GIRLFRIEND
BACK HOME.
SO SHOULD WE JUST GO BACK
DOWNSTAIRS?
BUT SHE KNOWS HOW IMPORTANT
THE FRAT IS.
AND SHE UNDERSTANDS
SOMETIMES I DO THINGS...
LIKE... MAKE OUT
WITH OTHER GIRLS?
OR PRETEND TO.
PASS ME YOUR PANTIES?
(MUFFLED BEAT OF MUSIC)
BEN: (CHANTING)
SPEECH! SPEECH! SPEECH!
UH, ONCE YOU GO BLACK,
YOU NEVER GO BACK.
PARTYGOERS:
OHHH!
BECCA:
SO, HOW WAS HE?
I DON'T KISS AND TELL.
BEN:
YEAH, BUT DO YOU DANCE?
YEAH, ONLY WITH US.
COME ON,
LET'S GO SHAKE SOME BOOTY.
LOOKING GOOD FOR A SPOT
IN PI GAMMA PI!
(DANCE MUSIC BLARES)
DON'T YOU DARE
MAKE ME LOOK STUPID.
BLUE:
YOU CARE A LOT ABOUT
WHAT PEOPLE THINK.
DON'T WORRY.
YOUR SECRET'S SAFE WITH ME.
HAVE YOU SLEPT
WITH MANY GIRLS?
IT'S JUST,
THAT'S WHAT PEOPLE SAY.
WELL, THAT'S BETWEEN ME
AND THE GIRLS I HAVE
OR HAVE NOT SLEPT WITH.
WELL, MANY ARTISTS
LIKE TO BE INTIMATE
WITH THEIR MODELS FIRST.
SO...
WE NEED TO MAKE OUT
FOR ART?
IF YOU'RE NOT INTERESTED...
I'M INTERESTED.
YOU DON'T WASTE ANY TIME.
I'VE GOT A CONDOM.
I'M NOT GOING TO HAVE SEX
WITH YOU.
WAIT. I MEAN...
(EXHALES)
(CLOMP OF FOOTSTEPS)
EMMA:
HEY! LIBERTY!
THIS SEAT
HAS YOUR NAME ON IT.
ROBSON:
AND SO DO THESE.
TELL ME HE DIDN'T JUST
HAND YOU YOUR PANTIES
IN HUMANITIES 101.
WE DIDN'T HOOK UP.
WE JUST PRETENDED TO.
KELLY:
A MATING RITUAL
I'M NOT ENTIRELY FAMILIAR WITH.
DO TELL MORE.
YEAH,
LIKE WHY YOU'D DO THAT?
EMMA:
TO IMPRESS HER NEW FRIENDS.
DO THEY STILL THINK
YOU'RE GHETTOLICIOUS?
YO' SISTA'!
JUST COME TO THE PI GAMMA PI
MIXER TONIGHT.
YOU'LL SEE GREEK LIFE
ISN'T AS EVIL AS YOU THINK.
KELLY:
OKAY.
BUT I'M NOT GIVING MY PANTIES
TO ANYONE.
(DIN OF CHATTER)
LIBERTY:
(INEBRIATED SQUEALS
OF EXCITEMENT)
HOW MANY SHOTS
HAVE YOU HAD?
HEY, GIRL!
(HAPPY SQUEALS)
BEN:
HEY!
(INEBRIATED SPEECH)
SO, WHICH ONE OF YOU TWO'S
G-GONNA BE THE ONE,
DO YOU THINK?
UH, WHAT "ONE"?
DAKOTA:
AH, WHO KNOWS?
HE'S DRUNK AS A SKUNK.
(GIGGLES AND SQUEALS)
WE ARE CLOSE
TO GETTING CHOSEN!
LIFE IS GONNA GET BETTER
FROM HERE.
WE SHOULD DO SOMETHING
TO CELEBRATE!
WE COULD GO STREAKING!
(MISCHIEVOUS GIGGLE)
WHO WANTS TO STREAKING
THROUGH CAMPUS?!
WOOOO!
HEY!
WE DECIDED TO CHECK OUT
SORORITY LIFE.
AND YOU'RE JUST IN TIME.
WE'RE GOING TO STREAK
THROUGH CAMPUS.
UM, THE ONLY PLACE
YOU SHOULD BE GOING RIGHT NOW
IS HOME TO BED.
WHO INVITED THE KILL JOYS?
LET'S GO, LIBERTY.
BECCA:
COMING? LET'S GO.
LET'S GO!
(GIGGLES)
WOOO!
LIBERTY:
WOOO! WHOA!
THROW FAST. THROW HARD.
COME ON, DEGRASSI.
ONE MORE YARD.
AND THAT'S THE NEW CHEER.
CHANTAY:
NICE COVER, BUT WE ALL KNOW
WHAT YOU WERE DOING
WHEN YOU MISSED SCHOOL.
DAYQUIL
AND "DAYS OF OUR LIVES"?
SAV.
HOLLY J:
WHAT, YOU GUYS DIDN'T HAVE SEX?
WE'RE WAITING.
I HAVEN'T EVEN
MET HIS PARENTS YET.
UM... CAN WE TALK?
I'M GONNA CHECK "NO"
ON THAT BOX.
OKAY.
LET'S GO PRACTICE THE NEW CHEER.
(DOOR OPENS)
DON'T TELL ME
YOU SLEPT WITH HIM.
DON'T WORRY,
I THREW MYSELF AT HIM
AND HE JUST TURNED AWAY.
TELL ANYONE...
AND YOU'LL DESTROY ME.
I KNOW.
(KNOCK AT THE DOOR)
UM, I'M LOOKING
FOR A HOLLY J.
OKAY, YOU DON'T NEED
TO TALK TO ME,
BUT WE DO NEED TO FINISH
OUR PROJECT.
ALL RIGHT, SO, ART ROOM.
AFTER SCHOOL.
OR I'LL TELL MS. DAWES
WHY YOU DIDN'T SHOW.
(HOSPITAL MONITOR BEEPS,
LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
THE NURSE SAID IT'LL BE HARD
TO SPEAK FOR A WHILE.
GETTING YOUR STOMACH PUMPED
DOES THAT.
HOW DID I GET HERE?
YOUR FRIENDS
DROPPED YOU OFF.
THE SORORITY KNOWS I'M HERE?
DID THEY CARE?
NOT ENOUGH TO STAY.
WELL, IT'S NOT THEIR FAULT.
WOW,
YOU MUST REALLY WANT THIS.
I DO.
AND YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THE SORORITY HAS A REPUTATION
TO MAINTAIN.
HELLO? YOU JUST
GOT YOUR STOMACH PUMPED.
BESIDES,
IT'S TOO LATE FOR THAT.
(DISSATISFIED EXHALE)
AND?!
I'M OUT.
LIBERTY:
THE LONGER I STAY RIGHT HERE,
THE LONGER I COULD STILL BE
A PI GAMMA PI.
GOOD LUCK.
WE'RE REALLY DISAPPOINTED
IN YOU TWO.
AND WE EXPECT BETTER
IN THE FUTURE.
WE CAN'T HAVE NEGATIVE PRESS
ABOUT PI GAMMA PI.
FUTURE?
WE CAN STAY?
YES!
WE WANT GIRLS
LIKE YOU TWO.
SMART, BEAUTIFUL, LEADERS.
BECCA AND LIBERTY:
(ELATED LAUGHTER)
UH, WHAT ABOUT JULIE?
SHE'S ALL THOSE THINGS.
WHY KICK HER OUT
FOR STREAKING?
BECAUSE WE ONLY NEED ONE.
(ANNOYED BREATH)
ONE WHAT?
WHAT SHANNON MEANS
IS WE'RE SEEKING DIVERSITY.
OUR FUNDING DEPENDS UPON IT.
SO THAT'S ALL I AM TO YOU?
A TOKEN.
(INCREDULOUS SIGH)
LET'S JUST
GET THIS OVER WITH?
BLUE:
I LIKE YOU, HOLLY J.
AND UH...
IF I HAVE TO DO THIS
TO PROVE IT TO YOU,
I WILL.
ALTHOUGH I'D PREFER TO WAIT
UNTIL YOU KNOW HOW AWESOME
I REALLY AM.
AREN'T WE HERE TO FINISH
OUR PROJECT?
SO, THAT'S A "NO"?
YOU'RE REJECTING ME?
AS YOU WISH.
BUT BEFORE WE GET TO BUSINESS,
LET ME SHOW YOU THIS.
HOLLY J:
I LOOK...
BEAUTIFUL.
AND IF WE DO SLEEP TOGETHER
SOMEDAY,
IT WILL MEAN SOMETHING.
LIKE YOU'LL EVER
GET ANOTHER CHANCE.
THREE LATTES
AND ONE PEPPERMINT TEA.
KELLY:
PEPPERMINT TEA?
FOR WHO?
LIBERTY.
TO SOOTHE HER STOMACH.
YEAH, WE WANNA SHOW HER
WE'RE HERE FOR HER.
'CAUSE WHATEVER WE THINK
OF SORORITIES,
SHE REALLY WANTED THIS.
HEY, WHAT HAPPENED?
WELL, I CAN APPLAUD THEM
FOR THE IDEA
OF SEEKING OUT DIVERSITY,
BUT...
I TURNED THEM DOWN.
YOU WERE RIGHT.
THEY HAD A QUOTA.
THEY DIDN'T WANT ME.
JUST A BLACK CHICK IN THE ROOM
TO SATISFY ADMINISTRATION.
I TOLD THEM
THAT WASN'T ME.
(CUPS CLINK)