(GUITAR PLAYS)
CRAIG:
♪ FOR ANY GIRL THAT'S UNHAPPY ♪
♪ FOR ANY BOY THAT IS BAD ♪
♪ EVERY FATHER GONE MISSING ♪
♪ OH... ♪
♪ MM, EVERY FATHER GONE MAD ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS AND APPLAUDS)
THANK YOU.
BE BACK IN 10 WITH MY NEXT SET.
(CHEERING AND APPLAUDING)
HEY! YOU CAME!
WHERE'S, UH,
MARCO AND PAIGE?
THEY WANTED TO COME.
THEY'RE... BUSY.
BUT THEY SEND THEIR LOVE.
THEY'RE BUSY?
YEAH,
PAIGE HAD STUFF TO DO
AND... MARCO AND I KINDA
GOT INTO A FIGHT.
WHICH YOU'RE NOT IN THE MOOD
TO TALK ABOUT?
AFFIRMATIVE.
OKAY. SO WHAT ARE YOU
IN THE MOOD FOR?
RELAXING.
WHICH IS PRACTICALLY
IMPOSSIBLE TO DO
AT PAIGE'S MANSION.
YOU CAN ALWAYS CRASH
WITH ME.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Oh! Oh! Oh! ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
YOU'RE BACK.
NOT FOR LONG.
YOU GOING HOME...
TO SEE YOUR DAD
IN THE HOSPITAL?
I'VE DECIDED TO STAY
ELSEWHERE.
WHERE?
CRAIG'S.
MARCO:
CRAIG'S?!
GREAT IDEA, EL.
REPLACE ONE DRAMA IN YOUR LIFE
WITH ANOTHER ONE.
THERE'S NO DRAMA
BETWEEN CRAIG AND ME.
NOW.
I STILL HAVEN'T FORGIVEN HIM
FOR THE LAST ROUND.
COME ON, ELLIE.
THIS GUY IS BAD NEWS
FOR GIRLS,
'SPECIALLY YOU.
I'M OVER HIM!
AND TRUST ME,
I KNOW I DON'T NEED
A RELATIONSHIP RIGHT NOW.
MARCO:
THEN WHAT DO YOU NEED?
A FRIEND WHO DOESN'T JUDGE ME.
I PROMISE I WON'T MENTION
YOUR DAD AGAIN...
(SIGHS)
IT'S JUST...
ELLIE, I REALLY THINK
YOU'RE GONNA REGRET IT
IF YOU DON'T GO SEE HIM.
HAVE FUN WITH THE MOVIE CROWD,
MARCO.
SAV:
JAY, GREAT SHORTCUT.
I CAN FEEL THE RADIO WAVES
FRYING MY BRAIN.
DANNY:
NOT MUCH TO FRY.
SAV:
(SARCASTIC LAUGH)
SHUT UP.
(BUS SPUTTERS TO A HALT)
PETER:
OH, LOOK OUT.
(CHUCKLES)
ALL RIGHT, GET UP.
OH, NICE.
LOOKS LIKE
A COMPRESSION PROBLEM.
PETER:
OH, CLOSE.
OH, KEEP GOING.
SAV, PETER AND DANNY:
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
DANNY:
NICE!
(WHACK)
MANNY:
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO PREPARE
FOR MY AUDITION
WHEN WE HAVEN'T HAD A MOMENT
OF SILENCE SINCE WE LEFT?!
I NEED TO THINK THROUGH
THE EMOTIONAL BEATS
OF THE SONG!
MICK'S METHOD
TAKES CONCENTRATION.
YOU CAN'T PRACTICE SINGING
IN YOUR HEAD.
JUST GO FOR IT.
FINE. JUST...
LET ME HAVE A FEW MINUTES
OF QUIET FIRST.
I NEED TO FIND MY CENTRE.
(EXHALES FORCEFULLY)
(WARBLED BREATHS,
CLEARS THROAT)
♪ WELCOME TO MY TRAIN WRECK,
BABY ♪
♪ I THINK WE'RE GETTIN'
OUT OF CONTROL ♪
♪ I THINK WE OUGHTA TEAR
THIS PLACE DOWN ♪
(VOICE TRAILS OFF)
♪ BEFORE THE NIGHT GETS OLD... ♪
WHAT?
THAT'S NOT REALLY HOW
YOU'RE GONNA SING IT,
IS IT?
(ANNOYED EXHALE)
VERY FUNNY, GUYS.
LET'S FREAK MANNY OUT
BEFORE HER BIG AUDITION.
I SHOULD GET OUTTA
YOUR WAY.
YOU PROBABLY HAVE
TO GET TO THE STUDIO.
NO WAY. I'VE GOT THE WHOLE DAY
PLANNED OUT FOR US.
YOU DO?
YOU'RE NOT TIRED?
NO.
BUT, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'VE GOT THIS, UM...
I'VE GOT THIS SONG
I WANNA PLAY FOR YOU.
I WROTE IT IN REHAB.
OKAY.
(STRUMS GUITAR)
♪ I SWITCHED OFF LIKE A LIGHT ♪
♪ A FIGHTER WITH NO FIGHT ♪
♪ STARING UP AT THE STARS ♪
♪ I'D GIVEN IN TO THE DARK ♪
♪ BURNT UP LIKE A MATCH ♪
♪ AT THE LOW END
OF THE CRASH ♪
♪ THE MOON GLOWED
LIKE A SCAR ♪
♪ HOW DID THINGS GO SO FAR ♪
♪ SOME HOW YOU SAW SOMEONE
WORTH SAVING ♪
♪ YOU PULLED ME BACK
INTO THE LIGHT ♪
♪ NOW IF EVER
I CAN RESCUE YOU ♪
♪ WHEN YOU NEED TWO ARMS
TO FALL INTO ♪
♪ GOING DEEP INTO THE BLUE ♪
♪ I WILL RESCUE YOU ♪
SO WHAT HAPPENED
WITH ASHLEY?
WE WENT ON TOUR
IN EUROPE,
SHE STAYED,
AND I CAME HERE.
IT'S SO PEACEFUL OUT THERE.
YEAH.
IF I COULD SWIM,
I'D WADE OUT...
JUST AS FAR AS I COULD GO
AND...
GET AWAY FROM EVERYTHING.
THANKS FOR
THE MOST AMAZING DAY.
AND FOR THAT SONG.
I WROTE IT FOR YOU.
CRAIG:
♪ OR THE BEAUTY OF YOUR FACE ♪
♪ SOMEHOW YOU SAW SOMEONE
WORTH SAVING ♪
♪ YOU PULLED ME BACK
INTO THE LIGHT ♪
SAV:
HEY, I CAN'T WAIT ANY LONGER!
I'VE GOTTA GO!
(BIRDS CAW AND CHIRP)
STILL FUSSING
OVER THAT THING?
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'M DOING WRONG.
I SCANNED THE METER
OF THE LYRICS.
I FOUND THE SUBTEXT.
MAYBE YOU'RE JUST
OVER-THINKING IT.
OR I'M NOT GOOD ENOUGH
TO FIGURE IT OUT ON MY OWN.
MICK WAS RIGHT,
I NEED HIM.
(KEYPAD BEEPS)
GIVE ME MY PHONE!
NO MORE PROFESSOR SOCIOPATH.
NOT ON MY WATCH.
OH, I SEE. THIS...
THIS IS A GAME, RIGHT?
NO! I JUST DON'T WANT YOU
TALKING TO HIM.
OH! AND I SHOULD DO
WHAT YOU WANT
BECAUSE YOU KNOW
WHAT'S BEST FOR ME, RIGHT?
NO, THAT'S NOT WHAT
I'M SAYING.
BUT YOU'LL LET ME GET IT
IF I CRY?
IF I TELL YOU
HOW STUPID I AM?
FINE! I'M STUPID!
I'M AN IDIOT.
I DO EVERYTHING WRONG!
NOW CAN I GET MY DAMN PHONE?!
(CRYING)
LOOK AT WHAT THIS GUY'S
DONE TO YOU!
(CRYING)
SAV:
HEY, GUYS!
LOOK WHAT I FOUND
IN THE BUSHES!
A PHONE! HUH.
(CRYING)
(LAUGHING)
THERE'S NO WAY
THAT WAS JOHNNY DEPP.
I'M TELLING YOU,
IT WAS HIM.
HE DOESN'T EVEN LIVE HERE
ANYMORE.
HE LIVES IN FRANCE.
GOD, I'VE MISSED YOU.
(BATHROOM DOOR OPENS)
YVETTE: CRAIG?
THERE YOU ARE.
YVETTE, YOU'RE BACK!
UH, ELLIE, THIS IS YVETTE,
MY GIRLFRIEND.
UH, SHE WAS JUST IN MAUI
FOR A MODELLING SHOOT.
YVETTE:
(GIGGLES)
OH! THAT'S...
THAT'S AWESOME.
SO THIS IS THE ELLIE.
I'VE HEARD SO MUCH
ABOUT YOU.
YEAH?
IT'S...
IT'S GREAT TO MEET YOU.
STAY FOR DINNER.
I JUST ORDERED SOME SUSHI
AND THERE'S MORE THAN ENOUGH
FOR ALL OF US.
LET ME JUST GO THROW
SOME CLOTHES ON.
OKAY.
SHE SEEMS...
NICE.
VERY NICE.
YOUR BIRTHDAY PARTY
WILL BE FAB.
WE'LL INVITE
ALL THE A-LISTERS.
LAUGH LIKE I SAID
SOMETHING FUNNY!
AND VOILA...
PAIGE'S STOCK?
TOTALLY ON THE RISE.
BUT IT'S NOT MY BIRTHDAY.
IT IS NOW.
HAPPY EIGHTEENTH.
YOUTH IS KING.
ACCORDING TO IMDB,
I'M NINETEEN!
WITH ALL THIS PARTY PLANNING,
HOW AM I POSSIBLY GONNA LEARN
ALL MY LINES FOR TOMORROW?
YOU'RE SO CUTE.
YOU THINK YOU NEED
TO LEARN YOUR LINES.
WELL, ISN'T THAT PART
OF THE JOB?
ALL THE BEST ACTORS
IMPROVISE.
AND DIRECTORS DON'T CARE?
MOST ENCOURAGE IT.
KEEPS THE MATERIAL FRESH.
BESIDES, WHO KNOWS YOUR PART
BETTER THAN YOU DO?
WELL, MEWES SEEMS PRETTY
PARTICULAR ABOUT HIS WORDS.
YOU'RE THE STAR,
PAIGEY.
IF YOU DON'T START ACTING
LIKE IT,
THIS TOWN WILL WALK
ALL OVER YOU.
HAPPY 18TH BIRTHDAY
TO ME!
MM-HM.
SO YOU MET AT ONE
OF CRAIG'S SHOWS?
I WAS OPENING FOR
"FALLOUT BOY."
HE PULLED ME UP ON STAGE.
SUCH A ROCK STAR MOVE.
WAS CRAIG LIKE THAT
IN HIGH SCHOOL?
NO. NO.
TOTAL NERD.
HE COULDN'T GET A DATE
TO SAVE HIS LIFE.
IS THAT SO?
HE WAS AWESOME.
ANY GIRL WOULD BE LUCKY
TO HAVE HIM.
YVETTE:
SO THINGS HAVEN'T CHANGED MUCH.
IT'S KINDA LATE.
I SHOULD GO.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
STAYING HERE.
NO. MARCO CALLED,
UM... UPSET.
SOMETHING ABOUT TAYLOR KITSCH
AT THE COFFEE BEAN.
JUST MISSING HIM.
IT WAS REALLY NICE
TO MEET YOU, YVETTE.
♪♪♪
(WATER FOUNTAIN SPLASHES)
MARCO:
SO YOU WOKE UP THIS MORNING
AND DECIDED
NO MORE CASA DE CRAIG?
YEAH. WELL...
HIS GIRLFRIEND JUST GOT BACK
FROM A MODELLING SHOOT
IN MAUI.
SO, I DECIDED TO GIVE THEM
SOME SPACE.
WHICH YOU'RE OKAY WITH?
(DOOR SHUTS)
OKAY,
I'M GONNA GO TAKE THIS
AND READ IT BY THE POOL,
BECAUSE I CAME HERE
TO RELAX.
YOU SHOULD TRY IT.
PAIGE:
ELEANOR, MUST YOU SHOUT?
HEY! AREN'T WE SUPPOSED
TO BE ON OUR WAY
TO YOUR REHEARSAL?
BECAUSE IT BEGINS...
LIKE, RIGHT NOW.
NOTHING STARTS
WITHOUT THE STAR.
BE A DEAR
AND GET ME MY IPHONE?
(DOOR SHUTS)
JASON:
JUST REMEMBER THAT "MEWES"
IN THIS SCENE,
HE JUST CAUGHT A 30-YARD PASS,
DUDE.
HE'S FEELING GOOD...
MICHEAL:
AH! HEY SUNSHINE.
I SUPPOSE YOU'RE LATE
'CAUSE YOU WANTED EXTRA TIME
TO LEARN YOUR LINES?
OF COURSE.
ALL RIGHT, PEOPLE,
LET'S TRY THIS FROM THE TOP,
SCENE FIVE.
AND THIS TIME
WITH OUR ACTRESS.
MICHAEL:
HEY, DID YOU SEE
THAT LAST CATCH?
PRETTY SLICK, UH?
YOU, UH, THINK JUST BECAUSE
YOU'RE A FOOTBALL PLAYER,
YOU'RE GONNA SCORE
A TOUCHDOWN WITH ME?
MICHAEL:
DUDE, SHE GOT THE LINE WRONG
AGAIN!
(STAMMERS)
CAN YOU JUST DO IT
AS SCRIPTED?
UNLESS,
IN ADDITION TO BEING LATE,
YOU STILL DON'T KNOW
YOUR LINES!
PAIGE:
OF COURSE I KNOW THEM!
IT'S JUST...
I LIKE MY LINE BETTER.
WHY'S THAT?
BECAUSE I KNOW TRIXIE.
I KNOW THE WAY SHE THINKS,
THE WAY SHE TALKS,
AND TRIXIE WOULD NEVER SAY...
"YOU'RE NOT MY TYPE,
GOLDIE LOCKS."
UH, YEAH SHE WOULD,
AND SHE DID.
TO ME.
I WAS THERE.
AND HOW MANY SCREENPLAYS
HAVE YOU WRITTEN?
YOU'RE A FIRST TIME
WRITER/DIRECTOR,
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
ALL RIGHT, IF YOU'RE NOT
GONNA TO DO IT MY WAY
THEN GET OFF OF MY SET!
FINE.
YEAH, FINE.
GOD, HE IS SUCH A DIVA.
SET DIRECTOR:
'KAY, EVERYBODY TAKE 15.
MAN:
♪ YOU CAN BUY
A FISHNET TRUCKER ♪
♪ HITCHHIKER LOVER ♪
♪ THAT GIRL,
SHE REALLY KNOCK ME OUT NOW ♪
CHECK IT OUT!
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
JAY:
ALL RIGHT,
YOU GUYS STAY HERE.
I'LL GET THE GRUB.
YES SIR.
MANNY:
WHY DO YOU GUYS DO
EVERYTHING HE SAYS?
'CAUSE JAY'S AWESOME.
AND HE SCARES US.
(BAR PATRONS APPLAUD)
MC:
OKAY, THAT WAS
"FREEWAY WARRIORS"
WITH "FISHNET TRUCKER."
UP NEXT, FOR OPEN MIC TUESDAY,
WE HAVE...
MANNY SANTOS.
DO WE HAVE A MANNY SANTOS?
SHE'S RIGHT HERE.
NO, NO...
MIA AND PETER: (CHANT)
MANNY! MANNY!
(FRIENDS JOIN IN)
MANNY! MANNY! MANNY!
(APPLAUD AND CHEER)
YA' SIGN UP,
YA' GO UP.
UM, I DIDN'T SIGN UP.
IS YOUR NAME MANNY SANTOS?
YES...
THEN YOU BETTER
GET THAT BUTT ON STAGE.
LET'S HEAR IT FOR MANNY SANTOS,
EVERYBODY.
(BAR PATRONS APPLAUD
AND CHEER)
COME ON, MANNY.
THEY'RE NOT GONNA
LET US OFF STAGE
'TIL YOU SING SOMETHING.
(DRUMS STICKS CLACK,
STUDZ BEGINS TO PLAY)
(EXHALES FORCEFULLY,
STUDZ PLAYS)
WELCOME...
(CLEARS THROAT)
UM...
MANNY: (SINGING BADLY)
♪ WELCOME TO MY TRAIN WRECK,
BABY ♪
♪ I GUESS WE'RE GETTIN'
OUTTA CONTROL ♪
(CLEARS THROAT,
GETTING INTO IT)
♪ I THINK WE OUGHTA TEAR
THIS PLACE DOWN ♪
♪ BEFORE THE NIGHT GETS OLD ♪
♪ I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE AFTER ♪
♪ ALL WE NEED'S
A FRESH DISASTER ♪
♪ IF YOU TELL ME NO ♪
♪ I'M GONNA TRASH THIS JOINT
NOW! ♪
♪♪♪
♪ LET'S LOSE IT ♪
♪ NOTHIN' TO IT ♪
♪ KICK THE DOOR DOWN
AND COME ON IN ♪
♪ LET'S START IT,
HIT IT HARDER ♪
♪ TEAR IT UP
LIKE I KNOW YOU CAN ♪
BAR PATRONS:
WOOO! WOOO!
♪ CRASH MY... ♪
♪ DON'T YOU WANNA CRASH
MY PARTY ♪
♪ CRASH MY... ♪
♪ DON'T YOU WANNA CRASH
MY PARTY ♪
♪ YEAH! ♪
♪ EH-YEAH! EH-YEAH! ♪
♪ CRASH MY... ♪
♪ DON'T YOU WANNA CRASH
MY PARTY! ♪
BAR PATRONS:
(WILD CHEERS, APPLAUSE
AND WHISTLING)
(ELATED LAUGHTER)
PAIGE IS OUT OF CONTROL.
ANOTHER MOJITO,
PLEASE.
HO HO!
SLOW DOWN THERE, CHAMP.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THERE'S THIS SPOT,
AT THE BEACH,
THAT IS SO...
SO BEAUTIFUL!
PAIGE:
MY PHONE KEEPS INTERRUPTING
MY PARTYING.
IT'S YOUR MOTHER.
AREN'T YOU GONNA
TAKE IT?
HEY, MOM.
HOW'S EVERYTHING AT HOME?
OF COURSE I CARE.
HEL... HELLO?
(BUTTON BEEPS)
MOM?
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
PAIGE:
OH! I AM GLAD YOU CAME.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT APOLOGIZING.
YOU ARE TOTALLY FORGIVEN.
FORGIVEN FOR WHAT?
FOR KICKING ME OFF SET,
OF COURSE.
IT WAS TRES RUDE,
BUT I'M OVER IT.
LOOK, BAD ACTING
I CAN DEAL WITH,
BUT KEVIN TOLD ME
NOT TO LET SOME CHICK
WITH A BAD ATTITUDE
RUIN MY FIRST FILM.
(STUNNED GASP)
ARE YOU TRYING TO EMBARRASS ME
IN FRONT OF MY GUESTS?
OR IS THIS A PLAN
TO REPAIR YOUR DAMAGED EGO?
ALL RIGHT,
FOR YOUR INFORMATION,
I CAME HERE TO GET
TRIXIE'S TIARA BACK.
OW! YOU CAN'T FIRE ME.
I'M THE STAR!
(MOCKING)
YOU CAN'T FIRE ME,
I'M THE...
NO! YOU'RE FIRED!
WELL, THE STUDIO LOVES ME!
MEWES...
SUCH A DRAMA QUEEN.
(ALCOHOL SLOSHES)
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
(PAINED SIGH)
WE, UH, NEED TO TALK.
YOU OKAY?
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
(PARTYGOERS CHATTER,
MUSIC PLAYS)
SO I HAVE THIS LIFE
IN L.A., RIGHT?
AND IT'S, UM...
IT'S PRETTY PERFECT:
DREAM JOB,
DREAM APARTMENT,
GREAT GIRLFRIEND...
OH, YEAH...
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN
YOU SHOW UP
AND SUDDENLY EVERYTHING
DOESN'T SEEM SO PERFECT ANYMORE.
(SNIFFLES)
'CAUSE THAT'S...
THAT'S WHAT I DO.
YEAH, UM...
I'M THE ONE WHO MESSES UP
PEOPLE'S LIVES.
NO, ELLIE, NO.
YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU SHOULD JUST, UM...
STAY AWAY FROM ME.
BECAUSE, UM...
YOU'LL BE BETTER OFF.
CRAIG:
ELLIE.
LET GO.
YOU DON'T GET IT.
CRAIG!
MARCO. HI.
HI.
LOOK, LET ME GO.
WE'RE NOT DONE TALKING.
YEAH, YOU ARE, DUDE.
♪ Hurry up and go ♪
♪ You're the last one to know ♪
♪ What is up ♪
♪ What is up with me? ♪
♪ Come on, come on and go ♪
♪ You're the last one, so ♪
♪ Come on, hurry up ♪
♪ Hurry up and leave ♪
♪ And the same old world's
above her... ♪
DANNY:
DUDE, THAT WAS SICK!
YOU NEVER TOLD US
YOU COULD PLAY THE DRUMS!
MANNY:
THERE ARE MANY THINGS
YOU DON'T KNOW ABOUT JAY HOGART.
THANKS FOR PUSHING ME
OUT THERE.
ANYTIME,
MY LITTLE SCHNITZEL.
DUDE,
DID YOU MOVE THE BUS?
IT WAS RIGHT HERE.
WELL,
THEN WHERE IS IT?
ELLIE!
♪ Hurry up and run ♪
♪ It's your last chance
for fun ♪
♪ Come on, hurry up up ♪
♪ Hurry up up and leave ♪
♪ Come on, come and go ♪
♪ You're the last one, so ♪
♪ Come on, hurry up up ♪
♪ Hurry up up and leave ♪
♪ And the same old world's
above her ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
IT'S GONNA BE OKAY.
MARCO:
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?!
I'M FINE! I'M FINE!
I KNOW. YOU'RE GONNA BE
OKAY NOW.
LET'S GET YOU HOME.
I'M OKAY.