CARLO: (IN DREAM)
NOW, BE A GOOD GIRL.
OKAY, JANIE-BEAR?
HEY, HON.
IS HE STILL HERE?
YES, AND IN HONOUR
OF YOUR FATHER,
LUCAS ACTUALLY GOT OUT OF BED
BEFORE NOON!
ARE YOU OKAY?
ACTUALLY, I COULDN'T,
I COULDN'T SLEEP.
JUST BAD DREAMS,
I GUESS.
EVELYN:
AW.
HAS DAD HEARD BACK
FROM HIS FRIEND YET?
YES, I DID.
(EVELYN AND CARLO KISS)
IT'S ON.
THIS AFTERNOON AT 3:15.
LUCAS:
COOL. UH, THANKS, DAD.
EVELYN:
OH, YOUR FATHER GOT LUCAS
A JOB INTERVIEW.
WOW.
EVELYN:
ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE, SIT.
I MADE PANCAKES.
UH, SORRY. NO TIME.
I GOTTA GET TO PRACTICE.
OH, HEY, HERE,
I'LL DRIVE YA.
NO. THAT'S OKAY.
UM...
I COULD USE THE FRESH AIR.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Oh! Oh! Oh!
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
CHEERLEADERS: (CHANTING)
♪ ALUMS THINK
THEY CAN BEAT US ♪
♪ BUT THEY NEED TO BE TOLD ♪
♪ YOU'LL NEVER BEAT DEGRASSI
'CAUSE YOU'RE JUST TOO OLD ♪
♪ ALUMS THINK
THEY CAN BEAT US, ♪
♪ BUT THEY NEED TO BE TOLD,
YOU'LL NEVER... ♪
LOOKING GOOD.
THANKS. WE'LL CHEER YOU
ON TO VICTORY
BEFORE YOUR BROTHER
AND ALL THOSE OTHER
SLUGGISH ALUMS.
YEAH. UM...
SO HOW WAS IZZY
AFTER HER SLEEPOVER?
GREAT.
I MEAN,
DID SHE GET HOMESICK OR...?
NAH. SHE LOVES HANGING OUT
WITH YOUR MOM.
AND SHE REALLY HIT IT OFF
WITH YOUR DAD.
IS SHE STAYING OVER AGAIN?
IT WAS JUST THE ONE NIGHT.
BUT YOUR MOM WAS SAYING
THAT WE SHOULD MAKE IT
MORE OF A REGULAR THING.
MAYBE THAT'S NOT
A GOOD IDEA.
WHY? YOU STILL WANNA BE
THE BABY OF THE HOUSE?
(HALF LAUGHS)
NO. NO.
IT'S, UM...
IT'S JUST THINGS ARE SORT OF
WEIRD RIGHT NOW AT HOME...
WITH MY PARENTS.
KIND OF UNSETTLED...
YEAH, SURE.
UM...
OKAY, WELL...
I SHOULD GET BACK
TO PRACTICE.
COME ON, WHAT'RE WE DOING?
LET'S GO.
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT.
CHEERLEADERS:
♪ ALUMS THINK THEY CAN... ♪
PA ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION, STUDENTS.
WOULD THE FOLLOWING STUDENTS
PLEASE REPORT...
HELPING OUT OTHERS...
HOW ANGELINA OF YOU.
BUT THERE'S NOTHING CELEB
ABOUT THAT STYLE.
NIGHTMARE.
WAY TO MAKE A STATEMENT,
BHANDARI.
CLARE:
ALLI? WHAT HAPPENED?
MY MOM WAS CLEANING OUT
MY CLOSET
AND SHE FOUND
MY SCHOOL CLOTHING.
ARE YOU IN TROUBLE?
UM, YES!
I LOOK ABOUT AS HOT AS YOU.
NO. THAT CLOTHING IS FOR
THE LESS FORTUNATE.
I THINK I QUALIFY.
JOHNNY:
CUTE LOOK, BHANDARI.
(SNORTED BREATH)
MY PARENTS ARE RUINING
MY LIFE.
(ROCK MUSIC BLASTS
FROM CAR STEREO)
(KEYS JINGLE)
SPINNER:
MY STUDENT LEADER
PLAYING HOOKY?
THIS IS A FIRST.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
JANE:
YEAH, YOU'RE NOT WORKING,
I'M IN A USELESS CLASS...
WE GOTTA TAKE ADVANTAGE!
COOL.
SO WHERE ARE WE GOING?
I DON'T KNOW.
WE SHOULD JUST, UH...
HEAD OUT ONTO
THE OPEN ROAD,
DRIVE AS FAR AWAY
AS POSSIBLE.
YUKON HERE WE COME.
YEAH, GET OUTTA HERE,
CHANGE OUR NAMES,
GO ALL WITNESS PROTECTION
PROGRAM.
TALK TO ME, JANE.
PLEASE?
I JUST HATE HAVING HIM AROUND.
WELL, THERE ARE WORSE THINGS
THAN HAVING YOUR DAD AROUND.
IF MY DAD WERE STILL ALIVE...
I'LL TRADE YOU.
I'M...
I'M SORRY, SPINNER.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE
SAID THAT.
THEN TELL ME WHAT'S WRONG?
YEAH, I SHOULD PROBABLY-
I SHOULD PROBABLY
GET BACK TO CLASS.
USELESS OR NOT.
JANE!
FINE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHEN YOU'RE READY TO TALK,
YOU COME FIND ME.
ALLI:
THANKS FOR LETTING ME BORROW
YOUR SISTERS CLOTHES.
DARCY DOESN'T NEED
FALL CLOTHES IN AFRICA.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU DON'T WEAR
THESE CLOTHES EVERY DAY;
YOUR LIFE WOULD BE
TOTALLY DIFFERENT.
I THINK THAT MOTH BALLS
ARE AFFECTING YOUR BRAIN.
YOU WANNA GET MORE PEOPLE
TO HELP YOU
WITH THE CLOTHING DRIVE?
TAKE YOUR LOOK
FROM SAINTLY...
TO SEXY.
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYS)
♪ Ba-dum ba-dum ba-dum
ba-da-da-dum ♪
ba-da-da-dum, Hey! ♪
♪ Seven miles out
and I feel like a black sheep ♪
♪ Yeah, make it all good,
make it all good ♪
♪ Promise me ♪
(DOOR CHIMES JINGLE)
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
I LOOK RIDICULOUS.
RIDICULOUSLY HOT.
TRUST ME, CLARE.
THIS'LL CHANGE YOUR LIFE.
CLARE?
YOU LOOK...
WOW.
CLARE:
THANKS.
ALLI:
TOLD YA.
DID THAT OUTFIT BELONG TO...?
UH, DARCY'S.
WELL, YOU LOOK MUCH BETTER
IN IT.
(DANCE SONG PLAYS
WITHIN THE DOT)
WHAT'LL IT BE?
A CHOCOLATE MILKSHAKE.
MAKE THAT TWO, PLEASE.
REESE:
HEY.
SO WHAT'S YOUR NAME, CUTIE?
ALLI.
I MEANT YOUR FRIEND.
ME?
I'M CLARE.
REESE.
(CUP CLATTERS ONTO TABLE)
NICE TO MEET YOU.
WASN'T THAT CRAZY?
TOTALLY.
IT WAS LIKE
I DIDN'T EVEN EXIST.
WE SHOULD GET STARTED
ON OUR CHEMISTRY HOMEWORK.
(STREETCAR RUMBLES,
TRAFFIC WHIRS)
YOU ARE LOOKING
AT AN OFFICE SECURITY GUARD.
STARTIN' TOMORROW NIGHT,
AFTER THE BBQ.
WHERE'S CARLO?
MOM AND DAD WENT
TO A MOVIE.
DO YOU KNOW WHY
THEY SPLIT UP?
"OH, THAT'S GREAT, LUCAS.
CONGRATS."
I'M HAPPY FOR YOU, LUCAS.
I AM.
I JUST...
I NEED TO KNOW ABOUT THIS.
DON'T START.
YOU NEVER APPRECIATED DAD.
WH-WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
IF MOM AND DAD
CAN FORGIVE EACH OTHER,
WHY CAN'T YOU
JUST LET GO?
WHAT'S SO BAD
ABOUT MOM BEING HAPPY
AND ME HAVING A JOB?
WH-WHY DO YOU SAY THAT
I NEVER APPRECIATED HIM?
BECAUSE YOU GRABBED
ALL THE ATTENTION
AND THEN YOU COMPLAINED
ABOUT IT.
WELL, WHAT DID
I USED TO SAY?
JUST FORGET IT!
I HATED YOUR WEIRD STUFF
ABOUT DAD
WHEN WE WERE KIDS,
AND I HATE IT NOW.
(HALF LAUGHS)
YOU AND YOUR DAMN
BACKWARDS PAJAMAS.
(GASPS)
OH MY GOD.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING NOW?
I'M CRASHING AT SPINNER'S,
I'LL SEE YOU AT THE GAME.
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYS)
♪ I awoke ♪
♪ Only to find my lungs empty ♪
♪ And through the night ♪
♪ So it seems
I'm not breathing ♪
LUCAS:
YOU AND YOUR DAMN
BACKWARDS PAJAMAS.
CARLO:
LOOK AT YOU, JANIE-BEAR.
YOU PUT YOUR PAJAMAS ON
BACKWARDS AGAIN
AND DADDY'LL FIX THEM...
AND WE WON'T TELL ANYONE.
♪ Someone come and... ♪
♪ Someone come
and save my life ♪
♪ Maybe I'll sleep
when I am dead ♪
♪ But now it's like the night ♪
♪ Is taking up sides ♪
♪ And all the worries ♪
♪ That occupy the back
of my mind ♪
♪ Could it be ♪
♪ This misery will suffice ♪
(BIRDS CAW)
(EXHALES)
(SPEED DIAL BEEPS,
PHONE RINGS)
EVELYN:
HELLO?
MOM, WHAT'S UP?
I'M ON MY WAY TO SCHOOL.
JUST THOUGHT I'D CALL...
EVELYN:
ANASTASIA JANE,
YOU ARE 17-YEARS-OLD!
YOU DO NOT GET TO SAUNTER OFF
AT NIGHT
WITHOUT TELLING ME!
ESPECIALLY AT SPINNER'S HOUSE!
MOM, I GOTTA GO.
I'LL BE LATE.
I'LL SEE YOU AT THE GAME.
WAIT, WAIT.
YOUR FATHER WANTS
TO TALK TO YOU.
CARLO:
JANE?
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
♪♪♪
♪ I can't buy a clue ♪
♪ But I hear that
they're going cheap ♪
♪ I filled out plans ♪
♪ And that's the better half
of me ♪
♪ Drink me till I'm wrong ♪
♪ And I'll write one more song
about you ♪
YOU'RE NOT GONNA DRESS
THIS WAY
ALL THE TIME,
ARE YOU?
I THOUGHT IT WAS
JUST AN EXPERIMENT?
IT WAS,
BUT I KINDA LIKED IT.
IS THAT WRONG?
DO YOU REALLY WANNA SUCCEED
BASED ON YOUR BODY
AND NOT YOUR BRAINS?
WELL, CAN'T I DO BOTH?
NO. NO, YOU CAN'T.
AND WHY NOT?
BECAUSE YOU JUST CAN'T.
YOU'RE NOT MAKING ANY SENSE,
ALLI.
SO NOW I'M UGLY AND STUPID?
NEVER MIND.
I HAVE TO GO.
WHAT'S UP, MAN?
GUYS, HEY!
WHERE'S VAUGHAN?
I DON'T...
I DON'T KNOW.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
OH.
THERE'S THE LUNCH BELL.
ALMOST GAME TIME.
SHE'LL BE HERE.
LET'S HOPE SO.
BECAUSE IF SHE DOESN'T
MAKE IT...
IT'LL BE A TERRIBLE SHAME.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW...
(STAMMERS)
WE'LL MISS HER.
SHE'S A REAL ASSET
TO THIS TEAM.
(SHEEPISH CHUCKLE)
UM...
THE NEW AND SENSITIVE SHEP
IS FREAKING ME OUT,
MAN!
I KNOW.
AND WITHOUT JANE
WE'RE IN TROUBLE.
READY TO GET YOUR ASSES
KICKED?!
SEEN YOUR SISTER?
WHY?
WORRIED WE'LL UH...
WHOOP YOU WITHOUT HER?
KIND OF. YEAH.
I DON'T KNOW.
SHE'S PROBABLY OFF
POUTING SOMEWHERE.
SHE DOESN'T LIKE IT
WHEN THINGS AREN'T
ABOUT HER.
DOESN'T SOUND LIKE JANE.
WE SHOULD CALL HER.
(DOOR CHIMES JINGLE)
JANE:
SORRY, I CAN'T PLAY.
STOMACH FLU.
I'M JUST GONNA GO HOME
AND REST.
HAVE A GREAT GAME.
(PHONE SNAPS SHUT)
SPIN STILL HERE?
ARE YOU BLIND?
HE'S OFF
TO THE BIG GAME.
RIGHT. RIGHT.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
NO, I'M NOT...
I'M NOT PLAYING.
DON'T FEEL LIKE BEING
ONE OF THE BOYS TODAY?
DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE BREAKING UP
WITH SPINNER AGAIN.
IT'S NOT THAT.
IT'S UM...
IT'S MY FAMILY...
IT'S JUST FAMILY STUFF.
I'M, I'M GONNA JUST WAIT HERE
FOR SPINNER.
(SOBBING)
HEY.
YOU LOOK REALLY NICE TODAY.
THANKS.
SOMEONE IS TRYING TO THINK
UP HERE.
(CHALK SCRATCHES AGAINST BOARD)
YOU HAVE TO MULTIPLY
THE EQUATIONS
SO THAT THE SAME NUMBER
OF ELECTRONS
ARE INVOLVED IN BOTH.
THANK YOU, ALLI.
DID EVERYONE ELSE
GET THE SAME ANSWER?
MM?
I DID UNTIL THE END.
ALLI DIDN'T NOTICE
THE HYDROGEN IONS
ON BOTH SIDES
OF THE EQUATION.
YOU CAN SIMPLIFY FURTHER.
NICE CATCH.
COME ON UP.
LET'S SOLVE THIS PROBLEM
BEFORE THE BIG GAME.
SPINNER WOULD GIVE ME GRIEF
IF I DIDN'T FEED YOU, SO...
THANKS.
SO YOU'RE GONNA MISS
THE WHOLE ALUM THING?
YEAH.
I DON'T WANNA SEE ANYONE...
MY FAMILY...
(TEARY EXHALE)
WHATEVER IT IS,
YOU'LL HAVE TO FACE IT
SOMETIME.
MAYBE IT'S NOT AS BAD
AS YOU THINK.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
SO YOU'LL BE SPENDING
THE REST OF YOUR LIFE
JUST HANGING OUT HERE
AT THE DOT?
GOOD LUCK WITH THAT;
WE CLOSE AT TEN.
(TEARY BREATH)
ISN'T IT ENOUGH THAT CLARE'S
THE SMARTEST GIRL IN THE CLASS?
DOES SHE HAVE TO BE
THE PRETTIEST TOO?
CLARE'S PRETTY;
DOESN'T MEAN YOU AREN'T.
YEAH, THEN WHY IS JOHNNY
IGNORING ME?
BECAUSE GUYS ARE STUPID.
I THOUGHT HE LIKED ME.
AND THEN HE DISSED ME
IN FRONT OF HIS FRIENDS.
LOOK AT ME.
ANY GUY WHO DOESN'T WANNA
TELL HIS FRIENDS ABOUT YOU
IS AN IDIOT.
OH MY GOD!
OH MY GOD,
THAT WAS BAD.
I MEAN,
NOT THE KISS SPECIFICALLY.
JUST THE ACT OF US KISSING.
OH MY GOD.
THANK YOU.
(BURGERS SIZZLE)
CELEBRATORY HOT DOGS
ON ME!
SPINNER:
DUDE, THOSE ARE FREE.
JAY:
(HALF LAUGHS)
THEY CAN'T BE FREE,
I PAID FIVE BUCKS.
SPINNER:
YEAH, MAN. RIGHT.
JANE:
SPINNER.
HEY.
I WAS WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
ARE YOU FEELING BETTER?
I'M BETTER.
UM, WHERE'S CARLO?
YOUR BRO HAD A GREAT GAME.
BIG STRONG LEGS.
GUESS IT'S THAT VALIERI
FOOTBALL GENE, HUH?
MY LAST NAME IS VAUGHAN.
I CHANGED IT.
DO YOU GUYS KNOW
WHERE MY MOM AND DAD ARE?
LUCAS, STOP IT.
WHY DO YOU NEED DAD?
I NEED TO TALK TO HIM
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED
WHEN WE WERE LITTLE,
OKAY?
J-JUST DON'T.
HE'S TRYING TO BE A GOOD DAD.
LEAVE HIM ALONE.
I CAN'T.
I CAN'T DO THAT!
I WON THE GAME.
DAD'S PROUD.
DON'T RUIN IT.
DO YOU REALLY WANNA PRETEND
LIKE NOTHING EVER HAPPENED?
FIGURE IT OUT, LUCAS.
WHY DO YOU THINK
IT TOOK HIM SO LONG
TO PUT ME TO BED?
HE SAID THAT...
HE SAID...
YOU JUST TOOK FOREVER
TO FALL ASLEEP.
DID HE TELL YOU
TO KEEP IT A SECRET TOO?
CARLO:
THERE YOU GO.
IZZY AND CARLO:
(GIGGLE QUIETLY)
JANE:
GET AWAY FROM HER.
NOW!
WHAT'S WRONG?
WHY'D YOU MISS THE GAME?
YOUR MOTHER IS VERY WORRIED.
HOW COULD YOU
DO THAT TO ME?
I WAS JUST A LITTLE GIRL.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT, JANIE.
I REMEMBER.
I REMEMBER WHEN YOU WOULD
PUT ME TO BED,
BEFORE YOU LEFT.
JANIE, PLEASE!
LOOK, I KNOW
YOU'RE NOT THRILLED
I'M BACK IN
YOUR MOTHER'S LIFE,
BUT THERE'S NO NEED
TO TELL STORIES.
IT WAS A LONG TIME AGO.
YOU'RE CONFUSED.
NO. NO, I'M NOT.
HEY, BUDDY.
YOUR SISTER'S MAKING UP
STORIES AGAIN.
NO.
SHE'S GOT IT RIGHT.
LUCAS, COME ON.
YOU SHOULD GO.
NO ONE IN THIS FAMILY
EVER WANTS TO SEE
YOUR FACE AGAIN.
(SHAKEN EXHALE)
THOUGHT NINERS
WEREN'T YOUR STYLE.
IT'S ALL OVER
THE ANTI-GRAPEVINE.
SO IS KC YOUR NEW SQUEEZE?
I APOLOGIZED TO CLAIRE.
BESIDES,
WHAT DO YOU CARE?
YOU DON'T WANT IT
TO BE YOU.
AND YOU'RE SURE
ABOUT THAT?
I DON'T LIKE KC.
I JUST...
IT SEEMED LIKE A GOOD IDEA
AT THE TIME.
I GET THAT.
SOMETIMES I DO STUFF
AND DON'T KNOW WHY EITHER.
DO YOU MISS HANGING OUT?
IT'S COMPLICATED.
NOT GOOD ENOUGH.
I'M A BAD GUY,
BACKWOODS,
AND YOU'RE BETTER OFF
WITHOUT ME.
(SCOFFS)
OBVIOUSLY.
YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
YOU KNOW, IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT YOU WEAR, ALLI.
YOU LOOK GOOD TO ME.
WHEN UM...
WHEN YOU WORKED
YOUR DOUBLE SHIFTS,
HE'D TUCK ME IN.
HE SAID HE WAS HELPING ME
GET TO SLEEP.
HE TOLD ME MY PAJAMAS
WERE BUTTONED WRONG...
AND HE SAID
HE WAS GONNA FIX THEM.
IT WAS...
IT WAS SO LONG AGO.
HE'D CURL UP WITH ME
IN BED AND...
AND TOUCH HIMSELF.
(SNIFFLING)
I GUESS LUCAS
WAS USUALLY WATCHING TV.
WHY...
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
WHEN HE LEFT, I...
I DIDN'T HAVE TO WORRY ANYMORE.
I JUST THOUGHT WE WEREN'T
GONNA TALK ABOUT IT
AND I THOUGHT MAYBE YOU'D THINK
IT WAS MY FAULT.
EVELYN: (SOBBING)
OH, HONEY, I WOULD NEVER THINK
THAT IT'S YOUR FAULT.
I WOULD NEVER THINK THAT.
OH, I'M SO SORRY.
BOTH:
(CRYING)
DR. YABLONSKI:
TO START,
I WANT TO APPLAUD JANE
FOR BEING BRAVE ENOUGH
TO SHARE HER STORY.
THE HEALING PROCESS ISN'T EASY.
BUT WITH ALL OF YOU
WORKING TOGETHER AS A FAMILY,
THIS IS AN IMPORTANT
FIRST STEP.
I'M SORRY.
I WOULDN'T LET YOU TELL ME.
I THOUGHT THAT YOU
WERE ASHAMED OF ME.
I WANTED TO BELIEVE
THE BEST OF MY DAD.
I DIDN'T PROTECT YOU.
WE WERE JUST LITTLE KIDS.
LUCAS:
STILL.
YOU'RE HERE NOW.
(RELIEVED HALF LAUGH)
(HALF LAUGHS)
(DEEP SIGH)