FOOTBALL PLAYERS:
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
ISN'T THIS AWESOME?
THANKS FOR COMING
TO MY TRYOUTS, GUYS.
LIKE I'D MISS THE CHANCE
TO WATCH YOU KICK SOME BUTT.
SHEP:
COME ON, LET'S MOVE!
(BLOWS WHISTLE)
PLAYER:
HUT!
SPINNER:
YES!
THAT'S MY GIRLFRIEND.
WOO!
DEREK'S JUST NOT USED TO BEING
THAT CLOSE TO A GIRL.
SHEP:
RUN IT AGAIN.
AND HAIG?
DON'T BLOW IT THIS TIME, HUH?
ON THE BALL.
YOU NEED ME TO SUB-IN
FOR YOU, DEREK?
NO. OKAY, I GOT THIS.
TRUST ME.
♪ Welcome to your life ♪
♪ Welcome to your life, yeah ♪
♪ Well, this is gonna be
a good year... ♪
SPINNER AND DARCY:
YES! WOOO!
GUESS DEREK'S JUST NOT
THAT USED TO BEING CLOSE
TO GOOD FOOTBALL SKILLS.
OBVIOUSLY I CHOSE
OUR WEAK LINK
FOR THIS LITTLE DRILL.
DANNY:
ACTUALLY DEREK RUNS
ONE OF OUR FASTEST FORTIES,
AND SHE BEAT HIM
BY LIKE TWO METRES!
SPINNER:
YOU'RE AWESOME, BABE.
SHEP:
'KAY, LET'S HIT THE SHOWERS.
EXCEPT FOR YOU, HAIG.
RUN SOME LAPS
AFTER THAT POOR DISPLAY.
LET'S GO.
DEREK:
ARE YOU SERIOUS?!
SHEP:
YOU HEARD ME!
(HELMET CLATTERS)
SO... (PLEASED SIGH)
DID I MAKE THE TEAM OR WHAT?
LET'S NOT JUMP ANY GUNS.
I HAVE TO SEE
WHAT THE SCHOOL BOARD RULES SAY
ABOUT A GIRL PLAYING FOOTBALL.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Oh! Oh! Oh! ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
SHEP:
JANE VAUGHAN, PLEASE REPORT
TO THE PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE.
JANE VAUGHAN.
YOU READY FOR A NEW
STAR WIDE RECEIVER?
'CAUSE YOU BEAT DEREK
AT A PASSING DRILL?
A TRAINED APE
CAN DO THAT.
IN REAL FOOTBALL,
THERE'S TACKLING.
THERE'S NO WAY
THEY'LL LET YOU PLAY;
YOU'LL GET HURT.
SHE'LL BE GREAT.
YOU WILL BE GREAT.
I'M JUST SORRY
I WON'T BE HERE TO SEE IT.
THAT'S OKAY.
YOUR TRIP'S GONNA
BE AMAZING.
HAVE YOU TOLD PETER YET?
PETER:
HUGE POST-GAME PARTY
AT MY HOUSE!
RAGER OF THE YEAR!
BE THERE!
DARCY,
YOU LEAVE TOMORROW!
YEAH, UM...
HE'S JUST SO EXCITED
ABOUT HIS PLACE
AND THIS PARTY...
WISH ME LUCK.
YEAH,
I NEED SOME OF THAT, TOO.
CALL ME LATER,
TELL ME HOW IT GOES?
I WILL.
(EXHALES)
ZERO DEGRASSI
FOOTBALL TROPHIES.
THIS YEAR,
I'D LIKE TO CHANGE THAT.
LOOK, YOU SAW ME.
I'M FAST, I CAN CATCH--
WHAT ABOUT A GIRLS' SPORT?
YOU TOOK AWAY
THEIR FUNDING
AND GAVE IT TO FOOTBALL,
REMEMBER?
YEAH, WELL,
FOOTBALL CAN BE DANGEROUS.
JANE:
I PLAYED RUGBY AT LAKEHURST.
IT'S BASICALLY THE SAME,
EXCEPT WITHOUT ANY PADDING.
I CAN DO THIS.
AND YOU'RE NOT DOING THIS
JUST TO MEET BOYS?
NO! NO!
WELL, THE BOARD SAYS
I CAN'T EXCLUDE YOU
FROM PLAYING, SO...
GRAB EQUIPMENT
FROM ONE OF THE GUYS
AND SHOW UP TO PRACTICE.
I WILL NOT LET YOU DOWN,
COACH.
OH, AND ONE MORE THING.
IF YOU'RE ON THE BOYS' TEAM,
THAT MAKES YOU ONE OF THE BOYS.
NO SPECIAL TREATMENT.
UNDERSTOOD?
YEAH.
HMM.
HOLLY J:
PLAYING ON THE BOYS TEAM,
BUT CHANGING WITH THE GIRLS?
SOUNDS LIKE THE DREAM
OF A BUDDING LESBIAN.
ANYA:
HEY, I LIKE IT
THAT SHE'S IN HERE.
BETTER THAN IN THE BOYS' ROOM,
OGLING MY SAV.
WHATEVER.
IT'S AMAZING
THAT YOU'RE PLAYING.
THIS TEAM COULD SERIOUSLY USE
YOUR OLD RUGBY SKILLS.
UH, I DON'T KNOW MUCH
ABOUT FOOTBALL, HON,
BUT YOU SHOULD BE BIGGER
ON TOP.
THE GUYS MUST'VE FORGOTTEN
TO GIVE ME MY SHOULDER PADS.
SEE? SHE'S TOO SMALL
FOR FOOTBALL.
THAT'S VERY FUNNY.
WHERE ARE MY PADS?
GUYS:
(LAUGH)
I THINK I GOT ONE.
BRUCE AND RILEY:
(MOCKING LAUGHTER)
FOR THOSE HEAVY FLOW DAYS.
THERE'S GONNA BE SOME
BLOOD LOSS OUT THERE.
BRUCE:
(CHUCKLING)
FORTUNATELY,
THIS IS ALL THE PADDING
I'LL NEED
AGAINST YOU WIMPS.
BRUCE:
(LAUGHING)
P.A. ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION, STUDENTS.
PLEASE WELCOME DEGRASSI'S
NEW ART TEACHER, MS. DAWES.
HER CLASSROOM WILL BE OPEN
FOR FREE ART EXPRESSION
ALL WEEK.
GAVE OUT ALL THE INVITES.
THIS IS GONNA BE HUGE!
JUST GOTTA GET FOOD
AND DRINKS.
I, UM, CAN'T.
AH, THAT'S COOL.
I CAN GET THE GUYS TO HELP
WHEN THEY'RE DONE PRACTICE.
I'M GOING TO KENYA.
LIKE AFRICA?
WHAT? WHEN?
TOMORROW.
I'M GOING TO HELP
BUILD A SCHOOL
IN A VILLAGE
NEAR NAIROBI.
IT'S AN AMAZING
OPPORTUNITY
AND I HAVE TO...
LEAVE?
WHEN DID YOU DECIDE
THIS?
A WHILE AGO.
BUT I DIDN'T WANNA HURT YOU.
SO TELLING ME
AT THE LAST MINUTE HURTS LESS?
PETER,
IT'S ONE SEMESTER.
I'M GOING TO HELP CHILDREN.
CAN'T SOMEONE ELSE
HELP THEM?
LOOK, I KNOW
IT'S GONNA BE HARD,
BUT WE CAN WRITE
AND CALL.
WHAT, FOR FOUR MONTHS?
WHEN MY MOM LEFT
I STAYED FOR YOU.
I'M ALONE HERE.
PETER,
YOU KNOW I LOVE YOU.
(METALLIC THUNK AND SQUEAK,
LOCK RATTLES)
YOU KNOW WHAT? GO.
I'LL SEE YOU
WHEN YOU GET BACK.
(MARCHING BAND PLAYS,
CROWD CHEERS AND WHISTLES)
PLAYERS:
FIVE!
SIX!
SEVEN!
EIGHT!
AT FULL BACK,
SAV BHANDARI.
(BAND PLAYS,
CROWD CHEERS)
ALLI:
YAY SAV!
WHAT'S A FULL BACK?
HE BLOCKS AND SOMETIMES
CARRIES THE BALL.
SHEP:
AT TIGHT END...
DEREK HAIG.
CROWD:
(CHEERING AND WHISTLING)
HE BLOCKS, TOO;
THERE'S A LOT OF BLOCKING.
SHEP:
AT WIDE RECEIVER,
JANE VAUGHAN.
YEAH, JANE!
YES!
(EVERYBODY STOPS CHEERING
EXCEPT MIA)
WHAT THE--?
YEAH, BABE!
(ENCOURAGING WHISTLE)
SHEP:
AT CENTRE...
BRUCE THE MOOSE!
CROWD:
(CHEERING AND WHISTLING)
(PLAYERS WHOOP AND HOLLER)
CROWD:
(CHEERING WILDLY)
DANNY:
TEN-HUT!
♪ Yes, I can make it
through this ♪
(FORCEFUL IMPACT,
CROWD CHEERS)
DANNY:
TEN-HUT!
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS,
PLAYERS HOLLER TO EACH OTHER)
(CROWD APPLAUDS)
(FORCEFUL IMPACT)
CROWD:
(CHEERING)
MISSED A PLAY, DANNY!
WAKE UP!
(FORCEFUL IMPACTS)
(CROWD LAUGHS,
WHISTLE BLOWS)
OKAY, THIS IS THE LAST PLAY.
COME ON.
COME ON, COME ON, COME ON.
DANNY:
MOVE! FLAT 18! FLAT 18!
TEN-HUT!
(CROWD CHEERS)
HE'S GOT JANE OPEN.
THROW TO JANE!
(FORCEFUL IMPACT,
HELMETS CLATTER)
DEREK MISSED THE BLOCK!
NICE WORK, LADY.
CROWD:
(CHEERING AND WHISTLING)
(CROWD CHEERS WILDLY,
GAME WHISTLE BLOWS)
(CAR WHIRS BY,
LIVELY MUSIC PLAYS FROM INSIDE)
HIGH SCHOOL PARTIES
ARE AWESOME.
THANKS FOR INVITING US,
PETER.
I'M SURE THAT MY SISTER
WISHES SHE WAS HERE.
PETER:
YEAH, I'M SURE SHE DOES.
(MUSIC PLAYS,
LOW DIN OF CHATTER)
IT'S YOUR PARTY
AND YOU'LL CRY IF YOU WANT TO?
HEY!
I'M KIDDING.
I KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO BE LEFT ALONE.
OH YEAH?
MY DAD, LUCAS,
AND MOST RECENTLY...
(MUTED CHATTER)
I GUESS I JUST EXPECT HER
TO WALK THROUGH THE DOOR
AND APOLOGIZE
OR WHATEVER.
THAT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN,
IS IT?
UNLESS SHE'S LIKE DANNY,
AND SHOWS UP
JUST TO IGNORE YOU ALL NIGHT.
HE MUST BE WORKING
PRETTY HARD
TO IGNORE SOMEONE
WHO LOOKS LIKE YOU.
HE'S GOT HIS REASONS,
I GUESS.
WHATEVER THEY ARE,
IT DOESN'T BOTHER ME.
THE PAST IS LIKE...
IT'S OVER.
I COULDN'T AGREE MORE.
THIS PARTY KINDA BLOWS.
YOU WANNA GO FOR A WALK
OR SOMETHING?
I'D LIKE THAT.
(MUSIC PLAYS,
PARTYGOERS CHATTER)
STUDENTS:
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
SO TONIGHT?
SOME ALONE TIME
AT THE DOT?
IF I SURVIVE PRACTICE.
I MEAN, THEY HATED ME
BEFORE THE GAME...
EVERYBODY ON THE SIDELINES
SAW THAT IDIOT
MISS THE BLOCK.
I KNOW.
BUT, ON THE FIELD,
ALL THEY SAW WAS A GIRL
FUMBLING THE BALL.
YOU'RE THE BEST PLAYER
OUT THERE.
YOU HAVE TO SAY THAT.
IT'S MY TEAMMATES
I NEED TO CONVINCE.
BRUCE:
JANE!
(LAUGHING)
THAT MIGHT NOT BE
TOO EASY.
DEREK:
THIS IS GOOD, HUH?
OH!
GIRLY-SIZED
JUST FOR YOU.
LOOK, I CAUGHT THE BALL,
OKAY?
YOU MISSED THE BLOCK.
I WOULD'VE SCORED.
WHOA, WHOA!
EXCUSES.
SOMETHING GIRLS ARE GOOD AT.
YOU TOO, DANNY?
WHAT?
IT'S JUST A FUNNY SHIRT.
NO. NO, IT'S NOT.
OKAY?
TAKE THEM OFF.
TAKE THEM OFF, NOW!
WHOA, WHOA.
I DON'T THINK
I GOT ANYTHING ON UNDERNEATH.
I THINK SHE WANTS A SHOW.
(LAUGHS)
DEREK:
OKAY, OKAY.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S WORSE:
THIS SHIRT OR DEREK SHIRTLESS?
RILEY AND DEREK:
(LAUGH)
MIA:
YOU GUYS FINALLY GET
A GOOD PLAYER
AND THIS IS HOW YOU TREAT HER?
NOT FOR MUCH LONGER.
WHAT?
RILEY:
WHATEVER.
HEY, SO DETAILS, MAN.
HOW FAR'D YOU GET?
OH, NOT VERY.
I IGNORED SOME TEXT
MESSAGES FROM DARCY,
SO I SORTA FEEL BAD NOW.
BAD ABOUT WHAT?
UH...
I SORTA HOOKED UP WITH SOMEONE
LAST NIGHT.
SWEET, DUDE.
WHO'S THE LUCKY LADY?
MIA.
DARCY FOR MIA?
THAT'S LIKE TRADING IN
A PORSCHE
FOR A BUS PASS.
AH, OOH-OOH.
I SHOULD ALSO LEAVE QUICKLY.
HEY.
THANKS FOR THE WALKING TOUR
OF THE 'HOOD LAST NIGHT.
I NEEDED IT.
YEAH, ABOUT THAT,
I WAS THINKING...
YOU DON'T WANT TO GIVE ME
ANOTHER TOUR.
I THOUGHT WE CONNECTED.
IT'S JUST...
I'M NOT READY
FOR ANYTHING...
SO I WAS JUST...
A REBOUND?
NO.
IT'S COMPLICATED.
IT'S TOO BAD,
BECAUSE AS MESSED UP
AS WE BOTH ARE,
I THOUGHT THAT THERE MIGHT BE
SOMETHING HERE.
WHATEVER.
(PLASTIC WRAPPER CRINKLES)
'KAY, GUYS.
OKAY, ENOUGH CHATTER.
NOW, LISTEN UP.
COME ON, LISTEN UP!
HERE WE GO.
THE GUYS WORE THESE
ALL DAY.
WELL, LISTEN, I GAVE 'EM
A STERN WARNING.
THEY WERE JUST DEALING
WITH THE LOSS, RIGHT?
PLAYERS:
(MURMURS OF AGREEMENT)
EXACTLY. YEAH.
SIMPSON:
YEAH, SHEP,
WHAT ABOUT THE FEMALE HALF
OF THE STUDENT BODY?
IT CAN'T BE CONDONED,
ALL RIGHT?
SHEP:
WHOA! WHOA, COWBOY.
OKAY, I'LL HANDLE IT.
OKAY, GUYS.
LISTEN UP.
IT APPEARS THESE T-SHIRTS
ARE OFFENSIVE TO GIRLS.
ER, YOU KNOW, "WOMEN."
SO, UH...
YOU'RE GONNA NEED SOME
SENSITIVITY TRAINING.
SO BEFORE WE HIT
THE FIELD TODAY,
DOWN-UPS
TILL YOU CRY.
THAT'LL GET YOU IN TOUCH
WITH YOUR EMOTIONS.
PLAYERS:
(MUTTERED COMPLAINTS)
WHAT?
WHINING. OH GREAT START.
YEAH, LET'S GO. LET'S GO.
ON THE HOP.
LET'S GO.
PLAYERS: (MUTTERING
BITCH! COACH, THAT'S NOT FAIR!
HAPPY?
YOU TOO. OKAY?
THE DRILL'S
FOR THE WHOLE TEAM.
WE CAN'T WIN UNLESS
WE'RE ALL ON THE SAME SIDE.
PLAYERS:
(EXHAUSTED MOANS)
MAN, I'M SO SPENT.
IF ONLY LITTLE
MISS LINEBACKER
COULD TAKE A JOKE.
BRUCE:
OR A HIT.
DEREK:
(SNICKERS)
OH! OH, STAYING STRONG?
AH, TOO BAD YOU COULDN'T
ON GAME DAY.
JANE:
YOU CAN'T EVEN TAKE A HIT
FROM A GIRL;
YOU'RE PATHETIC!
DEREK:
YOU WANNA BE A TOUGH GUY?
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN A TOUGH GUY
SUCKER PUNCHES A DUDE!
RILEY:
I THINK SHE'S GOT THE POINT,
MAN.
(GASPS IN PAIN)
RILEY:
CALM DOWN!
(GASPING FOR BREATH)
SHEP:
LADIES? LISTEN.
AS LOMBARDI SAID,
"PRACTICE DOES NOT MAKE PERFECT.
ONLY PERFECT PRACTICE
MAKES PERFECT."
THOSE THREE JUST JUMPED ME
IN THE HALL.
YOU GONNA DO SOMETHING NOW?
BRUCE:
SHE PUSHED DEREK FIRST.
I DIDN'T TOUCH HER.
YOU HIT HER?
NOT COOL, DUDE.
IT WAS SELF-DEFENSE.
BULL!
YOU SLAMMED ME INTO LOCKERS,
KNOCKED ME DOWN
AND KICKED ME!
ALL RIGHT, ENOUGH!
YOU KNOW WHAT THIS IS?
THIS IS JUST A SCUFFLE
BETWEEN TEAMMATES.
YEAH, THAT'S IT.
NOW, I CAN SUSPEND
ALL FOUR OF YOU
AND WE'LL FORFEIT
NEXT GAME
OR YOU CAN WORK OUT
YOUR DIFFERENCES.
COME ON!
LOOK, BOYS'LL BE BOYS.
I TOLD YOU:
NO SPECIAL TREATMENT.
(DISGUSTED EXHALE)
(MUSIC PLAYS
WITHIN THE DOT)
(DOOR CHIMES JINGLE)
HEY!
PEYTON JANE-ING!
YOU'RE READY
FOR OUR DATE.
WHAT, TACKLING PRACTICE
WITH A MACK TRUCK TODAY?
NO, I JUST CAUGHT AN ELBOW
THROUGH MY FACE MASK.
I'LL BE OKAY.
'KAY, 'CAUSE I HAVE
OUR OWN
LITTLE TACKLING PRACTICE
PLANNED.
(GASPS) OW.
JANE, ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE OKAY?
UM, DEREK AND SOME GUYS
JUMPED ME AFTER PRACTICE.
LIKE HIT YOU?
DEREK'S A DEAD MAN.
NO, SPIN, I CAN FIGHT
MY OWN BATTLES, OKAY?
SO I CAN'T EVEN DEFEND
MY GIRLFRIEND NOW?
(CHAIR CLATTERS)
WHAT ABOUT DANNY?
SAV?
THE-THE COACH?
NO ONE DID ANYTHING?
NO, THEY WEREN'T THERE.
THEY WEREN'T THERE, OKAY?
DANNY FELT BAD,
BUT HE HAS NO IDEA
HOW TO HELP,
AND THAT ASS OF A PRINCIPAL
SIDED WITH DEREK.
LOOK, YOU HAVE
TO TELL SOMEBODY.
I-I CAN'T SNITCH.
THAT'S WHAT THEY EXPECT ME
TO DO.
BUT IF YOUR TEAM'S
AGAINST YOU,
YOU COULD GET REALLY HURT.
I JUST WANNA PLAY FOOTBALL.
IS PLAYING FOOTBALL
REALLY WORTH ALL THIS?
STUDENTS:
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
I HAVE TO GO
TO THE OFFICE.
I KNOW,
I CALLED YOU.
USED AN OLD MOM-WAS-
THE-PRINCIPAL TRICK.
I THOUGHT THIS
WAS TOO COMPLICATED.
LOOK,
YOU'RE NOT A REBOUND.
YOU CAN'T...
YOU CAN'T HELP
WHEN YOU MEET PEOPLE,
AND YOU'RE GREAT.
AND PRETTY.
I MEAN,
YOU'RE A MODEL.
WHAT I'M TRYING
TO SAY IS,
WE DID CONNECT AT MY PARTY
AND I DO THINK
WE SHOULD HANG OUT AGAIN.
YOU'RE NOT RUSHING
INTO SOMETHING
JUST TO RUSH OUT AGAIN?
NO. NO RUSHING.
WE'LL JUST TAKE IT SLOW,
OR WHATEVER.
HOW 'BOUT THE SPEED OF...
"MEET ME FOR LUNCH?"
(PHONE RINGS)
DARCY SENT US SOME PRESENTS
BY AIRMAIL FROM THE AIRPORT.
OH, THANKS.
IT WAS SO AWESOME
IN THAT GAME
HOW YOU MADE THAT...
RECEPTION.
WE'RE GETTING
SOME GIRLS TOGETHER
TO MAKE POSTERS
FOR THE NEXT GAME.
UH, THERE MIGHT NOT BE
A NEXT GAME.
I'M GOING TO QUIT.
BUT YOU CAN'T QUIT.
YOU'RE OUR HERO.
UH... I, I DON'T KNOW.
(PAPER RUSTLES)
(HALF LAUGHS)
SHE HELPS PACK MY LUNCH
AND MAKES SURE THAT MY GRAPES
ARE ALWAYS CUT IN HALF.
YOU MUST BE SICK
OF IZZY STORIES.
NO,
I'VE GOT A BABY SISTER.
SHE'S JUST A LITTLE BLOB
RIGHT NOW
AND I'M GLAD SHE'LL BE
MORE ENTERTAINING.
DELIVERY.
SEE?
DARCY MISSES YOU.
YEAH, THANKS.
I'LL OPEN IT LATER.
(LOW MURMUR OF CHATTER)
LIKE MAYBE NEVER.
(BELL RINGS)
UH, SO WALK ME TO CLASS?
UH, I HAVE TO FIND SAV
AND TALK ABOUT STUDZ STUFF.
AFTER SCHOOL,
I'LL SEE YOU?
(PAPER RUSTLES)
(SIGHS)
SHEP:
OKAY, GUYS, LISTEN UP.
TAKE A KNEE.
LET'S GO! ON THE MOVE!
COME ON, DRESS IT UP.
NOW, AS MY MAIN MAN VINCE SAYS,
"THE ONLY PLACE SUCCESS
COMES BEFORE WORK
IS IN THE DICTIONARY."
YOU--YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE HERE.
WHERE YOU'RE GIVING
THE PEP TALK?
LOOK, I KNOW YOU WANT ME
TO QUIT--
MOST OF YOU DO--
BUT I LOVE FOOTBALL
AND I'M GOOD AT IT,
SO I'M NOT QUITTING.
I'LL CHANGE IN MY ROOM--
I DON'T WANNA SEE
ANYONE'S TINY JUNK--
BUT I'M GONNA BE IN HERE
FOR THESE TALKS
BECAUSE I AM A PART
OF THIS TEAM.
JUDGING BY RECENT EVENTS,
I'M NOT SURE
THE REST OF THE GUYS AGREE.
SHE'S ON MY TEAM.
MINE TOO.
RILEY:
SHE IS A GOOD PLAYER.
SO BE IT.
(HELMET CLATTERS)
ALL RIGHT, ENOUGH.
TAKE-TAKE A KNEE, TEAM.
LET'S GO.