SO, WHAT'S THIS MEETING
FOR EXACTLY?
THE CHOICES YOU MAKE
IN GRADE ELEVEN
CAN IMPACT
THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
NO PRESSURE.
WELL, THIS IS WHEN DOORS
BEGIN TO CLOSE.
HOLLY J:
NOT ON ME.
I MAINTAIN A 93 AVERAGE
WITH A PART TIME JOB,
STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT
DUTIES,
AND VOLUNTEER WORK
WITH FREE THE CHILDREN.
AND WHAT COURSES
ARE YOU CONSIDERING?
SAV:
CALCULUS, PHYSICS.
PREREQUISITES
FOR ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING.
WHY ENGINEERING?
UH, IT'S STABLE.
RUNS IN THE FAMILY.
BUT...
I'D ALSO REALLY LIKE
TO TAKE THE
MUSIC MASTER CLASS.
HM.
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE IT CONFLICTS
WITH PHYSICS NEXT TERM,
SO IT'S ONE OR THE OTHER.
DID YOU JUST
SAY I'M FAILING?!
IF YOU DON'T PULL UP
YOUR ENGLISH GRADE,
YOU'LL HAVE TO REPEAT IT.
I'M ALREADY A YEAR BEHIND.
WELL, PERHAPS MODELING
IS GETTING IN THE WAY
OF YOUR ACADEMIC FUTURE.
IT'S NOT GETTING IN THE WAY.
IT HELPED ME
GET ONTO SPIRIT SQUAD.
SAVE UP FOR UNIVERSITY,
UH, SUPPORT MY CHILD.
SAUVE:
I UNDERSTAND.
BUT THERE ARE OPTIONS THAT
MIGHT ALLOW YOU TO WORK LESS
AND FOCUS MORE ON SCHOOL.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THANK YOU FOR YOUR CONCERN,
BUT I CAN HANDLE BOTH.
I HAVE TO.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Oh! Oh! Oh! ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
I CAN'T LOOK.
I DON'T WANNA KNOW.
(DISAPPOINTED SIGH)
ANYA:
DON'T WORRY.
I MESSED UP TOO.
WHAT CAN I DO
TO IMPROVE MY GRADE?
KWAN:
I'VE GIVEN YOU EXTENSIONS
AND SECOND CHANCES
ON EVERY ASSIGNMENT.
IF I FAIL I'LL GONNA HAVE
TO REDO THE WHOLE TERM,
MS. KWAN. PLEASE.
OKAY.
I'LL COUNT YOUR PUBLIC SPEECH
FOR 60 PERCENT OF YOUR GRADE.
THANK YOU.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
REMINDER:
TOPIC FOR PUBLIC SPEAKING
IS "WHERE YOU SEE YOURSELF
IN FIVE YEARS AND WHY".
LAST ASSIGNMENT
FOR THE TERM, CLASS.
IMPRESS ME.
YOU SHOULD DO A RUNWAY WALK
INSTEAD.
WIND IN THE HAIR!
(GIGGLES)
STUDY SESH TONIGHT?
DEFINITELY. UNLESS...
OH SHOOT!
I HAVE TO WORK.
TELL ME YOU'VE FINISHED
YOUR SPEECH.
OH YEAH.
JUST WORKING ON MY CONCLUSION.
(EXHALES)
DAWES:
IT MAKES ME FEEL...
LONELY.
BLUE,
I BESTOW YOU WITH AN "A".
GOOD JOB!
THANK YOU.
WATCH ME MAKE MAMMA PROUD.
DAWES:
ALL RIGHT, HOLLY J.
TALK TO US.
WELL, IT TOOK ME EIGHT HOURS.
THE PROPORTIONS ARE FLAWLESS.
DAWES:
OKAY.
UM...
BLUE, THOUGHTS?
BLUE:
UM, I APPRECIATE THE REALISM.
BUT WHAT'S THE EMOTIONAL
PERSPECTIVE?
(SCOFFS) IT'S FRUIT.
DOESN'T HAVE FEELINGS.
DAWES:
THE ASSIGNMENT WAS
TO INTERPRET THE FRUIT BOWL
THROUGH AN EMOTION.
NOT JUST COPY IT.
BUT I'M GONNA BE GENEROUS
AND I'M GONNA GIVE YOU A "C".
MS. DAWES?!
(HUFFS) I WORKED
REALLY HARD ON THIS.
I DON'T DOUBT THAT
FOR A SECOND.
WELL, THEN GRADE ME
APPROPRIATELY.
I COULDN'T HAVE DONE
A BETTER JOB.
YOU FAILED TO GRASP
THE POINT OF THE ASSIGNMENT.
BUT IN RECOGNITION
OF YOUR HARD WORK,
UM, YOU CAN TRY IT AGAIN.
WHY? I DID IT RIGHT
THE FIRST TIME.
NO. NO YOU DIDN'T.
SEE, THERE'S NO...
THERE'S NO EMOTION IN THIS.
WELL, THAT'S YOUR OPINION.
(STUDZ PLAYS ROCK SONG)
PETER:
♪ MY FRIENDS ARE GONE ♪
♪ THE CITY SLEEPS ♪
♪ I'M ALL ALONE
MY COMPUTER BEEPS ♪
♪ THEY CALLED TO... ♪
PETER AND SAV:
♪ GOOGLE MY OWN NAME
GOOGLE MY OWN NAME ♪
PETER:
♪ SOME DUDE IN INDIANA ♪
♪ GOOGLE MY OWN NAME ♪
PETER AND SAV:
♪ GOOGLE MY OWN NAME!
GOOGLE MY OWN NAME! ♪
YEAH!
(LINGERING GUITAR NOTES PLAY,
CYMBALS RATTLE AND OUTRO)
SWEET HARMONY, YOU GUYS.
YEAH. GUYS.
COULD YOU IMAGINE DOING THIS
EVERY DAY,
LIKE, FOREVER?
WHY COULDN'T YOU?
WELL, IT'S NOT REALLY
PART OF MY PLAN.
OH RIGHT, THE PLAN.
ENGINEERING, INFINITY SEDAN,
MARRYING ANYA,
THREE KIDS...
SPINNER: (CHUCKLES)
CONCEIVED TO JOSH GROBAN'S
BEST OF!
PETER:
(LAUGHS)
SAV:
I CAN STILL PLAY
ON THE WEEKENDS.
BUT CAN'T TAKE MUSIC WITH YOU
NEXT TERM.
CONFLICTS WITH PHYSICS.
DANNY:
TAKE PHYSICS NEXT YEAR!
MASTER CLASS IS ONLY OFFERED
NEXT TERM.
ONCE IN A LIFETIME, MAN.
THEN I CAN'T TAKE ENGINEERING
IN UNIVERSITY.
IT'S TIME TO START THINKING
LONG-TERM.
MUSIC'S GOTTA TAKE
A BACK-SEAT.
PETER:
OH YEAH, 17 YEARS OLD.
TIME TO GIVE UP
ON YOUR DREAMS.
(SNORTED CHUCKLE)
PRINCIPAL SHEPPARD!
YEAH?
WHICH DO YOU LIKE BETTER?
OH.
THIS ONE. OBVIOUSLY.
EXACTLY!
THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
BUT DAWES-
WAIT.
MS. DAWES?
SHE GAVE ME A 'C'
AND DEATH STAR HERE AN 'A'.
OKAY THEN.
CLEARLY DEATH STAR IS BETTER.
BUT YOU JUST SAID-
TEACHER RULE
THE CLASSROOM.
(SNAPS FINGERS)
PHOO!
(HUM OF CHATTER)
MY KID IS GONNA HATE ME.
WE'RE THREE HOURS BEHIND.
WHAT?
MM.
NO, WE CAN'T BE!
I'M NOT GETTING ANY WORK DONE.
I'M TOTALLY FAILING IN LIFE.
IF YOU WERE MY KID,
YOU'D BE AT HOME STUDYING.
(SIGHS)
I TRIED TO CANCEL.
MY AGENT SAID
IT WAS TOO LATE.
MMM... DON'T STRESS,
WHEN IS IT DUE?
TOMORROW MORNING.
I'LL LEAVE YOU TO IT THEN.
(MUSIC PLAYS,
HUM OF CHATTER)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
(UKULELE PLAYS FOLK-LIKE TUNE)
HEY. HEY MR. FOWLER.
HEY.
HERE TO AUDITION?
WELL, NO.
I GOTTA TAKE PHYSICS
NEXT TERM.
WELL, DO YOU PLAY?
YEAH.
BUT I GOT PREREQUISITES
FOR ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING.
ROCK STAR'S NOT GONNA
PAY THE BILLS.
OKAY, NOT A ROCK STAR.
WHAT ABOUT A RECORD PRODUCER?
AUDIO ENGINEER?
COMPOSER?
THOSE JOBS ARE ALL
TOO IMPOSSIBLE TO GET.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I MEAN, NOT EVERYTHING
YOU TAKE RIGHT NOW
NEEDS TO BE ABOUT A CAREER.
EXPERIMENT A LITTLE.
TRIAL AND ERROR.
(SAV PLUCKS
AND STRUMS UKULELE)
(PLAYS UKULELE)
YOU JUST TUNED THAT,
BY EAR,
IN LESS THAN A MINUTE.
UM...
UH, THANKS FOR YOUR TIME,
SIR, BUT...
I GOTTA GO.
I'M HERE.
IF YOU WANT TO AUDITION,
THANKS AGAIN.
(CLASS DOOR OPENS)
KWAN:
WELCOME TO THE PODIUM.
YOU'RE LATE, MS. JONES.
WHO'D LIKE TO GO FIRST?
HOLLY J:
MY TOP CHOICES ARE SCIENCE
AND POLY-SCI AND MCGILL.
PEOPLE ALWAYS WONDER
IF IT'S MY PARENTS
WHO PUSHED ME TO ACCOMPLISH
AS MUCH AS I DO.
BUT, IT COMES FROM ME.
ANYTHING YOU THROW AT ME...
ANYA:
...KNEW THAT
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE
I WANTED TO SAVE ANIMALS.
I WOULD LIKE TO BE
A VETERINARIAN.
STATISTICALLY, IT'S MORE
DIFFICULT TO GET INTO VET
SCHOOL
THAN IT IS TO GET INTO REGULAR
MED SCHOOL.
WHICH MAKES SENSE,
BECAUSE VETS TREAT MORE
THAN JUST ONE SPECIES.
SAV:
...STRUCTURES AND MACHINES
WE INTERACT WITH EVERYDAY.
WHILE SCIENTISTS
DISCOVER THE WORLD,
ENGINEERS CREATE IT.
I LOOK FORWARD
TO A REWARDING CAREER
BRINGING INNOVATIVE IDEAS
INTO FRUITION.
(APPLAUSE)
THANK YOU, SAVTAJ.
MIA. YOU'RE NEXT.
MS. KWAN, FELLOW CLASSMATES.
I AM HERE TODAY
TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT WHERE I SEE MYSELF
IN FIVE YEARS AND WHY...
MARINE BIOLOGIST...
(HALF LAUGHS)
IS WHAT I WANT TO BE.
WHY? YOU MAY ASK.
BECAUSE...
I'VE ALWAYS LOVED DOLPHINS?
(CLASS LAUGHS)
SHE'S GOTTA BE KIDDING.
(LAUGHTER)
THIS HAS COST YOU
YOUR TERM!
YOU NEED TO RE-EVALUATE
YOUR PRIORITIES.
YOU DON'T KNOW ME! DON'T TELL ME
ABOUT MY PRIORITIES.
(PIANO PLAYS
LIGHT BALLET MUSIC)
ANNA:
HOW WAS YOUR DAY AT SCHOOL?
MIA: ACTUALLY...
ISABELLA: MOMMY!
MIA:
BABY!
HEY MUNCHKIN!
YOU SHOW MOMMY HOW TO DO
A PLIE LATER?
MS. LYDIA SAYS
SHE SHOULD TAKE
THREE CLASSES PER WEEK
IF SHE WANTS TO CONTINUE
MOVING UP.
SO EXPENSIVE.
IZZY LOVES IT.
SO SHE'LL DO IT.
YOU KNOW, I WASN'T SURE ABOUT
THIS MODELLING THING AT FIRST.
BUT IT'S BEEN
SUCH A BLESSING FOR US.
(MUSIC PLAYS,
LIVELY CHATTER)
I FEEL LIKE SUCH A FAILURE.
HOW DO YOU BALANCE THIS
WITH SCHOOL?
(HALF LAUGHS)
DROPPED OUT IN GRADE 10
AFTER I GOT SCOUTED.
SMARTEST THING I EVER DID.
DO YOU EVER MISS
BEING A REGULAR GIRL?
YOU MEAN
STRESSING OVER EXAMS
AND SCROUNGING FOR CASH?
GUESS NOT.
IT'S JUST HARD HAVING A FOOT
IN BOTH WORLDS.
THE WAY I SEE IT?
SCHOOL WILL ALWAYS BE THERE.
GIRLS LIKE US NEED TO
CASH IN WHILE WE CAN.
THIS IS OUR PRIME.
(MUSIC PLAYS,
HUM OF CHATTER)
♪ And it's all
you ever wanted ♪
PA ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION, STUDENTS.
WOULD DEREK HAIGE PLEASE REPORT
TO THE FRONT OFFICE.
DEREK HAIGE TO THE OFFICE.
ANYTHING ELSE
I NEED TO DO?
NO, I'LL INFORM YOUR TEACHERS
AND PRINCIPAL SHEPPARD.
AGAIN, ARE YOU SURE?
YEAH.
LEAVING SCHOOL IS
THE BEST THING FOR ME
RIGHT NOW.
OKAY. WELL...
DON'T FORGET TO CLEAN OUT
YOUR LOCKER BEFORE YOU GO.
RIGHT. UH...
MY LOCKER.
(FORCED BREATH)
PETER:
MIA! WAIT!
I HEARD.
YOU'RE MAKING A BIG MISTAKE.
OF COURSE YOU WOULD SAY THAT,
YOUR MOM'S A PRINCIPAL.
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
WHY, BECAUSE YOU GET
EVERYTHING HANDED TO YOU
AND I HAVE TO CHOOSE?
THIS ISN'T ABOUT MONEY.
YOU'RE GIVING UP.
ARE YOU LEAVING BECAUSE
OF WHAT HAPPENED WITH US?
BECAUSE OF ME?
(SCOFFS)
GET OVER YOURSELF.
(HEAVY INHALE AND EXHALE)
SHE WANTED ABSTRACT,
I'M GIVING HER ABSTRACT.
GOOD LUCK.
MS. DAWES!
I RE-DID THE ASSIGNMENT.
INTERESTING.
WHAT'S BEHIND IT?
IT'S A NATURAL GROWTH
OUT OF A NEED.
YOUR NEED FOR AN A?
I'M FAMILIAR WITH POLLOCK,
HOLLY J.
YOU COPIED THIS.
YOUR MARK REMAINS THE SAME.
YOU CAN'T PUNISH A STUDENT
FOR PRODUCING SOMETHING
OUT OF A TEXT BOOK.
THIS IS SCHOOL.
ART ISN'T GEOGRAPHY
OR SCIENCE.
IT NEEDS TO COME FROM WITHIN.
IT DOES!
I WORK HARD!
EVERY DAY!
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE DOING TO ME?
MAYBE...
MAYBE YOU'RE JUST
NOT MEANT FOR THIS.
(SCOFFS)
SOLID APPROACH.
TELLING STUDENTS
THEY CAN'T DO IT,
WHEN YOU'RE SOME...
FAILED ARTIST
WHO RESORTED TO TEACHING
BECAUSE NO ONE WOULD
BUY YOUR WORK.
IF YOU CAN'T DO, TEACH.
RIGHT?
I THINK YOU SHOULD
EXCUSE YOURSELF.
(SNORTED BREATH)
GLADLY.
(CLASSICAL JAZZ PLAYS)
UH, DAD,
I DON'T KNOW IF I WANNA BE
AN ENGINEER.
THIS SURPRISES ME.
YOU ALWAYS SAID
THIS IS WHAT YOU WANTED.
YE-YEAH.
BECAUSE I FELT PRESSURED TO.
BUT I THINK I WANNA
DO SOMETHING WITH MUSIC.
THIS IS A HOBBY, SAV.
I DIDN'T QUIT SCHOOL
TO PURSUE THE ACCORDION.
AS MUCH AS I LOVED IT.
DAD, I'M BEING SERIOUS.
AS AM I.
HOW CAN YOU RAISE A FAMILY
ON A MUSICIAN'S SALARY?
I DO NOT WANT MY SON
TO STARVE.
I WON'T STARVE.
YOU ALWAYS SAY
YOU AND MOM CAME HERE
SO THAT WE COULD HAVE
THE BEST.
THE BEST IS SEEING YOU
AND YOUR SISTER HAPPY.
SECURE.
SUCCESSFUL.
YOU NEED TO THINK REALISTICALLY
ABOUT THE FUTURE.
(BUS RUMBLES OFF)
(SAV PLAYS THE TRUMPET SLOPPILY)
(GRUNTS)
UH... S-SORRY.
I'M A LITTLE NERVOUS.
TAKE YOUR TIME.
(PLAYS TRUMPET TUNE SMOOTHLY)
IT'S ALWAYS BEEN SIMPLE.
WORK HARD,
GET GOOD GRADES.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO DO THIS.
THERE'S NO RIGHT
OR WRONG ANSWER.
ALL RIGHT?
JUST TRY.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHERE TO START.
HOW'RE YOU FEELING RIGHT NOW?
(HALF LAUGHS)
LIKE A DISASTER.
GO WITH THAT.
(PAPER RUSTLES AND CRINKLES)
(CRINKLING)
WHY WOULD YOU DO THIS?
I'M ALREADY A TEEN MOM
STATISTIC,
I THOUGHT I'D CONTRIBUTE
TO THE DROPOUT RATE.
IT'S NOT A JOKE.
IS THIS WHAT YOU WOULD WANT
FOR YOUR OWN DAUGHTER?
EVERY DAY AT SCHOOL
I FEEL LIKE
I'M NOT GOOD ENOUGH.
AND I WANNA SUPPORT YOU
AND IZZY.
YOU DON'T EVER NEED TO WORRY
ABOUT SUPPORTING THIS FAMILY.
WE DID JUST FINE
BEFORE MODELING.
YOUR EDUCATION COMES FIRST.
THIS IS MY DECISION.
OKAY?
I DON'T WANNA GO BACK.
(HEAVY SIGH)
ANNA:
REMEMBER WHAT YOU WANTED TO BE
WHEN YOU WERE LITTLE?
MOM.
ANNA:
YOU WANTED TO BE EVERYTHING.
BAKER. JUDGE.
FIRE-FIGHTER.
PRIME MINISTER.
VAMPIRE SLAYER!
I CAN'T HELP BUT WONDER
WHAT HAPPENED TO THAT GIRL.
SHE GREW UP.
YOU'RE NOT THINKING
LONG TERM.
I AM.
I'M BEING REALISTIC.
THEN AFTER MODELLING,
IF IT DOESN'T LAST?
WHAT WILL YOU DO?
(MUTED CHATTER AND LAUGHTER
OF CHILDREN)
IT'S OKAY NOT TO KNOW.
YOU JUST HAVE TO MAKE SURE
YOU HAVE THE TOOLS
TO FIGURE IT OUT.
(SNIFFLES)
HEY.
WHY ARE YOU CRYING MOMMY?
DO YOU HAVE A BOOBOO?
NO.
I JUST LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
CHANTAY:
...AND REMEMBER,
IN FIVE YEARS
WHEN TURN ON ETALK
OR PICK UP A COPY OF US WEEKLY,
LOOK FOR MY NAME.
BECAUSE MY FUTURE?
WILL BE ALL ABOUT REPORTING
ALL THOSE JUICY DETAILS.
(APPLAUSE)
KWAN:
CONGRATULATIONS, CLASS,
YOU HAVE MADE IT THROUGH
GRADE ELEVEN ENGLISH.
CLASS:
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
MIA:
I WAS WONDERING
IF I COULD JOIN YOU GUYS.
I HAVE A SPEECH
I'D LIKE TO SHARE.
YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED
TO BE HERE.
I'VE RE-REGISTERED.
MS. SAUVE GAVE ME A NOTE.
WELL, THAT'S NICE.
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
YOU GET ANOTHER SHOT
AT GIVING YOUR SPEECH.
THAT WOULDN'T BE FAIR
TO YOUR CLASSMATES.
PLEASE.
YOU CAN GIVE YOUR SPEECH
IF THEY'RE OKAY WITH IT.
OF COURSE WE ARE.
YEAH, LET'S HEAR IT.
BETTER BE GOOD, MS. JONES.
(SIGHS)
I UM...
DON'T REALLY KNOW WHERE
I SEE MYSELF IN FIVE YEARS.
AND I THINK THAT'S OKAY.
MY PLAN FOR NOW?
IS KEEP MY OPTIONS OPEN.
TAKE FRENCH AND HISTORY.
AIM FOR GENERAL ARTS.
BUT WITHIN THIS PLAN,
I HOPE
AND EXPECT
TO BE SURPRISED.
WHEN I WAS 12,
I HAD THIS...
PERFECT FUTURE
ALL MAPPED OUT.
...ORCHESTRA AND THEN
A REQUIRED INDUSTRY CO-OP
WITH A SYMPHONY
OR EVEN A RECORD LABEL.
AND I KNOW I HAVE TO BE
RATIONAL,
BUT, I WANNA START DOING THINGS
THAT INTEREST ME.
MR. BHANDARI:
I DO NOT WANT YOU
TO LIMIT YOUR FUTURE.
YOU ARE A BRIGHT YOUNG MAN.
NOTHING IS SET IN STONE.
IF I WANNA BE AN ENGINEER,
I'LL TAKE PHYSICS LATER.
FOR RIGHT NOW?
I'M PURSUING MY DREAM.
THIS DOES LOOK LIKE
A FASCINATING COURSE.
I JUST HOPE YOU ARE MAKING
THE RIGHT CHOICE.
MIA:
...THEN LIFE HAPPENED.
I HAD A DAUGHTER AT 13
AND SUDDENLY
I DIDN'T COME FIRST ANYMORE
I HAD TO ACCEPT A REALITY
THAT WAS VERY DIFFERENT
FROM THE ONE I ONCE IMAGINED...
I'M SORRY
FOR THE WAY I ACTED.
I TRIED AGAIN.
MAYBE THE OLD ONE'S BETTER...
MS. DAWES:
NO.
THIS IS A SINCLAIR ORIGINAL.
THIS UGLY THING IS RIGHT?
YES, BECAUSE IT'S YOUR
INTERPRETATION.
AN EXPRESSION.
BUT IT'S STILL
NOT VERY GOOD, IS IT?
LISTEN, I LOVE TO SING
IN THE SHOWER.
DOESN'T MEAN I'LL SELL OUT
CARNEGIE HALL ANYTIME SOON.
SO WILL I SEE YOU IN ART
NEXT TERM?
DON'T THINK SO.
BUT I'LL CONSIDER
ART APPRECIATION.
MIA:
THE UNEXPECTED
CAN BE TERRIFYING.
BUT I ENCOURAGE EACH OF YOU
TO EMBRACE IT.
BECAUSE SOMETIMES
IT'S THE THINGS
YOU DON'T ANTICIPATE
THAT MAKE THE BIGGEST IMPACT.
YOU CONVINCED YOUR PARENTS?
HOW?!
MIA:
SO, IT'S THE JOURNEY, RIGHT?
NOT THE DESTINATION.
AND HIGH SCHOOL,
I'VE DECIDED,
IS AN IMPORTANT PART
OF MY JOURNEY.
SAUVE:
WELL, EXAM WEEK IS GONNA BE
A LOT OF HARD WORK.
MATH FINAL TO ACE,
ENGLISH MAKE-UP
ASSIGNMENTS.
I KNOW.
AND WHAT ABOUT MODELING?
MIA:
STILL DOING IT.
BUT ONLY DURING HOLIDAYS
AND IN THE SUMMER.
SAUVE:
WELL, COMING BACK
TAKES A LOT OF COURAGE.
YOU SHOULD GIVE YOURSELF
A PAT ON THE BACK.
(HALF LAUGHS)
MAYBE AFTER EXAMS.
♪ Inside my heart
I know your... ♪
YOUR OFFICIAL WELCOME BACK?
ALREADY POSTED
ON THE ANTI-GRAPEVINE.
ANYA:
OH, WE MISSED YOU SO MUCH!
ANYA, I WAS ONLY GONE A DAY!
LUCKY I LET YOU BACK IN,
MAMMA MIA.
WITH GREAT RESPONSIBILITY
COMES GREAT POWER.
SAV:
UM, I KNOW MY SPIDEY QUOTES,
AND I'M THINK THAT'S
THE OTHER WAY AROUND.
WHATEVER.
NO ONE'S PERFECT.
STUDY SESH AT THE DOT?
WE'VE GOT EXAM WEEK
TO GET THROUGH.
LET'S DO IT.