♪♪♪
♪ Walking down the street ♪
♪ I see everyone
I've ever known ♪
♪ Walking down the street ♪
♪ Don't see anyone
I really know ♪
THEY WEREN'T KIDDING,
LOVE IS DEFINITELY IN THE AIR.
(CHUCKLES)
THAT MIGHT BE
SAV'S COLOGNE.
JANE:
YOU CAME TO DECORATE THE SCHOOL
BEFORE 6:30 PRACTICE?
ANOTHER UNSUCCESSFUL ATTEMPT
TO WIN ANYA BACK.
WELL, YOU WON'T BE
THE ONLY ONE FLYING SOLO
AT THE DANCE.
SPIN'S GOTTA WORK.
WHAT'S THE POINT OF A BOYFRIEND
WHO CAN'T TAKE YOU TO DANCES?
SOMETIMES YOU HAVE TO THINK
LONG TERM.
SPIN WORKS HARD TODAY,
SO WE CAN GO AWAY TO SCHOOL
TOGETHER NEXT YEAR.
HAS HE HEARD
FROM POLICE COLLEGE?
ANY DAY NOW.
AND I'LL BE PRE-LAW,
SO WE'LL BE OUR VERY OWN
"LAW & ORDER."
SOUNDS LIKE YOU GUYS
HAVE IT ALL FIGURED OUT.
WHOA.
POLICE SCHOOL.
BETTER SIT DOWN
FOR THIS.
(ENVELOPE CRINKLES AND RIPS)
(BRACING BREATH)
DEAR MR. MASON...
(LAUGHS)
WE REGRET TO INFORM YOU TH...
DAMN IT!
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
KC:
YOU REALLY THINK CLARE
WILL SAY YES?
ARE YOU KIDDING?
HOW COULD SHE SAY NO?
I AM SO EXCITED
FOR THIS DANCE.
JOHNNY:
YOU WANNA SPIN IN CIRCLES
WITH SWEATY TEEN BOYS?
BRUCE CAN MAKE THAT MAGIC
HAPPEN, RIGHT NOW.
COME ON, NINER.
(LAUGHS)
KC:
READY FOR DELIVERY.
WISH ME LUCK.
(HALF LAUGHS)
AW, THAT'S SWEET.
EVEN A GRADE NINE BOY
KNOWS HOW TO TREAT A LADY.
YEAH, WELL, WE'LL SEE
HOW HE TREATS THEM
AFTER THEY STOMP
ON HIS HEART.
SHE'LL SAY YES.
QUIT WORRYING.
WHAT WAS KC DOING
WITH THAT HEART?
SENDING CLARE A ROSE
TO ASK HER TO THE DANCE.
DON'T YOU DARE TELL.
SHE SHOULD GO WITH ME,
WE'RE BETTER FRIENDS!
SPINNER:
THERE'S GOTTA BE
SOME LOOPHOLE,
SOME WAY
YOU CAN LET ME IN.
YEAH, YOUR MARKS
ARE TOO LOW
AND YOUR PHYSICAL FITNESS TEST
ISN'T THERE EITHER.
I JUST FINISHED CHEMO
WHEN I TOOK THAT.
I CAN DO MUCH BETTER.
YOU'RE A CANCER SURVIVOR?
YES, SIR.
YOU'RE A FIGHTER.
THE FORCE NEEDS
PEOPLE LIKE YOU.
SO CAN MAKE AN EXCEPTION?
I DROVE TWO HOURS
TO GET HERE.
OKAY, UPGRADE YOUR MARKS,
MAYBE SOME NIGHT SCHOOL?
KEEP WORKING OUT.
I'LL PUT IN A GOOD WORD
WHEN YOU REAPPLY NEXT YEAR.
ONE YEAR.
KEEP YOUR EYES
ON THE PRIZE, OKAY?
I REALLY DO HOPE
TO SEE YOU NEXT YEAR.
LIBERTY:
YOU'RE SKIPPING '90S
DANCE-FIT?
IT'S ALL BOY BANDS
AND RESISTANCE BANDS.
HILARIOUS,
BUT I PROMISED KELLY
WE'D HANG OUT.
THIS AGAIN?
WHATEVER,
YOU CAN HAVE HIM.
BUT HE'LL HAVE
TO DETACH HIMSELF
FROM GWYNNIE FIRST.
KELLY:
WHAT A MARATHON.
OFFICE HOURS
WITH PROFESSOR POLLOCK?
BREAKUP WITH GWYNETH.
SHE SOBBED AND SOBBED...
AND WE ONLY WENT OUT
FOR A COUPLE WEEKS.
YOU HAVE THE WORST LUCK
WITH GIRLS.
JUST HAVEN'T FOUND SOMEONE
LIKE YOU, I GUESS.
BIG CONGRATULATIONS
TO TEAM DEGRASSI,
WHO WILL BRING PANTHRO HERE
TO THE BOT WARS FINALS
THIS WEEK.
STUDENTS:
(APPLAUD)
TOLD YOU YOUR DESIGN
WOULD QUALIFY.
ANYA:
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
DELIVERY...
...OF LOVE.
SO, THIS ONE'S FOR YOU.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
ANYA:
AND ANOTHER ONE.
ALLI:
I HAVE A REAL PROBLEM.
MINE'S BLANK.
A SECRET ADMIRER.
IT COULD BE ANYONE.
HOW DO I TELL HER THE TRUTH
ABOUT POLICE COLLEGE?
JAY:
DON'T.
WELL, SHE MIGHT
GET SUSPICIOUS WHEN,
YOU KNOW,
I NEVER START GOING.
HOLLY J:
THE WAY I SEE IT,
YOU HAVE TWO OPTIONS:
TELL HER NOW
OR TELL HER LATER.
DIFFERENCE BEING?
NO DIFFERENCE.
SHE BREAKS UP WITH YOU
EITHER WAY.
JAY:
MY SUGGESTION?
WORDS. VERBAL.
MAYBE WRITTEN.
A NICE LETTER.
PREFERABLY DELIVERED
FROM FAR AWAY.
JANE LOVES ME.
SHE'LL UNDERSTAND
IF WE HAVE TO BE APART
FOR A YEAR, RIGHT?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I KNOW WHAT TO DO.
I'LL GIVE HER THE BAD NEWS
WITH SOME GOOD NEWS.
WATCH THE PLACE FOR A BIT.
I'LL BE BACK BEFORE
YOUR SPARE'S OVER.
♪ Let's stop the lies... ♪
PERINO:
SO, IN 1791, QUEBEC SPLITS UP
INTO UPPER CANADA
AND LOWER CANADA.
WE'VE BEEN FEELING THE EFFECTS
OF THIS BREAKUP, EVER SINCE.
(KNOCKS ON DOOR)
MR. PERINO.
UH... COULD I TALK TO JANE
FOR A SECOND?
YOU CAN'T INTERRUPT CLASS,
MR. MASON.
BUT, HEY,
SINCE IT'S SWEETHEART WEEK,
KNOCK YOURSELF OUT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
CRAZY PERSON?
JANE...
WILL YOU GO TO
THE SWEETHEART DANCE WITH ME?
I THOUGHT YOU HAD
TO WORK.
I CLOSED THE DOT
FOR DANCE NIGHT;
YOU'RE THAT IMPORTANT
TO ME.
AW.
POLICE SCHOOL?
YOU GOT IN?
YEAH, I WANTED TO TALK
TO YOU ABOUT THAT.
I SPOKE TO THE RECRUITMENT GUY
AND-
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
YES, YES,
IT'S ALL VERY EXCITING, BUT-
SHEP:
VAUGHN.
GLAD I CAUGHT YOU.
LISTEN, GOOD NEWS.
YOU'VE BEEN CHOSEN
FOR THIS WEEK'S
NATIONAL YOUTH
LEADERSHIP SYMPOSIUM.
YOU AND VAN ZANDT.
(SPEECHLESS GASP)
THAT'S AWSE.
YOU'RE TO GIVE A SPEECH
ON GIRLS PLAYING FOOTBALL.
SO DON'T FORGET TO THANK
YOUR COACH.
WITH ME?
JANE: RIGHT.
SHEP: CONGRATS.
THANKS.
UM...
I SHOULD GET BACK TO CLASS,
BUT UH...
DINNER AFTER YOUR SHIFT
TO CELEBRATE MY LITTLE NEWS
AND YOUR BIG NEWS?
I WOULDN'T MISS IT
FOR THE WORLD, BABE.
(DOOR SHUTS)
(PANTHRO WHIRS)
CLARE:
OKAY, GOOD.
NOW PICK UP THE BALL.
(PANTHRO WHIRS)
IT'S NOT WORKING,
I DON'T GET IT.
THE TREAD ON THE CLAW
IS TOO SLIPPERY.
YEAH, MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT.
KC:
NO, IT'S THE ARM.
THERE'S SOMETHING WRONG
WITH THE MOTOR.
NO.
IT'S THE TREAD ON THE CLAW.
KC:
IT'S THE ARM.
THE MOTOR MUST BE
WIRED BACKWARDS.
NO, IT'S THE TREAD
ON THE CLAW.
WHY ARE YOU GUYS
ACTING LIKE IDIOTS?
BECAUSE...
YOU HAVEN'T DECIDED WHO'S
TAKING YOU TO THE DANCE.
THEN I JUST WON'T GO.
PERIOD.
I GOT THIS ROSE,
BUT I DON'T KNOW
WHO IT'S FROM.
ANY CLUES?
SORRY, UM, BUYER, SELLER
CONFIDENTIALITY.
THESE AREN'T STATE SECRETS.
(SCOFFS)
YOU'RE JUST MAD
BECAUSE NO ONE WILL TELL YOU
WHAT HOTTIE SENT ME THIS.
(SAV BANGS DESK)
YEAH, THERE'S...
NO CONFIDENTIAL THINGIE,
THERE'S JUST THINGS
YOUR BROTHER
DOESN'T NEED TO KNOW.
LIKE, I...
SENT THIS TO MYSELF.
SO YOU CAN TELL ME?
YEAH.
(INAUDIBLE WHISPER)
GLOBAL WARMING?
MORE LIKE
GLOBAL CLIMATE CRISIS.
PARTS OF THE WORLD
ARE ACTUALLY GETTING COOLER.
LIKE THIS HALLWAY?
WOW,
THAT WAS COLD.
GUESS HER IDEA
OF STAYING FRIENDS
WAS DIFFERENT THAN MINE.
WELL, YOU'VE STILL GOT ME
AND I'M ALL STUDIED OUT.
(PAPERS FLAP)
WILL YOU TEACH ME GUITAR?
ANYTHING IN PARTICULAR?
HOW ABOUT...
"MY BONNIE"?
IT WAS MY FAVOURITE SONG
AS A KID.
(HALF LAUGHS)
OKAY.
ONE HAND ON THE NECK.
MM-HMM.
NOW STRUM.
(STRUMS GUITAR)
'KAY.
HOW COME IT SOUNDS SO NICE
WHEN YOU PLAY?
YOU'VE GOT THESE DELICATE
LITTLE FINGERS,
PUT THEM ON TOP OF MINE.
NOW TRY.
(STRUMS GUITAR,
PLAYING A NEW CHORD)
UH, SO THAT'S A "C"
AND THEN, NEXT,
YOU'LL LEARN AN "F"
AND THEN YOU'LL BASICALLY
HAVE THE WHOLE SONG.
SPINNER:
JANE, I...
I KNOW YOU'RE REALLY EXCITED
ABOUT THIS WHOLE
POLICE COLLEGE THING.
BUT THERE'S SOMETHING YOU NEED
TO KNOW ABOUT IT THOUGH.
JANE: YEAH...
SPINNER: I...
(DOOR CHIMES OPEN)
STUDENTS:
SURPRISE! CONGRATULATIONS!
(NERVOUS CHUCKLE) GUYS!
AH, YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE.
AND THAT'S NOT ALL,
CRIME STOPPER.
JIMMY:
CONGRATULATIONS, MAN.
I KNEW YOU COULD
DO IT.
THANKS.
YOU MUST BE SO EXCITED
ABOUT POLICE COLLEGE.
JIMMY:
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE GONNA BE A COP.
I KNOW,
ME NEITHER.
ALLI:
ROBOTS AREN'T THE ONLY WAY
TO A GIRL'S HEART, YOU KNOW?
I GAVE HER THE ROSE.
WHAT ELSE
AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
SOMETIMES,
WHEN YOU LIKE SOMEONE,
YOU GOTTA PUT YOURSELF
OUT THERE.
TAKE A RISK.
I... LEFT MY SCIENCE NOTES
IN MY LOCKER.
CATCH YOU TOMORROW?
MR. SIMPSON
GAVE ME DETENTION TODAY.
I UH...
BACK-TALKED HIM.
WELL, YOU'RE NOT ON THE LIST,
SO, YOU CAN, UH,
SAVE ME YOUR SOB STORY AND...
TAKE A SEAT.
(WHISPERS)
THANKS FOR THE ROSE.
I THINK YOU GOT THE WRONG GUY,
BACKWOODS BHANDARI.
I DON'T DO FLORAL.
I KNOW IT WAS YOU,
I HAVE MY SOURCES.
LOOK, WE CAN'T DATE
OR ANYTHING.
I MEAN,
YOU'RE IN GRADE NINE.
MY FRIENDS WOULD MOCK US
AND YOUR BROTHER...
YOU DON'T EVEN
WANNA TRY?
FINE.
PERINO:
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, MISSY.
YOU CAN CHECK YOURSELF IN,
BUT ONLY I CAN CHECK YOU OUT.
SIT.
(MUSIC PLAYS,
LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
PETER:
I CAN'T BELIEVE IN A FEW YEARS
YOU'LL BE BUSTING PERPS.
YUP.
EH, YOU GUYS
WANT SOME COFFEE?
JANE:
OH, I'LL GET THEM.
IT'S YOUR PARTY.
PETER:
HEY, JANE, DOUBLE ESPRESSO.
SO THIS IS SOME STYLIN' CANE
YOU GOT HERE.
YEAH.
(HALF LAUGHS)
SO, STEM CELLS
DID YOU WELL THEN, HUH?
TRINA:
YEAH, YEAH.
I'M WALKING BETTER
AND YOU KNOW, JIMMY SEEMS TO BE
DOING A LOT BETTER TO.
JIMMY:
YEAH, YOU KNOW,
I'M WORKING OUT A LOT
AND UH, JURY'S STILL OUT
ON THE TREATMENT, BUT...
MY MOBILITY'S INCREASED,
SO...
IT'S WHATEVER.
IT'S SO PERFECT.
I'M GIVING A SPEECH
AT THE LEADERSHIP SYMPOSIUM,
SPIN'S OFF
TO POLICE SCHOOL...
AND ICING ON THE CAKE?
YOU WORKING AT THE DOT
SLINGING OUR DRINKS.
WELL, I DON'T THINK SPIN
WILL BE GIVING UP
HIS "DOT DRINK SLINGING"
ANYTIME SOON.
DON'T WANNA RUIN SPIN'S
REAL POLICE SCHOOL SURPRISE.
(CONFUSED HALF LAUGH)
EMMA:
I EVEN LET HIM TEACH ME GUITAR.
I THOUGHT THAT WAS BOY
MAKE-OUT BAIT?
MAYBE HE'S JUST PLAYING
HARD TO GET.
DYSON:
KEL, IT'S YOUR
"FLOOR GIRLFRIEND."
I HEARD YOUR MATING CALL
THIS AFTERNOON.
HE WAS TEACHING ME
A LULLABY.
BET HE WAS.
EASY, DYSON.
THERE IS NOTHING GOING ON
BETWEEN EMMA AND ME.
DYSON:
WHATEVER YOU SAY, BRO.
ULTIMATE?
OKAY.
MANNY:
HUH. HARSH.
(CLEARS THROAT)
MAYBE HE'S PLAYING
IMPOSSIBLE TO GET.
SO YOU MUST BE REALLY EXCITED
ABOUT POLICE COLLEGE?
I AM.
IT'S JUST LIKE WE PLANNED.
AND YOU'RE SURE THERE'S...
NOTHING YOU WANNA TELL ME
ABOUT GETTING IN?
NO.
GOOD.
GREAT.
DANNY:
YOU GET TO LIVE WITH SPIN
ALL NEXT YEAR,
QUIT HOGGIN' HIM.
WE WANNA HEAR
ABOUT COP SCHOOL.
PETER:
WHEN DO YOU GET TO DRIVE
THE CRUISER?
WHAT KIND OF COURSES
DO YOU TAKE?
SPINNER:
TICKET-WRITING,
HAND-CUFFING,
USING THAT...
POLICE BATON THINGIE.
YOU DIDN'T REALLY GET IN,
DID YOU?
NOT IMMEDIATELY.
UNBELIEVABLE.
I THREW YOU A PARTY,
I GOT YOU A CAKE,
HOW COULD YOU BE SO...
STUPID?
HAH.
BECAUSE MAYBE I AM STUPID.
TOO STUPID TO GET INTO
POLICE COLLEGE...
TOO STUPID FOR YOU.
NO, YOU'RE NOT STUPID,
LYING TO ME WAS.
KELLY:
WOO! (INVIGORATED EXHALE)
WHAT A BATTLE THAT WAS.
TWENTY 20 TO 18.
I SCORED SIX CALLAHANS.
IT'S WHEN YOU GET THE DISC
IN THE END ZONE.
THANKS.
UM...
IS THERE REALLY NOTHING
BETWEEN US?
(EXHALES)
WE'RE FRIENDS.
ROOMMATES.
WE CAN'T.
BUT...
I'M NOT IMAGINING THIS,
AM I?
I ALREADY LOST ONE FRIEND
THIS WEEK.
GWYNETH.
WELL, YOU GUYS WEREN'T REALLY
FRIENDS TO BEGIN WITH.
RIGHT.
SO, THERE'S MORE TO LOSE
BETWEEN YOU AND ME.
BUT MAYBE MORE TO GAIN.
WE DON'T WE GIVE US A SHOT?
IF IT DOESN'T WORK?
WE GO BACK TO BEING FRIENDS.
WELL, THEY DO SAY THAT FRIENDS
MAKE THE BEST LOVERS.
BUT...
JUST TO BE SAFE,
WE NEED TO MAKE SURE
WE'RE COMPATIBLE FIRST.
YOU NEED TO TAKE ME
ON A PROPER DATE.
I CAN DO THAT.
(LIQUOR SLOSHES)
(GLASSES CLINK,
LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
(GRUNTS) OH...
MY LIFE IS A MESS.
YOU'RE WAY TOO HARD
ON YOURSELF.
JANE HATES ME,
MY FRIENDS THINK
I'M STUPID,
AND I'M PROBABLY NEVER
GETTING INTO POLICE COLLEGE.
YOU DO SHAPE
A COMPELLING ARGUMENT.
THANK YOU.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
YOU... NO,
YOU NEED TO TALK TO HER.
AND TELL HER WHAT?
I'M NOT THE SAME MORON
SHE YELLED AT TWO HOURS AGO?
DUDE, YOU ARE...
YOU, YOU ARE IN... LOVE.
YOU KNOW?
LOVE! MAN, MY FRIEND,
LOVE CAN MOVE MOUNTAINS.
YOU REALLY THINK SO?
UH-HUH.
A MONTH AGO...
MANNY WOULDN'T
RETURN MY CALLS.
NOW, SHE ANSWERS...
AND THEN HANGS UP.
THAT IS LOVE AT WORK,
BUDDY.
SO, WHAT ARE YOU SUGGESTING?
YOU NEED TO TELL JANE
THAT YOU WILL DO ANYTHING,
A-NY-THING TO KEEP HER.
RIGHT NOW.
GUESS I GOT NOTHING
TO LOSE.
GO.
(SIGHS)
(GLASSES CLINK)
CHEERS.
JANE:
SOME THINK THESE ARMS WOULD BE
GOOD FOR CRADLING A BABY,
BUT THEY CAN ALSO CRADLE
A FOOTBALL.
NO. NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
(PEN SCRATCHES AGAINST PAPER)
(KNOCKING AGAINST WINDOW,
DOG BARKS IN THE DISTANCE)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
OUT THERE?
(DRUNKEN STAMMER)
I DIDN'T WANNA WAKE
YOUR MOM.
SHHH...
SHHH!
IT'S HOT IN HERE.
YES.
BABE, LISTEN,
I KNOW I MESSED UP
BIG TIME TODAY,
BUT I CAN CHANGE, JANE.
I, I CAN GROW UP.
'KAY, ARE YOU DRUNK?
YES, I AM.
SEE? I DIDN'T LIE THAT TIME;
I'M CHANGING ALREADY.
BABY, DON'T BE ANGRY
WITH ME, PLEASE.
I'M NOT ANGRY, SPIN.
I'M HURT
AND I'M EMBARRASSED.
I'M SO SORRY I LIED.
I JUST...
I THOUGHT THAT
WE WERE BEST FRIENDS.
YOU KNOW, PARTNERS.
BUT WHEN SOMETHING BAD
HAPPENED,
YOU COULDN'T EVEN TELL ME.
I DIDN'T WANT
TO DISAPPOINT YOU.
I WANTED US TO BE TOGETHER.
I KNOW YOU'RE THE ONE,
JANE.
YOU'RE NOT THE GUY
THAT I THOUGHT YOU WERE.
DON'T GIVE UP ON ME.
I NEED TIME
TO THINK ABOUT IT.
(DOOR OPENS)
EVELYN:
JANE, IT'S MIDNIGHT,
WHAT'S IS TH...
SPINNER...
(EXHALES)
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
TELLING YOUR DAUGHTER
THAT I LOVE HER.
ARE YOU DRUNK?
YES, I AM.
YOU MIND IF I TAKE THE STAIRS
INSTEAD OF THE TREE?
SPINNER:
FINE. I'M UP.
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE
ANYWAY?
DUDE,
IT'S 8:00 A.M.!
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU DIDN'T
GET TO BED 'TIL 7:00.
HAVE YOU SLEPT AT ALL?
JANE'S GONNA BREAK UP
WITH ME.
OH...
THIS IS PROBABLY A...
BAD TIME TO ASK
FOR YOUR ADVICE
ABOUT THIS THEN?
YOU'RE GO...
YOU'RE GONNA PROPOSE?
JIMMY:
YEAH.
I JUST NEED SOME HELP
WITH THE WHERE AND HOW.
YOU KNOW,
THE BIG ROMANTIC GESTURE.
EVERYBODY'S MOVING ON
WITH THEIR LIVES.
EVERYONE BUT ME.
I WENT ABOUT THIS ALL WRONG,
DIDN'T I?
SHE'LL FORGIVE YOU.
OKAY?
JUST MAKE SURE
THAT NO MATTER WHAT,
YOU CAN BE THERE
FOR EACH OTHER.
I KNOW EXACTLY
HOW I'M GONNA DO THAT.
KC:
HOW'RE THE MODIFICATIONS COMING?
WELL,
I CHANGED THE TREAD,
BUT I ALSO REWIRED
THE ARM.
(PIECES CLANK)
CLARE,
ABOUT THE DANCE.
I THINK YOU SHOULD GO.
WITH ME.
OKAY, I'LL GO.
BUT I'M NOT GOING
WITH ANYONE.
I'LL TAKE THAT
AS HALF-YES.
♪ Saw it in a parking lot... ♪
(DOOR CHIMES JINGLE)
WHAT WAS SO DIRE
THAT I HAD TO BE HERE
BEFORE SCHOOL OR ELSE?
I HAVE A PLAN TO CONVINCE JANE
TO GIVE ME A SECOND CHANCE.
DOES IT INVOLVE GETTING DRUNK
AND CLIMBING THROUGH HER WINDOW
AGAIN?
HMM. NO.
BUT IT DOES INVOLVE
YOUR HELP.
(SARCASTIC HALF LAUGH)
OTHERWISE,
YOU'RE OUT OF A JOB.
YOU DID TELL JANE THAT SPIN
DIDN'T GET INTO POLICE COLLEGE.
SO, SHE'S AT THIS LEADERSHIP
SYMPOSI-THINGIE ALL DAY
AND I NEED TO BE THERE
FOR HER SPEECH.
SPEECH.
YOU CAN'T JUST WALTZ IN
TO THOSE THINGS.
WHICH IS WHERE YOU COME IN;
I FIGURED YOU'D BE THE EXPERT
ON ALL THINGS,
UH, STUDENT LEADERSHIP.
EXPERT.
FINE.
I HAVE A SPARE THIS MORNING.
JUST PUT ON A SUIT
AND MEET ME AT THE SYMPOSIUM.
HEY! OKAY,
YOU MIGHT WANNA THINK ABOUT
WHAT YOU'RE GONNA SAY TO HER
WHEN YOU SEE HER.
OH, I HAVE.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA DO
ANYTHING STUPID?
NOPE.
IT'S BRILLIANT.