(CAR RUMBLES BY)
ALLI...
ALLI, STOP.
YOU SHOULD GET HOME.
IT'S ALMOST NINE.
JUST ONE MORE KISS...
DON'T WANT YOU TO BE LATE.
GO.
(DOOR AJAR SIGNAL DINGS)
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
(FRONT DOOR SHUTS)
HOW WAS THE LIBRARY?
ALLI:
STUPID.
(EXHALES)
(TV TURNS ON)
(SOAP OPERA MUSIC PLAYS)
LO: (ACTRESS)
IT'S PERFECT.
JUST YOU.
JUST ME.
BRETT: (ACTOR)
WHAT?
LO:
NO ONE'S EVER LOOKED AT ME
THE WAY YOU JUST DID.
BRETT:
GUESS NO ONE'S EVER LOVED YOU
AS MUCH AS I DO.
I HATE MY LIFE.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Oh! Oh! Oh! ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
HE SKIRTS INTIMACY,
CUTS DATES SHORT,
KEEPS ME
FROM HIS FRIENDS;
HE'S OBVIOUSLY
LOSING INTEREST.
YOU'VE BEEN BACK TOGETHER
TWO WEEKS.
WHICH MEANS OUR RELATIONSHIP
SHOULD BE PROGRESSING.
UNLESS HE WANTS
TO TAKE THINGS SLOW.
WHY CAN'T HE JUST
HOLD ME IN HIS ARMS,
SAY HE LOVES ME,
AND KISS ME ALL OVER?
(MOCK KISSING SOUNDS)
UH, HI,
COACH ARMSTRONG.
ARMSTRONG:
UH, BETTER PRACTICE
THOSE DIFFERENTIALS
BEFORE TOMORROW'S COMPETITION.
MIGHT HAVE OUR FIRST EINSTEIN
MATH COMPETITION CHAMPION
ON OUR HANDS.
A SOON-TO-BE SINGLE CHAMPION.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
THIS IS YOUR FIRST
RELATIONSHIP.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
HOW IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE.
WHEN YOU GUYS ARE, LIKE,
"WITH" YOUR BOYFRIENDS,
DO THEY EVER...
BEG?
PLEAD?
YOU'RE SAYING GUYS
ARE PRETTY MUCH
ALWAYS IN THE MOOD?
YOU'RE NOT TALKING
ABOUT JOHNNY, ARE YOU?
'CAUSE AT LAKEHURST
HE WAS A TOTAL DOG.
HE WENT OUT
WITH LOTS OF GIRLS?
UM... DON'T KNOW IF MUCH
"GOING OUT" WAS INVOLVED.
PA ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION, STUDENTS...
JOHNNY:
YOU'RE NOT BRUCE.
(PLAYFUL SCOFF)
REMEMBER THAT MOVIE
YOU WANTED TO SEE,
"THE HUSTLER"?
IT'S PLAYING AT THE PALACE.
I MENTIONED THAT
MONTHS AGO.
IF IT GETS BORING,
WE CAN...
KEEP OURSELVES ENTERTAINED.
I PROMISED BRUCE
I'D HANG AT THE RAVINE.
SO I'LL DROP BY.
IT'S NOT REALLY YOUR SCENE.
I MEAN, A BUNCH OF OLDER KIDS
GETTING INTO TROUBLE.
I'M A BIG GIRL,
I CAN TAKE CARE OF MYSELF.
OH...
SO I'LL SEE YOU
AT THE RAVINE?
YOU KNOW IT'S IMPOSSIBLE
TO SAY NO TO YOU, RIGHT?
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
HUJAMBO MZURI KIBIBI.
MZURI-WHAT NOW?
IT MEANS "HELLO, BEAUTIFUL LADY"
IN SWAHILI.
(HALF LAUGHS)
WE GOT KENYA
FOR MOCK UN.
THEY STILL NEED A SWEDEN,
IF YOU'RE INTERESTED.
PETER: (SWEDISH ACCENT)
BUT YOU NEED TO TALK LIKE THIS.
(HALF LAUGHS)
YEAH...
MEETING TIMES CONFLICT
WITH POWER SQUAD PRACTICE.
OH, THAT'S MY GIRL.
SAVING THE WORLD,
ONE LEAP AT A TIME.
RILEY:
THE WORLD'S PROBLEMS CALL,
DUDE.
OKAY, SEE YOU LATER?
YOU BET.
PETER AND MOCK U.N....
IT'S AN INTERESTING
COUPLE.
HE'S TRYING NEW THINGS,
HOPING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT TO DO NEXT YEAR.
SO YOU THINK
IT'S A COINCIDENCE THEN
THAT PETER CHOSE KENYA?
THE COUNTRY HIS EX-GIRLFRIEND
LIVES IN?
I DID UNTIL NOW.
(RAP SONG PLAYS)
OKAY, WE'RE HERE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I THINK THAT YOU SHOULD ZIP
YOUR JACKET BACK UP.
I THINK JOHNNY WON'T AGREE.
IS THIS HOW YOU WANNA
GET HIM TO LIKE YOU?
HE ALREADY LIKES ME.
AND ONCE I PROVE
I CAN RUN WITH HIS CROWD,
AND MY AGE
WON'T BE AN ISSUE.
AND IF THAT DOESN'T WORK,
WHAT'S NEXT?
MATCHING TATTOOS?
WHATEVER IT TAKES.
DON'T WORRY.
IT'LL BE LIKE ANY OTHER PARTY
WE'VE EVER BEEN TO.
KIDS:
(LIVELY CHATTER)
ALL RIGHT! WOOOO! COME ON! YEAH!
MY TWELFTH BIRTHDAY...
TOTALLY LIKE THIS.
THERE'S JOHNNY.
BRUCE:
WHAT'S UP?
HAVE YOU HIT THAT YET?
TELL ME YOU HAVEN'T
THOUGHT ABOUT IT?
WELL, I'M HUMAN,
AREN'T I?
MMM.
SO WHAT IS STOPPING YOU?
I LIKE HER, DUDE.
(TRAFFIC WHIRS)
ALL DONE.
DO YOU WANNA HIT
A MOVIE?
UH, I GOTTA FINISH
THIS BOOK.
YOU'RE REALLY GETTING INTO
THIS MOCK U.N.
WHY DID YOU CHOOSE KENYA
AS YOUR COUNTRY?
I MEAN, THERE ARE SO MANY
OTHER COUNTRIES OUT THERE.
KENYA IS THE HUB
OF AFRICA.
DARCY WAS SAYING
SHE CAN'T BE...
WAIT, WAIT.
YOU'RE STILL TALKING
TO DARCY?
YEAH.
THE WORK SHE'S DOING OVER THERE
IS AMAZING.
SHE'S WORKING
AT THIS ORPHANAGE...
IT DOESN'T BOTHER YOU
I'VE BEEN TALKING TO HER,
DOES IT?
I DON'T KNOW,
SHOULD IT?
WORK CAN WAIT.
LET'S GET A MOVIE.
(HEAVY ROCK MUSIC PLAYS,
KIDS CHATTER AND LAUGH)
SO YOU REALLY THOUGHT
ANIMAL FARM WAS ABOUT PIGS?
IT'S NOT?
IT'S A POLITICAL ALLEGORY
ABOUT THE RUSSIAN REVOLUTION.
WAIT A MINUTE.
PIGS STARTED
THE RUSSIAN REVOLUTION?
THAT'S TOTALLY MESSED.
(LAUGHING)
WE SAID WE'D BE HOME
BY SEVEN.
REESE:
OR MOMMY AND DADDY
WILL GET ANGRY.
BRUCE:
(CHUCKLES)
YOU GOTTA GO TOO,
BACKWOODS?
UH, NO.
I CAN STAY.
UH, CAN YOU COME WITH ME
FOR A MINUTE?
JOHNNY PUT HIS ARMS
AROUND ME
IN FRONT OF HIS FRIENDS.
I'M SURE YOUR PARENTS
WILL UNDERSTAND.
JUST TELL YOUR MOM
I'M NOT SLEEPING OVER.
I'LL FIGURE
THE REST OUT LATER.
BUT WHAT ABOUT
THE MATH COMPETITION?
WE WERE GONNA DO
EXTRA PREP.
YOU HEARD
COACH ARMSTRONG.
I'M TOTALLY READY.
DON'T WORRY.
I'LL BE FINE.
YOU GUYS OFF?
MAKE MAGIC HAPPEN.
YOU AND JOHNNY GONNA
SEAL THE DEAL TONIGHT?
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
WE HAVEN'T ALREADY?
DON'T WORRY.
LOTS OF GUYS COME HERE
TO DISCUSS
RUSSIAN LITERATURE.
NOW IF YOU'LL EXCUSE US,
WE HAVE SOME BUSINESS
TO TAKE CARE OF.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS,
HUM OF CHATTER)
♪♪♪
(FIRE CRACKLES,
HUM OF MUSIC AND CHATTER)
ALLI:
THIS IS PERFECT.
JUST YOU.
JUST ME.
YOU THINK WE'RE IN SOME
SORT OF EPIC ROMANCE.
WHERE YOU'RE
THE MISUNDERSTOOD BAD BOY.
AND YOU'RE...
AMAZING.
ALLI.
(HALF LAUGHS)
DON'T WORRY.
BRUCE:
WHOA...
NO GLOVE, NO LOVE.
(SARCASTIC)
THANK YOU.
(LAUGHING)
WELL...
DO YOU WANT TO?
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER,
BIRDS CHIRP)
ONLY IF YOU DO.
MAYBE WE SHOULD GO
SOMEWHERE PRIVATE.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS,
HUM OF CHATTER AND LAUGHTER)
AND NOW FOR THE UPLIFTING TALE
OF THE GENOCIDE IN DARFUR.
I THOUGHT IT SOUNDED
INTERESTING.
OH, REMOTE'S UPSTAIRS.
OH, THERE IT IS.
(DESCENDING FOOTSTEPS)
READY TO SHED SOME TEARS?
(REMOTE CLICKS,
OPENING MOVIE MUSIC PLAYS)
(HIP HOP MUSIC PLAYS)
(SHAKY BREATHS)
ALLI:
I SHOULD GET HOME.
LET ME DRIVE YOU.
THAT'S OKAY.
YOU'RE NOT WALKING HOME
ALONE.
OKAY.
(KNOCK AT THE DOOR)
SORRY YOUR SLEEPOVER
DIDN'T WORK OUT.
CLARE OKAY?
UH, YEAH.
IT'S JUST THE STOMACH FLU.
I HOPE SHE FEELS BETTER
FOR THE COMPETITION TOMORROW.
YOU DID THE RIGHT THING
BY COMING HOME.
I SHOULD GET TO BED.
WAIT.
DON'T I GET A HUG, FIRST?
GOOD NIGHT, SWEETHEART.
(LIGHT SWITCH CLICKS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
I JUST GOT INTEL
FROM THE MESSAGE BOARDS.
DIFFERENTIALS ARE TOTALLY
GONNA BE ON THE COMPETITION.
WHAT IF I GOT PREGNANT?
OR CAUGHT AN STD?
TWO GOOD REASONS
NOT TO HAVE SEX.
ALLI, YOU DIDN'T!
TELL ME YOU USED A CONDOM.
WHAT IF IT BROKE?
IT WAS MY FIRST TIME.
I DON'T KNOW HOW ANYTHING
IS SUPPOSED TO FEEL.
WAS IT...
LIKE YOU THOUGHT?
WE WERE KISSING,
AND THAT WAS NICE...
IT WAS PERFECT.
EVERYTHING YOU'D EXPECT IT
TO BE.
PERINO:
WE NEED ONE MORE TEAM
FOR THE MOCK U.N.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
ANY FUTURE DIPLOMATS
AMONG YOU?
DO YOU THINK HE WAS GONNA
LEAVE WITHOUT TELLING ME?
MAYBE HE HASN'T MADE UP
HIS MIND?
I DON'T GET IT.
DARCY DITCHES HIM
TO GO TO KENYA
AND NOW HE THINKS THAT
SHE'S SOME SORT OF A SAINT.
UM...
MIA AND I WOULD LIKE
TO VOLUNTEER FOR MOCK U.N.
ALL RIGHT.
WE MEET HERE AFTER SCHOOL.
OKAY. PETER HEARTS DARCY
BECAUSE SHE LOVES THE WORLD.
NOW SO DO YOU.
THAT'S TOTALLY PATHETIC.
(PA ANNOUNCEMENT RUNS,
STUDENTS CHATTER)
JOHNNY:
HEY, BACKWOODS!
DON'T CALL ME THAT.
ARE YOU OKAY?
(DEEP BREATH)
WHAT'S YOUR MIDDLE NAME?
I MEAN, I THINK I SHOULD KNOW
CONSIDERING.
GEORGE.
LISTEN,
ABOUT LAST NIGHT...
WE WERE SAFE, RIGHT?
YEAH.
GOOD.
I JUST WANTED TO MAKE SURE.
I SHOULD GO.
I HAVE TO GET READY
FOR THE COMPETITION.
SURE.
RILEY:
THOUGHT YOU GIRLS
HAD POWER SQUAD?
ANYA:
SHE RESCHEDULED IT.
PERKS OF BEING THE CAPTAIN.
WATCHING THE MOVIE
LAST NIGHT
MADE ME START THINKING
ABOUT THE WORLD.
MAYBE WE CAN SAVE IT
TOGETHER.
PERINO:
WE'VE GOT TWO WEEKS BEFORE
WE ENTER THE CITY CHAMPIONSHIPS,
SO LET'S GET STARTED.
FOREIGN TRADE EMBARGOES.
SHOULD THE U.N. BE ABLE
TO TELL ONE COUNTRY
WHO THEY CAN DO BUSINESS WITH?
KENYA,
START WITH YOU.
UH, FOREIGN TRADE EMBARGOES
PUNISH CITIZENS,
NOT GOVERNMENTS.
WHICH IS WHY WE SHOULDN'T
STOP ONE COUNTRY
FROM TRADING WITH ANOTHER.
EVEN IF THE COUNTRY
IN QUESTION
COULD INFLUENCE THE OTHER
TO HURT SOMEONE
WITHOUT EVEN MEANING TO?
PERINO:
NOW THAT'S THE DILEMMA,
ISN'T IT?
SHOULD WE WAIT FOR PEOPLE
TO MAKE THE RIGHT DECISION,
OR DO WE TRY
AND FORCE THEIR HAND?
IF THEY'RE LOOKING OUT...
I KNOW ALL ABOUT KENYA.
WHAT?
WERE YOU EVEN GONNA TELL ME?
LOOKS LIKE KENYA
HAS SOME DIPLOMATIC
RELATIONS TO MEND.
PERINO:
NEXT TOPIC:
ILLEGAL OCCUPATIONS.
COACH ARMSTRONG:
ONE MORE HOUR.
MAKE DEGRASSI PROUD.
(SHAKY BREATH)
MR. ARMSTRONG,
I'M NOT FEELING WELL.
(ROOM DOOR OPENS
AND CLOSES)
HEY.
NO, MIA, WAIT.
IT'S TRUE, I'VE BEEN THINKING
ABOUT DARCY A LOT LATELY.
AND WHEN SHE CALLED
TO APOLOGIZE FOR LEAVING
A COUPLE OF WEEKS AGO...
WELL,
IT WAS REALLY CONFUSING.
DO YOU STILL LOVE HER?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHICH IS WHY
YOU'RE GOING TO KENYA.
THINKING ABOUT GOING
TO KENYA.
I DIDN'T WANT TO TELL YOU
TILL I WAS COMPLETELY SURE.
I WAS TRYING TO AVOID
HURTING YOU,
WHICH OBVIOUSLY WORKED OUT.
ARE YOU BREAKING UP
WITH ME?
NO.
I REALLY LIKE YOU.
IT'S JUST...
I ALSO HAVE FEELINGS FOR DARCY.
I JUST NEED TO FIGURE
SOME STUFF OUT.
YOU UNDERSTAND,
DON'T YOU?
EVERYTHING LOOKS NORMAL.
(SNIFFS)
YOU ARE A LITTLE PEAKED.
WHY DON'T YOU LIE DOWN
FOR A BIT?
(KNOCKING)
I JUST WANTED TO CHECK
ON MY FRIEND.
OKAY.
SHE SAYS I'M FINE.
I WISH I WASN'T.
IT WOULD EXPLAIN
WHY I FEEL SO BAD.
ALLI.
IT WAS AWKWARD
AND UNCOMFORTABLE,
AND AFTERWARDS
I DIDN'T WANNA TOUCH HIM.
CLARE:
DID YOU TELL HIM
HOW YOU FEEL?
I DIDN'T WANT HIM TO THINK
I WASN'T COOL.
HOW COULD I SHARE SOMETHING
SO SPECIAL
WITH SOMEONE
I CAN'T EVEN TALK TO?
CLARE:
IT'S OKAY.
IT'S OVER.
BUT I CAN'T TAKE IT BACK.
(HUM OF CHATTER)
SHEP:
THE RESULTS FOR THE 49TH
NATIONAL MATH COMPETITION
ARE IN,
AND I'M GLAD TO ANNOUNCE
THAT CLARE EDWARDS
FINISHED IN THE TOP
ONE PERCENT.
CONGRATULATIONS.
HI.
I UH...
I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT ELSE TO DO.
IT'S KINDA LAME,
ISN'T IT?
I THOUGHT I WAS READY.
I WANTED TO BELIEVE
YOU WERE.
BHANDARI, I LIKE YOU...
A LOT.
I DON'T THINK
WE SHOULD HANG OUT ANYMORE.
SHEP:
SO... LET'S GO OUTSIDE
AND GET A PHOTOGRAPH OF YOU
FOR THE YEARBOOK.
HEY.
HOW 'BOUT DINNER
AT THE DOT?
I WON'T WAIT FOR YOU
TO PICK ME.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
I TOLD DARCE
I'M NOT COMING TO KENYA.
"LOVE THE ONE YOU'RE WITH,"
RIGHT?
(SCOFFS IN DISBELIEF)
"WHEN YOU CAN'T BE
WITH THE ONE YOU LOVE."
REAL ROMANTIC, PETER.
OKAY, THE WORDS
ARE COMING OUT ALL WRONG,
BUT WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY
IS...
I CHOOSE YOU.
THE FACT THAT YOU WERE
EVEN CONSIDERING LEAVING
MEANS THAT THERE WAS SOMETHING
SERIOUSLY WRONG WITH US.
I LOVE DARCY.
I PROBABLY ALWAYS WILL.
BUT...
I'M FALLING IN LOVE
WITH YOU.
YOU DON'T GET IT,
DO YOU?
I'M NOT GONNA BE
YOUR CONSOLATION PRIZE.
WE NEED TO BREAK UP.
SO THAT'S IT?
YOU GUYS ARE THROUGH?
THERE ARE SOME THINGS
I'M NOT WILLING TO DO
TO BE IN A RELATIONSHIP.
BUT YOU STILL WANNA
BE WITH HIM?
THEN TELL HIM THAT.
WHAT IF HE DOESN'T WANNA BE
WITH ME ANYMORE?
THEN HE SUCKS.
IT'S BETTER TO KNOW THAT NOW.
I'M NOT GONNA HAVE
SEX AGAIN
FOR A LONG TIME.
AND, UH...
WHY SHOULD I WORRY
ABOUT THAT?
'CAUSE I'D LIKE
TO KEEP HANGING OUT.
AND YOU WON'T PRESSURE ME
TO DO ANYTHING
I'M NOT READY FOR?
YOU'RE SUCH AN IDIOT.
I WAS A VIRGIN TOO.
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
I DIDN'T THINK THAT WAS
THE GUY YOU WANTED.
AND ALL THOSE OTHER GIRLS?
I NEVER STUCK AROUND
LONG ENOUGH.
(HALF LAUGHS)
SO I DIDN'T HAVE TO?
I MEAN...
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE CARED
IF I HADN'T?
I WISH I COULD CHANGE A LOT
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED,
BUT NOT THAT I WAS WITH YOU.
SO WE CAN TAKE THINGS
SLOWLY?
YOU KNOW IT'S IMPOSSIBLE
TO SAY NO TO YOU, RIGHT?