(SPLASH)
RILEY:
I'VE BEEN SWIMMING PRACTICALLY
SINCE I WAS BORN,
SO I THOUGHT,
"WHY NOT TURN IT INTO A JOB?"
SAM:
WELL, IT'S A GREAT WAY
TO STAY IN SHAPE
IN THE SUMMER.
LOUNGING BY THE POOL?
BEFORE LIFE-GUARDING,
I SAT ON THE BENCH.
THE NEXT YEAR,
I SET THE CITY
RUSHING RECORD.
THAT WAS YOU?
SAM:
ALL RIGHT, COME ON GUYS.
BRING IT IN!
BRING IT IN, COME ON.
FIRST YOU CHECK FOR
A RESPONSE.
IF THERE'S NO RESPONSE
YOU CALL 9-1-1.
NEXT, YOU TILT THE HEAD
AND YOU LISTEN
FOR BREATHING.
IF THERE'S NONE,
PINCH THE NOSE,
AND COVER THE MOUTH.
(BLOWING)
WHOA!
(ASTONISHED LAUGHTER)
(SPLASH)
RILEY, IS EVERYTHING OKAY
IN THERE?
YEAH, EVERYTHING'S JUST FINE.
FITZ:
"FINE?" OR "FIRM?"
(STUDENTS LAUGHING)
SAM:
GUYS, CAN WE GET BACK TO THIS?
OKAY, I JUST NEED ONE MORE SEC.
(STUDENTS LAUGHING)
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, whatever ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
RILEY:
...I WAS THINKING TECUMSEH POOL,
BUT, THE BEACH
WOULD BE COOL, TOO.
FITZ:
YEAH, MAN, SCOPE THE CHICKS
IN BIKINIS AND GET PAID?
RILEY:
YOU CAN HAVE THE BIKINI CHICKS.
I ALREADY HAVE
MY PERFECT GIRLFRIEND.
FIONA:
WELL, WANT TO BE THE PERFECT
BOYFRIEND?
I FORGOT MY LUNCH.
NOW, YOU'LL HAVE TO TELL ME
WHAT'S EDIBLE IN THE CAF.
YOU KNOW ME,
HUMAN GARBAGE DISPOSAL.
I'LL EAT ANYTHING.
WELL,
YOU ARE A GROWING BOY.
HE SURE WAS 'GROWING'
IN LIFEGUARD CLASS.
(LAUGHING)
YOU SHOULDA SEEN IT
SAM'S GIVING
MOUTH TO MOUTH-
RILEY:
I TOLD YOU.
I WAS THINKING
ABOUT MY GIRLFRIEND,
SO ARE YOU TWO, YOU KNOW,
SEXUALLY ACTIVE?
HEY, KNOCK IT OFF.
ACTUALLY,
WE'RE WAITING.
BECAUSE UNLIKE YOU?
RILEY'S A GENTLEMAN.
C'MON, I'LL WALK YOU
TO CLASS.
ANYA, IT'S STUDZ FIRST
UNPLUGGED SET AT THE DOT!
SAV, YOU KNOW
I CAN'T DO MONDAYS.
SAV:
COULD YOU SKIP YOUR STUPID
SELF-DEFENSE CLASSES THIS ONCE?
NO.
AND IT'S NOT STUPID.
WHATEVER.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
LEIA:
YOU'RE NOT COMING?
NOW I HAVE TO SIT THROUGH
THOSE SAME SONGS
FOR THE HUNDREDTH TIME -
ALONE!
WHY DO YOU THINK
I NEED A BREAK?
CAN I COME TO YOUR
SELF-DEFENSE CLASS?
YOU WOULDN'T LIKE IT.
DAWES:
SCULPTURE.
THE ART OF TAKING AWAY
ALL OF THE EXCESS
UNTIL ONLY THE MASTERPIECE
REMAINS...
ARMSTRONG:
SIXTY-THREE POINT FIVE KILOS.
WHAT WERE YOU?
EIGHTY.
CLOSE ENOUGH.
YOU'RE THE LAST TWO.
YOU'RE GOING DOWN,
PAL!
RIGHT. JUST TRY NOT
TO KILL ME, PLEASE.
RILEY:
ONLY REASON I WON'T?
I GOTTA ASK YOU
A GIRL QUESTION.
WHAT HAPPENED, FIONA REALIZED
SHE'S OUT OF YOUR LEAGUE?
(FAKE LAUGHS)
HILARIOUS.
NAH, I JUST NEED TO CONVINCE
HER TO SLEEP WITH ME.
WELL, YOU GUYS HAVE BEEN
DATING HER A WHILE.
I GUESS YOU'VE GOT THOSE
CONFUSED THOUGHTS
OUT OF YOUR SYSTEM?
I JUST HAD TO FIND
THE RIGHT GIRL.
ONLY THING IS,
SHE WANTS TO WAIT.
AH. WELL,
IF SHE WANTS TO WAIT?
YOU'RE WAITING. YOU CAN'T
JUST CONVINCE HER.
SO YOU'RE SAYING
DO NOTHING?
GREAT ADVICE, MAN.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(BOUNCES)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(HOOTS AND HOLLERS)
(CHEERS,
WHISTLE BLOWS)
(APPLAUSE)
THREE BASKETS?
A WHOLE QUARTER
OF FLOOR TIME,
AND A CUTE GIRLFRIEND
CHEERING YOU ON IN THE STANDS?
YEAH.
I'M A SUPERSTAR.
YEAH. MY TIME
WILL COME SOON.
MEANWHILE, I'LL GET
COMFORTABLE ON THE BENCH.
COACH CARSON:
DAVE, YOU'RE GOING IN.
WHAT!? WHAT ME?
OKAY...
ANY LAST MINUTE TIPS?
YEAH.
LET THE GAME
COME TO YOU.
(GAME WHISTLE BLOWS)
FITZ:
I'D KILL TO BE A DUMMY
LIKE THAT.
BLUE:
YOU'RE ALMOST THERE.
RILEY:
HEY GUYS,
WHO DO YOU GUYS THINK IS
THE HOTTEST GIRL IN THE CLASS?
OH!
(LAUGHING)
KA- KATIE.
I THOUGHT YOU ONLY HAD EYES
FOR FIONA.
FITZ:
CHANTAY, MAN.
THAT GIRL IS FINE!
AND WAY OUTTA MY LEAGUE.
RILEY:
HEY, SAM?!
CHANTAY OR KATIE?
WHO'S HOTTER?
UM... IT'S NOT REALLY
MY PLACE TO SAY.
AH, COME ON.
YOU HAVE AN OPINION,
GIRLS IN SWIMSUITS?
YEAH, NOT FOR ME.
RILEY:
WHY, BECAUSE THEY'RE STUDENTS?
RILEY. FORGET IT.
SAM:
NO, NO. IT'S OKAY, BLUE.
RILEY, I'M GAY.
(LAUGHING)
HE'S MISSING OUT.
FITZ:
AS IF YOU'D KNOW,
MR. "WE'RE WAITING."
IF FIONA WAS MINE?
I'D TURN DOWN THE LIGHTS,
ROCK SOME SLOW GROOVES...
WHAT CHEESY MOVIE GAVE YOU
THAT IDEA?
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(WHISPERING TO HIMSELF)
LET THE GAME COME TO YOU...
(PANICKING) DON'T COME TO ME,
DON'T COME TO ME!
DO-ON'T COME TO ME!
(BALL BOUNCING)
THREE SECONDS! SHOOT!
(GAME BUZZER SOUNDS,
SWISH!)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
KC:
THAT WAS SICK, MAN!!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
(GRUNTING WITH EFFORTS)
(GRUNTS)
(STRENUOUS GRUNTS CONTINUE)
HAH!
DAWES:
(BATTLE CRIES)
ANYA:
(EXCLAIMS, LANDS WITH A THUD)
UGH!
(GRUNTS WITH EFFORT)
LIGHTNING BOLT!
COME ON!
(AS IF ZAPPED BY LIGHTING)
ZZZZZZ-ZZZZZ-ZZZZZ.
(LAUGHS)
EXCELLENT WORK,
PRINCESS CARELLA.
THANK YOU.
I'VE BEEN WAITING
TO USE THAT ENCHANTMENT.
WELL, YOUR IMPROVEMENT
IS NOTED.
THANKS.
IT'S WEIRD. I'M-
I'M PLAYING A ROLE,
BUT I FEEL LIKE
I CAN BE MYSELF.
YEAH. IT SHOWS.
THERE'S A,
A CONFIDENCE ABOUT YOU
THAT I DON'T SEE
AT SCHOOL.
WELL, I'M MORE IMPORTANT HERE
THAN IN REAL LIFE.
OH, NO.
NO, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
ANYA:
NO, IT IS.
QUEEN ADAMANTIA,
WE RETURN
WITH GRAVE NEWS.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
THE KNIGHTS OF TAHA,
WITH THEIR GROWING RANKS,
WILL ATTACK US AND
THE DREADAMORT REALM
AT NEXT WEEKEND'S
BATTLE.
IF THEY CONQUER
BOROGARD?
THEY'LL STRIP YOU
OF YOUR TITLE.
AND YOURS.
WE MUST THINK OF SOMETHING,
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
UH, IT WON'T ESCAPE ME,
MY QUEEN.
GOOD.
AS YOU WERE.
DAVE:
TURNER FADES BACK.
JUMP SHOOTS. SWISH.
THE CROWD GOES WILD!
KC:
LEBRON, KOBE,
DAVE.
IT'S GOT A NICE RING
TO IT.
YEAH.
ALL I NEED NOW
IS A HOT LITTLE NUMBER
LIKE JENNA ON MY ARM.
THINK SHE'S INTO YOU?
DUDE, SHE IS NOT
NOT INTO ME, ALL RIGHT.
SHE SMILES A LOT...
SHE'S FRIENDS WITH CLARE,
WE COULD DOUBLE DATE.
WANT ME TO PUT IN
A GOOD WORD?
YEAH, YEAH.
THAT'D BE GREAT.
DAVE:
ACTUALLY, NO-NO-NO-NO-NO!
WAIT. WAIT. WAIT. WAIT.
UH-UH.
THAT'S CHICKEN STYLES.
I'VE GOTTA ASK HER OUT
ON MY OWN.
JUST GOTTA
FIGURE OUT HOW.
FOOTBALL, BASEBALL,
SWIMMING.
YOU HAVE TROPHIES
FOR EVERYTHING.
I DON'T REALLY
LIKE LOSING.
(MUSIC STARTS PLAYING)
WHAT ARE ALL THESE FOR?
THOSE ARE FOR KISSING.
(NERVOUS) OH.
DIDN'T KNOW YOU WERE
IN TRAINING FOR THAT.
♪ ... AND WE GONE BE TOGETHER
FOREVER ♪
♪ I WANNA HOLD YA SO CLOSE ♪
(SMOOCHES)
♪ WANNA HOLD YA SO CLOSE ♪
♪ SHE GOT CLASS
EVEN WHEN HER SKIRT TIGHT ♪
♪ I AIN'T EVEN TRIPPIN'
ABOUT THE FIRST NIGHT ♪
RILEY!
THIS ISN'T LIKE YOU!
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
SURE IT IS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I DON'T KNOW,
I JUST WANT YOU SO BAD.
OKAY, YOU'VE BARELY
TOUCHED ME SINCE WE MET
AND NOW YOU'RE ACTING
LIKE THIS HORNY GORILLA?
YOU'RE MY GIRLFRIEND.
WE'RE SUPPOSED
TO MAKE OUT, OKAY?
NOT OKAY.
I THOUGHT WE BOTH DIDN'T
WANT THE PHYSICAL STUFF.
WHY WOULD YOU
THINK THAT?
WELL, YOU'VE NEVER SHOWN
MUCH INTEREST UNTIL NOW.
FIONA, IF YOU'RE LISTENING
TO THOSE RUMOURS-
IT'S NOT JUST THAT.
IT'S-
HOW YOU PARADE ME
AROUND AT SCHOOL.
IT'S LIKE YOU HAVE
SOMETHING TO PROVE.
I THOUGHT
YOU LIKED ME!
I DO. WE CAN KEEP DATING
WHILE YOU FIGURE
THIS STUFF OUT.
BUT IF I THOUGHT
YOU WERE STRAIGHT,
WE WOULDN'T BE DOING THIS.
GET OUT.
RILEY,
DON'T BE LIKE THIS.
JUST GO!
(SPLASH)
(WATER SPLOOSHES)
SO RILEY,
HOW X-RATED WAS IT
LAST NIGHT?
I WANT DETAILS, MAN.
BLUE:
COME ON, MAN.
DON'T BE CRASS.
SO, DID YOU "MAKE LOVE,"
LAST NIGHT?
SHUT UP.
ACTUALLY? NO.
STILL WAITING?
RILEY:
WAITING FOR HER TO STOP BEING
SO UPTIGHT.
SHE'S A TOTAL ICE QUEEN.
OOH.
WOULDN'T GIVE YOU
THE TIME, HUH?
NO, HOLDEN.
I GOTTA BREAK IT OFF.
I NEED SOME ACTION,
YOU KNOW?
SAM:
HEY, DEGRASSI GUYS.
UM, I'M DOING AN AQUATIC
LEADERSHIP PROMO
AT YOUR SCHOOL FAIR.
YOU GUYS GOING?
FITZ: YEAH, BRO.
BLUE: PROBABLY.
GOOD. SO, RILEY?
YOU UP FOR A LITTLE
FRIENDLY COMPETITION?
MAYBE SOME SKEE-BALL?
YEAH, I DON'T KNOW.
ALL RIGHT, MAN.
FITZ:
YOU GOTTA GO, MAN.
YOU KNOW WHO GOES TO THE FAIR?
HOT SINGLE GIRLS.
YEAH. AND SOMEBODY'S GOT TO WIN
'EM ALL THOSE CARNIVAL PRIZES.
OKAY,
SO I DUMP FIONA AT NOON;
WIN A STUFFED BEAR AT FOUR;
GET A NEW GIRLS' DIGITS
AT FOUR-O-ONE?
I COULD DO THAT.
GUY:
NICE, MAN.
DAWES:
BAN BAYRAN'S EARLY STILL LIFES,
WERE OFTEN OF DEAD FISH
BEING PREPPED FOR COOKING.
NOW, PERSONALLY-
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
-I HAVE A WEEK SPOT FOR TIME.
DON'T FORGET.
FOR TOMORROW
I WANT STILL LIFES
THAT EXPRESS THE REAL YOU
WHAT IS YOUR
INANIMATE OBJECT?
OKAY, THANK YOU.
HI, JENNA.
I WAS WONDERING IF
I COULD ASK YOU SOMETHING.
YEAH, SURE.
UH... THERE COMES A TIME
IN-
IN A MAN'S LIFE WHEN HE...
NEVERMIND.
DID YOU CATCH
WHAT DAWES SAID?
UM... A STILL LIFE
OF THE REAL YOU?
WHATEVER THAT MEANS.
YEAH. I WAS THINKING
OF PAINTING A BASKETBALL.
OR MAYBE A BENCH.
AS IF!
YOU WON THE GAME!
HEY, WAIT!
THERE'S... SOMETHING ELSE.
ARE YOU GONNA CHECK OUT
THE CLUBS FAIR AFTER SCHOOL?
UH, WE GET OUT EARLY.
THOUGHT I'D SPLIT.
BUT I WAS WONDERING
IF MAYBE YOU WOULD
WANT TO GO WITH...
ME?
I MEAN,
AND CLARE AND KC.
THEY'RE GOING?
COOL.
I'LL MEET YOU
AFTER SCHOOL.
WHOO!
TOTALLY MISSED YOU
LAST NIGHT.
I WAS DROWNING IN
"JANIE 'N THE STUZS"
UNPLUGGED.
THAT BAD, HUH?
SORRY I SKIPPED OUT.
DID SAV EVEN NOTICE
I WASN'T THERE?
HE, HE WAS IN A MOOD.
NEXT TIME, CAN I PLEASE
GO TO SELF-DEFENSE?
ONLY THING YOU GUYS'LL NEED
SELF-DEFENSE FOR?
IS TO FIGHT OFF
OUR BAND'S GROUPIES!
NOW WHO'S LIVING
IN A FANTASY WORLD?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
NOW?
WHAT'S GOING ON
WITH YOU THESE DAYS?
IT'S LIKE WE'RE THEIR
GIRLFRIENDS,
BUT THEY'RE MARRIED
TO THE BAND.
LEIA, YOU ARE A GENIUS.
WHY?
WHAT'S THAT?
OKAY, JUST TELL ME
ONE THING.
DO YOU HAVE
A LONG DRESS?
ANNOUNCEMENT OVER PA:
ATTENTION DEGRASSI:
IT'S PIZZA DAY IN THE CAF!
$2 GETS YOU TWO SLICES.
HEY, DUDE.
I NEED SOME
MORE ADVICE.
HOW DO I BREAK UP
WITH A GIRL?
UHHHH...
JUST YESTERDAY,
YOU WANTED
TO SLEEP WITH HER.
YEAH,
DIDN'T WORK OUT.
ANYWAY, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY.
ANY IDEAS?
MAN, YOU CAN'T JUST
BREAK UP WITH A GIRL
'CUZ SHE WON'T SLEEP
WITH YOU.
WASN'T THAT
THE WHOLE POINT?
REALLY? DUDE, REALLY,
TAKE IT FROM A GUY
WHO ROUTINELY
LOSES GIRLFRIENDS
TO OTHER CONTINENTS.
THAT IS NOT
THE WHOLE POINT.
HEY.
SO, WANNA HIT UP
THE CARNIVAL?
I'M SURE
YOU WOULDN'T WANT
AN "ICE QUEEN"
DRAGGING YOU DOWN.
I- IT WAS JUST
LOCKER ROOM TALK.
ABOUT HOW I
WOULDN'T PUT OUT?
WELL, IT'S SORTA TRUE.
(SIGHS)
FIONA WAIT!
JUST COME HANG OUT
WITH ME. IT'LL BE FUN.
LOOK, MAYBE I DON'T
REALLY KNOW WHO YOU ARE
BUT WHEN IT COMES
TO BEING SOME VERSION
OF YOUR GIRLFRIEND
I'M NOT PLAYING ANY MORE.
(MUSIC BEINGS)
♪ I DON'T WANT YOU TO HOLD ME ♪
(BELL CLANGS,
CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
♪ IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT
THAT I CAN'T STAND ♪
♪ I DIDN'T WANT TO GO ♪
JENNA:
WOW. MY OLD SCHOOL WOULDA
JUST HELD A BAKE SALE.
DAVE:
I TOLD YOU. DEGRASSI
DOES IT RIGHT.
THANKS FOR CONVINCING
ME TO COME.
UM, YOU CAN FINISH THIS.
I NEED TO RUN
TO THE GIRLS' ROOM.
CLARE?
OH, YEAH.
MY DRINK WAS MASSIVE.
DAVE:
DON'T WORRY.
WE WILL WAIT RIGHT HERE.
OH, MAN!
CAN YOU BELIEVE HOW WELL
THIS IS GOING?
SEEMS TO BE GOING OKAY.
OKAY?
DUDE,
LOOK AT YOUR PLATE.
YOU GOT TWO FORKS.
NOW LOOK AT MINE.
ONE FORK!
WE'RE SHARING CUTLERY
ON THE FIRST DATE.
YEAH, I GUESS
THAT'S A THING.
GUESS, NOTHING.
DUDE,
IT. IS. SO. ON.
OKAY, NOW WHAT'S MY NEXT MOVE?
SAME AS BASKETBALL,
MAN.
RIGHT. RIGHT. RIGHT. RIGHT.
LET THE GAME COME TO ME.
(A BELL RINGS)
SAM:
HEY, Q.B.!
TAKE A SHOT!
OH, C'MON,
LET'S SEE THAT ARM!
HEY FITZ!
I GOT FOUR TICKETS LEFT,
WANNA TRY THE RING TOSS?
NAH. WE'RE GONNA GET
MY NEW FRIEND HERE
SOME COTTON CANDY.
ALL RIGHT, COOL.
YOU SEEN BLUE?
BLUE:
THIS IS MY NUMBER.
I'LL GIVE YOU THE SKETCH
IF YOU CALL ME.
OR WE COULD JUST
HANG OUT NOW?
SO. BIG EXAM TOMORROW.
DO YOU WANNA GO OVER
PROPER FIRST-AID
SPINEBOARD PLACEMENT?
NO, MAN.
I'M HERE TO HAVE FUN.
OH.
YEAH, ME TOO.
BUT IT SEEMS LIKE EVERYBODY'S
PAIRED UP, BUT US.
I GUESS WE'RE THE LONE WOLVES,
RIGHT?
I'M A LONE NOTHING,
DUDE.
I'M STILL ON THE PROWL,
YOU KNOW?
ALL RIGHT.
PROWL AWAY, BIG GUY.
HEY, CHANTAY!
HEY, RILEY.
YOU TRIED THE SNO-CONES?
MAYBE AFTER
I WIN YOU A BEAR.
REALLY?
AWESOME!
(A BELL RINGS,
SOMEONE CHEERS)
SO THIS IS CALLED
LARFING?
LARPING.
GUY:
(BATTLE CRY)
LIVE ACTION
ROLE PLAYING.
LIKE A VIDEO GAME,
BUT REAL.
EXCEPT
FOR THE SWORDS.
UM... IF DANNY
AND SAV SAW THIS?
THEY'D LAUGH
THEIR HEADS OFF.
WHY DO YOU THINK
I HAVEN'T TOLD ANYONE?
MS. DAWES,
FROM SCHOOL IS HERE?
SHE'S QUEEN ADAMANTIA...
OH, AND CALL ME
PRINCESS CARELLA.
AH! FAIR DAUGHTER,
GREETINGS.
HAST THOU FOUND
A SOLUTION TO OUR PROBLEM?
I HAVE, MY QUEEN!
PERMISSION TO ADDRESS
THE GUILDS?
GRANTED.
BOROGARD! GATHER.
AN ORACLE HAS COME TO ME
WITH A SOLUTION.
I WILL CONTACT
DREADAMORT
AND PROPOSE TO MARRY
THEIR CROWN PRINCE.
AND TOGETHER,
WE CAN DEFEAT THE KNIGHTS.
THAT ALLIANCE
WOULD MAKE YOU...
EMPRESS OF DREADAMORT?
I KNOW, RIGHT.
EMPRESS?
WORTH MISSING OUR BOYFRIENDS'
UNPLUGGED SHOW FOR?
NICE FREE-THROW,
SHAQ.
HA! THINK YOU CAN
DO BETTER?
THE TRICK?
GO UP CLOSE,
USE BACKSPIN,
TRY TO HIT THE TOP LIP,
AND... BAM!
YOU'VE GOT YOURSELF
A TEDDY BEAR.
GRRR!
THANKS, RILEY.
NO ONE HAS EVER WON ME
A STUFFED ANIMAL BEFORE.
DO YOU LIKE
ROLLER-COASTERS?
(UNSURE)
I UH... LOVE THEM.
COOL. MAYBE WE COULD GO
TO WONDERLAND SOMETIME?
YOU NAME IT
AND I'M THERE.
COOL.
WHOA, WHOA!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
DON'T YOU HAVE
A GIRLFRIEND?
WE BROKE UP
AND I THOUGHT UH-
US!? WE'RE JUST
BARELY FRIENDS, DUDE!
BUT YOU JUST SAID THAT-
WHAT? THAT I WANT
TO GET WITH A GUY
WHO JUMPS FROM GIRL
TO GIRL IN AN AFTERNOON!
OKAY! JUST KEEP IT DOWN,
ALL RIGHT?
KEEP WHAT DOWN?
JUST BECAUSE I DON'T LIKE
BEING JUMPED
IN THE DEGRASSI PARING LOT?
CHANTAY?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH,
IT'S JUST RILEY HERE,
PRACTICING
HIS MOUTH-TO-MOUTH.
STUDENTS:
OOH!
BETTER LUCK NEXT TIME, HUH?
GUY:
OOOH.
(HITS HARD, SPLASH)
(SEETHING)
GAMES MASTER:
AND WE ARE UNDERWAY!
LET'S GO! NUMBER FOUR
GOT THE EARLY LEAD!
NUMBER FOUR'S ABOUT TO STRIKE!
COME ON, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN!
NUMBER THREE IS TAKI-
OH! NUMBER THREE'S COMING UP
FROM BEHIND!
OH, WHERE'S NUMBER ONE?
NUMBER ONE'S-
LET'S GO!
NUMBER THREE STILL LEADS
TOWARDS STADIUM!
YES! FOUR'S THE WINNER!
HERE YOU GO.
HEY, ANY WAY I COULD
BUY ONE OF THOSE?
I'LL MAKE A HANDSOME DONATION.
I GOT...
THREE BUCKS?
WE'RE SHUTTING DOWN.
(GROANS)
BUT I NEED ONE.
SORRY.
LET'S TRY
THE BASKET TOSS.
YOU'RE BOUND TO WIN
SOMETHING THERE,
MR. THREE-POINTER!
ONE WAY OR ANOTHER,
I'M GONNA GET A PRIZE
FOR MY GIRLFRIEND.
(WHISPERS, BEWILDERED)
UM... GIRLFRIEND?
HEY MAN, HARSH SCENE
OUT THERE WITH CHANTAY.
YOU GOT YOUR SIGNALS
CROSSED, I GUESS.
IT'S NONE
OF YOUR BUSINESS.
LOOK, I KNOW IT'S TOUGH
DATING IN HIGH SCHOOL.
EVERYBODY SEES EVERYTHING.
WHAT DO YOU CARE,
DUDE?
I- I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW
IT'S GONNA BE OKAY.
YOU REMIND ME OF ME.
WHAT? GAY?!
SAM:
NO.
WHY? ARE YOU?
(HARD HITTING PUNCH)
(HUFFS OUT A BREATH)
HEY, SAM!
WAIT!
I'M SORRY!