♪♪♪♪♪
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
♪ I feel good ♪
♪ 'Cause it's time
you and me ♪
♪ Got a date
with the sunshine ♪
♪ Let's get free,
let's get loud ♪
♪ Find a place to kick back
and hang out ♪
CAMPING, HERE I COME.
♪ You're the one
gonna light my fuse ♪
♪ If you're crazy
let it show ♪
♪ That makes two,
so here we go... ♪
AMPHIBIAN ADVERSARIES
FOR 400, HM?
ANYONE?
WHAT, UH, WATER MAMMAL
PROTECTS ITSELF
BY SWIMMING IN PACKS?
OH, COME ON, FOLKS!
(LAUGHTER FROM THE HALLS)
JANE:
(TITTERS MISCHIEVOUSLY)
(TICKING)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS,
STUDENTS CHEER WILDLY)
♪ ARE YOU READY
FOR THE GREAT ESCAPE ♪
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH! ♪
♪ SET ME UP
FOR THE GREAT ESCAPE ♪
♪ OH! ♪
♪ CAN'T WAIT TO VACATE ♪
♪ UNDER PRESSURE,
I'M ABOUT TO BREAK ♪
♪ HE-E-EY! ♪
♪ IT'S THE GREAT ESCAPE ♪
♪ WE GOT DRUMS AND GUITARS ♪
♪ GOT IT PUMPING
LIKE GASOLINE SO FAR ♪
♪ COUNT DOWN TO BUST-OUT ♪
♪ IT'S ALL ROLLING UP
TO RIGHT NOW ♪
HOLLY J:
COUNTDOWN?
48 HOURS TO NEW YORK CITY!
DECLAN:
PERFECT PLACE
FOR A SWELTERING,
SUPER CROWDED,
UTTERLY SPONTANEOUS SUMMER.
SO HERE'S OUR BUILDING,
AND TVM IS EIGHT BLOCKS SOUTH.
YOU GONNA COME VISIT ME
ON MY LUNCH BREAK?
MEH.
(LAUGHS)
ANYTHING FOR SOME "YOU" TIME.
♪ IT'S THE GREAT ESCA-A-APE ♪
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH! ♪
♪ SET ME UP
FOR THE GREAT ESCAPE ♪
♪ OH! ♪
♪ CAN'T WAIT TO VACATE... ♪
HOW DID YOU CRAM
SO MANY SKIMPY CLOTHES
IN YOUR LOCKER?!
NOW I JUST HAVE
TO SMUGGLE THEM HOME.
WELL, LOOKY HERE, CLARE,
"SOMEBODY" APPROACHES.
CLARE:
DECLAN! HI!
DECLAN:
PROPMASTER CLARE!
THINK YOUR GROUPIE'S GONNA
STALK US TO THE BIG APPLE?
I'VE GIVEN MY FAN CLUB
IMPLICIT INSTRUCTIONS:
NOTHING INTERRUPTS
OUR SUMMER OF LOVE.
(STUDENTS CHEER AND CHATTER)
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it,
I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, Woo-ooh ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
DANNY:
LET THE SUMMER OF AWESOME
COMMENCE!
SAV:
MAN, KICKIN' BACK,
PLAYIN' SHOWS,
MOWING LAWNS,
IT'S GONNA BE SWEET!
YEAH. WE GOT TWO MONTHS
OF MAYHEM
BEFORE WE HAVE TO GO
TO UNIVERSITY!
HEY, THERE'S NO REASON
THE MAYHEM HAS TO END
IN THE FALL.
SOME OF US ARE HITTING
THE IVY LEAGUE, REMEMBER?
CORNELL?
OH CORNELL...
GOOD THING BASS PLAYERS
ARE EASY TO REPLACE.
NOT LIKE SINGERS
OR GIRLFRIENDS.
AW...
(LAUGHS)
SMOOTH.
HEY, UM,
DO WE STILL HAVE TIME
TO SQUEEZE IN OUR GRAD PACT
TONIGHT?
YOU KNOW IT,
MS. VALEVICTORIAN.
WELL, GOTTA GET BACK
TO WORK.
SEE YOU, GUYS!
SEE YA!
DANNY:
LATER, SPIN.
LARA:
I'LL SEE YOU IN GENEVA,
DARLING.
OKAY, BYE.
YOUR TRANSCRIPTS
HAVE BEEN FORWARDED
TO VANDERBILT PREP.
I STILL WISH I COULD
STAY HERE NEXT YEAR.
OH, I KNOW, HONEY,
BUT SENIOR YEAR
WILL FLY BY.
MEANWHILE, I'M GLAD THAT
HOLLY J WILL BE MAKING USE
OF THE PENTHOUSE
GUEST ROOM FOR AWHILE.
FIONA:
TRY THE WHOLE SUMMER.
WHOOP-DE-DOO.
I MEAN, IT'LL BE SO NICE
TO HAVE A GIRL WITH US
IN NEW YORK.
LARA:
WELL, TAKE CARE
OF YOUR SISTER,
I'LL BE BACK IN NEW YORK
IN A COUPLE OF WEEKS.
E A GOOD FLIGHT.
THANK YOU.
(CAR STARTS UP)
TWO DAYS WITH AN EMPTY MANSION
BEFORE WE LEAVE FOR NEW YORK.
DID I MENTION
IT HAS A POOL?
IT WOULD BE SHAME
FOR IT TO GO TO WASTE.
HEY, EVERYBODY!
POOL PARTY!
MY PLACE TOMORROW!
(WILD CHEERING)
(JANE AND SPINNER LAUGH)
JANE:
OH, WHO KNEW A GRAD PACT
COULD BE SO EXCRUCIATING?
SPINNER:
UNGH, IT DOESN'T HURT
THAT BAD.
YEAH.
(LAUGHS)
UM... I HAVE SOME NEWS.
I KNOW THAT I PLANNED TO STAY
IN TOWN NEXT YEAR...
PROMISE.
JANE:
BUT...
THIS CAME YESTERDAY.
WHERE'S STANFORD?
NORTHERN CALIFORNIA.
I GOT A SCHOLARSHIP,
SPINNER.
IT'S SUCH AN AMAZING
OPPORTUNITY.
BUT YOU'LL BE A BILLION MILES
AWAY!
LOOK. LOOK, WITH READING WEEK
AND SUMMERS,
AND HOLIDAYS,
THE MOST WE'D EVER BE APART
IS LIKE, LIKE, TWO MONTHS.
(TATTOO NEEDLE BUZZES)
COULD YOU STOP, SIR?
NO. NO.
JANE:
SPINNER...
(BAND PLAYS
"POMP AND CIRCUMSTANCE NO.1")
SAV:
SWEET!
DANNY:
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE AN HONOURS GRAD.
DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
YOU COULD READ.
JOHNNY:
NOW IF COULD
JUST MASTER WALKING.
WHY ARE WE TALKING?
(BAND CONTINUES PLAYING
"POMP AND CIRCUMSTANCE NO.1")
HATZILAKOS:
HAPPY GRADUATION, EVERYONE!
(APPLAUSE AND CHEERS
THROUGHOUT CROWD)
THIS IS A MOMENTOUS DAY
FOR ALL OF THE STUDENTS
AT DEGRASSI.
WE'RE HERE TO CELEBRATE
THE ACCOMPLISHMENTS...
HEY, UM, HAVE YOU GUYS
SEEN SPINNER?
DANNY:
UH, HE'S SUPPOSED TO BE HERE?
HE PROBABLY JUST GOT SLAMMED
AT THE DOT.
HATZILAKOS:
...TO ALL OF OUR GRADUATES.
THREE LATTES AND A CAPPUCCINO
FOR THE BRIDE-TO-BE.
JAY:
WOW, MAN.
DID THAT HURT?
NOT AS MUCH
AS WHEN JANE TOLD ME
SHE'S MOVING TO CALIFORNIA.
I DON'T KNOW, CALIFORNIA COULD
BE KIND OF A FUN BOOTY CALL.
DUDE, MANNY'S BACK
EVERY OTHER WEEK, OKAY?
WE'RE TALKING MONTHS APART
HERE.
BRO, SOME GIRLS ARE WORTH
THE TROUBLE.
AND ABSENCE MAKES
THE GIRL GROW, YOU KNOW...
HAPPY TO SEE YOU.
REALLY HAPPY.
(HALF LAUGHS)
JANE AND I HAVE BEEN
THROUGH A LOT...
ALL RIGHT, SURE,
DUMP HER.
YEAH. NO, THAT SOUNDS LIKE
AN EXCELLENT IDEA, MY FRIEND.
ACTUALLY,
WHEN I SAY EXCELLENT,
I MEAN SUPER DUMB.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
OKAY, YOU'RE RIGHT.
HEY, HOLLY J,
TAKE OVER, OKAY?
BUT WHAT ABOUT
THE INTERVIEWS!
YOU KNOW I'M LEAVING!
I'LL BE BACK!
(DOOR CHIMES JINGLE)
(LAUGHS TO HIMSELF)
WOW, I'M GOOD.
AND CORNELL-BOUND,
DANNY VAN ZANDT!
(CROWD CHEERS AND APPLAUDS)
ALL RIGHT.
AND FINALLY... JANE VAUGHN!
AND SHE'S ALSO
YOUR VALEDICTORIAN!
(APPLAUSE AND CHEERS)
CONGRATULATIONS, JANE.
HI, EVERYBODY.
OUR TEACHERS,
FELLOW STUDENTS,
AND FAMILIES DESERVE
CONGRATULATIONS
FOR PUSHING US TOWARD
THIS FINISH LINE.
NO ONE GETS THROUGH HIGH SCHOOL
ALONE AND...
(EXHALES HAPPILY)
HATZILAKOS:
CONGRATULATIONS
TO OUR GRADUATING CLASS!
HATS OFF!
(CHEERING AND WHISTLING)
JENNA:
I SOLD GIRL GUIDE COOKIES,
HAD A PAPER ROUTE,
AND VOLUNTEERED
AT THE ANIMAL SHELTER...
RIGHT.
UM, SERVING EXPERIENCE?
UH... I SERVED FLAPJACKS
AT THE CALGARY STAMPEDE.
OH.
UM, WELL, I WILL
LET YOU KNOW, JENNA.
THANKS.
CAN I JUST PUT YOU
ON THE PAYROLL?
SCHOLARSHIP, DUDE.
PLUS... PLUS,
IF WE'RE BOTH HERE,
WHO IS GONNA STAND IN LINE
FOR CONCERT TICKETS
ALL SUMMER, HM?
(GIGGLES)
LOOK, IT'S NOT EVEN BUSY.
YOU CAN GO TO DECLAN'S
POOL PARTY.
NO. I NEED TO MAKE SURE
YOU DON'T HIRE SOME BIMBO.
EMMA:
HI, PEEPS!
HEY!
EMMA NELSON!
BACK FROM BIKING
ACROSS THE COUNTRY, HUH?
YEAH, I JUST GOT BACK
YESTERDAY!
COOL. SO WHAT'S YOUR NEXT
BIG ADVENTURE NOW?
WELL, OUT ON THE ROAD,
I HAD A LOT OF TIME
TO MISS HOME,
SO I TRANSFERRED TO T.U.
ENVIRONMENTAL STUDIES
IN THE FALL.
T.U.?
IT'S A GREAT SCHOOL.
IT'S NICE AND CLOSE
TO RIGHT HERE.
ARE YOU STILL LOOKING
FOR A NEW SERVER?
YEAH. I'LL NEED SOMEONE
WHO CAN COMMIT THOUGH.
FULL-TIME, ALL SUMMER;
PART-TIME IN THE FALL.
I CAN START RIGHT NOW.
WHOA, EH, OKAY, WAIT.
KEEP YOUR SHIRT ON!
DO YOU EVEN HAVE ANY EXPERIENCE?
UM, TWO PULLS
FOR ESPRESSO,
ONE FOR AMERICANO.
COLD MILK FOR GOOD FOAM.
I SPENT WAY TOO MUCH TIME
AT THE CAMPUS CAFE
AT SMITHDALE.
SHE'S GOOD.
POOL PARTY?
YES. OKAY,
UH, JOB'S YOURS.
(EXCITED SQUEAL)
UM...
NO HOT SANDWICHES,
AND NO DEEP FRYER.
I WILL BE BACK
TO HELP YOU CLOSE UP, OKAY?
OKAY.
THE DOT'S IN GOOD HANDS.
OH!
(ELATED EXHALE)
(CAR RUMBLES UP THE DRIVE)
(GIRL GIGGLES)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
(CHATTER AND LAUGHTER)
...WITH SOME KETCHUP.
ALL:
(EXCHANGE GREETINGS)
YOU WANNA GO CHANGE?
HOLLY J: YEAH!
JANE: OKAY.
JANE: SAVE US SOME FOOD.
HOLLY J: WE'LL BE BACK!
SPINNER:
NICE HOUSE.
FIONA:
THANK YOU.
SPINNER:
DUDE?
COME ON, DON'T TURN
THAT LITTLE SLICE OF HEAVEN
INTO A HOCKEY PUCK
OVER THERE!
ALL RIGHT, GUYS AREN'T SUPPOSED
TO ADMIT THIS,
BUT I HAVE NO CLUE
HOW TO BARBECUE.
SPINNER:
WOULD YOU MIND?
OKAY, NOW,
JANE LIKES HER STEAKS BLUE.
THAT'S REALLY RARE.
HOW DOES HOLLY J
LIKE HERS?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'LL ASK HER,
SAVE YOUR REP.
YOU'RE A GOOD MAN,
SPINNER.
MUCH TO LEARN,
DECLAN-SAN.
EMMA:
HEY, UH,
HERE ARE YOUR SALADS.
I WILL BE RIGHT BACK
WITH YOUR DRINKS. SORRY.
MANNY:
ANYBODY ORDER A BEST FRIEND
WITH A SIDE OF HUG?!
(EMMA AND MANNY SQUEAL)
WHAT AM I,
CHOPPED LIVER?
HI.
JAY:
HEY.
SO YOU'RE WORKING HERE?
UM, DOES THIS MEAN
WE GET FREE COFFEE?
I WOULD HAVE TO CHECK
WITH THE BOSS.
HE AND JANE ARE
AT DECLAN'S PARTY.
MANNY:
OH. STILL GOING STRONG.
UH, YES, I GUESS.
OH... OKAY,
IT IS MY FIRST DAY
AND I AM SWAMPED!
HELP?!
WHAT? I JUST GOT OFF
THE PLANE, SO...
MANNY, YOU'RE AN ACTRESS
IN L.A.
YOU KNOW HOW TO MAKE
A CAPPUCCINO.
(SULKY BREATH)
WELL,
FOR HALF YOUR TIPS,
I CAN FOAM WITH THE BEST
OF THEM.
JANE:
OW!
IT LOOKS LIKE IT HURT.
YES, IT'S STILL RAW.
LET'S JUST SAY I WON'T BE
SWIMMING IN DECLAN'S POOL.
YOU'VE TAKEN THAT DIP
BEFORE.
WOW, ARE WE REALLY
TALKING ABOUT THIS?
HEY, IT WORKED OUT
FOR BOTH OF US.
JANE: YEAH?
HOLLY J: YEAH.
SPINNER NEVER FOUND OUT.
DECLAN AND I FELL IN LOVE.
PLUS, I THINK THE BOYS
ARE EVEN BONDING OVER FIRE.
JANE:
THANK GOD IT WENT
INTO THE VAULT, HUH?
HOLLY J:
AS IF DECLAN'S GONNA BRAG
TO SPINNER
ABOUT SLEEPING WITH YOU!
JANE:
I'M SO DONE
WITH HIGH SCHOOL DRAMA.
HOLLY J:
ESPECIALLY THE SELF-CREATED
KIND, RIGHT?
♪ Hurry up and go out ♪
♪ Find myself another girl ♪
♪♪♪♪♪
(GROANS)
MANNY:
HOLY, BRIDEZILLA PORN!
PEOPLE GET CRAZY
ABOUT WEDDINGS.
I GET IT.
IT'S THE HAPPIEST DAY
OF YOUR LIFE!
SO, NOW THAT THE RUSH
IS OVER,
I WILL REQUIRE A SPINWICH.
WHICH IS HAM, CHICKEN,
BACON...
AVOCADO AND BRIE.
I KNOW.
EXCEPT SPINNER
SAID NOT TO.
OH, I GET IT.
YOU'RE NOT READY
FOR A SPINWICH.
IT IS A DELICATE ART.
PLEASE,
IT'S A TOASTED SANDWICH,
NOT BRAIN SURGERY.
OOH, CAN YOU, UH,
MAKE THAT TWO?
AIRPLANE FOOD
DOES NOT SATISFY.
COMING RIGHT UP,
MY LITTLE CARNIVORES.
MANNY:
YOU KNOW WHAT'S CUTE?
YOU AS DINER MISTRESS.
GUY TRAFFIC'S ABOUT
TO SKY-ROCKET IN HERE.
EMMA:
WELL, I AM TRES SINGLE.
(FRYER CRACKLES)
(LAUGHTER AND CHATTER)
PETER:
HEY, SPINNER, GET YOUR STICKS
IN THE POOL, MAN!
SAV:
HEY, SHOW US
THE FAMOUS CANNONBALL!
SPIN!
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
ARE YOU AFRAID OF
A LITTLE HORSE- WHAT?
YOU THINK I'M STUPID,
JANE?
OKAY, WHAT...
WHAT IS WRONG?
GOOD OLD SPINNER
WON'T EVEN KNOW.
KNOW WHAT?
I HEARD YOU!
IN THERE.
TALKING ABOUT DECLAN.
YOU HAD SEX WITH HIM,
DIDN'T YOU?
IT DIDN'T MEAN ANYTHING,
I SWEAR...
I SWEAR, SPINNER.
HOW LONG?
HOW LONG DID YOU GUYS...?
TWO WEEKS! IT WAS...
IT WAS MONTHS AGO!
AND THAT IS...
THAT'S WHAT I'M TRYING
TO SAY - IT'S OVER!
IT'S SO OVER, SPINNER.
SO EVERYTHING SINCE THEN,
EVERY MINUTE HAS BEEN A LIE?
NO.
NO, SPIN, DON'T!
DECLAN:
(PAINED GRUNT)
HOLLY J:
SPINNER?!
OH SHUT UP!
YOU KNEW ABOUT THIS!
KID:
WHAT IS GOING ON?
GOOD LUCK WITH THE REST
OF YOUR LIFE.
(PLEADING WHISPER)
PLEASE...
SPINNER:
I'M GLAD IT'S HAPPENING
FAR AWAY FROM MINE.
(SOBBING)
(JANE SOBS)
HE HATES ME.
HE, HE SHOULD HATE ME.
I AM...
I'M A HORRIBLE PERSON.
OH... I'VE RUINED
YOUR PARTY AND...
DECLAN, YOUR FACE.
KIND OF HAD IT COMING.
JANE:
AND THE BAND...
I'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO LOOK AT THEM AGAIN.
I'M GONNA GO CAMP OUT
ON THE STANFORD LAWN
UNTIL SEPTEMBER.
OR...
YOU COULD JUST COME
WITH US?
JANE:
WHAT, TO NEW YORK?
YEAH.
MILES AWAY FROM...
ALL THIS.
THERE'S TONS OF ROOM.
MOM'S GONE FOR TWO WEEKS.
YOU'D LOVE IT.
SERIOUSLY?
YEAH.
BOTH:
(SIGH HEAVILY)
EMMA: (OVER FIRE ALARM)
EVERYBODY, GET OVER!
JAY:
PLEASE, OKAY, LADY,
YOU GOTTA GET ACROSS THE STREET
RIGHT NOW, OKAY?
JAY: GET BACK!
EMMA: GET ACROSS THE STREET!
(FIRE ALARM RINGS)
SPINNER!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
SPINNER, I AM SO SORRY!
I ALREADY CALLED 911.
ARE YOU OKAY?
YES, SPINNER,
EVERYONE'S FINE.
THE SANDWICH MAKER-
I TOLD YOU NOT TO TOUCH-
I KNOW, I KNOW!
OKAY, THEY'RE COMING.
I ALREADY...
IT MIGHT NOT BE THAT BAD.
(THUNDEROUS EXPLOSION)
(PANICKED CRIES)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(FIRE TRUCK SIRENS WAIL
AND GROW LOUDER ON APPROACH)
(FIRE TRUCKS HONK
AS THEY ARRIVE)
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ There's something
in the air today ♪
♪ I look outside
to see my dream awaits ♪
♪ In a New York minute ♪
♪ Life is changing,
never ending ♪
♪ Time is wasting ♪
♪ In a New York minute,
liberating... ♪
WELCOME BACK, MR. COYNE.
MS. COYNE.
UH, I'LL GET THOSE FOR YOU,
SWEETHEART.
THANK YOU.
(CARS BLAST THEIR HORNS)
WHAT AM I DOING HERE?
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
THIS IS YOURS?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
(EXHALES, AWESTRUCK)
I FEEL LIKE I'M IN
THE PRINCESS DIARIES.
DECLAN:
IT'S COZY.
COZY?!
I CAN HEAR AN ECHO
IN HERE!
JANE, CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS?
OH MY GOD!
CHANTAY'S TWEET -
THERE WAS A FIRE AT THE DOT
YESTERDAY.
WHAT? IS SPINNER...?
IT SAYS EVERYONE'S OKAY.
WOW, THAT GUY HAD
A REALLY BAD DAY.
YOU KNOW,
I SHOULD CALL HIM.
HOLLY J:
NO.
YOU, MY FRIEND,
ARE THE LAST PERSON
HE WANTS TO HEAR FROM
RIGHT NOW.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
FIONA:
HEY, LOOK! IT'S HOLLY J'S
PLACE OF INTERNMENT,
AND KRISTIN'S STILL HOSTING!
...AND WHAT YOU'VE BEEN
WAITING FOR...
MY INTERVIEW WITH RIDICULOUSLY
HOT RAP SENSATION, DRAKE!
(SIGHS) WHAT?
IS SHE GONNA CRY AGAIN?
NO. BECAUSE WE'RE GOING
SIGHTSEEING.
WELL, YOU GUYS HAVE FUN!
OKAY, WHO WANTS TO PLAY
SIGHTSEER?
OKAY.
(LAUGHS)
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Wherever the wind blows ♪
♪ That's where I'm gonna go ♪
LET'S GO.
♪ Wherever it takes me ♪
♪ That's where I wanna be ♪
♪ Got to be,
Got to be ♪
Got to believe ♪
♪ Got to see to believe ♪
♪ Got to be,
Got to be ♪
HOLLY J:
UGH... THAT'S THE STUFF.
THIS CITY WAS NOT MADE
FOR HIGH HEELS.
JANE:
THOSE ARE SOME SWEET
NEW KICKS, LADY.
HOLLY J:
HM, THANK YOU.
UNFORTUNATELY THEY DO
NOTHING FOR MY...
(CLEARS THROAT)
VERTICALLY CHALLENGED
PREDICAMENT.
THERE'S NO HEIGHT REQUIREMENT
TO LEAP FROM TV INTERN
TO CORPORATE CEO.
AW, YOU'RE SO CUTE.
OKAY... OKAY,
WHY DON'T YOU TWO GO RENT
A ROWBOAT ON THE LAKE?
REALLY?
WE COULD ALL GO.
JANE:
NO, NO, NO!
I'LL CHECK OUT THE BUSKERS.
I'VE BEEN A THIRD WHEEL
LONG ENOUGH.
HOLLY J:
OKAY.
HAVE FUN!
OKAY...
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(POWER TOOLS WHIR,
HAMMER TAPS)
GAMAL:
THE FIRE DEPARTMENT SAYS
IT STARTED
WITH THE SANDWICH MAKER.
YEAH, I'M SORRY,
GAMAL.
IT'S MY FAULT.
ARE WE GONNA REBUILD?
DEPENDS ON INSURANCE.
WE'LL DEFINITELY BE CLOSED
FOR THE SUMMER.
I GUESS WE'LL BE LOOKING
FOR NEW JOBS.
WHO'S THIS?
NOBODY.
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO COVER
FOR ME.
I'M THE MANAGER,
EMMA.
YOUR SCREW-UPS
ARE MY RESPONSIBILITY.
I JUST WANTED TO SEE
IF THERE WAS ANYTHING
I COULD DO.
HOW 'BOUT YOU GO BACK IN TIME
AND NOT BURN DOWN THE DOT?
AND, HEY,
WHILE YOU'RE AT IT,
GET JANE NOT CHEAT ON ME
WITH DECLAN, OKAY?
SPINNER, I AM SO SORRY.
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE.
PLEASE.