HOLLY J:
CARMEN LENNON?
HER PRET-A-PORTER LINE
ARRIVES AT H&M TODAY -
OUR ONE CHANCE TO GET COUTURE
CLOTHES AT HOBO PRICES!
LEIA:
WE HAVE TO RESCHEDULE.
ANYA AND SAV HAD
A MASSIVE BLOW-OUT.
THEN IT MUST BE
THURSDAY.
YOUR RELATIONSHIP
HAS STAGNATED,
SO YOU FIND MINUTIAE
TO FIGHT OVER.
HOLLY J!
HOLLY J:
GOOD NEWS IS,
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE SAV SHOWS UP
WITH SOME UNORIGINAL,
"SPONTANEOUS" GESTURE.
(GUITAR CHORD IS PLAYED)
SAV:
♪ I LOVE TO WATCH YOU CHEER ♪
♪ IT'S BEEN THAT WAY
FOR A HALF A YEAR ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE WE BELONG... ♪
AW! CUTE!
SAV:
♪ YOU'RE MY ONE ♪
♪ MY ONLY... ANYA ♪
(APPLAUSE)
HOLLY J:
MARVY, MAGICAL,
LOVE CONQUERS ALL.
NOW, CAN WE PLEASE
CONQUER THE MALL?
LET'S GO
FOR ICE CREAM!
HOLLY J:
WHAT ABOUT THE SALE?
I...
I BEEN SAVING UP
FOR OUR GIRL-SHOP FOR WEEKS.
ANYA:
YOU CAN TAG ALONG.
THOUGH IT IS
TWO-FOR-ONE CONES SO...
FORGET IT.
I'LL FIGHT OFF FASHIONISTAS
BY MYSELF.
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make through ♪
♪ If I hold out,
I know I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ooh ooh
ohh-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, whatever ♪
(Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes
(Whatever!) ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
MR. KING:
I'M LOOKING FOR BUSINESS IDEAS
WITH REAL WORLD APPLICATION.
YOU CAN PARTNER UP
OR FLY SOLO.
OKAY?
BLUE:
HOLLY'S NOT THE PARTNER TYPE.
THERE'S NO "I" IN TEAM.
THERE IS IN "BITE ME"!
BURN! UP TOP.
WHAT? WHAT, SPINACH OMELET
IN MY TEETH?
DO YOU WANNA WORK TOGETHER
ON THIS?
LIKE, YOU-AND-ME
TOGETHER?
WE'RE THE ONLY GIRLS
IN THE CLASS.
WE COULD SHOW THESE DOOFS
HOW IT'S DONE.
YEAH!
AND WE'RE THE SMARTEST
PEOPLE HERE.
I MEAN, WE CAN ACE
THIS PROJECT.
RELAX. RELAX,
YOU HAD ME AT "DOOFS."
SO, AFTER SCHOOL BRAINSTORM
AT THE DOT?
LATTES ON ME.
WELL, I WORK THERE,
SO...
I MEAN, SURE!
ANNOUNCMENT:
ATTENTION, DEGRASSI.
ALL LATE STUDENTS
MUST REMEMBER TO SIGN IN...
HEY! JANIE
AND THE STUDS, BRO!
THAT WAS A GREAT JAM
YESTERDAY!
THANKS...?
DAVE.
COOL.
UH, WELCOME TO DEGRASSI.
A WHOLE SEMESTER
AND STILL NO ONE KNOWS WHO I AM.
STARTS WITH A "D,"
RIGHT?
(SARCASTIC LAUGH)
VERY FUNNY.
HELP YOUR COUSIN OUT.
POST SOME DAZZLING ITEM
ABOUT ME
ON THE ANTI-GRAPEVINE!
NO DEAL.
YOU MAY RULE
OUR FAMILY REUNIONS
WITH YOUR KANYE
IMPRESSIONS...
UH-HUH,
WHICH RULE.
BUT MY BLOG
IS STRICTLY RESERVED
FOR THE "WHO'S WHO"
OF DEGRASSI,
NOT THE "WHO'S THAT."
OKAY, SO CAN'T YOU
ANOINT ME
KING OF MINOR NINERS
OR SOMETHING?
NICE TRY.
CALL ME WHEN YOU DO
SOMETHING BLOG-WORTHY.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
DECLAN!
WHAT'S UP?
SO I WAS THINKING...
WHY DON'T WE HAVE
A HIGHLY INAPPROPRIATE
LUNCHTIME RENDEZVOUS?
EASY THERE.
WE DON'T DO THIS
AT SCHOOL, REMEMBER?
YOU AND YOUR RULES.
NOT AT SCHOOL,
NOT IN FRONT
OF YOUR BOYFRIEND.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO BRING UP SPINNER
EVERY TIME, YOU KNOW?
COME ON. ISN'T THAT
WHAT MAKES IT FUN?
OKAY.
I'LL BE THE PERFECT
GENTLEMAN.
HEY.
DO YOU WANNA SAUNTER
OVER TOGETHER?
SURE.
ANYA:
HOLLY J?
HI.
SAV DITCHED ME
TO WATCH A SOCCER GAME.
YOU WANNA HANG OUT
WHILE I WAIT FOR HIM TO CALL?
OR YOU COULD GO FIND
YOUR OWN "SOCCER GAME."
DON'T YOU HAVE ANY
NON-SAV INTERESTS?
ANYA:
UM... DO YOU MIND?
LIKE...
ANYA, JANE'S RIGHT;
YOU NEED TO GET A LIFE.
ONE THAT DOESN'T INVOLVE
WAITING AROUND
FOR YOUR BOYFRIEND
TO CALL.
SOME FRIEND YOU ARE.
TRUTH HURTS, DOESN'T IT?
(CAR HORN HONKS)
HOLLY J:
OKAY, SO...
WHAT DO PEOPLE LIKE?
CLOTHES.
UM, MUSIC, BLOGS,
TATTOOS.
SPINNER:
COFFEE!
PEEPS LOOOVES THEM SOME COFFEE.
AND IT'S SO HARD
TO COME BY.
(BABY FUSSES)
UGH. TODDLER YOGA
JUST LET OUT.
TALK ABOUT
YOUR BAD KARMA.
MEGAN:
BARRISTA!
I'LL TIP YOU FIVE BUCKS
TO WATCH DAKOTA
WHILE MOMMY TINKLES.
FYI? I BITE BACK.
HERE.
HEY.
HI. DO YOU KNOW
ITSY BITSY SPIDER?
♪ THE ITSY BITSY SPIDER
WENT UP THE WATER SPOUT ♪
HEY, YOU'RE REALLY GOOD
AT THAT.
YOU KNOW, IF WE'RE TALKING
MARKET DEMAND?
MOMS PAY BIG BUCKS
FOR CHILDCARE.
COME.
LOOK AT ALL THE ADS
FOR SITTERS.
YEAH. THE ONLY PROBLEM
IS I HATE KIDS.
OKAY,
SO DIAPER CHANGING
AND KINDNESS
AREN'T YOUR FORTE,
BUT YOU'RE GREAT AT BOSSING
AROUND TEENAGE GIRLS.
WE COULD BE THE...
FACILITATORS.
WHAT, LIKE,
BABYSITTING PIMPS?
AGENTS, JANE.
BABYSITTING AGENTS.
YUMMY MUMMYS
ARE THE MARKET,
AND WE SUPPLY THEM
WITH WHAT THEY NEED.
DUDE, NEVERMIND
THE BUSINESS PROJECT.
WE COULD ACTUALLY
MAKE A KILLING.
(BABY BABBLES)
(LAUGHS)
("Lifted" by Alysha Brillinger)
♪ So just put on the records
you used to love ♪
♪ Oh, you gotta get on up,
you gotta get lifted ♪
♪ Oh, you gotta get lifted ♪
♪ Said you've gotta turn... ♪
JANE:
SO WE HAVE A HOLE BUNCH
OF SITTERS
WHO ARE PUNCTUAL...
JANE:
YES, AND VERY AFFORDABLE,
AND GREAT WITH KIDS...
HOLLY J:
RESPONSIBLE,
COMPLETELY FIRST AID CERTIFIED.
AND, YOU KNOW,
WE'RE WILLING TO WORK WEEKENDS
AND HOLIDAYS.
JANE:
ALL RIGHT,
POTENTIAL BABYSITTERS,
OUR AGENCY WOULD ARRANGE
ALL THE JOBS FOR YOU.
WE GUARANTEE GOOD PAY.
ALL FOR A MERE TEN PERCENT CUT!
TWENTY PERCENT.
THIRTY ON HOLIDAYS.
YEAH.
♪ ...get lifted ♪
♪ Oh na-na-na,
you got to lift it ♪
♪ Oh come on now,
you gotta love what you do ♪
♪ But do what you love ♪
♪ And you gotta get up ♪
(CAR HORNS HONKING)
(INCESSANT HONKING)
NO, LEIA.
YOU CAN'T BRING DANNY
TO BABYSITTING.
THAT'S REALLY
UNPROFESSIONAL!
GOD FORBID THEY SPEND
TWO MINUTES APART.
IT'S LIKE AS SOON AS A GIRL
GETS A BOYFRIEND,
SHE POWERS DOWN
HER BRAIN.
(LAUGHS)
'CEPT YOU, OF COURSE.
OH, SPINNER KNOWS
THAT I NEED "ME" TIME.
HUH. A GAL PAL
WITH NO BOY DRAMA.
THAT'S...
THAT'S PRETTY REFRESHING,
JANE.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
(SIGHS)
WHAT NOW, LEIA?
JANE:
STOP.
SERIOUSLY.
O BRAKE!
(LOUD CRASH)
OH.
THE OTHER BRAKE.
JANE. YOU OKAY?
BETTER THAN
YOUR BACK BUMPER.
I AM SO SORRY.
YOUR POOR CAR.
GOVERNMENT'S CAR.
DIPLOMATIC PLATES,
DIPLOMATIC IMMUNITY.
I COULD DRIVE IN REVERSE,
NO ONE WOULD BAT AN EYE.
YOU'RE SURE?
SHOULD WE EXCHANGE
INSURANCE?
ARE YOU TRYING
TO GET MY NUMBER?
IT'S PRETTY SNEAKY.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
(DECLAN'S CAR STARTS)
HEY.
I'VE COME UP WITH SOME
JUICY GOSSIP ABOUT ME
THAT YOUR READERS
WILL LOVE.
CHANTAY,
WHO IS THIS?
MY COUSIN,
NOBODY.
FORMALLY KNOWN
AS NOBODY!
CHANTAY:
DAVE, TRUST ME,
YOU'RE LAME
AND I'M THE EXPERT.
THE EXPERT ON LAME?
HEY,
NO ARGUMENT HERE!
OKAY,
HOW LAME IS THIS?
CHECK THIS OUT.
(LAUGHING)
COOL, HUH?
BRUCE:
OH... OOPS!
WIENER BOY PEED HIMSELF!
(LAUGHS)
THE GUY WHO TAKES DOWN
BRUCE
IS GONNA GET A MEDAL.
FOR REAL.
GUY LIKE THAT'D BE
A HERO.
INSTRUCTOR:
A PORTABLE BATH IS IDEAL.
NO FAUCETS FOR THE BABY
TO BUMP AGAINST.
AND WHEN DEALING
WITH AN INFANT,
ALWAYS USE A CLEAN WET CLOTH,
NO SOAP.
UM...
YOUR BABY'S DROWNING.
ISN'T DECLAN
ON THE SWIM TEAM?
WHAT?
I REALLY WOULDN'T KNOW.
HE WAS SO COOL
ABOUT THE CAR.
YEAH, I GUESS.
HEY, YOU WERE
KIND OF IN SHOCK,
ARE YOU FEELING OKAY?
WHY HAVEN'T I TALKED
TO HIM BEFORE?
WHAT'S HIS DEAL?
WHAT'S YOUR DEAL,
CHATTY CATHY?
IT ALMOST SOUNDS
LIKE YOU LIKE HIM.
NO.
WELL,
MAYBE A LITTLE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I JUST TOLD YOU THAT.
ME NEITHER.
NEXT STOP,
DECLAN AND I DOUBLE DATE
WITH YOU AND SPINNER.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
HI. UM...
I PROMISED MY MOM I'D GO SEE
"SOUND OF MUSIC" THIS EVENING,
SO I KINDA HAVE TO BAIL
ON THAT EVERHART GIG.
UNACCEPTABLE, ALLI!
HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO FIND A SITTER?
JANE:
HEY, UM... I'LL COVER.
IT'S THE LEAST I CAN DO.
("I Know What I Am"
by Band of Skulls plays)
♪ But it's all right,
it's okay ♪
♪ I got the time
but the time don't pay ♪
♪ It's all right,
it's okay ♪
♪ I got the time,
but the time don't pay ♪
♪ It's all right,
It's okay ♪
♪ I got the time
but the time don't pay ♪
♪ It's all right
It's O-kay... ♪
♪ Flip Flop,
don't stop ♪
♪ I've got the wit
that my enemies lack... ♪
IT'S TIME TO MAKE MY MARK,
BRUCE.
♪ So let me be ♪
♪ Trick some,
just begun ♪
♪ Giving you more
when you only want one ♪
♪ 'cause I know what I am... ♪
BRUCE:
HEY!
BRUCE!
(ANGRY GRUNT)
YOU'RE A DEAD MAN, DAVE!
IT'S, IT'S DARRYL!
(SIZZLING)
GRILLED BRIE HOAGIES?
WHO'RE YOU FEEDING TONIGHT,
THE POPE?
I'M SURPRISING JANE
AT HER BABYSITTING JOB.
WE CAN WORK ON OUR PROPOSALS
AND GIRL OUT.
OH.
BY THE WAY, I...
FINALLY GET IT.
HOW TO WORK
THE SANDWICH MAKER?
YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
SHE'S FUNNY,
SMART, COOL.
NO WONDER YOU'RE CRAZY
ABOUT HER.
YEAH, WE'RE CLOSE,
BUT JANE COULD USE
A CHICK FRIEND, TOO.
HMM.
HAPPY TO OBLIGE.
NOW CLEAN THIS MESS UP,
WILL YA?
AFTER I MAKE ONE.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(KNOCKING)
DECLAN?
(FRONT DOOR CLOSES)
JANE, WE GOTTA TALK.
NO KIDDING!
I TEXTED YOU, LIKE,
50 TIMES LAST NIGHT.
WE ARE TRIPLE-BOOKED
FOR BABYSITTING
THIS WEEKEND, MS. TRUMP!
PROPS!
GREAT. NOW WE NEED
MORE SITTERS.
I ALREADY BOOKED
THREE INTERVIEWS FOR LUNCH.
NINER GIRLS,
FIRST AID CERTIFIED,
DESPERATE FOR CASH.
ANYTHING YOU WANT?
I GOT IT.
YEAH, NO KIDDING.
YOU'VE EVEN GOT...
DECLAN.
WHAT?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I SAW YOU TWO SUCKING FACE
OUTSIDE THE EVERHARTS'!
I KNOW, JANE.
(SIGHS)
SOME PARTNER YOU ARE.
COOL OVERCOAT, GUY.
GOT SOMEONE TO FLASH?
SHH!
I'M INCOGNITO!
PLEASE, SIR.
SIR, DON'T KILL ME!
THAT'S BRUCE'S
PREROGATIVE.
BACK ALLEY,
AFTER SCHOOL.
JENNA:
I MEAN, I HAVE SIX NIECES
AND NEPHEWS,
SO I'M "AUNT BABYSITTER."
HOLLY J:
YOU GOT THE GIG.
THAT'S THE ADDRESS.
AND REMEMBER,
15 MINUTES EARLY
IS LATE.
JENNA:
OH MY GOD!
THANK YOU!
AND YOU KNEW
I LIKED HIM!
AND YOU HAVE
A BOYFRIEND!
REMEMBER SPINNER?
YEAH.
YEAH, I DO.
SO, WHY EXACTLY DO YOU
ONLY GET CRUSHES
ON GUYS THAT I LIKE?
SPINNER TOLD YOU
ABOUT THAT?
DUDE,
HE'S MY BOYFRIEND!
BUT IT'S NOT LIKE THAT
STOOD IN YOUR WAY.
ALLI!
ALLI, WEDNESDAY?
SMITH HOUSE?
YOU OWE US OUR COMMISSION.
FINE, BUT NOTHING HAPPENED
WITH SPIN!
YOU'RE THE ONE
CHEATING ON HIM.
YOU KNOW WHAT,
"FRIEND?"
I DON'T CARE WHAT YOU
THINK YOU SAW,
STAY OUT
OF MY BUSINESS.
CLARE!
TWENTY PERCENT!
YOU KNOW, THIS WHOLE PARTNERSHIP
WAS MY IDEA.
WHOA! OUR IDEA!
WHATEVER. I'M OUT.
GOING SOLO.
BUT OUR BUDGET
IS DUE THIS AFTERNOON!
THEN I'LL GET
AN EXTENSION.
I'D RATHER TAKE A "B"
THAN DEAL WITH YOUR B.S.
THAT WAS INTENSE.
LOOK, I DON'T WANT TO ENCROACH
ON "BOYFRIEND" TERRITORY,
BUT UH...
YOU WANNA TALK?
THANKS, DEX,
BUT I GOT IT.
GIRL DRAMA'S NOT IN
YOUR JOB DESCRIPTION.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
MM, WHAT'S THIS?
DAVE:
MY AUTOGRAPHED BOSH JERSEY
YOU ALWAYS WANTED.
REALLY?
WHAT'S THE CATCH?
BRUCE WANTS ME DEAD.
I GOTTA GO
INTO HIDING;
CHANGE MY NAME,
TRANSFER TO BARDELL.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT
THE WORST PART ABOUT IT IS?
IS NO ONE WILL EVEN KNOW
I WENT TO DEGRASSI
IN THE FIRST PLACE!
DID YOU REALLY...
RELIEVE YOURSELF
ON BRUCE'S LOCKER?
WELL, NOT EXACTLY,
BUT I'M STILL DEAD.
EVERYONE'S TALKIN'
ABOUT IT.
WE'LL BE PRAYING
FOR YOUR SOUL.
(LAUGHS)
WANT ME TO WALK
YOU HOME?
YOU KNOW, IF I SHOW UP
FOR THE FIGHT,
EVERYONE WILL KNOW
WHO I AM.
MR. KING:
SO, I'VE RECEIVED
YOUR PROPOSALS.
YEAH, MR. K?
I'M GONNA NEED
AN EXTENSION;
CHANGE OF STAFF.
MR. KING:
...AND I'M DISTRIBUTING HOLLY J
AND JANE'S WORK,
SO YOU CAN SEE JUST HOW HIGH
THE BAR HAS BEEN SET.
YOU DID
THE WHOLE BUDGET?
TYPED IT UP
ON MY SPARE.
MR. KING:
GREAT WORK, GIRLS.
I THINK YOU'RE REALLY
ONTO SOMETHING.
UM, THE COMMISSION
REVENUE MODEL
WAS ALL HOLLY J.
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING
TO PROVE?
THAT YOU NEED
A BUSINESS PARTNER,
AND, AND I NEED
A FRIEND.
CAN WE TALK?
(POLICE SIREN WAILS)
SAV:
FIFTY BUCKS SAYS BRUCE
MAKES HIM EAT THAT HOODIE.
STATISTICALLY,
DAVE'S CHANCES
OF WINNING ARE...
NIL.
DAVE:
WOW, THAT'S A BIG CROWD.
HEY, AND FOR THOSE
WHO DON'T KNOW ME,
I'M DAVE.
AND ALSO,
WHEN THE PARAMEDICS ARRIVE,
MY HEALTH CARD'S IN MY SHOE.
(STUDENTS LAUGH)
BRUCE:
HEY, KID!
YOU READY FOR THIS?
OKAY, BRUCE, LOOK.
LISTEN. LISTEN, OKAY?
YOU BEAT ME UP,
WHAT DOES THIS PROVE, HUH?
I'M A LITTLE SKINNY NINER
NOBODY KNOWS.
WE CAN BREAK THE CYCLE
OF VIOLENCE.
TOGETHER.
I'M NOT GONNA
BEAT YOU UP.
AS SOON AS I SAW YOU,
I KNEW YOU WERE
A REASONABLE GUY.
THAT'S A WATER BALLOON.
WHO SAID
IT WAS WATER?
(BIG SPLASH)
(SCREAMS AND GROANS)
IT'S WARM.
NOW WE'RE EVEN, DAVE.
(SMATTERING OF APPLAUSE)
DAVE,
YOU'RE NUMBER ONE, MAN.
FOR REAL.
OKAY.
DECLAN AND I,
WHATEVER WE ARE,
IT'S BEEN GOING ON
FOR A COUPLE OF WEEKS.
THIS IS GONNA
KILL SPINNER.
LOOK, I LOVE SPIN.
I DO.
BUT WE'RE...
WE'RE SETTLED.
AND (STAMMERS)
AND DECLAN, HE...
HE MAKES ME FEEL
LIKE MORE
THAN JUST ONE OF THE GUYS.
THAT'S PRETTY RICH,
COMING FROM THE GIRL
WHO HAS ALL THE GUYS.
TRY THE GIRL WHO HAS
NO FEMALE FRIENDS,
NOW THAT YOU HATE ME.
WELL, IS DECLAN
IN LOVE WITH YOU?
ARE YOU WITH HIM?
PICK SPINNER,
DECLAN'LL BOUNCE BACK
IN MINUTES.
PICK DECLAN,
BREAK SPINNER'S HEART.
FOREVER.
IT UH...
LOOK IT UM...
IT'S NOT THAT DRAMATIC,
HOLLY J.
YOU WANT FRIEND ADVICE?
FOR REAL?
UNLESS YOU BREAK UP
WITH YOUR BOY TOY ASAP,
THIS DOESN'T END WELL.
I WORK WITH SPIN
EVERY DAY, JANE.
I CAN ONLY LIE TO HIM
FOR SO LONG.
DANNY:
THERE HE IS!
YOU DA MAN, DAVE!
DAVE:
I AM THE MAN!
BRUCE:
DAVE!
WASSUP?
DOWN LOW.
CHANTAY:
DAVE?
I THINK YOU MEAN
"THE ARTIST FORMALLY KNOWN
AS WHO'S THAT?"
THE BLOG'S BUZZING.
I WANNA DO
AN INTERVIEW:
DAVE VS. GOLIATH.
I'LL SEE IF I CAN
PENCIL YOU IN
SAY... NEXT WEEK?
CIAO, CUZ.
♪ But it's all right,
it's okay ♪
♪ I got the time
but the time don't pay ♪
♪ It's all right,
it's okay ♪
♪ I Got the time
but the tie don't pay ♪
SPINNER:
HEY, J!
COME TO COOK UP SOME
OF YOUR SIGNATURE SAMMIES?
(AWKWARD LAUGH)
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
JANE HELD UP HER END
OF OUR AGREEMENT.
YEP. IT'S OVER.
DEAL A BRO A CLUE?
IT'S JUST GIRL STUFF.
HI. I NEED A SITTER
FOR NEW YEAR'S EVE.
ARE YOU BOOKING YET?
UM...
UH...
YEAH. YEAH, OF COURSE.
JUST, UH SHOOT US
AN EMAIL.
MICHELLE:
THANKS.
ARE YOU... OKAY?
UM, RELIEVED, MOSTLY.
AND... TERRIFIED THAT SPIN'LL
FIND OUT SOME DAY.
WELL, IT WON'T BE
FROM ME.
THANKS, HOLLY J.
FOR EVERYTHING.
YEAH, YOU OWE ME.
HUGE.
AND I'M GONNA BE AROUND
A LONG TIME TO COLLECT.
DEAL.
SEE YOU IN CLASS?
♪ A random accident of fate
brought me to trust ♪
♪ And now I'm on my way... ♪