(LOCKER RATTLES)
(NOISE MAKER SQUEALS,
SAV GRUNTS, SURPRISED)
ANYA:
GOTCHA!
(GIGGLES AND LAUGHS)
DID YOU DO THIS?
READ IT.
OF COURSE
I'LL GO TO FORMAL WITH YOU!
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO GO
TO ALL THIS TROUBLE!
I JUST WANTED IT
TO BE VERY, VERY SPECIAL.
IT'LL BE EVERYTHING
WE'VE ALWAYS DREAMED.
ANYA:
HMM.
NOW, WE NEED PHOTOS!
OF ME IN MY DRESS
AND YOU IN YOUR SUIT.
AND I WAS THINKING
YOUR BACK YARD?
FOR THE PHOTOS?
UH, WHY DON'T WE DO 'EM
AT YOUR PLACE?
AS IF! THAT BEAUTIFUL GAZEBO
IN YOUR MOM'S GARDEN?
IT'S PERFECT!
YEAH.
(KISS)
YOU'RE GETTING PRETTY GOOD
AT THAT.
KEEPING ANYA HAPPY.
NICE WORK.
ONE MINOR PROBLEM.
SHE WANTS TO COME TO MY PLACE
FOR FORMAL PHOTOS.
HEY, WELL, COME ON,
YOU'RE NOT THAT UGLY.
VERY FUNNY.
ANYA CAN'T COME
TO MY PLACE.
I TOLD MY PARENTS
WE BROKE UP FOR GOOD.
AFTER OUR LAST BREAKUP,
I JUST...
OMITTED THE FACT THAT
WE GOT BACK TOGETHER.
IF SHE FINDS OUT,
IT'S GONNA GET UGLY.
YOU ALWAYS KNOW HOW TO MAKE ME
FEEL SO MUCH BETTER.
ALL RIGHT.
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it,
I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, Woo-ooh ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever)
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
LIVE BUNSEN BURNERS MEAN...
SAFETY GOGGLES, PEOPLE!
PUT 'EM ON BEFORE YOU START
PLAYING WITH FIRE.
MAKE SURE YOU TIE BACK
YOUR LONG HAIR...
DANNY-DANNY-DANNY!
HEY.
NICE GOGGLES.
YOU GOTTA HELP ME OUT
WITH THIS ANYA THING, MAN.
SO ASIDE FROM YOUR OBVIOUS
FORGETFULNESS,
WHY ARE YOU KEEPING ANYA
A SECRET FROM YOUR FOLKS?
THEY'RE ANTI-GIRLFRIEND.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY
WE CAN BE TOGETHER.
(BUBBLES SPUTTER)
IT'S GONNA BLOW UP.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I GOTTA COME CLEAN.
DANNY:
NO THE BUNSEN BURNER
BEHIND YOU, DUDE!
OH JEEZ!
UH...
(HALF LAUGHS)
YOU SHOULDN'T PLAY
WITH FIRE!
(P.A. ANNOUNCEMENT PLAYS,
DIN OF STUDENTS' CHATTER)
ALLI!
WE SHOULD GO TO FORMAL
TOGETHER.
(SCOFFS) IS THAT YOUR WAY
OF ASKING ME OUT?
DIRECT.
IT'S HOW I ROLL.
WELL, UH,
NOT IN A MILLION YEARS.
WHATEVER.
I JUST THOUGHT I WOULD ASK
SINCE YOU ALWAYS
TALKED ABOUT IT.
WELL... BEFORE.
EXACTLY.
BEFORE THE PICTURES,
THE LYING AND THE...
I'M NOT EVEN GONNA GO THERE.
READ MY LIPS:
WE'RE OVER!
NICE HAIRCUT.
JOHNNY:
(GRUNTS SMUGLY)
BRUCE:
AHN, DON'T WORRY, MAN.
SHE WASN'T THE ONE.
SHE WAS ONE OF MANY.
YEAH.
FORGET HER.
ALLI:
HEY, DORK.
SAV:
HEY, SPAZ.
WHAT'S WITH THE BALLOONS?
SAV:
THEY'RE FROM ANYA.
HELP ME OUT A SEC?
NOW WHAT?
I'M TRYING TO RUN
THROUGH A SCENARIO.
PRETEND TO BE MOM.
DO WE HAVE TO ROLE-PLAY
EVERY TIME YOU HAVE A CRISIS?
COME ON, ALLI!
I'M TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO TELL THEM
I'M STILL WITH ANYA.
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
OH, I DON'T KNOW,
HONESTY BEING THE BEST POLICY
AND ALL?
IN OUR FAMILY? YOU KNOW
THEY'RE MAKE IT IMPOSSIBLE
FOR YOU AND ANYA
TO BE TOGETHER.
(AS HER MOTHER)
NO BOYFRIENDS OR GIRLFRIENDS
UNTIL COLLEGE!
(LAUGHS)
MRS. BHANDARI:
(SING-SONG)
HELLO-O!
BUT IF YOU'RE GONNA
COME CLEAN?
I'M GONNA WATCH!
WHAT'S ALL THIS?
UH, THEY'RE...
FOR SPRING FORMAL.
I TOLD YOU ABOUT IT.
YES, YOU'RE GOING
WITH PETER AND DANNY.
IT'S SO GOOD YOU BOYS
AREN'T OBSESSED WITH GIRLS
AND DATES.
WAY TO BE HONEST, BRO.
(LAUGHS)
(POOL BALLS CLATTER)
WHAT ABOUT THAT ONE?
TOO MOUSE-LIKE.
HMM.
WHAT ABOUT THIS ONE
IN THE T-SHIRT?
HER KNEES LOOK SHARP.
UH...
WELL, THERE'S ALWAYS
SWEET, SWEET LINDSAY.
JOHNNY:
THE WAITRESS?
I'VE TOTALLY SEEN HER SMILE
AT YOU, DUDE.
SHE'S A WAITRESS.
SHE SMILES AT EVERYONE.
NO, MAN I THINK
YOU HAVE A CHANCE.
BUT ISN'T SHE, LIKE,
IN COLLEGE?
SO WHAT? WITH THAT HAIRCUT,
YOU LOOK MATURE.
KIND OF.
LINDSAY!
JOHNNY:
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?!
I DIDN'T EVEN SHAVE.
HEY, GUYS,
WHAT CAN I GET YOU?
MY FRIEND THINKS
YOU'RE REALLY HOT.
THANKS.
JOHNNY, RIGHT?
(UNCOMFORTABLE GRUNTS)
DON'T LISTEN TO HIM...
HE'S DUMB.
OH, SO YOU DON'T THINK
I'M HOT?
NO! I-I-I-I-I...
(STAMMERING)
LOOK, ARE YOU GUYS
GONNA ORDER SOMETHING?
UH, WE'RE FINE.
SO, CAN HE HAVE
YOUR NUMBER, SWEETHEART?
NICE MOVES, PLAYA.
SHUT UP.
(SCOFFED LAUGHTER)
ANYA:
(LAUGHS)
(GIGGLES)
SAV, WHERE ARE WE?
WE HAVE TO GET TO SCHOOL!
MINOR DETOUR.
DON'T PEEK!
SMELLS AMAZING.
OKAY.
T, IS IT...?
TAKE IT OFF.
IT'S THE BOTANICAL GARDEN!
I KNEW IT!
(LAUGHS)
I COULD SMELL
THE BLOSSOMS!
BUT WHAT ARE WE DOING HERE?
WE WALK PAST IT EVERY DAY,
I THOUGHT IT'D
BE THE PERFECT PLACE
FOR OUR FORMAL PHOTOS.
WELL, THAT'S VERY THOUGHTFUL.
NO PARENTS,
NO DISTRACTIONS.
JUST ME AND YOU
AT OUR OWN SPECIAL PLACE.
I WILL TAKE THAT
AS A YES?
IT'S MORE THAN A YES.
IT'S SUCH A BEAUTIFUL WAY
TO START A SPECIAL NIGHT.
LIKE WE ALWAYS PLANNED.
PETER:
THEN WHAT HAPPENED?
SAV:
AND THEN SHE SAID SHE WANTED
TO MAKE THE NIGHT "SPECIAL."
WHOA!
LIKE, VERY SPECIAL?
DO YOU NEED ME
TO DRAW YOU A DIAGRAM?
OH, SEXY TIME,
DIRTY DAWG!
BUT IT'S NOT JUST ABOUT THAT.
I WANT IT TO BE ROMANTIC.
CLASSY.
ALL RIGHT, THEN LET'S START
WITH THE THREADS.
WILFORD TUXEDOS IS HERE
FOR ALL OF OUR FORMAL ATTIRE
RENTING NEEDS.
("DEAD ON FASHION"
BY "POP FASCIST" PLAYS)
♪ Hey sexy mama ♪
♪ Let's get it on ♪
♪ You've got the face,
you're about the race ♪
♪ And it turns me on ♪
♪ Hey sexy, baby ♪
♪ Don't make it worse ♪
♪ You got the face
don't go to waste ♪
♪ Let's make it hurt ♪
♪ It's in our fashions ♪
♪ You've got the look,
you've got the look ♪
♪ So come alive ♪
♪ It's in our fashion ♪
♪ You've got the look
you've got the look ♪
♪ I can't survive ♪
ALLI:
HEY. SO, IS ANYA
STILL TALKING TO YOU?
OH,
SHE'S MORE THAN TALKING
TO ME.
EW, YOU ARE SO GROSS.
(SIGHS)
FORMAL'S GONNA ROCK, SIS.
I'VE GOT IT ALL PLANNED OUT.
MRS. BHANDARI:
SAVTAJ? ALLIAH?
I JUST GOT OFF THE PHONE.
THE HASSANS ARE COMING
A WEEK EARLY.
THEY'LL BE HERE TOMORROW.
TOMORROW?
IS FARRAH COMING TOO?
OF COURSE!
WE HAVE TO GET MOVING.
WHERE'S THE SWIFFER?
UH, BUT MOM,
TOMORROW'S MY SPRING FORMAL.
I HAVE TO GO!
OKAY.
MAYBE YOU COULD TAKE FARRAH.
UH... PARDON?
I KNOW HOW IMPORTANT FORMAL
IS TO YOU AND YOUR FRIENDS.
AND WHAT BETTER WAY
TO GET TO KNOW
YOUR POSSIBLE FUTURE WIFE?
(HALF LAUGHS)
MOM!
FARRAH WON'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO WEAR, SO...
I'LL CALL BACK TO MAKE SURE
SHE BRINGS A DRESS.
I'M SURE SHE'LL BE DELIGHTED.
(PHONE BEEPS)
MAYBE UNCLE AMIR CAN RENT
YOU TWO A LIMO!
YEAH.
GREAT!
ALLI:
YOU KNOW, IT'S A GOOD THING
YOU'VE EVERYTHING WORKED OUT.
(SNORTED LAUGHTER)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
YOU CATCH THE UFC FIGHT
LAST NIGHT?
I'M NOT TALKING TO YOU.
WHY NOT?
'CAUSE YOU'RE A LAME-ASS.
I MADE YOU TALK TO ME!
LOOK, IT'S NOT MY FAULT
YOU COULDN'T SEAL THE DEAL
WITH LINDSAY.
IF YOU WEREN'T THERE,
I ACTUALLY MIGHT'VE
HAD A CHANCE.
RIGHT.
SHE'S A UNIVERSITY CHICK.
SHE'S OUTTA YOUR LEAGUE.
NEXT FALL,
I'LL BE IN THAT LEAGUE.
UNLIKE YOU,
MR. TWO-CREDITS-SHY.
HAVE FUN BEING THE OLDEST
LOSER IN HIGH SCHOOL.
WHAT? YOU'RE SOME SORT
OF BIG MAN NOW?
BIG? MAYBE.
MAN? YEAH.
AND YOU SHOULD TRY ACTING
LIKE ONE.
BOTH: (IN UNISON)
YOUR FUTURE WHAT?
MY MAYBE-POSSIBLY FUTURE WIFE.
MY PARENTS ARE MAKING ME
TO TAKE HER TO SPRING FORMAL.
DANNY:
HOLD ON. REWIND.
MY PARENTS WANT ME TO MARRY
WITHIN THE CULTURE, RIGHT?
SO, SOMEONE MUSLIM...
LIKE, ARRANGED MARRIAGE
STYLES?
MORE INTRODUCTION STYLES.
I DON'T HAVE TO MARRY HER.
BUT THEY'D JUST LIKE IT
BETTER IF I DID.
OKAY, I'M GONNA
ASK THE QUESTION
THAT WE'RE BOTH THINKING
RIGHT NOW:
IS SHE HOT?
I DON'T KNOW. LAST TIME
I SAW HER SHE WAS 10 YEARS OLD.
OKAY. SECOND QUESTION
THAT WE'RE ALL THINKING:
HOW DO YOU GET TWO GIRLS
AND I HAVE NONE?
IT DOESN'T HAVE
TO BE THAT WAY.
MAYBE YOU COULD TAKE FARRAH.
ANYA DOESN'T KNOW HER
BY NAME.
SHE'LL JUST THINK THAT
YOU'RE GOING WITH SOME-
NO WAY, DUDE.
I DON'T DO BLIND DATES.
DANNY:
ISN'T THIS MAYBE-POSSIBLE
FUTURE WIFE
GONNA WONDER WHY SHE'S HANGING
WITH THIS DUDE ANYWAYS?
MAYBE SHE'D PLAY ALONG.
I GOTTA AT LEAST TRY
TO PULL THIS OFF FOR ANYA.
COME ON, MAN. I WILL PAY
FOR YOUR FORMAL TICKET.
DUDE, FORGET IT.
AND PICK YOU UP IN A LIMO!
COME ON, MAN!
YOU GOTTA HELP A GUY OUT!
OKAY, FINE.
BUT YOU STILL OWE ME.
SAV:
ANYTHING. YOU NAME IT!
WHEN THE TIME COMES,
I WILL.
THANK YOU.
ANYA:
WHATCHA YOU SO EXCITED ABOUT?
UH... I GOT US A LIMO!
WE'RE GONNA SHARE WITH PETER
AND HIS DATE!
A LIMO?!
YEAH.
SAV, I CAN'T WAIT!
UM, OH, I TOOK A QUIZ
TO FIGURE OUT
MY "PASSION PERSONALITY".
COOL.
YOU'RE NERVOUS.
THAT'S SO SWEET!
COSMO SAID IT MIGHT HAPPEN.
I'M NOT NERVOUS.
OH, IT'S OKAY!
EVERYONE'S NERVOUS
THEIR FIRST TIME.
TRUST ME, SAV,
IT'LL BE PERFECT.
BRUCE:
YO, JOHNNY!
HEY, WHAT TIME WE HANGING
TONIGHT?
CAN'T, GOT OTHER PLANS.
LOOK.
YOU'RE NOT STILL PISSED
ARE YOU?
NAH, MAN,
I JUST GOT OTHER PLANS.
ALL RIGHT. FINE.
BE THAT WAY.
ALL RIGHT.
(DOOR CLICKS,
KEYS JINGLE)
MRS. BHANDARI:
SAVTAJ? IS THAT YOU?
HEY, MOM, SORRY I'M LATE.
OH.
HEY. IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU
AGAIN.
HELLO AGAIN, SAVTAJ.
MRS. HASSAN:
SAVTAJ! MMMM.
I WOULD NOT HAVE EVEN
RECOGNIZED YOU!
SO TALL!
YOU.
YOU REMEMBER FARRAH.
YES. RIGHT.
FARRAH!
UH... IT'S, UH...
IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU-
MEET YOU AGAIN.
I-I MEAN...
RE-MEET YOU.
UH, IT'S BEEN...?
SEVEN YEARS.
I KNOW.
YOU LOOK... SO DIFFERENT!
YOU CAN PICK YOUR JAW UP
OFF THE FLOOR, ANYTIME NOW.
(CARS WHIR BY,
MUSIC PLAYS WITHIN BILLIARD)
(POOL BALLS CLATTER)
LINDSAY. HEY.
SO, HOW'S IT GOIN'?
PRETTY GOOD.
WHERE'S THE OGRE?
OH, YOU KNOW,
UNDER A BRIDGE SOMEWHERE.
(LAUGHS)
I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU HANG OUT
WITH THAT LOSER.
HE'S NOT THAT BAD.
I GUESS I DON'T KNOW HIM
THAT WELL.
IT'S OKAY.
I MEAN, I GUESS YOU CAN'T
CHOOSE YOUR FRIENDS.
SO? YOU GONNA STAND THERE,
OR MAKE YOURSELF USEFUL?
YEAH, SURE.
I'VE GOT A PASSION
FOR CUTLERY.
MR. HASSAN:
SO, SAV, WHAT DO YOU PLAN
ON DOING AFTER YOUR STUDIES?
SAV:
UH, WELL, I REALLY LOVE MUSIC.
MAYBE TOUR THE WORLD
WITH A BAND.
I MEAN, AFTER I GET MY MUSIC
PH.D. OF COURSE.
THAT SOUNDS REALLY COOL.
MR. BHANDARI:
DON'T WORRY,
I KEEP TELLING HIM,
"SAV, 'COOL'
DOESN'T PAY THE BILLS".
AND I KEEP SAYING,
"DAD, I DON'T HAVE ANY BILLS."
MRS. HASSAN:
YES, BUT WHEN YOU HAVE
A FAMILY,
AND A HOUSE AND KIDS,
SWIMMING LESSONS...
OH, COME ON, AMEENA.
LET'S NOT SCARE THEM.
THEY HAVE TIME STILL.
BUT NOT TOO MUCH TIME.
I WANT TO HOLD MY GRANDCHILDREN
BEFORE I DIE!
(CLEARS THROAT)
HERE MOM,
UH, LET ME GET THAT FOR YOU!
LET ME HELP YOU WITH THAT,
SAV.
MRS. BHANDARI:
WHAT? NO, YOU'RE THE GUEST.
YOU SIT DOWN.
UH, NO, I INSIST.
BESIDES, DAD,
DIDN'T YOU WANNA SHOW THEM
THE PHOTOS FROM OUR TRIP?
OF NEWFOUNDLAND, YES!
I BROUGHT THE SLIDE SHOW.
DVD OR BLU-RAY?
MR. BHANDARI:
WE HAVE BOTH!
COME.
THERE YA GO.
ALL DONE.
YOU'VE GOT A BRIGHT FUTURE
AS A BUSBOY, JOHNNY.
YEAH, MAYBE I'LL SKIP
UNIVERSITY.
(HALF LAUGHS)
WHERE'RE YOU GONNA GO?
WHAT'RE YOU GONNA STUDY?
JOHNNY:
I'M NOT SURE.
I'M GOOD AT LOTS OF STUFF.
I KNEW YOU HAD TO BE SMARTER
THAN YOU LOOK.
(HALF LAUGHS)
KIDDING!
SO, WHAT'RE YOU DOING
SATURDAY?
WHY? YOU GOT SOMETHING
PLANNED?
IT'S JUST MY SPRING FORMAL.
YOUR HIGH SCHOOL FORMAL?
YEAH, YOU WANNA COME?
YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
THAT'S SWEET, JOHNNY,
BUT I...
NO, NO, I WAS JUST JOKING
ANYWAY. I...
BRUCE:
WELL, WELL, WELL.
LOOKIE HERE.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE HANGING
AT HOME TONIGHT?
CHANGED MY MIND.
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
'CAUSE NOW WE'RE EVEN.
IF YOU EVER TOUCH ME
AGAIN...
OR WHAT?
YOU'RE GONNA SHOW ME HOW YOU'RE
A BIG UNIVERSITY MAN NOW?!
HUH?!
LINDSAY:
GUYS!
KNOCK IT OFF!
THIS IS WHY I DON'T HANG OUT
WITH HIGHSCHOOLERS.
THEN I GUESS IT'S TIME
FOR ME TO LEAVE.
♪ Down with the losers... ♪
I'M SORRY,
MY PARENTS WERE SO...
EMBARRASSING BACK THERE.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
THIS WHOLE THING
IS JUST...
FARRAH: AWKWARD?
SAV: AWKWARD.
SAV:
I TRY NOT TO GET FREAKED OUT
BY THE WHOLE ARRANGED MARRIAGE
THING.
I KNOW, IT SEEMS SO...
OLD SCHOOL.
MY MOM SAYS TO THINK OF IT
AS A FAMILY DATING SERVICE.
AS IF WE'RE THAT DESPERATE!
I KNOW.
(PHONE RINGS)
UH, "ANYA."
IT'S 4 MISSED CALLS.
WHO'S ANYA?
UH... SHE'S MY GIRLFRIEND.
SHE'S CUTE.
YOU SHOULD PROBABLY
CALL HER BACK?
YEAH.
UH, FARRAH THERE'S SOMETHING
I GOTTA BE HONEST ABOUT.
IT'S ABOUT THE FORMAL.
ANYA THINKS
I'M GOING WITH HER.
RIGHT...
AND YOUR PARENTS
ARE MAKING YOU GO WITH ME.
YEAH. THEY DON'T REALLY KNOW
ABOUT ANYA.
AH, THE SECRECY THING.
BEEN THERE, DONE THAT.
SO, YOU'RE NOT MAD?
THERE'S A GUY I LIKE
BACK HOME, TOO.
I GET IT.
SO...
HOW'RE WE GONNA
PULL THIS OFF?
(KNOCK AT THE DOOR)
UH...
I'LL TAKE THESE
TO THE KITCHEN.
WHY HAVEN'T YOU BEEN
ANSWERING YOUR PHONE?
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
DRESS SWATCH. I WANTED
TO SEE IF IT MATCHED YOUR TIE.
EVERYONE'S MATCHING
THIS YEAR.
NOW'S NOT A GOOD TIME.
HOW COME?
FARRAH:
SAV? YOUR DAD WANTS YOU TO...
OH.
UH... THIS IS FARRAH.
PETER'S DATE!
HIS FORMAL DATE.
FARRAH:
I SHOULD GET BACK
TO THOSE DISHES.
SO THAT WAS HER?
THE POSSIBLE-FUTRE
MRS. BANDHARI.
AND YOUR PARENTS?
YOU NEVER TOLD THEM WE GOT
BACK TOGETHER, DID YOU?
THAT'S GREAT.
I HOPE YOU AND FARRAH
HAVE A NICE LIFE.
(BIKE BELL DINGS,
HUM OF STUDENTS CHATTER)
WHAT'S THAT?
FORMAL TICKET.
IT'S FOR ME?
BETTER THAN GOING ALONE.
THANKS.
SO...
SHOULD WE HOLD HANDS?
SHUT UP.
GHS)
YOU KNOW, UH, JONATHAN,
I'M NOT GONNA LET YOU TAKE
ADVANTAGE OF ME
ON THE FIRST DATE.
MAN, YOU'RE A MORON.
YEAH, YOU'RE FRIENDS
WITH A MORON!
A ONE-OF-A-KIND MORON.
BRUCE:
GOOD LUCK REPLACING ME
WHEN YOU GO AWAY.
DON'T WORRY, BRUCIE.
I WON'T EVEN TRY.
(JOHNNY SQUEALS IN PROTEST,
BRUCE LAUGHS)
SAV:
ANYA! WAIT!
GIMME A SECOND.
DON'T TALK TO ME.
I AM SO SORRY
ABOUT LAST NIGHT.
BUT EVERYTHING I'M DOING -
IT'S FOR US.
LYING?
KEEPING ME A SECRET?
EXACTLY.
KEEPING YOU A SECRET MEANS
THAT EVERY TIME
I LEAVE THE HOUSE
MY PARENTS
DON'T QUESTION ME.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY
THAT WE CAN BE TOGETHER!
THEY REALLY HATE ME,
DON'T THEY?
NOBODY HATES YOU.
WELL, IT'S PRETTY OBVIOUS
WHO THEY LIKE.
LOOK, THE FACT THAT
FARRAH'S HERE
CHANGES NOTHING ABOUT US,
OR MY FEELINGS FOR YOU.
SO YOU STILL WANNA GO
TO FORMAL WITH ME?
OF COURSE I DO.
THE QUESTION IS,
DO YOU STILL WANNA GO
WITH ME?
(RELIEVED BREATH)
SO BADLY.
AS LONG AS WE'RE TOGETHER,
NOTHING ELSE MATTERS, RIGHT?
YOU KNOW IT.
AND PEOPLE ARE EVEN SAYING
THAT WE MIGHT BE THE FORMAL
KING AND QUEEN!
REALLY?
THAT WOULD BE INCREDIBLE!
SAV:
I KNOW. I KNOW.
SO, UH, PETER, FARRAH
AND I WILL PICK YOU UP
IN THE LIMO!
PA ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION, DEGRASSI STUDENTS:
TICKETS ARE ON SALE NOW
FOR THE DEGRASSI SPRING FORMAL.
GREAT.
(SIGHS)
(STAPLER CLICKS)
VOILA!
OH YEAH.
GREAT JOB, ANYA.
THAT'LL KEEP THOSE PESKY
FORMAL GUESTS OUT.
ARE YOU FEELING ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, I'M OKAY.
HAVE YOU TWO
HEARD ABOUT THIS?
MY SOURCES TELL ME THAT
PETER'S TAKING
SOME "FARRAH" GIRL
AS HIS DATE FOR THE FORMAL.
"SOURCES?"
FINE. DANNY.
CHECK YOUR SOURCES,
IT'S NOT A REAL DATE.
ANYA WITH THE INSIDER INFO.
GO ON.
FARRAH'S THE GIRL SAV'S KINDA,
SORTA,
NOT REALLY ARRANGED
TO BE MARRIED TO.
HE CAN'T GO
UNLESS SHE COMES TOO.
SO HE PAWNED HER OFF
ON PETER.
THAT'S WHY
YOU'RE SO SPACED OUT.
NO, IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
SO, HIS PARENTS THINK
THAT SHE'S HIS DATE?
NO, BUT I'M HIS REAL DATE.
WILL HIS BOUTONNIERE MATCH
YOUR CORSAGE OR HERS?
UH... I DON'T KNOW.
CHANTAY:
SO YOU'RE LETTING HIM HAVE
HIS CAKE AND EAT IT TOO?
THERE'S NO CAKE.
OR THERE'S CAKE,
ALL RIGHT.
LOOK, SAV AND I
LOVE EACH OTHER
FARRAH BEING HERE
ISN'T GONNA CHANGE ANYTHING.