HOLLY J:
I CAN'T TAKE THIS!
DECLAN:
I WANT YOU TO HAVE IT.
(EXHALES HAPPILY)
I LOVE IT.
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE SURE ABOUT THIS?
WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER
AN AMAZING THREE MONTHS,
YOU'RE REALLY GREAT
ABOUT NOT PRESSURING...
AND THE PILL'S BEEN GREAT
FOR MY SKIN!
(HALF LAUGHS)
YOU ARE LOOKING
PARTICULARLY RADIANT.
OKAY, LAST TIME.
YOU'RE SURE?
YEAH!
WHY?
AREN'T YOU SURE?
I JUST DON'T WANT THINGS
TO GET WEIRD.
DECLAN,
YOU'RE THE RIGHT PERSON,
AND THIS IS THE RIGHT TIME.
AND...
I LOVE YOU.
THEN IT'S PERFECT.
(HUFFS)
WAIT, DECLAN.
DO YOU...
HOW DOES THIS THING WORK?
(CHUCKLES)
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it,
I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, Woo-ooh ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
JANE:
WELL DONE, FASHIONISTA!
I SAW YOUR TWEET ABOUT
THE SIZZLE TEEN INTERNSHIP?
OH RIGHT.
IT WENT THROUGH.
SO, DID YOU AND DECLAN
CELEBRATE LAST NIGHT
AS PLANNED?
(DEADPAN)
YEAH.
JANE:
BOO-YA!
WELCOME TO THE CLUB!
(LAUGHS)
I'M SORRY,
I'M KIDDING!
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
I TOLD HIM I LOVE HIM.
WOW, OKAY!
WHAT DID HE SAY?
HE DIDN'T SAY IT.
MAYBE HE JUST DIDN'T
GET THE CHANCE.
DECLAN:
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
BESIDES ANYA'S LACK
OF FASHION SENSE?
ANYA:
I JUST DON'T SEE WHY AN ALIEN
NEEDS A KEFFIYEH.
FI, ANYA'S YOUR BOSS.
WORK IT OUT.
MUSICAL STRIFE?
NOTHING ANOTHER NIGHT OF FUN
CAN'T SOLVE.
OH NO, IT GOT WEIRD.
DECLAN,
THE WAY WE FEEL
ABOUT EACH OTHER,
WE'RE ON THE SAME PAGE,
RIGHT?
OF COURSE!
WHERE ARE WE EATING LUNCH?
WAIT.
LAST NIGHT,
WHEN I TOLD YOU I LOVE YOU-
CAN WE NOT TALK ABOUT THIS?
DECLAN, DO YOU LOVE ME?
IT'S NOT THAT SIMPLE.
OH MY GOD.
PETER:
WE SHOULDN'T DO THIS.
I WON'T TELL,
I PROMISE.
THIS HAS TO BE
OUR LAST KISS.
I KNOW.
YOUR HEART BELONGS TO DIDI.
BUT JUST FOR THIS MOMENT...
MAKE ME FORGET.
DANNY:
WHOA! HEY!
UH, INTENSE SCENE.
LOOKS GREAT!
OKAY, EVERYONE,
TAKE FIVE.
I GOT YOUR TICKETS.
ALL 14 OF THEM.
AW, DANNY!
(TITTERS)
MOM GOT A LITTLE
CARRIED AWAY
WHEN SHE HEARD
I GOT THE LEAD.
SO YOUR WHOLE FAMILY'LL
BE THERE...
TO WATCH YOU KISS
ANOTHER GUY!
(SCOFFS)
DON'T BE JEALOUS.
AH... I'M NOT.
(COUGHING)
HOLLY J:
THERE YOU ARE.
FIONA.
FIONA!
HELLO?
PERSONAL SPACE?!
I'LL LEAVE YOU
TO YOUR PRECIOUS SOLITUDE.
I JUST NEED YOU TO GIVE THIS
BACK TO YOUR BROTHER.
WHY DO YOU HAVE
MY GRANDMOTHER'S BRACELET?
DECLAN GAVE IT TO ME.
HE DID?
(SIGHS) WOW.
I THOUGHT HE WAS SAVING IT
FOR SOMEONE SPECIAL.
GUESS HE LOVES YOU.
THEN WHY CAN'T HE SAY IT?
LOOK, MY BROTHER'S
ONLY DROPPED THE L-BOMB
ON ONE PERSON.
AND THEN OF COURSE,
LIKE, TWO SECONDS LATER,
SHE CHEATED ON HIM.
SMASHED HIS HEART
INTO A MILLION PIECES.
SO YOU THINK HE'S JUST SCARED
TO SAY IT?
THEN I GUESS
I'LL KEEP THIS.
THANKS, FIONA!
WHATEVER.
PETER:
♪ ALL OUR GOOD TIMES
WENT TO WASTE ♪
♪ BUT FROM THE SKY ABOVE ♪
♪ MY LIFE'S BEEN ERASED ♪
♪ A GIRL FROM OUTERSPACE ♪
(COUGHING)
♪ IN SPACE... ♪
DANNY.
MAN, CAN I HELP YOU?
UH... YOU AND CHANTAY
HAVING FUN?
OH, THE MUSICAL?
YEAH, IT'S GOOD TIMES.
YOU KNOW SHE HAS
A THREE OCTAVE RANGE?
IT SOUNDS LIKE YOU'RE
GETTING TO KNOW HER.
YEAH, WITH ALL THE INTENSE
REHEARSAL TIMES...
YOU KNOW, MOST GIRLS
WOULD DRIVE YOU CRAZY,
BUT NOT CHANTAY, MAN.
SHE'S COOL.
ONE TIME WE WERE REHEARSING
THE KISSING SCENE,
I HAD SALAD IN MY TEETH-
I DON'T WANT YOU
TO KISS HER.
OH. LIKE, IN THE SHOW?
IT BLOWS WATCHING YOUR GIRL
KISS SOMEONE ELSE.
FAKE- (COUGHS)
FAKE OR NOT.
(COUGHS)
I GET IT, MAN.
WHEN I WAS WITH MIA,
EVERY TIME SHE'D RUB UP
AGAINST SOME MALE MODEL
AT A PHOTO SHOOT,
I'D WANT TO CLOCK HIM.
I'M NOT GONNA CLOCK YOU,
DUDE.
THANKS.
I'LL SEE WHAT I CAN DO,
OKAY?
ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION, DEGRASSI!
BRING YOUR INSTRUMENT
OR JUST YOUR VOICE!
OPEN JAM SESSION IN THE ATRIUM,
EVERY WEDNESDAY AT LUNCH.
THERE'S SOMETHING I-
AY-
ME FIRST?
LOOK,
AS LONG AS YOU SHOW IT?
I DON'T REALLY CARE
WHAT YOU CAN
OR... CAN'T SAY.
FIONA TOLD ME.
JUST KNOW THAT
I'LL NEVER BREAK YOUR HEART.
(EXHALES, RELIEVED)
HOW'D I GET SO LUCKY?
MAYBE YOU WILL AGAIN
TONIGHT?
(LAUGHS)
I'D LOVE TO,
BUT MOM'S BACK EARLY.
SHE'S PICKING ME UP
AFTER REHEARSAL.
RAINCHECK?
CAN WE AT LEAST GO
ON A LUNCH DATE TOMORROW?
I'M THERE.
PETER:
WE SHOULDN'T DO THIS.
I WON'T TELL,
I PROMISE.
NO. WE REALLY SHOULDN'T
DO THIS.
JANE:
PETER! MOVE CLOSER!
PETER:
UH, I FORGOT TO DEODORIZE.
HOW EMBARASSING.
CHANTAY:
YOU SMELL FINE.
I THINK THE SCENE WOULD BE
STRONGER WITHOUT THE KISS.
WHAT?
PETER:
I VOTE FOR A REWRITE.
WE HAVE BEEN REHEARSING IT
FOR WEEKS!
WHY IS IT A PROBLEM NOW?
IT'S NOT.
FROM THE KISS.
UH, AFTER I HIT THE CAN.
JANE:
OH MY GOD.
THEN HIT THE "CAN," SIR.
TAKE FIVE.
(ANNOYED)
(DANNY COUGHING)
(COUGHING)
THEY'RE NOT GONNA
CHANGE IT.
DANNY:
OKAY, SO WHAT'RE WE GONNA DO?
OH! I GOT IT!
IF I GET SICK,
JANE CAN'T MAKE ME KISS
CHANTAY.
YOU'D DO THAT?
YEAH, MAN.
IT'S THE BRO-CODE!
CHANTAY:
HEY, GUYS!
REHEARSAL'S TAKING FOREVER.
I'M SO THIRSTY.
DANNY:
NO! DON'T-
I'M NOT GONNA DRINK YOURS,
SICKY.
SEE YA.
(DANNY COUGHS)
OH! MUAH.
HI, SWEETIE!
YOU ALL SET?
I'LL BE STAYING LATE.
REHEARSAL'S A NIGHTMARE.
AW.
I MISSED YOU!
HOW WAS THE TRIP?
WHERE WAS IT, GENEVA?
NEW YORK.
YOU WERE THERE
AND YOU DIDN'T BRING ME
MY SUMMER CLOTHES?
I'M GOING TO DO YOU
ONE BETTER -
I'M BRINGING YOU TO THEM.
WE'RE MOVING AGAIN.
TO MANHATTAN?
MM-HM.
REALLY?
I'VE GOT YOU BOTH BACK
INTO VANDERBILT PREP
FOR SENIOR YEAR.
FIONA:
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
THIS IS BETTER THAN CHRISTMAS
IN SAINT TROPEZ!
YOU'RE JOKING, RIGHT?
NO. IT'S ALL BEEN ARRANGED.
WE LEAVE NEXT WEEK!
FIONA:
LATER, DEGRASSI.
PUBLIC SCHOOL
WAS A FUN EXPERIMENT.
SORT OF.
JENNA:
GREG! HURRY!
PETER:
DIDI! WAIT!
CHANTAY:
SHE'S NOT ONE OF US, GREG!
PETER:
NO, I NEED HER IN MY LIFE!
JENNA:
NO!
UH-OH! HELP! OH.
UH OH... HELP?
PETER:
NO!
JENNA:
UM...
(GROANS)
TAKE FIVE
ON DRESS REHEARSAL.
ANYBODY GOT AN ADVIL?
YOU'VE GOT A SQUEALING ALIEN
ON A LIFT.
STRESSED?
CHUCKLE)
THIS MUSICAL'S A DISASTER.
FIONA:
WELL, SOON OUR OWN MOTHERSHIP
WILL WHISK US BACK
TO PLANET PARK AVE.
HAVE YOU TOLD HOLLY J?
MM-MM.
(INHALES) IF I TELL HER,
IT BECOMES REAL, YOU KNOW?
DON'T BE SAD.
AT LEAST WE HAVE EACH OTHER.
HOLLY J:
HEY.
SORRY TO INTERRUPT
YOUR VIRTUAL LUNCH DATE.
OH, ARE YOU COMING
TO SAY GOODBYE?
WHAT? NO.
WHAT'RE YOU...?
HE SAID HE'D MEET ME,
BUT NOW...
RADIO SILENCE.
HE'S STILL IN REHEARSAL.
SO, DID YOU GUYS TALK?
YEAH. DRAMA AVERTED.
YOU SHOULD'VE SEEN HIM
LAST NIGHT.
SO UPSET.
WHAT? WHY? HE'S GOT NOTHING
TO BE UPSET ABOUT!
COLD-HEARTED MUCH?
THINK YOU'D CARE
THAT THE GUY YOU LOVE
IS MOVING BACK TO NEW YORK.
HOLLY J:
OH, HOLD ON.
WHEN DID THIS HAPPEN?
YESTERDAY.
DIDN'T HE TELL YOU?
I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM TODAY.
OH! YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT
THE WHOLE "I LOVE YOU" ISSUE.
GUESS YOU HAVE
BIGGER PROBLEMS NOW.
DECLAN:
AND THIS?
THE MUSIC, SET DESIGN,
COSTUMES -
IT'S ALL ME.
LARA COYNE:
IT'S VERY IMPRESSIVE.
I NEVER KNEW YOU HAD
SUCH AN ARTISTIC SIDE.
MOM...
THIS IS THE FIRST SCHOOL
I'VE COME TO AND JUMPED IN.
YOU KNOW,
I LIKE IT HERE.
PEOPLE LOOK UP TO ME.
AND YOU CAN TAKE
THAT LEADERSHIP
RIGHT TO VANDERBILT PREP.
I'M NOT GOING.
YOU CAN'T DO THIS TO US AGAIN.
LARA COYNE:
YOUR SISTER CAN'T WAIT
TO GET BACK TO NEW YORK.
DECLAN:
FINE. SHE CAN GO.
I'LL GET AN APARTMENT HERE.
I'LL FLY TO NEW YORK
ON THE WEEKENDS - WHATEVER!
LARA COYNE:
YOUR FATHER HAS BEEN TRYING
TO GET POSTED
BACK TO NEW YORK FOR YEARS.
HE WON'T BE TRAVELLING.
WE CAN BE AT HOME -
ALL OF US.
IT'S NOT FAIR.
I DON'T WANNA LEAVE HOLLY J.
LARA COYNE:
YOU HAVE ONE MORE YEAR
OF SCHOOL
AND YOU CAN GO ANYWHERE
YOU WANT.
I NEED US TO BE TOGETHER.
I'M SORRY, SWEETIE.
CAN I COME VISIT,
MRS. COYNE?
LARA COYNE:
UH, HEH...
HOLLY J, UM...
OF COURSE.
ANY TIME.
YOU HEARD?
KNOCK 'EM DEAD TONIGHT.
SO WHAT'S THE PLAN?
JUST DO THE STUPID KISS.
I'LL COVER MY EYES
OR SOMETHING.
CHANTAY'S JUST DOING HER JOB.
IS SHE BACKSTAGE?
YEAH, PROBABLY LOOSENING UP
HER VOCAL CHORDS.
(CHANTAY COUGHS)
DOES THAT INVOLVE CRYING?
(CHANTAY COUGHS AND SNIFFLES)
I WORKED SO HARD...
BABY, WHAT'S WRONG?
CHANTAY:
I'M A MESS.
I CAN'T HIT ANY OF MY NOTES.
MY ENTIRE FAMILY'S HERE.
(COUGHING)
(COUGHS AND WHIMPERS)
CHANTAY, IT'S MY FAULT.
NO, I SWITCHED MY WATER BOTTLE
WITH DANNY'S
SO I WOULD CATCH HIS COLD
AND I WOULDN'T BREAK
THE BRO-CODE.
AND I DRANK DANNY'S WATER?
YOU'RE JOKING.
DANNY?
I DIDN'T WANT YOU
TO KISS HIM.
SO YOU TWO WERE WILLING
TO RUIN EVERYTHING
WE ALL WORKED SO HARD FOR
BECAUSE OF YOUR STUPID
INSECURITY?!
I GOT YOU FLOWERS.
SAVE THEM FOR JANE.
SHE'S TAKING MY PLACE.
(CHANTAY COUGHS)
(KEYS CLACK,
COMPUTER BEEPS)
HOLLY J: (RECORDING)
HELLO PROSPECTIVE INTERNSHIP
PROVIDERS.
MY NAME IS HOLLY J SINCLAIR,
STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT,
VIDEO ANNOUNCEMENTS DIVA,
AND MISTRESS
OF THE EXTRACURRICULAR.
I'D LIKE TO TAKE YOU
ON A QUICK TOUR OF MY GOALS,
SKILLS, AND ACHIEVEMENTS...
(MOUSE CLICKS)
(COMPUTER KEYS CLACK)
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
CROWD'S GETTING ANTSY.
WAIT,
YOU'RE A CHEERLEADER?
YES,
AND OUR DIRECTOR'S GONE AWOL.
WHAT'RE WE GONNA DO?
OH MY GOD.
IT'S NOT LIKE HIM TO BE LATE.
OKAY, WELL,
I KNOW ALL THE CUES.
JUST GO!
THANK YOU.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, CUE ATMOSPHERE!
CUE MUSIC!
(MUSIC BEGINS)
CUE...
WHERE WERE YOU!?
SORRY!
HOLLY J:
UH, JENNA, GO!
CUE RAMP!
OVER TO YOU.
YOU WERE DOING SO WELL.
CUE LIGHTS!
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDS,
MUSIC PLAYS)
WAIT! DON'T LEAVE ME!
I DON'T BELONG IN THIS WORLD!
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS)
(MUSIC PLAYS)
PETER:
♪ ALL OUR GOOD TIMES
WENT TO WASTE ♪
♪ BUT FROM THE SKY ABOVE ♪
♪ MY LIFE'S BEEN GRACED ♪
♪ A GIRL FROM OUTERSPACE ♪
♪ MISPLACED ♪
♪ SHE'S A GIRL FROM OUTER... ♪
PETER:
HEY. YOU NEW HERE?
YEAH. I'M DIDI.
GREG.
WHERE YOU FROM?
JANE:
UM, THE TEAM'S WAITING!
WHO'S THIS FREAK?
NOBODY.
COMING, TESS!
(AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
♪ SHE'S A GIRL
FROM OUTERSPACE ♪
DECLAN:
IT'S TIME TO COME HOME,
MY CHILD.
JENNA:
BUT I'VE SEARCHED THE GALAXIES
FOR LOVE.
I FINALLY FOUND IT!
DECLAN:
IF YOU STAY, YOU WILL DIE.
PETER:
THEN I'M COMING WITH YOU!
AUDIENCE:
AWW...
♪ IT'S HARD TO IMAGINE
THAT OUR LOVE STORY ♪
♪ IS ONE THAT WILL COME
TO AN END ♪
♪ I FELL SO HARD FOR YOU ♪
♪ YOU PULLED ME RIGHT IN ♪
♪ BUT I'M NOT GONNA SIT
AND PRETEND ♪
♪ I KNOW I'M SO OVER IT ♪
♪ AND I DON'T WANNA SEE YOU ♪
♪ AND DEEP DOWN INSIDE
THAT'S A LIE ♪
♪ I LOOK AT THE PICTURES
OF YOU AND ME ♪
♪ AND IT HURTS
THAT I HAVE TO SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ AND I BELIEVE
IN WISHING ON STARS ♪
♪ DREAMING OUT SO FAR ♪
♪ AND I BELIEVE THAT
THINGS WOULD CHANGE ♪
♪ YOU'D STOP PLAYING GAMES ♪
♪ TO LIVE LIKE YOU'VE NEVER
BEEN HURT BEFORE ♪
♪ TO LIVE LIKE THIS HEAVEN'S
ON EARTH ♪
♪ I BELIEVE ♪
(APPLAUDING AND CHEERING)
(INSTRUMENTAL PLAYS,
AUDIENCE CHEERS AND APPLAUDS)
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU DID IT.
I LOVE YOU, HOLLY J.
(STUNNED BREATHS)
DANNY:
THINK SHE'LL GO FOR IT?
PETER:
I THINK SO.
HEY. HEY, UH...
FEELING ANY BETTER?
(COUGHS)
STILL NOT TALKING
TO ME?
OKAY, WELL, UM...
ABOVE THE DOT PRESENTS
AN ENCORE PERFORMANCE OF...
SPACE AWAKENING,
STARRING CHANTAY BLACK.
PETER:
WE PULLED IN EVERY FAVOUR
WITH THE CAST AND CREW
WE EVER HAD.
SO YOU'RE OKAY
WITH THE KISS?
WELL, IT'S STILL WEIRD,
BUT IT'S JUST ACTING,
RIGHT?
I'M SORRY YOU GOT SICK.
I PROBABLY ALREADY
HAD THE GERMS.
THAT'S WHAT I WAS THINKING.
CHANTAY:
THANKS, GUYS.
I'M GONNA GO MAKE
SOME PHONE CALLS!
(GIGGLES EXCITEDLY)
SO NOW I HAVE TO KISS HER?
SHE'S SICK, DUDE!
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
TRY NOT TO SLIP
ANY TONGUE, DUDE.
♪ My heart beats fast
when I think of your name ♪
♪ And I know after you
I won't be the same ♪
♪ But we should talk... ♪
(HEAVY SIGH)
SPINNER:
YOU GONNA SIT THERE
ALL DAY?
JUST GONNA SPEND
EVERY WAKING MOMENT WITH MY GIRL
UNTIL I LEAVE.
HOLLY J:
WELL, I BET SIZZLE TEEN
FROWNS ON MAGAZINE INTERNS
WITH AN ENTOURAGE.
HAVE YOU HIRED
MY REPLACEMENT YET?
I'M WORKING ON IT!
(HOLLY J'S PHONE BEEPS)
HOLLY J:
AN EMAIL... FROM TVM?
SPINNER:
WHAT, THE MUSIC CHANNEL?
HOLLY J:
YEAH, IN NEW YORK.
IT'S PROBABLY JUST SPAM.
AH, CHECK IT.
JUST IN CASE.
(PHONE BEEPS AND CHIMES)
WHAT?!
IT SAYS THEY'RE OFFERING ME
A SUMMER INTERNSHIP.
YES!
THANK YOU.
DO YOU KNOW ABOUT THIS?
UH... I KINDA HACKED YOUR EMAIL
AND SENT YOUR DEMO.
THE REST IS ALL YOU.
YOU SAID YOU WANTED
MORE TIME.
NOW WE HAVE
THE WHOLE SUMMER.
SUMMER OF LOVE,
HERE WE COME!
HOLLY J AND DECLAN:
(ELATED CHUCKLING)
Jenna:
♪ ...wishing on stars ♪
♪ Dreaming out so far ♪
♪ And I believe
that things would change... ♪