(DOOR OPENS)
MORNING.
HEY, COACH.
I'M GONNA BE LATE
FOR HOMEROOM.
CHILL OUT.
I'LL DRIVE YOU.
MAKE SURE YOU CHECK IN
WITH THE GROUP HOME.
NO PROBLEM.
(HALF LAUGHS)
$14.99 FOR
"BETTY DOES BARCELONA?"
WASN'T THAT GOOD.
HUH. YEAH.
I'LL MEET YOU DOWNSTAIRS.
ARE YOU OKAY?
I FEEL KINDA GROSS.
IT'S CALLED A HANGOVER.
YOU'RE GONNA WANNA DRINK
SOME WATER.
(INHALES AND EXHALES DEEPLY)
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out,
I know I can make it through ♪
♪ Oooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
HEY!
IT'S OUR V.I.P.:
VERY IMPORTANT PLAYER.
CONNOR:
JENNA SAYS YOU HUNG OUT
WITH COACH IN HIS HOTEL ROOM.
THAT'S SO COOL,
MAN.
YEAH,
WE TALKED BASKETBALL.
DAVE:
BRO, I'D KILL
FOR A ONE-ON-ONE.
ALLI:
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT ALBERTA.
BUT HERE, WE DON'T STEAL
PEOPLE'S BOYFRIENDS.
I DIDN'T STEAL ANYTHING,
ALLI!
GO TIP A COW
OR SOMETHING.
(EXHALES)
DON'T LET THEM
GET TO YOU.
KINDA HARD.
GOT YOUR TEXT
LAST NIGHT.
SORRY I DIDN'T GET
TO SAY BYE.
NO WORRIES.
DID YOU GET HOME OKAY?
YEAH.
COACH DROVE ME.
DID HE SAY ANYTHING?
ABOUT WHAT?
WELL, HE WALKED IN
ON US KISSING.
IT WAS CREEPY.
(LAUGHS) YOU'RE JUST MAD
HE INTERRUPTED.
(SCOFFS)
I'M SERIOUS, KC.
I GOT THIS VIBE.
KC:
JENNA, COACH IS COOL.
HEY.
IT'S ALL GOOD.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
TOP O' THE MORNING
TO YA!
EASY.
THAT'S A LOT OF IRISH
FOR 8 A.M.
(TITTERS AFFECTIONATELY)
THIS ISN'T AN ALMOND MILK
LATTE.
THAT'S BECAUSE
IT'S MY SKIM MACCHIATO.
OKAY IF MY SISTER
HAS IT?
SURE. WHY NOT?
I'VE GOT TO GET
TO A PEP RALLY...
UN-CAFFEINATED.
FIONA:
PEP RALLY?
THINK THAT'S HOW OPRAH
GOT HER START?
IF YOU HAVE NOTHING NICE
N'T.
HOLLY J WORKS HARD TO KEEP
THE STUDENT BODY CONNECTED.
PARENTALS FLY OUT
THIS AFT.
I WAS THINKING...
SASHIMI FEST TONIGHT?
YOUR TURN TO ORDER,
DECLAN-SAN.
I HAVE A LATE
MUSICAL MEETING,
WE'RE ORDERING IN PIZZA.
PEASANT FOOD AGAIN?
(EXASPERATED SIGH)
SO I'M EATING ALONE.
FIONA, I'D CANCEL,
BUT...
NO WORRIES.
MORE YELLOWTAIL FOR ME,
RIGHT?
SEE YOU AT LUNCH.
(HUM OF CHATTER,
MARCHING BAND DRUMS BEAT)
OKAY, PUT DOWN
YOUR JAMAICAN PATTIES, PEOPLE.
IT'S PEP RALLY TIME.
CHEERLEADERS:
(EXCITED CHEERS)
NOW, LET'S GIVE IT UP
FOR COACH CARSON!
STUDENTS:
(APPLAUDING AND CHEERING)
CARSON:
LET'S HEAR YOUR BEST
PANTHER ROAR!
STUDENTS:
GRRRR!
NOW, LET ME INTRODUCE YOU
TO OUR FIRST EVER
DEGRASSI PANTHER MIDGET
PROVINCIAL FINALISTS!
DAVE TURNER.
KC GUTHRIE.
(STUDENTS CHEER)
CONNOR DELAURIER.
ETHAN MCBRIDE.
JEWAN SANDERS.
DAVID DEVANTES.
ELLIOT COHEN.
GUY:
WHOA, DUDE!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH KC?
(SPITS AND VOMITS)
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH.
JUST PREGAME NERVES.
THAT'S NOT LIKE YOU.
I ALSO HAD SOME BEERS WITH COACH
LAST NIGHT.
SO, HE DROVE YOU HOME DRUNK?
NO.
I STAYED OVER AT THE HOTEL.
SO YOU LIED?
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
JENNA:
IF THERE'S ONE THING
I'VE LEARNED,
IT'S TO TRUST MY INSTINCTS.
SOMETHING'S OFF WITH HIM.
HE'S THE ONE WHO HELPED ME
BREAK UP WITH CLARE.
YOU SHOULD BE THANKING HIM.
(STUDENTS APPLAUD)
MUSICAL CASTING HAS BEGUN.
THINK YOU'VE GOT WHAT IT TAKES
TO JOIN THE CHORUS?
SIGN UP NOW!
HEY, SPREAD THE WORD.
STARTED WITHOUT YOU.
HAD SOME JOINER STUFF TO DO.
PRODUCING A MUSICAL,
DATING THE STUDENT COUNCIL
PRESIDENT.
SINCE WHEN DID YOU BECOME
MR. HIGH SCHOOL?
I CAN'T HELP IT.
I LIKE PEOPLE.
ALL THESE LONELY LUNCHES
IN THE ZEN GARDEN...
YOUR LIFE'S STARTING TO LOOK
LIKE A SOFIA COPPOLA MOVIE.
(SIGHS) WHAT DO YOU SUGGEST
I DO ABOUT IT?
SOMETHING THAT INVOLVES
MORE HUMAN CONTACT.
UGH...
IT'LL BE GOOD FOR YOU.
TRUST.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
CARSON:
GOOD PRACTICE TODAY, GUYS.
ETHAN, DAVE...
RIGHT IN THE ZONE.
GUTHRIE,
COME AND SEE ME.
WHERE WAS YOUR HEAD TODAY?
THIS IS CRUNCH TIME.
I CAN'T HAVE YOU MESSING UP
WHEN IT MATTERS MOST.
DON'T WORRY,
I'LL BE FINE.
ARE YOU SURE?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
READY FOR THIS?
I AM READY!
YOU BETTER BE.
OTHERWISE,
YOU'RE JUST WASTING MY TIME.
COACH...
WHAT'RE YOU DOING LATER?
ANY BEERS LEFT?
NOT BEFORE A CHAMPIONSHIP,
BUD.
BUT WE CAN WORK ON
GETTING YOU FOCUSED.
I'LL PICK YOU UP.
SOUNDS GOOD.
CHANTAY:
(SINGING)
♪ GLORY, HALLELUJAH ♪
THANKS, CHANTAY.
NEXT.
THINK WE FOUND OUR GIRL.
WHAT?
I'M HERE TO AUDITION.
FOR REAL?
OKAY, WHEN YOU'RE READY.
(CALMING BREATH)
9SINGING OFF-KEY)
♪ BEAUTIFUL DREAMER ♪
♪ WAKE UNTO ME ♪
♪ STARLIGHTS AND DEWDROPS
ARE WAITING FOR THEE ♪
♪ SOUNDS OF THE RUDE WORLD
HEARD IN THE DAY ♪
♪ LULL'D BY THE MOONLIGHT
HAVE ALL PASSED AWAY ♪
THANKS, FIONA.
WE'LL LET YOU KNOW.
MAN, NO OFFENSE,
BUT YOUR SISTER'S
VOCALLY CHALLENGED.
YEAH.
SHE'S NO LEA MICHELE,
BUT SHE'S THE BEST
WE'VE SEEN TODAY.
UM, HELLO? CHANTAY?
UNTIL JANE'S BACK,
I HAVE FINAL SAY.
NEXT!
WHY'D JANE'S GREAT AUNT ERICA
HAVE TO DIE THIS WEEK?
(CAR ENGINE REVS)
(TURNS IGNITION OFF)
CARSON:
(EXHALES)
THIS TIME TOMORROW,
WE'RE GONNA BE CHAMPS.
YOU PSYCHED?
IT'S JUST... FINALS.
I MEAN, WHAT IF WE LOSE?
CAN'T THINK THAT WAY,
SON.
HEY, I GET SCARED TOO
SOMETIMES.
I'M NOT SCARED.
HEY, IT'S NORMAL.
YOU JUST HAVE TO LEARN
HOW TO CONQUER IT.
GLOCK SEVENTEEN.
POW!
WHEN YOU OWN THE FEAR, KC,
NOTHING CAN HURT YOU.
YOU GOOD?
YEAH.
CARSON:
GOOD.
NOW WE GOT A GAME PLAN
TO DRILL INTO
THAT OVERSTUFFED HEAD
OF YOURS.
YOU READY?
LET'S DO IT.
(DOOR CLOSES,
KC EXHALES CALMLY)
CARSON:
RIGHT, SEE THAT AGGRESSIVE
DEFENSE?
HANDS UP.
LOOK HOW HE USES HIS SHOULDER.
CAN'T BE SCARED OF FOULS,
RIGHT?
THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE GONNA
NEED TO CHANNEL TOMORROW,
IF WE'RE GONNA WIN.
LIKE LESS THINKING,
MORE INSTINCT.
SKY'S THE LIMIT.
COLLEGE, SCHOLARSHIPS,
NBA...
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
YOU HAVE TO KNOW.
YOU HAVE TO WANT IT.
YOU WANT IT?
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
I'VE NEVER...
FORGET IT.
WHAT?
IT'S LIKE... YOU GET ME.
I'VE NEVER HAD THAT BEFORE.
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
I NEVER THOUGHT
I'D MAKE IT IN!
HAVEN'T SEEN YOU
THIS EXCITED
SINCE YOUR FIRST
FASHION WEEK.
I NEVER CONSIDERED MYSELF
THE MUSICAL TYPE.
BUT, HERE I AM!
ALREADY NERVOUS.
YOU'LL BE GREAT.
SO, NOBODY THINKS
I'M A TOTAL NOOB?
NO WAY.
HOPE YOU'RE PREPARED
TO GIVE UP YOUR SATURDAY.
YOU HAVE A VOICE LESSON
WITH MR. LAVIGNE.
YOU THINK I NEED HELP?
NO!
NO, IT'S STANDARD.
EVERYONE HAS TO DO IT.
(KNOCK AT THE DOOR)
WANNA GET THAT?
HI.
HEY.
CARSON:
YOU REMEMBER STACIE?
YOU BROUGHT HER
TO THE DEGRASSI CAR WASH.
STACIE:
FIRST TIME I'D BEEN
TO A HIGH SCHOOL PARKING LOT
IN YEARS!
SO... WHO WANTS A DRINK?
OOH! I DO.
WE TALKED ABOUT
GETTING YOU FOCUSED, KC.
YEAH.
I SHOULD GET GOING.
REST UP.
NO, NO. STAY.
HAVE A SEAT.
RELAX.
(POP MUSIC PLAYS,
BEER BOTTLES CLANK)
CARSON: CHEERS!
STACI: CHEERS!
(BOTTLES CLANK)
YOU, MY FRIEND,
HAVE BEEN HARBOURING
SO MUCH FRUSTRATION...
GIRL TROUBLES.
STRESS.
I CAN'T HAVE YOU TAKING
THAT ON THE COURT.
YOU NEED TO GET THAT
OUT OF YOUR SYSTEM.
SHE'S A PRO.
SHE'LL SHOW YOU HOW IT'S DONE.
HOW WHAT'S DONE?
COME ON,
YOU'RE NOT THAT DUMB.
IT'S GOOD THING I PAID
FOR A FULL NIGHT.
STACI:
(LAUGHS)
SHE'S A PROSTITUTE?
IT'S OKAY.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA
GET IN TROUBLE.
LESS THINKING,
MORE INSTINCT.
NO.
PLEASE, DON'T.
ARE YOU SURE HE'S 18?
IT'S STAGE FRIGHT.
HE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
MM-HM.
LOOK, BUDDY.
IF YOU'RE NERVOUS,
WE'LL GIVE YOU SOME POINTERS.
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
(STRESSED SHAKY BREATHS)
(HUM OF CHATTER)
FIONA: (OFF-KEY)
♪ SOUNDS OF THE RUDE WORLD
HEARD IN THE DAY ♪
♪ LULL'D BY THE MOONLIGHT
HAVE ALL PASSED AWAY ♪
(UNDER HIS BREATH)
OH GOD.
THANKS, FI.
DON'T FORGET ABOUT YOUR
COSTUME-FITTING WITH ANYA.
AS IF.
♪♪♪♪♪
GRR, PANTHERS, GRR!
CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU DRAGGED ME HERE.
ALLI:
IT'S THE CHAMPIONSHIP FINALS,
CLARE.
WHAT ELSE ARE WE GONNA DO?
I'M GONNA GO GET A DRINK.
♪ So crank it up ♪
♪ Crank it up ♪
♪ Man, I've got a feeling ♪
♪ That you're not
a brilliant one ♪
♪ 'Cause we came here
to raise a glass ♪
(STUDENTS CHEER WILDLY,
WHISTLE)
(WILD CHEERING)
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Crank it up ♪
WHERE'S KC?
NO IDEA.
(STUDENTS CHEER)
YOU KNOW, DROP THE WAIST
A FEW INCHES
AND YOU'LL GET A SUPER
DYNAMIC SILHOUETTE.
GOOD CALL.
MY EXPERIENCE IS LIMITED
TO MEDIEVAL-WEAR, SO.
(GIGGLES, PLEASED)
CAN I HAVE A WORD
WITH MY SISTER?
SURE.
DEX, EVERYTHING OKAY?
YOU CAN'T BE
IN THE MUSICAL.
WHY?
YOU'RE NOT A STRONG ENOUGH
SINGER.
I'M SORRY.
I REALLY WANTED US
TO DO THIS TOGETHER.
BUT EVERYONE THINKS I SUCK.
WHY WOULD YOU DO THIS
TO ME?
I WANTED YOU TO HAVE FUN
AT DEGRASSI, TOO.
YOU MEAN LET ME MAKE
A FOOL OF MYSELF.
SUPER FUN!
(DISTANT CHEERING)
SHOULDN'T YOU BE IN THERE
BEING EVERYBODY'S HERO?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
I'M SORRY, CLARE.
FOR EVERYTHING.
KC!
GET DRESSED!
WE GOT A CHAMPIONSHIP
TO WIN.
I'M NOT PLAYING, COACH.
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I'M OWNING THE FEAR.
I TRUSTED YOU.
LOOKED UP TO YOU.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE SCUM.
AND EVERYBODY'S GONNA FIND OUT.
WHAT'RE YOU GONNA
TELL THEM?
THAT WE WATCHED A MOVIE?
THAT YOU'RE A PERVERT!
A LOSER.
NOTHING HAPPENED.
I NEVER TOUCHED YOU!
(STUDENTS CHEER,
SNEAKERS SQUEAK ON FLOOR)
HEY! HEY,
SHOULDN'T YOU BE OUT THERE?
FORGET IT.
NEVER MIND.
HATZILAKOS:
WAIT.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
IT'S ABOUT COACH CARSON.
WHAT ABOUT HIM?
HE KEEPS THIS IN HIS CAR.
HATZILAKOS:
KC...
ARCHIE, GET THE POLICE.
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE
I NEED TO KNOW?
♪ I need to be alone ♪
♪ And I don't need
to be with someone ♪
♪ I don't need
to join this war ♪
♪ And everywhere
you look out ♪
♪ Like two birds
that lose home ♪
♪ They're blocking
all the street cars ♪
♪ They're holding up
our phones ♪
♪ And if it leaves
a bad taste ♪
♪ You need to wash it down ♪
♪ And if you built
a model home ♪
♪ Just burn it to the ground ♪
♪ I refuse to show
my good side ♪
♪ In no place to call my own ♪
♪ It's no home
No-no, no-no ♪
♪ No home ♪
♪ No home... ♪
(no-no, no-no)
DECLAN:
CHANTAY HAS KINDLY AGREED
TO TAKE THE CHORUS PART...
WHICH WAS HERS
TO BEGIN WITH.
SO,
WHERE'S MY DRESSING ROOM?
KIDDING!
I'M NOT A DIVA...
YET.
FIONA:
SO, I MAY NOT BE A SINGER,
BUT I CAN SEW A MEAN HEMLINE.
APPARENTLY I'M INDISPENSABLE.
TOTAL LIFE-SAVER.
'KAY, LADIES, LET'S GO.
SO YOU'RE THE WARDROBE
ASSISTANT?
EXCUSE ME?
WARDROBE MISTRESS.
HAS A NICE RING TO IT.
THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
WHAT I DID WAS STUPID.
IT'S JUST...
WHEN YOU'RE NOT HAPPY,
I'M NOT HAPPY.
SHOO!
I HAVE TO GET TO WORK.
WHERE WERE YOU
YESTERDAY?
YO, WHAT HAPPENED
TO COACH?
WHAT DID HE DO?
YOU LEFT THIS IN THE GYM.
I DON'T WANT IT.
BUT YOU'RE PART
OF THE TEAM.
♪ I refuse to show
my good side ♪
♪ In no place to call my own ♪
YOU WERE RIGHT ABOUT CARSON.
SORRY.
♪ No home ♪
(no-no, no-no)
♪ No home... ♪