(CHEERING)
(BASKETBALL THUMPING)
(SNEAKERS SQUEAKING)
(BALL WHOOSHING)
(BALL CLANKING)
(NET SWISHING)
(BUZZER BLARES,
CROWD CHEERS)
WE'RE IN THE FINALS.
CARSON:
WE'RE GOING TO PROVINCIAL
FINALS, BABY!
THANKS TO OUR STAR
SHOOTING GUARD!
JENNA:
KC!
(LAUGHING EXCITEDLY)
KC:
THAT'S MY NAME.
DON'T WEAR IT OUT.
CLARE:
DON'T WEAR YOURSELF OUT.
UM, I WANT A HUG N' TWIRL, TOO!
OR AT LEAST A KISS.
CARSON:
MY, MY.
SOMEONE'S POPULAR.
I GUESS THERE'S A FIRST TIME
FOR EVERYTHING?
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out,
I know I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(DOOR CHIME RINGS)
SPINNER:
HEY, MARCO!
OR, SHOULD I SAY,
"HEY TEACH"?
HEY, THAT'S STUDENT-TEACH
TO YOU.
SPINNER:
READY FOR YOUR FIRST DAY
OF DEGRASSI, AGAIN?
WHO'S YOUR PLACEMENT WITH?
PERINO.
SPINNER:
(CHUCKLES)
YOU NEED THIS.
AS IF I WASN'T
NERVOUS ENOUGH.
HOLLY J.:
AT LEAST YOU WON'T BE HUNGRY.
I SAVED YOU THE LAST SCONE.
THANKS, H.J.!
HEY, I THOUGHT YOU WORKED
THE P.M. SHIFT.
OH, I'M NOT WORKING.
DECLAN HERE CAN'T DO WITHOUT
HIS MORNING DOT JAVA FIX.
DID YOU CATCH "SO YOU BELIEVE
YOU CAN BOOGIE" LAST NIGHT?
UH, YEAH.
YOHAN? SO DREAMY.
WELL, HATE TO BE
THE RESPONSIBLE ONE,
BUT IF YOU GUYS
DON'T BOOGIE
YOU'RE GONNA BE LATE,
SO...
(GRIMACING)
WISH ME LUCK!
YOU WON'T NEED IT.
YOU'VE GOT A BUILT-IN
FAN BASE.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
HOLLY J.:
AS IF YOU NEEDED AN EXCUSE
TO BREAK OUT YOUR BIKINIS,
OUR FINALS-BOUND MIDGET
BOYS BASKETBALL TEAM
WILL BE SUDSING IT UP
AT THE ATHLETIC ASSOCIATION'S
CAR WASH.
MAKE SURE TO SPREAD THE WORD
AND GET YOUR FAMILY AND FRIENDS
TO COME OUT.
KIDS:
(GIGGLING)
JENNA:
MY HALF-BROTHER'S HERE
WITH HIS TRUCK
AND HE'S BEEN MUDDING
ALL WEEKEND!
KC:
SOUNDS DIRTY.
THE TRUCK, I MEAN.
JENNA:
WHEN DO I GET TO MEET
YOUR FAMILY?
KC:
MY PARENTS AREN'T
REALLY AROUND.
UH, BUT HE HAS ME.
UH, ONE QUESTION:
WHAT IS MUDDING?
JENNA:
ONE, TAKE PICKUP TRUCK;
TWO, DRIVE THROUGH MUD;
THREE, IT'S AWESOME.
KC:
SOUNDS AWESOMELY AWESOME.
YOU SHOULD COME SOME TIME.
KYLE, THESE ARE MY FRIENDS,
CLARE AND KC.
OH, YOU'RE KC?
AH, THE MAN,
THE LEGEND.
MUCHO CHATTER ABOUT YOU
IN OUR HOUSE LATELY.
SHUT UP, KYLE.
(HORN HONKS)
(RADIO BLARING)
DAVE:
IS THAT COACH'S GIRLFRIEND?!
CARSON:
HELP ME WITH SOMETHING
IN THE TRUNK, BOYS.
CONNOR:
OUR TEAM JACKETS!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING, KC?
KC:
I COULDN'T AFFORD ONE,
WHAT WITH THE STOCK MARKET
TUMBLE.
IT'S COOL.
LADIES...
CLARE AND JENNA:
(SQUEALING)
KC:
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO ABOUT IT?
JENNA:
GET HIM, CLARE!
KC, YOU'RE DEAD!
KC:
(YELPING)
MR. PERINO:
WATCH YOUR BACK,
ESTABLISH DOMINANCE EARLY.
OTHERWISE THESE KIDS
WILL EAT YOU UP ALIVE.
THANKS, DOM,
BUT THERE'S BEEN A LOT
OF PROGRESS MADE
IN CLASSROOM MANAGEMENT
TECHNIQUES
SINCE YOU WERE
IN TEACHER'S COLLEGE.
IT'S YOUR FUNERAL.
I APPRECIATE THE SUPPORT.
(INHALING DEEPLY)
PEOPLE!
LIKE TO INTRODUCE MYSELF.
I AM MARCO DEL ROSSI.
NOW, CALL ME MARCO.
MR. DEL ROSSI IS MY DAD.
FITZ:
IS HE A MIDGET, TOO?
STUDENTS:
(LAUGHING)
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY -
THE SHORTER THE MAN,
THE BIGGER THE BRAIN?
HOW TALL ARE YOU?
STUDENTS:
OOH...
DOWN TO BUSINESS.
SO, DID YOU GUYS KNOW THAT
RIGHT HERE IN TORONTO...
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
KC:
DO I HAVE SOMETHING
ON MY FACE?
(CHUCKLING)
HERE, MR. LINCOLN,
LET ME WASH THAT OFF
FOR YOU.
JENNA:
(WATER SPRAYING)
IT'S ON, GUTHRIE!
(GIGGLING)
(SPONGE SPLASHES)
KC:
MAN, I AM SOAKED!
I TOTALLY HAVE
TO GET JENNA BACK1
I THINK THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT MISS FLIRTY FLIRT WANTS.
WHAT?
CLARE, WE'RE JUST
PLAYING AROUND,
HAVING FUN.
YOU SHOULD TRY IT.
I AM TRYING.
HERE.
I'LL HELP.
(CLARE SHRIEKS)
KC!
HOW WAS THAT FUN?!
JENNA:
I LOST MY CONTACT!
IT FELL OUT.
KC:
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA,
CAREFUL!
TURN THE WATER OFF.
JENNA, WE CAN'T HAVE
YOU SCRUBBING CARS
ALL ONE-EYED.
KC, IT'S FINE.
JENNA, YOUR BUTT CRACK'S
SHOWING.
JENNA:
I HAVE SPARE CONTACTS INSIDE.
YOU TOTALLY ROCKED
THE CLASS-BAH.
YOU TREAT STUDENTS
LIKE ADULTS,
THEY WILL RESPECT
YOU LIKE ADULTS.
TOTALLY.
I SHOULD KNOW.
I'M SWAMPED WITH NEAR GROWN-UP
RESPONSIBILITIES:
BABYSITTING BIZ,
STUDENT COUNCIL,
THIS ATHLETIC BANQUET
TOMORROW NIGHT.
I'M A CHAPERONE!
WE COULD SHOW OFF
OUR DANCE MOVES.
NOPE, I CAN'T GO.
UNLESS YOU GIVE ME AN EXTENSION
ON PERINO'S ESSAY?
(CHUCKLES)
IT'S NOT REALLY
MY JURISDICTION.
PLEASE, MARCO?
IT'S BEEN SO LONG
SINCE WE'VE HAD A TEACHER
WHO REALLY REMEMBERS
WHAT IT'S LIKE.
(RESIGNED SIGH)
OKAY, EXTENSION GRANTED.
ONE DAY ONLY!
(HAPPY GRUNT)
DECLAN:
SO...?
WE GOT THE EXTENSION.
WE?
CARSON:
THE WAY YOUR GAME'S IMPROVED,
YOU BETTER START PRACTICING
SMILING FOR THE NBA CAMERAS.
KC:
"SMILING JUST LETS THE WORLD
KNOW YOU'RE SCARED."
LITTLE TIP
FROM MY JAILBIRD DAD.
CARSON:
HOLD UP.
YOUR DAD'S IN PRISON?
MOMMY TOO.
DRUGS ARE BAD.
SO AM I APPARENTLY.
CARSON:
HEY, WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
MY GIRLFRIEND KEEPS
GETTING MAD AT ME.
SHE NEVER USED TO.
IT'S MY FAULT.
I LOOKED AT ANOTHER GIRL
LIKE... ONCE.
KC, HAVING EYES FOR OTHER GIRLS
DOESN'T MAKE YOU BAD.
IT MAKES YOU 15.
COME ON,
THE BLONDE CHEERLEADER?
I GET IT.
YOU DON'T GET ANYTHING,
COACH.
AND IT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS,
OKAY?
SORRY, CHAMP.
I'M JUST TRYING TO HELP.
(DOORBELL CHIMES)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
JUST...
TELL ME WHAT HAPPENED
AT THE CAR WASH.
(SIGHING)
YOU REALLY DON'T KNOW?
WE WERE ALL HAVING FUN,
THEN YOU LOST YOUR MIND.
WHAT'S UP WITH YOU?
JENNA'S TRYING
TO EDGE ME OUT
AND YOU'RE LETTING HER.
CLARE, NOBODY'S EDGING
ANYONE OUT.
I'M ALLOWED TO BE FRIENDS
WITH OTHER GIRLS, YOU KNOW.
AND FLIRT WITH THEM, TOO?
YOU KNOW,
COACH THINKS IT'S NORMAL
TO LOOK AT OTHER GIRLS.
REALLY?
SO DO YOU DO EVERYTHING
COACH SAYS?
NO.
BUT WE JUST MAKE
EACH OTHER MAD.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
IF WE CAN'T BE HAPPY,
MAYBE WE SHOULDN'T BE TOGETHER.
SO WE'RE BREAKING UP?
YEAH, I GUESS WE ARE.
I'M SORRY.
CLARE:
(SNIFFS)
JUST TELL ME ONE THING.
HOW LONG HAVE YOU
LIKED HER?
I TRIED NOT TO, CLARE.
SURE.
(DOOR BANGS SHUT)
MARCO:
IF IT HELPS,
THINK OF THE YONGE STREET
REBELLION...
AS A CELEBRITY FEUD...
WITH PITCHFORKS!
FITZ, MY GOOD MAN.
FITZ:
SO WE'RE GETTING AN EXTENSION
ON THIS ESSAY?
'CAUSE HOLLY J. AND DECLAN
GOT ONE.
STUDENTS:
(MURMURING)
SWEET, NOW I CAN GEAR UP
FOR THE BANQUET TONIGHT!
(STUDENTS MURMUR HAPPILY)
I AM NOT SPENDING MY WEEKEND
MARKING ESSAYS
BECAUSE YOU CAN'T SPROUT
A BACKBONE.
IT'S NOT THAT
BLACK AND WHITE.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S
BLACK AND WHITE?
YOUR EVALUATION
THAT I TYPE.
OKAY, GUYS, SORRY,
BUT YOUR ESSAYS ARE DUE TODAY
VIA EMAIL AT 6:00 P.M.,
BEFORE THE ATHLETICS BANQUET.
PERINO:
NOW THAT'S WHAT I CALL
CLASSROOM MANAGEMENT.
(BELL RINGS)
TODD:
HEY, NICE PANTS.
SO, YOUR TEAM DOING GOOD?
YUP.
YOUR COACH CAME BY.
HE LEFT SOMETHING FOR YOU.
(PACKAGE SNAPS)
RIGHT ON.
DID HE BUY YOU THAT?
I GUESS SO.
HE'S UH...
HE'S PRETTY AWESOME.
I'M GONNA BE LATE.
CURFEW IS STILL 9:30.
HIT ME AGAIN, SPIN.
CAREFUL, LITTLE BUDDY.
YOU'LL BE UP ALL NIGHT.
I MAY HAVE TO BE.
CHAPERONING THE BANQUET,
MARKING PAPERS...
YOU'RE OFFICIALLY
"THE MAN."
(DOOR CHIME JINGLES)
HEY, HOW'D YOUR ESSAY GO?
IT DIDN'T.
WHAT? WHY?
LOOK, I KNOW YOU HAVE
TO TREAT ME LIKE EVERYONE ELSE
WHEN WE'RE IN CLASS.
BECAUSE YOU'RE A STUDENT,
HOLLY J.
YEAH, I KNOW.
US KIDS CAN BE
SO FRUSTRATING, SO...
I'LL JUST HAND IT IN
TOMORROW?
NO BIG?
DECLAN:
LET'S GO.
GONNA BE LATE
FOR THE JOCK JAM.
SEE YOU THERE, MARCO.
(BLOWS KISS)
(FRUSTRATED)
UGH!
MARCO, EVEN FOR HOLLY J.,
THAT WAS...
(IMITATES A WHIP CRACKING)
GUESS I NEED
A NEW LESSON PLAN.
(MUSIC THUMPING)
DAVE:
HEY, SUPERSTAR.
YOU GOT A JACKET.
YOU STEAL IT?
I GOT IT TOTALLY LEGIT.
NICE THREADS.
THANKS.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE
TO DO THIS.
YOU EARNED IT.
BE PROUD.
I BROKE UP WITH CLARE.
WE'RE... WE'RE TOO DIFFERENT.
ONE THING I CAN TELL YOU,
IS YOU GOTTA GO AFTER
THE THINGS YOU WANT.
MAYBE I WILL.
GIRL:
GIVE IT UP FOR COACH CARSON!
AUDIENCE:
(APPLAUDING)
(CHEERING LOUDLY)
CARSON:
WELCOME TO A CELEBRATION
OF AN AMAZING ATHLETIC YEAR
AT DEGRASSI.
YOU KNOW, THE FIRST THING
I LOOK FOR IN A PLAYER
IS A LOVE FOR THE GAME,
AND THESE GUYS HAVE IT
IN SPADES.
IT'S MORE THAN A COACH
COULD EVER ASK FOR.
THEIR COMMITMENT,
COMBINED WITH DEDICATION
AND HOURS OF HARD WORK...
HI.
I LIKE YOUR JACKET.
I LIKE YOUR...
EVERYTHING.
CARSON:
GIVE IT UP FOR, KC.
(BOOMING VOICE)
KC GUTHRIE! GET UP HERE!
YOU JUST WON
MOST IMPROVED PLAYER!
AUDIENCE:
(APPLAUDING AND CHEERING)
(WOLF WHISTLES)
KC:
UM...
PANTHERS RULE!
TEAMMATES:
(CHEERING WILDLY)
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Well, I got my friends ♪
♪ I never knew that they'd
be here tonight ♪
♪ Ooh! I thought these guys
would be rolling outside ♪
♪ But you can say
what you want ♪
♪ When you've finally got a crew
right by your side ♪
♪ And I got the girl ♪
♪ Funny how I got her
back again ♪
♪ I could've been with her
or maybe her friend ♪
♪ Ooh! The time I met them
was the shop with the cops ♪
♪ I never even got her name ♪
DAVE:
STAR GUARD
AND A BOUNCY CHEERLEADER...
(SNIFFING)
OH, I SMELL A POWER COUPLE
IN THE MAKING.
ALLI:
YEAH, SO POWERFUL THEY PUSHED
KC'S GIRLFRIEND
RIGHT OUT OF THE WAY.
THAT'S NOT HOW IT IS.
ALLI:
JENNA, YOU'VE BEEN TRYING
TO STEAL KC SINCE DAY ONE.
I GUESS ALL IT TOOK WERE
A PAIR OF POM-POMS, HUH?
YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT ANYTHING, ALLI!
I KNOW EXACTLY WHAT CLARE'S FACE
IS GONNA LOOK LIKE
WHEN SHE FINDS OUT
ABOUT THIS!
I'M GONNA GO
GET SOME PUNCH.
TOUGH CROWD, HUH?
HEY...
YOU AND YOUR GIRL WANNA
GET OUT OF HERE,
GET SOME PRIVACY?
MY ROOM KEY.
ROOM 309.
TAKE YOUR TIME.
OH.
JENNA.
WAIT UP.
(DOOR OPENING)
KC:
LOOK AT THE SIZE OF THE BED!
JENNA:
THERE'S A WHIRLPOOL TUB.
(LAUGHING)
KC:
OH, LOOK AT THIS!
YOU KNOW THAT'S PROBABLY
A $10 CHOCOLATE BAR.
WHEN I KNOW WHAT I WANT...
I GO AFTER IT.
(DOOR OPENING QUIETLY)
JENNA:
UH...
KC:
COACH!
CARSON:
JUST WANNA GRAB MY WALLET.
I DON'T WANT TO INTERRUPT.
PRETEND I'M NOT EVEN HERE.
JENNA:
(EXHALING NERVOUSLY)
I SHOULD HEAD BACK
TO THE PARTY.
KC:
IT'S ALMOST MY CURFEW.
CARSON:
HEY, DON'T WORRY.
WHILE WE'RE HERE,
I'VE GOT A FEW THOUGHTS
ON A NEW PLAY.
LET ME GIVE TODD A CALL,
TELL HIM I'LL DRIVE
YOU HOME LATER.
AWESOME.
JENNA, IS THAT OKAY?
JENNA:
SURE.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
CARSON:
HEY, TODD, IT'S COACH CARSON.
I'M HERE WITH KC
AT THE ATHLETICS BANQUET.
YEAH, YEAH, HE JUST WON
MOST IMPROVED PLAYER.
YEAH, GREAT JOB.
LISTEN, I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU COULD EXTEND HIS CURFEW
FOR THE NIGHT.
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYS)
HOLLY J.:
(GIGGLING)
(CLEARING THROAT)
MARCO.
I WAS JUST ABOUT TO GO
TO THE WASHROOM.
NO MORE AVOIDING ME,
YOUNG LADY.
I GUESS YOU'LL BE TAKING
THE ZERO?
WHAT?
EVERYONE ELSE HANDED IN
THEIR ASSIGNMENTS ON TIME.
(SIGHING)
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
NOTHING.
JUST DOING MY JOB.
OKAY, FIRST YOU SAID
I COULD HAVE EXTRA TIME,
AND THEN YOU TOOK IT BACK.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED
TO BELIEVE?
FINE.
WE COMPROMISE.
I'LL SUBMIT YOUR PAPER
FOR MARKING
IF THE TIME STAMP ON YOUR EMAIL
FALLS BEFORE MIDNIGHT.
TONIGHT?!
THAT ONLY GIVES ME...
TWO HOURS TO FINISH.
HOPE YOU'VE DONE
YOUR RESEARCH.
(MIFFED GASP)
MARCO, YOU ARE SUCH A...
TEACHER!
THAT'S MR... DEL ROSSI TO YOU.
(PLAYERS' VOICES ON TV)
CARSON:
YOU GOTTA COVER THE DROP.
YOU TAKE A BREATH,
THEN SHOOT.
KC:
OKAY, COACH. GOT IT.
YOU BROUGHT ALL YOUR STUFF.
CARSON:
I'M STAYING HERE
WHILE I COACH AT DEGRASSI.
I'LL MOVE ON
AFTER THE FINALS.
GOTTA KEEP MOBILE.
OH. THAT SUCKS.
LET'S ENJOY THE TIME
WE GOT LEFT.
(BOTTLES CLINKING)
HERE...
DON'T TELL THE REST
OF THE TEAM, OKAY?
(BOTTLES OPENING)
I ONLY DRINK WITH
MY MOST IMPROVED PLAYERS.
OKAY, YEAH.
TO YOU.
KILLING IT ON THE COURT,
AND TO OUR NEW FRIENDSHIP.
CHEERS.
TO VICTORY!
(SLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
I REMEMBER MY FIRST DAY
OF TEACHING.
DID YOU BRING
YOUR OWN STRAP?
TRY GUITAR.
I HAD THEM SITTING
IN A CIRCLE,
ON THE FLOOR,
AND IT WAS
ALGEBRA CLASS.
(LAUGHING)
AND YOU THOUGHT I WAS SOFT.
NO, IT'S NOT ABOUT
BEING SOFT,
OR A HARD-ASS,
FOR THAT MATTER.
IT'S ABOUT BEING
WHAT THESE KIDS NEED.
A TEACHER?
THEY HAVE PLENTY OF FRIENDS.
HMM.
THANKS, DOM.
THAT'S MR. PERINO.
RIGHT.
HEY!
LEAVE ROOM
FOR THE HOLY GHOST.
WHAT... GHOST?
JUST NOT IN FRONT OF A TEACHER,
OKAY?
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
(BURPS)
EXCUSE ME.
CARSON:
OH, NO EXCUSE REQUIRED.
I'M NOT YOUR GRANDMA.
IT'S ALMOST MIDNIGHT.
I SHOULD GET HOME.
SORRY, BUDDY,
CAN'T DRIVE.
THE BREWS WENT DOWN
TOO EASY TONIGHT.
(CHUCKLING)
HEY, WHY DON'T YOU CRASH
ON THE PULLOUT?
KC:
IF YOU THINK THAT'S OKAY.
CARSON:
HAND ME YOUR PHONE.
I'LL CALL TODD.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
WHAT IS IT?
"GOING HOME.
C U TOMORROW.
KISSES, JENNA."
KISSES.
(CHUCKLING)
SORRY I INTERRUPTED EARLIER.
KC:
(CHUCKLING)
WHATEVER.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW.
SUCKS, RIGHT?
WHEN YOU GET ALL RILED UP
AND YOU GOTTA STOP?
(LAUGHING)
NOT THAT I WOULD HAVE HAD
ANY IDEA WHAT TO DO NEXT!
CARSON:
WELL, THEN HOW ABOUT WE GET
YOU SOME VISUAL AIDS?
HELLO, ADULT PAY-PER-VIEW.
YOU LIKE BLONDES, RIGHT?
"BETTY DOES BARCELONA."
THAT'S A GOOD ONE.