PETER:
WOO! YEAH!
ALL RIGHT, HIGH-FIVE!
LOW-FIVE!
NO FIVE! PSYCHE!
(LAUGHS)
HA HA HA!
I'M A COLLEGE-GOING GUY!
ALL RIGHT!
T.U. BY A HAIR.
HOW 'BOUT YOU GUYS?
T.U.,
AND A COUPLE OTHERS.
UM, I'M STILL WAITING TO HEAR.
SO WHAT'S NEXT, A FREE RIDE
ON DADDY'S UNIVERSITY SAVINGS?
NO, NO, MY DAD GOT SLAMMED
JUST LIKE EVERYONE.
I MEAN, MY PARENTS
ARE GONNA HELP,
BUT I GOTTA GET A JOB,
OR SOMETHING.
SAV AND DANNY:
(MOCK FEAR) WHOA.
PETER STONE?
WORKING STIFF?
WHATEVER.
I'LL PUT A RESUME TOGETHER.
HOW HARD CAN IT BE?
COME ON, PETER!
NAME ONE THING YOU'VE WORKED ON
FOR, HMMM...
LONGER THAN A WEEK?
WELL, 'TIL YOU GUYS
KICKED ME OUT?
MY BAND.
RIGHT.
(UNCOMFORTABLE MURMUR)
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, Woo-ooh ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
PETER:
"HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA.
EYES: BLUE.
SEMI-SUSPENDED DRIVER'S
LICENSE."
THIS IS SOME RESUME.
PETER:
(SNORTS, SCOFFING)
ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE NOT HIRING?
WHAT, AND CUT INTO
HOLLY J'S TIPS?
HOLLY J:
HEH, DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT IT.
OH, GUITAR AND BASS,
HUH?
YEAH,
IT'S TWO DIFFERENT SKILLS!
IT'S NOT LIKE I HAVE
ANY REAL WORK EXPERIENCE.
HEY, YOU WANT SOME?
HELP ME BRING SOME BEANS DOWN
FROM THE UPSTAIRS.
THERE'S AN UPSTAIRS?
(HUM OF TRAFFIC)
CAREFUL. THAT'S 50 POUNDS
OF DARK ROAST.
THIS SPACE IS HUGE.
WHAT DO YOU DO UP HERE?
SPINNER:
STORAGE.
AND SOMETIMES I'LL TAKE A NAP
ON A SLOW DAY.
CHECK IT OUT,
CHECK IT OUT.
THIS... IS A STAGE.
YOU ADD A SOUND SYSTEM,
CLEAN THIS UP A LITTLE BIT -
WE'RE IN BUSINESS!
HOW ARE WE IN BUSINESS?
WELL, YOU'RE ALWAYS TALKING
HOW BANDS DON'T HAVE
ANY PLACES TO PLAY, RIGHT?
SO, LIKE...
WHAT,
YOU WANNA PUT ON SHOWS?
YEAH, MAN,
IT'S A SLAM DUNK!
THE KID IN THIS NEIGHBOURHOOD
DO NEED A PLACE TO PARTY.
YEAH, AND WHEN YOUR BANDS
NOT PLAYING,
I'LL BOOK OTHER BANDS,
I'LL DO THE SOUND,
SELL BOOZE-FREE DRINKS.
AND WHAT DO I TELL THE OWNER?
WELL, WHAT HE DOESN'T KNOW
DOESN'T HURT HIM, RIGHT?
WRONG.
LOOK,
CLEAN THE PLACE UP,
AND...
WE'LL TALK TO HIM
IN THE MORNING, OKAY?
(GRUNTS)
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ In a time of doubt ♪
♪ It's easy to feel sorry
for yourself ♪
♪ Yeah, I Know, I know,
I know ♪
♪ My love was there for me ♪
♪ Never lied to me
Never left me by the road ♪
♪ And if you hear my song ♪
♪ Sing along ♪
WHEN I WON THE MATH PRIZE,
MY FAMILY ALL WENT OUT
FOR ICE CREAM,
EVEN THOUGH IT WASN'T
THAT HOT OUTSIDE.
IT WAS A GREAT DAY
FOR ALL OF US AND-
HOW DID YOU FEEL?
IT FELT GOOD.
AND PROUD, I GUESS?
KWAN:
CLARE, THIS IS LIFE-WRITING.
I WANT YOU TO TAKE US
ON AN EMOTIONAL JOURNEY.
WHY DON'T YOU TRY AGAIN
TOMORROW?
WHO'S NEXT?
JENNA.
LET'S HEAR IT.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT -
YOU'RE SHELTERED.
SOMEDAY YOU'LL HAVE
AWESOME STORIES.
OR I'LL BE SQUARE CLARE
FOREVER.
(HUFFS)
JENNA:
THIS IS THE STORY OF A LONELY
SMALL TOWN GIRL
TRYING TO MAKE FRIENDS
IN THE BIG CITY.
ONE THING I LEARNED
ABOUT CITY PEOPLE,
THEY DON'T GET EXCITED
WHEN SOMEONE NEW COMES TO TOWN.
SPINNER:
GOTTA ADMIT,
THE PLACE LOOKS AWESOME.
SO, I WAS THINKING,
I'LL WORK PRO-BONO THE FIRST
TWO WEEKS, AND THEN-
SO, NO ALCOHOL, NO DRUGS?
YEAH, ALL-AGES SHOWS,
FOR KIDS WHO CAN'T
GET INTO BARS.
GAVIN,
YOU'LL VOUCH FOR HIM?
YEAH.
I LIKE YOUR FRIEND,
BUT THIS IS ON YOU.
ANY TROUBLE, AND I MEAN THE
SMALLEST BIT OF FUNNY BUSINESS,
AND IT'S SSHHT!
NO FUNNY BUSINESS, SIR.
SCOUT'S HONOUR.
GAMAL:
YOU TURN A PROFIT?
I'LL PUT YOUR FRIEND
ON THE PAYROLL.
SEE YOU NEXT WEEK.
YEAH, DUDE!
THERE YOU GO.
AND IN OTHER NEWS TODAY,
UH, WE HAVE A SPECIAL
ANNOUNCEMENT
FROM PETER STONE.
THAT'S YOU.
READ THAT.
I WISH THERE WAS A COOL
ALL-AGES PLACE
PEEPS LIKE US COULD GO
TO WATCH LIVE BANDS.
HOLY COINCIDENCE!
TONIGHT'S THE GRAND OPENING
OF EXACTLY THE PLACE
YOU JUST MENTIONED!
WHERE AND WHEN CAN
MY MANY FRIENDS
AND I PARTAKE
IN SUCH EXCITEMENT?
GOOD QUESTION, NANCY!
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD
OF THE DOT?
HOLLY J:
UH, YEAH, DOOFUS,
I WORK THERE.
PETER:
THE CLUB IS CALLED
"ABOVE THE DOT!"
AND IT'S RIGHT ABOVE THE DOT!
GET IT?
THIS IS STUPID.
ON OTHER NEWS, THE LEPIDOPTERY
SOCIETY BAKE SALE
IS HAPPENING IN THE CAFETERIA
TODAY.
(MUSIC FROM LAPTOP PLAYS)
DECLAN:
'KAY, SAV, I CAN'T TALK
RIGHT NOW, OKAY?
(BEEPS PHONE OFF)
CLARE EDWARDS.
INTERVIEWING FOR PROPMASTER,
RIGHT?
SORRY ABOUT THE PHONE CALL.
OH, THAT'S OKAY,
IT'S A REALLY BIG JOB TO
PUT TOGETHER THIS WHOLE SHOW.
HEH, YEAH. TELL THAT TO MY
DEMANDING CAST AND CREW
THEY THINK IT'S EASY.
CLARE:
NO WAY!
I STAGE MANAGED
MY SUNDAY SCHOOL MUSICAL
AND WORKED EVERY WEEKEND
FOR TWO MONTHS!
TWO MONTHS, HUH?
THAT'S COMMITMENT.
WELL, IT WAS WORTH IT.
I MEAN,
I LOVE STUFF LIKE THIS.
OKAY, DONE DEAL!
WE MEET ON THURSDAYS, OKAY?
(ELATED BREATH)
WHAT WERE WE LISTENING TO?
UH, THE BATALIS.
AN INDIE BAND
I HEARD IN ITALY.
EVER BEEN?
OH, YOU GOTTA GO.
PICK SOME GRAPES,
DRINK SOME WINE,
MET A CRAZY GIRL
WITH A VESPA.
TUSCANY CHANGED MY LIFE.
(PHONE RINGS)
OH, SORRY,
I'M BORING YOU.
NO, NO,
IT WAS A GREAT STORY.
♪ I've been looking back ♪
♪ La la la ♪
PETER:
OH.
FIONA.
VICTORIA.
HEY, PETER.
I'M SURPRISED
YOU REMEMBER ME.
YEAH, YOU'RE FIONA'S COUSIN,
RIGHT?
YEAH, I DON'T REALLY REMEMBER
MUCH ELSE FROM THAT NIGHT.
I MEAN, POST-METH.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE
GIVEN IT TO YOU.
I'M SORRY.
VICKI'S BEEN CLEAN FOR,
WHAT, TWO MONTHS NOW?
NA DOES WONDERS!
HOW ABOUT YOU?
I HAVEN'T TOUCHED A THING
SINCE THAT STUPID WEEKEND.
VICTORIA:
GOOD FOR YOU, SWEETIE!
WELL...
NICE TO SEE YOU.
UH, WAIT, WAIT-WAIT!
UM...
I'M STARTING A NEW CLUB.
IT'S LIKE A...
ALL-AGES LIVE-MUSIC THING.
COOL.
I'LL CHECK IT OUT.
YOU WORKING ON YOUR STORY?
GREAT GUESS.
I DIDN'T THINK
YOUR OTHER ONE WAS SO BAD.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
WE HAVEN'T TALKED SINCE...
THAT'S KIND OF WHAT HAPPENS
AFTER A BREAKUP.
I JUST WANNA KNOW
IF YOU'RE OKAY.
MY LIFE DIDN'T REVOLVE
AROUND YOU, KC.
I HAVE A WHOLE BUNCH
OF THINGS GOING ON
THAT YOU KNOW NOTHING ABOUT.
SO SPARE ME THE PITY.
OKAY.
SO I'LL SEE YA.
♪♪♪♪♪
JANE:
♪ HOUSE ARREST
HOUSE ARREST ♪
♪ PUT MY RECORD TO A TEST ♪
♪ HOUSE ARREST
HOUSE ARREST ♪
♪ THREE GREAT MONTHS
AND NEVER... ♪
I THOUGHT
YOU'D BE ON STAGE.
OH. ONE OF THE SIDE EFFECTS
OF METH USE -
YOU LOSE YOUR BAND.
COULD'VE BEEN WORSE.
SO, UH...
THIS IS A COOL SPACE.
YEAH, IT'S THE FIRST NIGHT.
SO IT SHOULD
PROBABLY PICK UP.
YOU KNOW, LIKE, WORD OF MOUTH,
OR WHATEVER.
(BAND PLAYS)
SO YOU THINK PEOPLE'LL
KEEP COMING FOR COFFEE
AND BOTTLED WATER?
AS IF.
NO, IT'S ALL ABOUT BOOKING
AWESOME BANDS.
FRITZ HELDER AND THE PHANTOMS
ARE ABOUT TO DO A CLUB TOUR.
THEY MIGHT DO A LOW-PRESSURE
TUNE-UP SHOW.
THAT'D BE GREAT,
BUT LIKE, HOW?
I KNOW THEM.
AND THEY OWE ME A FAVOUR.
NO WAY!
WOULD YOU'D DO THAT?
I'LL LOOK INTO IT.
NO PROMISES.
DO YOU SMELL SOMETHING?
UH, HEY, GUYS.
I DON'T MEAN TO NARC YOU OUT
OR ANYTHING,
BUT YOU GOTTA GET RID OF THAT.
OR MY SIX FRIENDS AND I
COULD GO SOMEWHERE ELSE,
AND TELL EVERYONE HOW LAME
THIS PLACE IS.
'KAY, JUST TAKE IT
TO THE BATHROOM, ALL RIGHT?
HEY, COOLIO?
YOU WANT SOME OF THIS?
NO, YOU GO AHEAD.
(STUDS CONTINUES TO PLAY)
PETER:
SO, MINUS THE COSTS,
WE MADE 18 BUCKS.
SPINNER:
HM. WHATEVER, MAN,
TONIGHT WAS AWESOME.
YEAH,
AND WORD'S GONNA SPREAD.
I ENLISTED SOME HELP.
YEAH,
SO WHO IS THE LOVELY LADY?
SHE'S, UM...
THAT GIRL I WAS TALKING
TO YOU ABOUT.
FIONA AND DECLAN'S COUSIN.
THE METH CHICK?
YEAH,
BUT SHE'S CLEAN NOW.
SHE'S BEEN IN NA
FOR TWO MONTHS.
COOL.
HEY, SORRY, MAN,
WE'RE CLOSED.
COME BACK TO...
I'M WITH METRO DRUG
TASK FORCE.
WE JUST BUSTED SOME KIDS
WHO SAID THEY BOUGHT DRUGS
HERE.
THAT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
COP:
WELL, WE KEEP HEARING THINGS,
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO SEND
THE PERMIT FOLKS OVER.
AND THEY COULD
SHUT YOU DOWN.
NO, NO, IT WON'T HAPPEN
AGAIN, OKAY.
I GUARANTEE THAT.
SEE YOU AROUND.
DID YOU SEE ANYTHING?
JUST A COUPLE OF STONERS.
GREAT. SO, THE FIRST NIGHT,
WE'RE TURNING INTO A DRUG DEN.
HEY, DUDE,
YOU WANT ANYMORE OF THIS?
THEN MAYBE IT'S NOT OUR JOB
TO BE A COUPLE OF NARCS.
YOUR JOB IS TO MAKE SURE
I DON'T LOSE MY JOB,
ALL RIGHT?
SO, ANYONE WITH DRUGS
GETS THE BOOT! CLEAR?
YES, SIR!
PETE?!
YEAH, I GOT IT.
CLARE:
I GOT THE BEST TAN
WHILE PICKING GRAPES.
AND THAT'S WHEN I MET MATTEO.
HE TOOK ME FOR A RIDE
ON HIS VESPA.
AND AS THE WIND BLEW
THROUGH MY HAIR,
I REALISED THAT TUSCANY
TRULY CHANGED MY LIFE.
MOVING, COMPELLING.
WELL DONE.
TUSCANY? A VESPA?
REALLY?
YOU DON'T KNOW EVERYTHING
ABOUT ME.
(WITH A LAUGH)
I GUESS NOT.
(HALF LAUGHS)
SIMPSON:
NOW THE LINUX OPERATING SYSTEM
IS AN EXCELLENT EXAMPLE
OF FREE AND OPEN SOFTWARE
COLLABORATION.
NO WAY!
PETER. IS THERE, UH...
SOMETHING YOU'D LIKE
TO SHARE WITH THE CLASS?
UH, ACTUALLY, YES,
THERE IS.
TONIGHT FRITZ HELDER
AND THE PHANTOMS
ARE PLAYING
ABOVE THE DOT!
(IMPRESSED AND EXCITED MURMURS)
THEIR VIDEOS ARE SICK!
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
HAVE I EVER LIED TO YOU,
DANIEL?
WHATEVER, WHATEVER.
UH, DOORS ARE AT EIGHT!
IF IT'S, UM,
OKAY WITH YOU
CAN WE GET BACK
TO WINDOWS VS. LINUX?
GO RIGHT AHEAD, SIR.
THANK YOU.
NOW LINUX OFFERS TWO-TIERED
SECURITY, WHICH MEANS...
(HUM OF CHATTER)
BAND MEMBER:
CHECK. ONE, TWO...
PETER:
THANKS, VICKI,
YOU'RE A LIFESAVER.
I'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO PAY YOU BACK.
VICTORIA:
NEVER SAY NEVER, SWEETIE.
PASTEL:
VICKI!
IS THIS THE LUCKY GUY?
THIS IS THE FRIEND
I TOLD YOU ABOUT.
PULLING IN A PRETTY BIG FAVOUR
FOR JUST A FRIEND.
ENJOY THE SHOW.
THANKS, PASTEL.
YOU ROCK!
SO, FRIEND.
BEEN TALKING ME UP?
YOUR NAME MAY HAVE COME UP.
YEAH? LIKE, AS IN,
"I MET THIS REALLY CUTE GUY"?
FOLLOWED BY
"AND I BLEW MY CHANCES
WHEN I GAVE HIM CRANK."
WELL, IT SORTA CAUSED ME
TO BREAK UP WITH MY GIRLFRIEND.
SO, IN A WEIRD WAY,
I GUESS IT MADE
YOUR CHANCES BETTER.
SO, WHAT ARE THEY NOW?
I'D SAY THEY'RE PRETTY GOOD.
SO I GUESS
I'M A LUCKY GIRL.
(FRITZ HELDER AND THE PHANTOMS
BEGINS TO PLAY)
♪ FIVE, SIX, HERE WE GO ♪
(MUSIC BEGINS,
CROWD CHEERS)
(MUTED BEAT OF MUSIC)
CLARE, I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU WANTED TO COME HERE.
WELL, I'M NOT GOING TO
GET ANYMORE GREAT STORIES
LYING IN MY BEDROOM.
WELL, UH, THAT DEPENDS...
BOTH:
(GIGGLE)
DECLAN! HI.
PROPMASTER CLARE!
YOU'RE A FAN OF THE FRITZ TOO?
SURE. I ALSO DOWNLOADED
THE BATALIS ALBUM.
THEY'RE AMAZING.
ALLI:
WHO'RE THE BATALIS?
JUST THIS INDIE BAND
FROM ITALY.
DID YOU HEAR THEM
WHEN YOU WERE THERE,
RIDING AROUND ON A VESPA?
DECLAN:
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
YOU WERE NEVER THERE.
PICK GRAPES, TOO?
I WAS BORING HER
WITH MY STORIES EARLIER.
SEE YOU IN THERE.
OH MY GOD! CLARE,
YOU STOLE DECLAN'S STORY?
I'M BUSTED.
CONGRATULATIONS.
(EXHALES)
CLARE?
CLARE!
YOU'RE OVERACTING.
COME BACK HERE.
(BAND PLAYS, KIDS CHEER)
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ EVERYBODY'S UP IN THE VIP ♪
♪ LIVIN' LIKE THE POPSTARS
IN THE TRASH MAGAZINES ♪
♪ I WALK RIGHT IN
AND THEY STOP ♪
♪ AND STARE AT ME ♪
♪ MY HEAD STARTS TO SWELL
'CAUSE I'M OUT LOOKIN' FINE ♪
♪ YOU'VE GOT YOUR OWN EGO
WHY YOU FLOATIN' INTO MINE ♪
♪ YOU ONLY HATE ME
'CAUSE I GOT WHAT YOU WANT ♪
♪ IT'S TRUE ♪
♪ NOW IF YOU'RE ALL SO COOL ♪
♪ THAT YOU GOT YOUR FAME... ♪
PETER:
DO YOU BELIEVE THIS CROWD?
SPINNER:
CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS CASH?
OH, I LOVE THE STINK
OF COVER CHARGE.
THIS PLACE IS GONNA BLOW UP!
THANKS.
DUDE, YOU DID IT!
COME HERE.
I MIGHT EVEN GET A RAISE
OUTTA THIS.
WHAT CAN I SAY?
I'M AN ENTREPRENEUR.
AND A LOTHARIO, APPARENTLY.
OH, THAT?
THAT MUST BE FROM WHEN I...
TOTALLY MADE OUT
WITH VICTORIA!
YOU DIRTY DAWG!
COME HERE, COME HERE.
OH, WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
SPINNER:
RUBBING YOUR HEAD
FOR GOOD LUCK.
HE'S ON A ROLL.
TOUCH HIM, TOUCH HIM.
OKAY, BOYS, I'M GONNA HEAD
TO THE BATHROOM.
♪♪♪♪♪
(MUTED BEAT OF MUSIC)
(SNIFFING)
UH, I LIKE YOUR TOP.
IT'S CUTE.
UH, THANKS.
(SOUND OF KIDS CHEERING
AND HOLLERING AS DOOR OPENS)
♪♪♪♪♪
UM, I JUST SAW
VICTORIA IN THE BATHROOM.
TAKING DRUGS.
SHE CAME OUT OF THE STALL,
WIPING HER NOSE.
MAYBE SHE HAS A COLD!
NO, I KNOW WHAT I SAW,
PETER.
WELL, THEN GET YOUR EYES
CHECKED, JANE.
HEY, HEY, HEY!
SHE ALREADY SCREWED UP
YOUR LIFE ONCE, ALL RIGHT?
WE'RE NOT GONNA LET THAT
HAPPEN AGAIN.
VICTORIA HAD A DRUG PROBLEM,
ALL RIGHT?
SHE'S IN A PROGRAM.
THAT'S HISTORY.
PEOPLE CHANGE.
YEAH, WELL, HISTORY OFTEN
REPEATS ITSELF.
(BAND CONTINUES PLAYS)
ARE YOU SURE?
YES.
ALLI:
CLARE!
CLARE, WAIT A SECOND!
WHY, SO YOU CAN CALL ME
A LIAR?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WHY ARE YOU TRYING TO BE
SOMEONE ELSE?
CLARE:
BECAUSE I'M BORING, ALLI!
YOU'RE GROWING UP
AND I'M JUST...
WATCHING!
WHAT'RE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU HAVE LOTS OF STORIES
TO TELL.
THERE'S, UM...
UH, THERE'S THAT TIME YOU
GOT THAT FUNNY HAIRCUT.
AND, UM...
WELL, YOU AND KC
JUST BROKE UP.
I MEAN, THAT IS DRAMA,
RIGHT?
THANKS, ALLI.
I ALMOST FORGOT.
I'M SORRY, CLARE.
IT'S OKAY TO FEEL BAD.
CAN WE FEEL BAD
AT THE MALL AT LUNCH?
CAN'T FACE KC AND JENNA
IN THE CAF TODAY.
PETER:
HEY.
THANKS FOR MEETING ME
ON MY LUNCH BREAK.
DIDN'T GET A CHANCE
TO SAY GOODBYE LAST NIGHT.
SORRY.
SOMETHING CAME UP.
BUT, UH, ABOVE THE DOT'S
GONNA BE THE PARTY PLACE
THIS SUMMER.
YEAH,
IT'S GOING SO WELL.
I'M STARTING TO GET
THE PARTY VIBE AGAIN.
LOOK, I KNOW YOU'RE IN NA
AND EVERYTHING,
BUT I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU HAD ANY
OF YOUR OLD HOOKUPS?
LIKE, FOR DRUGS?
NO PRESSURE.
I'M GLAD YOU'RE CLEAN.
IT'S JUST, I GUESS
I'M NOT AS STRONG AS YOU.
I'M NOT THAT STRONG.
I'VE BEEN CHEATING.
HERE.
I CAN GET MORE.
GREAT.
AND, UH, IF YOUR FRIENDS
ARE LOOKING TO SCORE,
YOU KNOW WHERE TO FIND ME.
WHERE WILL THAT BE?
REHAB OR JAIL?
I DON'T WANT
YOUR STUPID DRUGS.
WHAT WAS THIS?
SOME KIND OF TEST?
DON'T COME TO THE CLUB.
DON'T CALL ME.
OKAY, I CAN'T BE AROUND
THAT CRAP ANYMORE.
(INHALES AND EXHALES)
ALLI:
CLARE, WHY ARE YOU PUSHING ME?
HOW IS THIS
GONNA HELP?
IT'S DIFFERENT!
(GIGGLES)
THANKS.
HERE, HOLD MY STUFF.
(STRAINING)
OH... OKAY.
(BOOKS CLATTER)
I'M NOT PLANNING ON ANYONE
SEEING THIS LACY BRA, YOU KNOW.
IT'S JUST FOR ME.
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?!
(READING)
"THE ONLY THING I THINK
I DID WRONG WITH KC
WAS TO BE MY HONEST SELF,
SO WHY WASN'T THAT ENOUGH?"
CLARE, THIS IS A STORY!
IT'S PATHETIC.
IT'S...
IT'S HEARTBREAKING.
IT'S HONEST.
IT WOULD BLOW MS. KWAN AWAY.
I CAN'T TELL PEOPLE, ALLI.
(EXHALES)
TOO PERSONAL?
NO.
IT'S NOT FINISHED.
I STILL HAVE TO WRITE
THE PART
WHERE THE GIRL
GETS THE GUY BACK.
CLARE! ARE YOU SERIOUS?!
MAYBE IT'S TIME
TO GET INTERESTING.
EEE!
(EXCITED GIGGLING)
PETER:
OKAY, HERE COMES AN AMP.
(STRUGGLING GRUNT)
SAV:
MAN, WHEN'RE YOU GONNA
MAKE ENOUGH MONEY
TO BUY THE CLUB
A SOUND SYSTEM?
THE WAY THINGS ARE GOING?
PROBABLY PRETTY SOON.
HEY, UM...
SPINNER TOLD US WHAT YOU DID.
MUST'VE BEEN HARD.
DANNY:
YOU KNOW, IT'S COOL
THAT YOU GOT THE VAN
AND SET UP THE CLUB.
YOU TAKE GOOD CARE OF US.
SAV:
COME ON, LET'S GET ON WITH IT.
BASS DRUM?
PETER:
ALL RIGHT,
BACK TO ROADIE WORK.
HERE YA GO, BOSS.
HEY, HOLD UP, HOLD UP.
WE HAD A NEW SIGN MADE.
"JANIE AND THE STUDS
FEATURING PETER STONE"?
GUYS, WHAT IS THIS?
WELL, WE THOUGHT THAT YOU
AND I COULD SING DUETS.
SO, I'M BACK IN?
YOU GUYS ARE SERIOUS?
AH, COME HERE, GUYS.
COME HERE.
JANE:
AWWW...
YOU GUYS ROCK.
THANK YOU!
AW, I LOVE YOU GUYS!
(STUDS PLAY)
♪ Hey, Cali-hey-forni-a-i-a ♪
(Hey, California)
♪ Hey, Cali-hey... ♪