PETER, MAN,
I DON'T WANT TO FIGHT!
PETER:
WHY NOT?
YOU'RE A LOSER!
EVERYONE KNOWS IT, WE ALL TALK
ABOUT YOU BEHIND YOUR BACK!
YOU GONNA HIT ME,
HUH?
YOU GONNA HIT ME?
(TAKES DEEP BREATH)
INHALE, COUNT.
EXHALE.
I'M NOT GONNA HIT YOU.
WE'LL DEAL WHEN WE'RE CHILL.
(SIGHS)
(APPLAUSE)
MS. SAUVE:
NICE, RILEY!
YOU TOOK YOURSELF
OUT OF A VOLATILE MOMENT.
ANGER IS JUST A REACTION.
TO SADNESS, FEAR,
INSECURITY.
ACKNOWLEDGE
THE REAL PROBLEM,
AND YOU'LL BE FREE.
THANKS, EVERYONE.
(BELL RINGS)
PETER:
SO, HAVE YOU TALKED TO SAUVE
ABOUT THE "REAL" PROBLEM?
YOU KNOW,
I WISH I COULD TELL EVERYONE.
MEET NEW PEOPLE,
MAKE NEW FRIENDS.
GAY FRIENDS?
ANYA:
THERE YOU ARE!
I NEED TO INTERVIEW DEGRASSI'S
MOST ELIGIBLE BACHELOR
FOR THE VIDEO YEARBOOK.
I'LL BE RIGHT WITH YOU.
NO, NOT YOU.
(SCOFFS) ME?
ANYA:
YEAH,
YOU WON BY A LANDSLIDE!
THE GIRLS WANNA KNOW
WHAT MAKES YOU TICK!
GREAT...
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, whatever ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
PA ANNOUNCEMENT:
PASSION FOR THE PLANET?
DEGRASSI GREEN COMMITTEE
IS LOOKING FOR NEW MEMBERS.
VISIT THEM
IN THE CAFETERIA TODAY.
DOES RILEY STAVROS
LIKE BLONDES OR BRUNETTES?
HUH? UH...
THEY'RE ALL GOOD.
KEEPING AN OPEN MIND!
SO, WHAT'S A GIRL GOTTA DO
TO GET YOUR ATTENTION?
JUST UM...
BE NICE?
YOU REALIZE I'M BEING
MARKED ON THIS
FOR COMMUNICATIONS CLASS,
RIGHT?
I'M SORRY,
I'M TRYING.
(RECORD BUTTON BEEPS)
ANYA:
RILEY STAVROS,
MAN OF MYSTERY.
MR. ARMSTRONG:
MOST OF YOU DID VERY WELL
ON YOUR MOCK EXAMS.
YOU SHOULD BE PLEASED.
KC:
MR. ARMSTRONG?
CAN I GET SOME TUTORING
BEFORE THE EXAM?
WELL, IT'S LATE
FOR THAT, KC.
I'LL SEE
WHAT I CAN DO.
WE COULD STUDY TOGETHER.
I MEAN,
I NEED TO REVIEW TOO.
IT WOULDN'T BE WEIRD,
STUDYING WITH YOUR EX?
WHY WOULD IT BE?
WE'RE JUST TWO CLASSMATES
HELPING EACH OTHER OUT,
RIGHT?
NO BIG DEAL.
IF YOU WANT.
THAT'D BE GREAT.
(SIGHS HAPPILY)
(CALMING MUSIC PLAYS)
YOGA INSTRUCTOR:
AND... RELEASE.
CONTINUE TO COOL DOWN
AT YOUR OWN SPEED.
NAMASTE.
ZANE:
SEE 'YA NEXT TIME,
RILEY.
(SIGHS)
SEE 'YA, ZANE.
GOOD LUCK
ON THE BIOLOGY FINAL!
ANYA:
THAT WAS SO RELAXING!
THANKS FOR LETTING ME
TAG ALONG.
ANYWAY, UM...
YOU SAID YOU WERE GONNA TELL ME
WHO YOU HAD A CRUSH ON.
OH UM, UH, I GUESS...
NOBODY RIGHT NOW.
REALLY?!
RILEY:
ANYA...
I HAVE SOMETHING
TO TELL YOU.
IT MIGHT FREAK YOU OUT.
WELL, LUCKY MY CHAKRAS
ARE ALIGNED.
OKAY, UM...
I-I LIKE...
I LIKE GUYS.
WHAT?
YOU DO?
ARE YOU SURE?
YEAH.
VERY SURE.
(LAUGHS)
THIS SO EXCITING!
AM I THE FIRST PERSON
YOU'VE TOLD?
ONLY PETER KNOWS, BUT-
YOU TOTALLY HAVE A CRUSH
ON ZANE!
RILEY:
WHA-?!
(LAUGHS SELF CONSCIOUSLY)
NO! I MEAN, HE'S-
HE'S NOT EVEN... GAY.
MMM...
OH, FORGET IT.
LET'S JUST KEEP THIS
TO OURSELVES, OKAY?
YEAH.
BELIEVE ME, I'VE GOT STUFF
I WOULDN'T WANT PEOPLE TO KNOW.
SO, IT GOES IN THE VAULT.
PROMISE.
THANKS.
FOR BEING COOL.
(KC SIGHS)
I SHOULD KNOW
THIS STUFF!
CLARE:
HOW'D YOU GET
SO FAR BEHIND?
YOU USED TO BE
SO GOOD AT MATH.
YOU KNOW, ALL THE STUFF
WITH COACH CARSON.
NOT REALLY.
I MEAN, I SAW COACH CARSON
GET TAKEN AWAY,
BUT THERE WERE A LOT
OF RUMOURS.
(SIGHS)
HE WOUND UP WANTING TO TEACH ME
A LOT MORE THAN BASKETBALL.
I MEAN,
HE DIDN'T TOUCH ME,
BUT HE WANTED ME
TO WATCH PORN,
AND... DO OTHER STUFF.
AFTER ALL THAT,
STUDYING KINDA
WASN'T IMPORTANT.
WE'LL GET YOU THROUGH
THIS TEST, KC.
I PROMISE.
CLARE,
JENNA AND I ARE-
OH!
KC, IT'S-IT'S OKAY.
WE'RE JUST HANGING OUT
LIKE CLASSMATES.
FRIENDS.
THAT'LL MAKE BEING
IN THE SAME CLASSES
FOR THE NEXT THREE YEARS
A LOT EASIER.
PA ANNOUCEMENT:
REMINDER:
SMOKING IS NOT PERMITTED
ANYWHERE ON SCHOOL PROPERTY.
ANYONE CAUGHT, WILL BE
IMMEDIATELY SUSPENDED.
(CLEARS THROAT)
ANYA: I HAVE INTEL.
RILEY: WHAT?
RILEY,
ZANE'S GAY!
SAYS WHO?
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
IT'S NOT THAT BIG
A SECRET,
ONCE YOU START
ASKING AROUND.
WELL, GOOD FOR HIM.
SO,
YOU GONNA ASK HIM OUT?
I-I DON'T KNOW!
WELL, YOU'D BETTER DECIDE.
HEY!
I THINK I NAILED IT!
THAT BIO EXAM?
OH!
THANKS FOR
WISHING ME LUCK.
HEY, GREAT.
NOW THAT I'M DONE STUDYING,
I DON'T, UH...
KNOW WHAT TO DO
WITH MYSELF.
UH, WANNA HANG?
SURE!
UH, COFFEE AT THE DOT?
IF YOU'RE FREE.
'KAY.
COOL!
I'LL... SEE YOU IN AN HOUR.
(RILEY LAUGHS)
YOU HAVE A DATE!
NO,
IT'S JUST UH...
WAIT, IS IT?
DON'T BE NERVOUS, WHAT'S
THE WORST THAT COULD HAPPEN?
(SIGHS)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
RIGHT ON TIME!
THEY DON'T CALL ME
"BIG BEN" FOR NOTHING.
THEY CALL YOU "BIG BEN?"
NO, NOT REALLY.
(LAUGHS)
THE COFFEE SUCKS HERE,
YOU WANNA GO SOMEWHERE ELSE?
OH!
SURE.
I GOT 48 SQUARED
FOR QUESTION C.
UH... NO.
YOU FORGOT TO REDUCE,
RIGHT THERE.
I MISS THIS STUFF.
I'M GLAD WE'RE GETTING
TO BE FRIENDS AGAIN.
HI!
MMWAH!
I JUST FINISHED
MY HISTORY EXAM,
AND, HAVE NO REHEARSAL
'TIL TOMORROW!
HOPE YOU GOT LOTS
OF STUDYING DONE!
THANKS, CLARE.
SEE YOU TOMORROW?
UNLESS YOU WANNA HANG
WITH US?
I'M GONNA REALLY MAKE SURE
I REALLY KNOW THIS STUFF.
YOU GUYS HAVE FUN.
SO...
INVITE ME FOR DINNER?
BUT WHAT ABOUT
YOUR EXAM?
(SIGHS)
I'M GONNA FLUNK ANYWAY,
I THOUGHT YOU
AND CLARE CRAMMED.
YEAH, BUT STILL.
IT'S HOPELESS.
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU ASK
CLARE FOR HELP?
SHE DID HELP.
NO, I MEAN...
DURING THE EXAM.
SHE WOULDN'T WANNA SEE YOU
FLUNK MATH, WOULD SHE?
THIS IS SAINT CLARE
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT.
YOU SAID
YOU WERE FRIENDS AGAIN.
SO, WHAT ARE FRIENDS FOR?
(SIGHS)
ZANE:
WHOO!
I FEEL LIKE SPIDER MAN!
RILEY:
SOMETIMES I COME HERE AFTER
THE CONSTRUCTION GUYS GO HOME.
YOU CAN KINDA BE ALONE.
SECRET CLUBHOUSE,
HUH?
WHAT ARE THE RULES?
NO GIRLS ALLOWED?
GUYS ONLY CLUB.
AND UH,
WHAT DO WE DO?
WELL, IF I TELL YOU,
I'D HAVE TO KILL YOU.
WOW, THIS CLUB
SURE HAS A LOT OF SECRETS.
ARE WE HIDING
FROM THE WORLD UP HERE?
(SIGHS)
IT'S GOOD TO BE AWAY
FROM PEOPLE WE KNOW.
LESS STUFF TO EXPLAIN
IF ANYONE SEES US.
YOU MEAN...
EXPLAIN THAT YOU'RE GAY.
SO YOU ARE.
WHAT ARE YOU ASHAMED OF?
SECURITY GUARD:
HEY!
NO TRESPASSING!
WE'RE TALKING!
NOT ANY MORE.
LET'S GO.
GET YOUR HANDS
OFF ME!
SECURITY GUARD:
COME ON!
GET YOUR HANDS OFF-
I SAID,
GET YOUR HANDS OFF ME!
INHALE, COUNT.
EXHALE.
YOU'RE OKAY.
(SIGHS)
YOU'RE OKAY, RILEY.
CLARE!
CAN WE UH, RUN THROUGH
ONE MORE EQUATION?
THE TEST STARTS
IN TWO MINUTES!
WHAT MORE CAN WE DO?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
SIT BESIDE ME.
YOU COULD SHARE.
YOU MEAN, CHEAT?
I'M A FRIEND,
ASKING HIS FRIEND FOR HELP.
WE COULD GET ZEROES, GET KICKED
OUT OF GIFTED, SUSPENDED-
YOU'RE RIGHT!
YOU'RE RIGHT.
SORRY I ASKED.
IT'S COOL HOW YOU ALWAYS
DO THE RIGHT THING.
(BELL RINGS)
GOOD LUCK.
MR. ARMSTRONG:
OKAY, SO...
YOU WORK OUT
THE EQUATIONS,
AND FILL IN
YOUR ANSWER SHEET.
EVERYONE READY?
BEGIN.
PA ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION DEGRASSI:
COME OUT AND SUPPORT
OUR DEGRASSI
MIDGET BASKETBALL TEAM...
HEY, CAN WE TALK?
ARE YOU SURE
YOU WANNA BE SEEN WITH ME?
AW MAN, I'M REALLY SORRY
ABOUT YESTERDAY.
SERIOUSLY, YOU LEFT ME
WITH THAT RENT-A-COP?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
I'VE BEEN DEALING
WITH SOME ANGER ISSUES.
I HAD TO LEAVE BEFORE
I DID SOMETHING STUPID,
LIKE,
PUNCHED HIM OUT!
THE YOGA,
THAT PART OF IT TOO?
WELL, IT'S HELPING.
SOUNDS LIKE
YOU'RE WORKING ON IT.
SO...
DOES UH, THERAPY INCLUDE COMING
TO THE LGBT MIXER TONIGHT?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
SO REALLY,
YOU'RE NOT COMING OUT AT ALL.
MAYBE NOT.
YOU'RE GONNA BE LONELY,
RILEY.
I HOPE YOUR PRIVACY'S
WORTH IT.
ZANE...
(JENNA GIGGLES)
CLARE!
HEY.
I WAS JUST TELLING JENNA
HOW YOU TOTALLY BAILED ME OUT
ON THE FINAL.
WELL, I'M NOT EXACTLY
PROUD OF CHEATING.
I THOUGHT WE MIGHT
KEEP IT A SECRET?
JENNA:
OH, IT'S OKAY!
I TOLD KC
YOU'D BEND THE RULES FOR HIM.
IT'LL BE...
ALL OUR SECRET.
S-SO THIS WAS YOUR IDEA?
YOU'RE A GOOD FRIEND,
CLARE BEAR!
FIRST YOU CHEAT ON ME
WITH HER,
NOW YOU CHEAT OFF OF ME
BECAUSE OF HER.
JENNA'S...
JUST TRYING TO HELP ME!
BUT YOU USED ME!
SO YOU AND YOUR PERKY
LITTLE GIRLFRIEND
COULD SLACK OFF
AND MAKE OUT!
CLARE, COME ON!
CLARE:
DON'T TALK TO ME!
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ This isn't me ♪
♪ I'm not happy ♪
♪ Can you feel it too? ♪
♪ How long ♪
♪ Should I drag this on ♪
♪ Waitin' around ♪
♪ For what's already gone ♪
♪ I don't know
what to believe in ♪
♪ Sink into this ♪
♪ Straightjacket feeling ♪
♪ I am afraid ♪
♪ I am falling ♪
PETER:
YOU GUYS,
THE MIXER'S UPSTAIRS.
FOLLOW ME.
♪ Ah ah ♪
♪ I pray ♪
♪ I... I pray ♪
♪ I... ♪
MR. ARMSTRONG:
WELL DONE, MS. EDWARDS!
SOME IMPRESSIVE RESULTS.
BUT NOBODY'S PERFECT,
SO, WE'RE GONNA TAKE UP
THE ONES THAT GAVE YOU GUYS
TROUBLE, OKAY?
YES, KC,
YOU WANNA GET US STARTED?
I CHEATED.
YOU CHEATED?
HOW?
I LOOKED AT CLARE'S ANSWERS.
EVERY ONE OF THEM.
SHE DIDN'T KNOW.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL,
HEAD TO THE OFFICE.
WE'LL DISCUSS THIS WITH
MS. HATZILAKOS AFTER CLASS.
(SIREN WAILS)
OH, RILEY!
PERFECT TIMING!
CAN YOU HELP ME
CARRY SOME OF THESE UP, MAN?
I CAN'T GO UP THERE.
I GOT HALFWAY UP,
BUT I...
I JUST CAN'T.
THERE'S A LOT
OF HETEROS UP THERE.
YOU CAN PRETEND
YOU'RE ONE OF US.
WE DON'T MIND, REALLY!
BUT I DO!
I'M SICK OF PRETENDING.
OH OKAY, WELL,
YOU CAN SELL DRINKS.
AND BE MY ASSISTANT.
(SIGHS WITH RELIEF)
THANKS, MAN.
WE'D BETTER HURRY.
AH, YOU NERVOUS?
I FEEL LIKE
I'M GONNA HURL.
OKAY WELL,
LET'S HURRY THEN.
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYS)
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ I can't wait ♪
♪ 'Til you pick me up ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
♪ You know,
I should take the wheel ♪
♪ And drive ♪
♪ As I thought you know ♪
♪ Ultimately why... ♪
YOU CAME!
EVENTUALLY.
DON'T WORRY,
I WON'T OUT YOU.
JUST UH,
TRY TO HAVE SOME FUN.
ZANE,
THIS IS ALL NEW TO ME.
(LAUGHS)
IT'S NEW FOR ALL OF US!
YOU THINK I CAME OUT
IN PRESCHOOL?
LET'S SEE YOU DANCE!
YOU WANT
TO TRY THAT AGAIN?
MAYBE PUT SOME EFFORT
INTO IT THIS TIME?
WHATEVER,
I HAVE MOVES!
(BOTH LAUGH)
COME ON,
JOIN THE CLUB.
I THINK YOU'LL LIKE IT.
♪ I can't wait ♪
♪ 'Til you pick me up ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
♪ You know ♪
♪ I should take the wheel ♪
♪ And drive ♪
(BELL ON DOOR RINGS)
DECAF TEA, PLEASE.
SO, I GOT A ZERO.
BUT I'M GLAD I OWNED UP.
GREAT.
YOU WANT A MEDAL?
CLARE,
I REALIZED SOMETHING.
ALL MY PROBLEMS
THIS YEAR STARTED
AFTER YOU AND I
BROKE UP.
OH.
SO IT'S MY FAULT?!
IF ANYTHING,
IT'S JENNA'S.
ALL MY PROBLEMS
WITH CARSON STARTED
AFTER...
JENNA AND I GOT TOGETHER,
AND THE WHOLE CHEATING THING
WAS HER IDEA.
YOU'RE PATHETIC.
I DON'T CARE WHAT
HAPPENED WITH COACH CARSON,
OR, OR HOW HARD
YOUR SEMESTER'S BEEN.
AS SOON AS THINGS
GET ROUGH,
YOU BLAME EVERYONE
BUT YOURSELF.
I-I JUST WANT US
TO BE FRIENDS!
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU WANT.
SEE YOU IN SEPTEMBER, KC.
(PARTYGOERS CHATTER)
ZANE:
SO, HOW WAS YOUR FIRST
LGBT MIXER?
RILEY:
NEXT TIME, I'M TAKING YOU
TO A BASEBALL GAME.
HEY, YOUR DANCING
WASN'T SO BAD!
WAIT... NEXT TIME?
(SIGHS)
WELL, WE HAD FUN, RIGHT?
SO CHANCES ARE,
WE'D HAVE FUN AGAIN?
GOOD PLAN.
UM...
I SHOULD GRAB THIS-
TOTALLY.
YOU HAVE MY NUMBER,
RIGHT?
MM-HMM.
OH.
I'M UH...
I'M GLAD YOU CAME OUT TONIGHT.
YEAH...
ME TOO.
ZANE!
(LAUGHS)
♪ Someday ♪
♪ Be all right ♪
♪ It's a long way ♪
♪ To happiness ♪