ALLI:
IT'S ALL CLEAR.
LET'S GO.
BREAKING AND ENTERING.
LOVELY CHOICE
OF EXTRA CURRICULAR.
ALLI:
I'D DO THE SAME FOR YOU
IF KC HAD PICS OF YOUR
BREASTS IN HIS LOCKER.
JENNA: (LAUGHS)
THAT WOULD NEVER HAPPEN.
I MEAN, NO OFFENSE.
NONE TAKEN.
OBVIOUSLY.
CAN'T YOU JUST
GET YOUR HAIRCUT
IF YOU NEED
TO GET OVER HIM?
I AM OVER JOHNNY.
I JUST NEED
TO GET THAT PHONE,
DELETE THOSE PICS,
AND FORGET
HE EVER EXISTED.
COURTESY OF DAD'S
TOOLCHEST!
(CLACKS)
OR, THERE'S
AN EASIER WAY.
IT'S NOT LOCKED.
WOW, IT'S ACTUALLY...
NORMAL IN THERE.
WHAT WERE YOU
EXPECTING, CLARE,
A DEAD BODY?
JENNA:
DID YOU FIND THE CELL PHONE?
AWWWWW...
CUTE!
I KNOW.
CLARE:
NO! NO "I KNOW".
HE SENT NAKED PHOTOS
OF YOU TO BRUCE, REMEMBER?
I KNOW!
JENNA:
YOU GUYS LOOK SO HAPPY THOUGH.
I KNOW.
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it,
I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, Woo-ooh ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
GOT IT!
♪♪♪♪♪
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
NUMBER ONE RULE
TO A SPEEDY RECOVERY?
TIME TO PURGE ALL THINGS
JOHNNY FOR GOOD.
GOOD. YOU CAN'T
TRUST HIM.
YOU'LL FEEL BETTER
ONCE YOU CUT TIES.
RIGHT.
THANKS, FRIEND.
HEY.
UM, WHAT'S UP?
DID YOU FIND WHAT
YOU WERE LOOKING FOR?
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
I NEVER KEEP VALUABLES
IN MY DECOY LOCKER.
ESPECIALLY CELL PHONES
WITH INTERESTING
PHOTOS.
I WANT IT BACK,
JOHNNY.
IF I GIVE IT BACK,
YOU'LL HAVE NO REASON
TO COME TALK TO ME.
RIGHT.
THAT'S THE POINT.
YOU KNOW,
I KEPT MY PROMISE.
NO ONE SEES
THOSE PHOTOS BUT ME.
THANKS.
I MEAN... GOOD.
YOU STILL SHOULDN'T
HAVE THEM.
WE'RE BROKEN UP,
REMEMBER?
(STRING INSTRUMENTS TUNING UP)
HEY, YOU GUYS WANNA
SHOOT SOME POOL AFTER SCHOOL?
UHH...
WE HAVE TO WORK ON SOME STUFF
FOR MUSIC THEORY CLASS.
OH. COOL.
I'VE BEEN WORKING
ON A NEW SONG.
IT'S CALLED "HOUSE ARREST".
NICE. WE'D LOVE
TO HEAR IT.
YEAH. WE, WE SHOULD JAM
OR SOMETHING.
UH, MAYBE TOMORROW?
DANNY:
UH... SO SORRY, MAN.
BUT WE HAVE TO PLAY THE MASTER
MUSIC JAM TOMORROW.
OH.
COOL.
BUT WHY DON'T YOU COME?
YEAH?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
DANNY,
I CAN HEAR YOU.
SAV:
UH,
PETE,
JUST SO YOU KNOW, UM...
JANE'S SINGING
WITH US NOW.
PETER:
WHAT?!
YOU GUYS REPLACED ME?
PLEASE,
DON'T FREAK OUT!
JANE:
DUDES! WORKED OUT A
HELLA-HARMONY FOR TOMORROW.
OH. UH... HEY, PETER.
PETER:
WATCH OUT.
ONE MISTAKE AND THESE SO-CALLED
FRIENDS'LL REPLACE YOU TOO.
JANE:
OKAY.
GIRL:
HERE! HERE!
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
OKAY, LET'S ROTATE.
CLARE, YOU'RE IN.
GIRL:
I THINK IT'S MY SERVE.
GIRL 2:
OKAY, OVERHAND OR UNDERHAND?
WHERE WERE WE?
SO THEN I SAID,
"WE'RE BROKEN UP,"
AND HE JUST SMIRKED.
UGH! CLAIRE THINKS
I SHOULD HATE HIM
BUT I CAN'T.
I TRIED.
SOMETIMES WE CAN'T
HELP WHO WE LIKE.
CLAIRE JUST DOESN'T
WANT YOU TO GET HURT.
CAN I TELL YOU
A SECRET, THOUGH?
UM...
JOHNNY WAS MY FIRST
AND I WAS HIS AND,
IT WAS SPECIAL.
WOW, ALLI.
NO WONDER.
DO YOU THINK
BREAKING UP WITH HIM
WAS A BAD MISTAKE?
IF IT'S MEANT TO BE,
YOU AND JOHNNY
WILL BE TOGETHER,
LIKE, DESTINY.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
COACH:
OKAY, LET'S ROTATE.
BHANDARI, YOU'RE IN.
SIMPSON:
WE RELY ON SECURE WEBSITES
TO PROTECT SO MUCH
OF OUR INFORMATION.
SO LET'S LOOK AT THESE SITES
AND SEE HOW THEY USE DESIGN
TO ESTABLISH TRUST.
OKAY, I WANT EACH OF YOU
TO CHOOSE A COMPANY SITE.
IT CAN BE A BANK, CLOTHING
STORE, INSURANCE,
AUCTIONS...
SOMEONE'S HERE
TO SEE YOU.
SIMPSON:
ASK QUESTIONS LIKE:
HOW ACCESSIBLE
IS THE COMPANIES INFORMATION?
IS THERE ENOUGH PRODUCT
DESCRIPTION?
LOOK AT UH, HOW-
HERE.
PHOTOS AND ALL.
JOHNNY, I-
SIMPSON:
SOMEWHERE TO BE, DI MARCO?
YUP.
ALLI,
BACK TO CLASS.
DI MARCO.
HEY.
UM, MEET ME IN MUSIC
DETENTION, OKAY?
YOU'RE -
YOU'RE RIDICULOUS.
WHY ARE YOU DOING
THIS TO YOURSELF?
WE'RE JUST TALKING,
OKAY CLARE?
FULLY CLOTHED
AND EVERYTHING.
YEAH, BUT HE'S STILL
THE SAME SLIMEBALL.
WHAT'S CHANGED?
EVER THINK THAT
MAYBE HE'S SORRY?
I MEAN, HE GAVE
THE PHONE BACK, REMEMBER?
JENNA UNDERSTANDS.
SO YOU GUYS
GOT A NEW SINGER?
YEAH.
WELL, I MEAN...
YOU WE'RE TRYING TO
STAY OFF THE METH
AND WE NEEDED SOMEONE,
SO-
YEAH, I KNOW.
I KNOW.
JANE'S COOL.
IT'S JUST LIKE,
THE BAND WAS MY CREW.
I FEEL LIKE I GOT FIRED
FROM MY FRIENDS OR SOMETHING.
SO TRY TO
GET 'EM BACK?
OH, YEAH,
I NEVER THOUGHT OF THAT.
WELL LISTEN.
TOMORROW MORNING,
THE BAND HAS TO SCHLEP
ALL THE GEAR
FROM THE LOFT
ALL THE WAY TO DEGRASSI.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
STOP BY? SAY HI.
AND WHAT? STAND
AROUND LIKE A KNOB?
NO. IDIOT.
JUST COME BY AT SEVEN.
A.M.?
ARE YOU INSANE?
HOW BAD DO YOU MISS
YOUR BUDS?
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
JUST LIKE OLD TIMES,
RIGHT?
JUST WAIT!
ALL RIGHT?
I FOUND SOMETHING.
ON...
MY JUNK.
YOU'RE-?
UM, WHAT?
A WART.
OR SOMETHING.
WHAT ARE YOU,
WHAT YOU YOU GONNA DO?
GET IT CHECKED OUT
AFTER SCHOOL.
YOU SHOULD GET
CHECKED OUT, TOO. OKAY?
ME? WHY?
WAIT, WHERE DID IT-
WHERE DID IT COME FROM
LIKE YOUR JOCKSTRAP
OR SOMETHING?
BECAUSE WHEN WE HAD SEX
IT WAS BOTH OUR
FIRST TIMES. RIGHT?
RIGHT?
NOT EXACTLY.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
I SAID IT TO MAKE YOU
FEEL BETTER.
WHO WAS SHE?!
MORE THAN JUST ONE.
(SHARP EXHALE)
JENNA:
THERE YOU ARE!
CLARE AND I HAVE BEEN
LOOKING FOR YOU.
I'M GONNA THROW UP.
WANT ME TO TAKE YOU
TO THE NURSE?
(WORRIED)
ALLI?
JOHNNY LIED TO ME.
HE HAS A THING.
AND NOW,
I MIGHT HAVE A THING.
DID YOU USE
PROTECTION?
YEAH, BUT LOOK -
IT SAYS, CONDOMS MAY NOT ALWAYS
PROTECT YOU FROM HPV!
HANG ON A SECOND.
YOU CAN HAVE IT
FOR LIFE, JENNA.
YOU NEED TO STOP SCARING
YOURSELF
AND SEE A REAL DOCTOR.
NOT MY-OWN-DIAGNOSIS
DOT-COM. OKAY?
(SIGHS)
WILL YOU COME WITH ME?
SAV:
(KNOCKING) ALLI!
ALLI:
I'M- NAKED!
(SIGHS) OKAY.
HEY, HAVE YOU SEEN
MY MIRROR?
I GOTTA CHECK
THE BACK OF MY HAIR.
YOU'RE SUCH A DORK.
WHAT'S WRONG?
DID MOM FIND OUT
ABOUT YOUR SECRET
TEEN VOGUE
SUBSCRIPTION?
CAN I ASK YOU
SOMETHING SERIOUS?
OH MAN, ALLI.
WHY DO GUYS LIE
TO GIRLS?
TO HOOK UP WITH THEM.
UM, AND... SOMETIMES
IT'S TO KEEP FROM HURTING
SOMEONE THAT
WE REALLY LIKE.
(SCOFFS)
AND THEY DON'T
THINK LYING HURTS?
ARE ALL GUYS
COMPLETE IDIOTS?
MOSTLY, YEAH.
SO, AM I BEATING UP
JOHNNY DI MARCO?
NO.
GOOD.
BUT, I MEAN,
IF YOU INSISTED...
I'D LET HIM WAIL
ON ME FOR A WHILE.
HOW'D YOU GET TO BE
SUCH A GOOD GUY?
I GOT A LITTLE SISTER
TO LOOK OUT FOR.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M HERE.
I'M A SLUT!
STOP IT.
YOU'RE NOT A SLUT.
MYTH: STIS ONLY HAPPEN
TO PROMISCUOUS PEOPLE.
UH, FACT.
PEOPLE WHO TRUST LOSERS
LIKE JOHNNY ARE STUPID.
DON'T BE SO HARD
ON YOURSELF.
WHO KNOWS HOW MANY GIRLS
JOHNNY HAS BEEN WITH.
OR HOW MANY GUYS THOSE
GIRLS HAVE BEEN WITH.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT CLARE
WOULD SAY IF SHE KNEW?
PROMISE NOT TO TELL HER.
I PROMISE.
CLINIC RECEPTIONIST:
IF I COULD JUST GET YOU TO FILL
OUT THIS FORM?
(TIRES SQUEALING)
SAV:
I'M GONNA BLOW A HAMMY!
JANE:
HOLD ON, SPAGHETTI ARMS.
THAT'S THE LIGHT SIDE.
(CAR HORN HONKS)
PETER:
ANYONE NEED A RIDE?
WHAAAAT!
WHOSE VAN?
PETER:
MEWESICAL HIGH MONEY,
MEET SWEET NEW RIDE.
DANNY:
YOU BOUGHT IT?
YEAH. PICKED IT UP CHEAP.
MY DAD HOOKED ME UP
WITH A DEALER.
A USED CAR DEALER,
YOU IDIOTS!
SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I THINK MY ARMS
LOVE YOU.
DANNY:
SERIOUSLY, MAN.
THIS IS AWESOME.
PETER:
GREAT.
WELL, LET ME GIVE YOU
A HAND.
NO, I GOT IT.
SAV:
ALL RIGHT.
(GRUNTS WITH EFFORT)
YOUR EXAMINATION DIDN'T SHOW
ANY ABNORMALITIES.
ANY...?
DOCTOR:
WARTS?
NO.
WE'LL CHECK YOUR PAP SMEAR
TO BE SURE,
BUT IT'S A GOOD SIGN.
HAVE YOU CONSIDERED
THE HPV VACCINATION?
I'M NEVER
HAVING SEX AGAIN.
(LAUGHS)
SORRY.
BUT, I MEAN...
OKAY, FINE.
CAN I GET MORE
INFORMATION?
SURE.
OF COURSE, AT YOUR AGE,
YOU'LL NEED YOUR PARENTS'
CONSENT.
GREAT.
COME ON, ALLI.
YOU'LL BE HPV
INVINCIBLE! LIKE ME.
WE GOT THE SHOT
AT MY OLD SCHOOL.
DOCTOR:
WELL, IT'S A TRICKY ONE.
OVER A 100 STRAINS.
THIS ONLY PROTECTS
AGAINST CERTAIN TYPES.
WELL, PLEASE SAY
THE WARTS TYPE.
CERVICAL CANCER'S WHAT
YOU GOTTA WORRY ABOUT.
AND THIS VACCINE
WILL PROTECT YOU
AGAINST CERTAIN STRAINS
THAT CAN LEAD TO THAT.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
SIMPSON:
OKAY.
SO WE'LL PICK UP
WHERE WE LEFT OFF.
YOU'VE ALL READ THE SMALL PRINT
OF YOUR CHOSEN WEBSITE'S
PRIVACY POLICY.
NOT TURN IN YOUR ONE PAGE
REPORTS, PLEASE.
ARE YOU OKAY?
DO YOU HAVE
A HEADACHE?
NO.
SIMPSON:
ALL RIGHT, NOW TEAM UP
AND COMPARE RESULTS.
TRY AND FIND A PARTNER
WITH A SIMILAR COMPANY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
JOHNNY LIED TO ME.
HE WAS HONEST
ABOUT HPV.
THAT MEANS SOMETHING.
OUR WHOLE...
EVERYTHING WAS A LIE.
I WISH HE COULD FEEL
WHAT I'M FEELING RIGHT NOW.
HE SHOULD FEEL WORSE!
HOW DO WE
MAKE THAT HAPPEN?
WHAT IF EVERYONE
KNEW HE HAD AN STI?
SIMPSON:
(WHISPERED) GIRLS!
IF YOU WANT TO BROADCAST
YOUR CONVERSATION
TO THE WHOLE SCHOOL,
GO ON THE VIDEO
ANNOUNCEMENTS.
OTHERWISE,
(SHOUTS) CLAM UP!
(STUDENTS GIGGLE AND LAUGH)
WHAT IF JOHNNY TELLS
THE WHOLE SCHOOL HIMSELF?
HOW IS THAT EVER
GOING TO HAPPEN?
TRUST ME. I CAN BE
VERY PERSUASIVE.
(SAXOPHONE PLAYS
OVER A REGGAE BEAT)
FOR A SAX PLAYER,
THAT GUY HE REALLY BLOWS!
AND WITHOUT A BAND,
TOO.
TAKES GUTS TO PLAY WITH
YOURSELF ON STAGE.
(LAUGHING)
(APPLAUSE)
GIRL:
GOOD JOB!
BOY:
NICE!
MR. LAVIGNE:
NICE. VERY MOODY, I LIKE IT.
THE MASTER MUSIC JAM
OPEN STAGE CONTINUES.
GIVE IT UP FOR JEFF AND ELANA!
(APPLAUSE)
HERE YA GO.
HERE I GO - WHAT?
WELL, I'M BACK,
SO I FIGURED YOU'D
HELP SPIN KEEP THE BEAT.
LOOKED SEXY
WHEN MIA DID IT.
IS THAT RIGHT?
(SARCASTIC LAUGH)
JENNA:
HE STILL HAS DETENTION.
THAT'S DI MARCO.
PREDICTABLE.
ARE YOU SURE
THIS IS GONNA WORK?
LAST CHANCE TO BACK OUT,
COMPADRE.
DIMARCO'S GOING DOWN.
ARE YOU GETTING
JOHNNY BACK?
YOU WOULDN'T
UNDERSTAND, CLARE.
I THINK
IT'S A GREAT IDEA.
HE SHOULD PAY
FOR KEEPING
THOSE NUDE PHOTOS.
IT'S NOT JUST...
ABOUT THAT.
WHAT? WHAT ELSE
DID HE DO?
IT'S MORE LIKE
'WHO' ELSE.
OH, NO. ALLI!
IT'S PAYBACK.
SO OPEN WITH
"SHARED CUST"?
SPINNER:
DUDE,
JANE'S SINGING.
IT'S HIS GIRLFRIEND,
I GET IT.
BUT I'M YOUR SINGER!
COME ON, GUYS!
OH. SO YOU DON'T
WANT ME BACK?
THAT'S JUST GREAT.
I GOT A VAN
FOR YOU GUYS!
I KNOW.
I MESSED UP ONE TIME.
WHEN AM I GONNA
GET OFF THE HOOK?
COME ON, GUYS.
WE'RE STUDZ.
(APPLAUSE)
ACTUALLY, WE'RE NOT
CALLED THAT ANYMORE.
MR. LAVIGNE:
ALL RIGHT DEGRASSI, UP NEXT,
WE GOT A REAL TREAT FOR YOU.
GIVE IT UP FOR
JANIE AND THE STUDZ!
(LOUD CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
JANE:
1, 2, 3, 4!
♪ I SLAM AROUND
WASTE AWAY ♪
♪ WAITIN' FOR YOU ♪
♪ I'M STARIN' AT THE CEILING ♪
♪ I GOT NOTHING TO DO ♪
♪ GOOD TIMES
GOOD TIMES ♪
♪ NO TIME TO WASTE
HEY,
JOHNNY DI MARCO.
I'VE NOTICED YOU...
AROUND SCHOOL.
YOUR EYES WORK.
GOOD.
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY
ABOUT...
GUYS WITH BIG
HEADPHONES?
BIG EARS?
YOU AND ALLI BROKE UP,
RIGHT?
YOU'RE... AVAILABLE?
♪ GOOD TIMES
GOOD TIMES ♪
♪ NO TIME TO WASTE
NO TIME TO WASTE ♪
♪ GOOD TIMES ♪
(BROADCAST ON LOUD SPEAKER
CUTS OUT)
JENNA:
JOHNNY. DI. MARCO.
SUCH A BAD BOY.
WANNA MAKE IT
HOT IN HERE?
NOPE. CAN'T.
JENNA:
SURE YOU CAN.
I MEAN, LOOK AT YOU.
JOHNNY:
JUST STOP, ALL RIGHT?
I'M NOT INTERESTED.
JENNA:
WHY, JOHNNY DI MARCO?
IS THERE A REASON?
SOME KIND OF MEDICAL PROBLEM
I SHOULD KNOW ABOUT?
YOU CAN BE HONEST WITH ME,
I WON'T JUDGE.
FINE!
YOU REALLY
WANT TO KNOW?
YOUR FRIEND ALLI
IS THE ONLY GIRL I WANT.
STUDENTS:
AAAAAAAAAAW!
AAAAW!
(ECHOING WITH FEEDBACK)
ALLI! HE LOVES YOU!
UH... OOPS!
IS THIS THING ON?
ALLI?
DID YOU PUT HER UP TO THIS?
WELL, I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE GONNA SAY THAT!
STUDENTS:
(LAUGH AND SNICKER)
(MUSIC PLAYING LOUDLY
ON CAR RADIO)
YOU TOOK OFF
YESTERDAY.
YEAH. I DIDN'T WANT TO
GET IN THE WAY OF JANIE
OR HER STUDS.
DANNY:
GIMME A BREAK, DUDE, OKAY?
WHAT WERE WE SUPPOSED TO DO?
PETER:
UH, I DON'T KNOW, HAVE MY BACK?
BE MY FRIEND?
DANNY:
DUDE! WE ARE YOUR FRIENDS.
IT'S JUST GONNA-
TAKE TIME TO...
READJUST, YOU KNOW?
IT'S JUST HOW IT IS.
IT'S A COOL VAN
THOUGH.
AND UH, WE DO NEED
A ROADIE.
TALK ABOUT A DOWNGRADE.
WELL, WE CAN STILL GET
HOT WINGS AFTER SHOWS, RIGHT?
OF COURSE.
WHY NOT.
OKAY COOL.
YOU'RE BUYING.
(LAUGHS)
SO YOU ASKED
YOUR PARENTS?
"JUST BECAUSE
I GET THE VACCINE
DOESN'T MEAN
I PLAN ON HAVING SEX,
BLAH BLAH BLAH..."
AND...?
THEY WERE SURPRISINGLY
COOL ABOUT IT.
OH! HE'S COMING!
WHAT DO I DO?
JENNA:
WHAT'S YOUR GUT TELLING YOU?
HOW SHOULD I KNOW?
IT'S DOING BACK-FLIPS!
COME ON,
DO YOUR CLARE THING.
TELL ME EVERYTHING
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR.
NO WAY. YOU ALWAYS
GET MAD WHEN I DO THAT!
PLEASE!
I NEED TO HEAR IT.
HE LIED,
HE HURT YOU,
HE PUT YOUR BODY
AT RISK.
HE'S A GREASY,
OLD, DISHONEST-
OKAY! I GOT IT!
THANKS, CLARE.
ANNOUNCER ON PA:
ATTENTION DEGRASSI STUDENTS:
LUNCHTIME IS HAPPENING
IN THE GYM
FOR STUDENTS INTERESTED
IN PURSUING
UNIVERSITY SPORTS SCHOLARSHIPS.
(TAKES DEEP BREATH)
EVERYONE IS WELCOME!
PROUD OF YOURSELF?
YOU'RE HOLDING
ALL THE CARDS NOW.
SO YOU UPPING
THE STAKES?
I CAN'T PLAY WITH SOMEONE
I DON'T TRUST.
GAME OVER.
HEY, BHANDARI.
MIGHT NOT HAVE BEEN
MY FIRST TIME.
BUT IT WAS MY FIRST TIME WITH
SOMEONE I ACTUALLY LIKED.
BYE, JOHNNY.