(LOW DIN OF AUDIENCE CHATTER,
DRUMS BEAT RHYTHMICALLY)
PETER:
SPINNER!
(STUDZ PLAYS)
PETER:
♪ I'M LIKE "WHOA!" ♪
♪ THE CALIFORNIA SUN ♪
♪ THIS RIDE HAS JUST BEGUN ♪
♪ I'M LIKE "WHOA!" ♪
♪ JUST LIKE A SUBMACHINE GUN ♪
♪ WITH OUR GUITARS
AND ALL OUR GIRLS ♪
STUDZ:
♪ HEY-CALI-HEY-FORN-HEY-I-A! ♪
HI, I'M CHANTAY,
DEGRASSI'S UNOFFICIAL
VIDEO BLOGGER.
YOU MUST BE
THE DIPLOMAT'S KIDS?
WORD TRAVELS.
AND I'M THE DESTINATION.
SO WHAT BRINGS
THE UPPER CRUST
TO DEGRASSI?
OLD MAN'S A PUBLIC EDUCATION
ATTACHE.
PRIVATE SCHOOL'S
BAD POLITICS.
WE'RE BORING,
BELIEVE ME.
SO, WHAT'S THE DEAL HERE?
WHO ARE THE PLAYERS?
CHANTAY:
HOLLY J IS THE DE-FACTO
STUDENT COUNCIL PREZ.
THE BAND, STUDZ,
JUST SHOT A MOVIE IN L.A.
THE SINGER'S GIRLFRIEND
IS DEGRASSI'S NEXT TOP MODEL.
SPEAK OF THE DEVIL.
PETER:
OH, SHE'S BACK FROM GAY PARIS!
ALL THE PHOTO SHOOTS
IN THE WORLD
COULDN'T KEEP ME
FROM A STUDZ SHOW.
ALL RIGHT,
CONGRATS, GUYS.
YOU'RE IN
THE WINTER BEACH BASH.
LADY, WE ARE
THE WINTER BEACH BASH!
OH, DID I TELL YOU
I'M A "MASTER MUSICIAN" NOW?
YOU GOT INTO
THE MUSIC PROGRAM?
WELL, BASICALLY.
CAN'T EXPECT THESE GUYS
TO MAKE IT LOOK COOL
ON THEIR OWN.
THAT'S AMAZING,
PETER!
I KNOW.
THIS SEMESTER'S ALL ABOUT
ME AND YOU, BABY.
WOO!
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out
I know I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it,
I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, Woo-ooh ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
CHANTAY:
SO, FOR THE BLOG,
WHAT DOES DEGRASSI'S
COUPLE-OF-THE-WEEK GO BY,
MIA-TER? PIA?
WOW, WE'RE COMBO WORTHY?
BUT WHO REALLY WANTS TO READ
THE STORY OF A GIRL
JUGGLING HER DAUGHTER,
HIGH SCHOOL,
AND HER MODELLING CAREER?
AND HER ROCK STAR
BOYFRIEND!
MIA, YOU JUST SPENT
THE WEEKEND IN PARIS.
YOU'RE WHAT WE CALL
"ASPIRATIONAL."
NEWBIE ALERT!
THIS IS FIONA AND DECLAN.
SEE YA!
WORD IS YOU TWO ARE MR.
AND MRS. HIGH SCHOOL.
PETER:
YEAH, PETER.
'SUP?
MIA JONES.
I HEAR YOU MODEL.
OH, MY MOM'S IN
WITH T.O. FASHION MAG.
NEW STYLE EDITOR.
I SHOULD HOOK YOU UP
SOMEDAY.
AND YOUR BAND ROCKS, SIR.
YEAH, CHECK US OUT
FRIDAY NIGHT!
AH, WOULDN'T MISS
THE BEACH BASH!
IT'S REFRESHING
TO HEAR LYRICS
THAT AREN'T TRYING
TO BE INTELLIGENT.
PETER:
TOTALLY. THANKS.
DECLAN:
SURE BEATS
THE DIPLOMAT'S SCHMOOZEFEST
MY PARENTS ARE THROWING
TOMORROW, ANYWAYS, SO...
MIA:
AND WHO GETS TO SCHMOOZE
AT THIS FEST?
OH, RICH OLD GUYS,
FASHION AND MEDIA TYPES...
ANYONE WHO'S ANYONE.
DOESN'T SOUND SO BAD.
(BELL RINGS)
NO PDA'S IN SCHOOL,
BACKWOODS.
CLARE!
ALLI!
SHOW ME YOUR CLASSES.
THEY'RE ALMOST ALL THE SAME,
EVEN THE NON-GIFTED ELECTIVES!
ALLI:
HERE.
I'M SO GLAD TO BE BACK
AT SCHOOL.
LATER, HOODIE!
PA ANNOUNCMENT:
ATTENTION, DEGRASSI.
IT'S PIZZA DAY IN THE CAF.
TWO DOLLARS
GETS YOU TWO SLICES.
HEY!
WATCH OUT WITH THAT THING!
WHAT, ARE YOU NEW
OR SOMETHING?
JENNA:
SORRY. I'M JENNA.
I'M CLARE. THIS IS ALLI.
WE'RE BFFS.
I'M SO GLAD
ALL THE GIRLS HERE
DON'T HATE EACH OTHER.
MY OLD SCHOOL
WAS "BACKSTAB HIGH."
UH, THAT'S MY SEAT.
MR. SIMPSON:
WELCOME BACK, EVERYBODY!
SIR? SHE'S...
JENNA MIDDLETON!
WELCOME TO DEGRASSI.
TAKE A SEAT, ALLI.
OKAY?
SAV:
DUDE! DID YOU NAIL IT?
ARE YOU PSYCHED?
YOU KNOW I HAD TO BEG
MR. FOWLER
TO GET YOU THAT AUDITION.
PETER:
DUDE, I ROCKED AN ENTIRE
HOLLYWOOD FILM CREW.
IT'S IN THE BAG.
SWEET! NOW WE CAN ALL TAKE STUDZ
TO THE NEXT LEVEL!
WHO KNEW THAT GOING
TO SCHOOL
COULD ACTUALLY HELP YOU
BECOME A ROCK STAR?
MR. FOWLER:
GOOD MORNING,
MASTER MUSICIANS!
I SEE MR. LAVIGNE HAS GIVEN YOU
YOUR HANDOUT PACKAGES...
PETER...
I DIDN'T SEE YOU THERE.
YEAH,
I JUST SORTA SHOWED UP.
DID YOU GET MY EMAIL?
I WAS HOPING TO SEE YOU
AFTER CLASS. I'M...
I'M SORRY, BUT WE DON'T HAVE
A PLACE FOR YOU HERE RIGHT NOW.
WHATEVER. THAT LOSER DOESN'T
KNOW THE FIRST THING
ABOUT MUSIC.
(WHACKS DRUM)
♪ SHINE,
JUST BELIEVE ♪
♪ TOUCH THE SKY... ♪
ALLI:
WHEN DID OUR SCHOOL
BECOME SOME BIZARRE,
WHITE VERSION OF FAME?
CLARE:
PLEASE TELL ME IT HASN'T
BECAUSE I CAN'T DANCE.
OR SING.
NOT LIKE JENNA.
SHE IS SO NICE.
IN CLASS...
TONGUE,
NOBODY IS SUNSHINE
AND RAINBOWS ALL THE TIME.
JENNA:
(SINGS AND PLAYS FINAL NOTES)
STUDENTS:
(SCATTERED APPLAUSE)
AND WE HAVE
OUR FINAL PERFORMER
FOR THE BEACH BASH.
CONGRATS!
THANK YOU SO MUCH,
MS. J.
(EXHALES, ANNOYED)
SO, MS. PRETTY SMILE
AND PERFECT TEETH?
WHAT'S YOUR DEAL?
YOU THINK I'M PRETTY?
THANKS, ALLI!
BUT I'M NOT HALF AS PRETTY
AS YOU.
(SARCASTIC HALF LAUGH)
PA ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION TENNIS TEAM.
PLEASE RETURN ALL UNIFORMS
TO MR. ARMSTRONG TODAY.
THANK YOU.
SO YOU DIDN'T GET IN.
JUST DO REGULAR SCHOOL.
MIA, I'VE LIKE TASTED FAME
OR WHATEVER.
BEING REGULAR SUCKS.
PETER...
PETER, LOOK AT ME.
YOU CAN DO
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
HOW DID I LUCK IN TO DATING
THE MOST AMAZING GIRL
IN THE WORLD?
(FLATTERED BREATH)
REALLY, MIA,
IF I DIDN'T HAVE YOU...?
MAN, I DON'T KNOW...
CAN YOUR MOM BABYSIT LATER?
SHE IS;
I'M MEETING WITH MY AGENT.
SHE'S TRYING TO SET UP
ANOTHER SHOOT.
AGAIN?
HOW MANY SHOOTS DO YOU NEED?
THAT'S JUST THAT IT.
I'VE BEEN TURNING DOWN
A LOT OF JOBS LATELY.
YEAH, WELL, WASN'T THAT
PART OF THE PLAN?
PUT MODELLING
ON THE BACK-BURNER
AND FOCUS ON
THE MORE IMPORTANT STUFF?
IT'S ABOUT PRIORITIES
OR WHATEVER.
SINCE WHEN ARE YOU THE EXPERT
ON PRIORITIES?
THANKS FOR BEING SUPPORTIVE,
PETER.
MIA!
CAN WE STILL HANG OUT
AFTER SCHOOL?
NO.
I'M PICKING UP IZZY.
TROUBLE IN PARADISE?
YEAH, LAUGH IT UP,
NEW GUY.
IT'S NOT AGAINST DEGRASSI RULES
FOR ME TO EAT LUNCH
WITH MY NEW PAL, IS IT?
YOU WANNA BE MY PAL?
GET ME AND MIA
INTO YOUR PARTY.
SHE'D LOVE
TO MEET YOUR MOM.
THE MAKE-UP GESTURE.
WELL DONE, SIR!
WELL, CAN YOU HELP A GUY OUT
OR NO?
WHO'D COMPLAIN ABOUT
HAVING THE LOVELY MIA
IN ATTENDANCE?
SHE'LL WEAR SOMETHING LOW-CUT,
I ASSUME?
WHATEVER SHE WEARS,
KEEP YOUR EYES TO YOURSELF.
ALL RIGHT, SIR?
ALL RIGHT,
SCOUT'S HONOUR.
HERE'S THE INFO.
(BELL RINGS)
PAIR UP.
WE'RE GONNA ANALYZE
THE BACTERIAL COMPONENTS
OF CHEEK SCRAPINGS.
SWABS, PEOPLE!
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
ALLI:
YOU AND JENNA
MAKE GREAT PARTNERS.
(SINGSONG)
HAVE FUN!
OPEN WIDE,
CLARE BEAR!
(EXHALES, TROUBLED)
HI.
PETER:
I THOUGHT YOU HAD A MEETING?
IT TURNED INTO A PHONE CALL.
(DOOR CLOSES)
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
GOOD.
'CAUSE I HAVE A SURPRISE.
I GOT US INTO DECLAN'S
SWANKY PARTY THING.
HE'S INTRODUCE YOU
TO HIS MOM!
OH MY GOD!
THAT'S AMAZING!
I'M SORRY FOR BEING
SUCH A KNOB, BABE.
I'LL BE MORE SUPPORTIVE,
PROMISE.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
HOW GOOD IT MAKES ME FEEL
TO HEAR YOU SAY THAT.
MMM.
WHY?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I HAVE A SURPRISE TOO.
DON'T GET MAD,
BUT YOU ARE LOOKING
AT THE NEW EURO FRESH FACE.
WHAT? WOW! THAT'S...
THOSE GIRLS ARE HOT!
PETER, THIS CONTRACT,
IT'S WORTH $250 GRAND.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
OH... WAIT.
WHY WOULD I BE MAD?
UM...
OKAY.
I HAVE TO MOVE TO PARIS.
PARIS, FRANCE?
WHEN?
SATURDAY.
DON'T WORRY THOUGH.
WE'LL MAKE
THE LONG-DISTANCE THING WORK.
YOU CAN COME VISIT
IN THE SUMMER.
YEAH.
OKAY. SURE.
OKAY, I HAVE TO GO
SIGN SOME STUFF.
THEY'RE GETTING ME
A RUSHED VISA.
BUT, UM... I'LL SEE YOU
TOMORROW AT SCHOOL, OKAY?
MMM.
ALLI:
BREAKFAST BURRITO
FOR MY BESTIE.
SO WE ARE STILL FRIENDS?
WHY WOULDN'T WE BE?
OH, I DON'T KNOW,
SCIENCE CLASS?
LIKE THEY SAY,
"KEEP YOUR FRIENDS CLOSE
AND YOUR ENEMIES CLOSER."
SO JENNA'S OUR ENEMY NOW?
AND BY WORKING
WITH OUR WOLF
IN LITTLE BABY LAMB'S
CLOTHING,
YOU'LL DISCOVER
ALL HER DIRTY LITTLE SECRETS.
JENNA AND STUDENTS:
(GIGGLE AND LAUGH)
YEAH, I BET SHE'S TOTALLY
INTO SATAN.
YOU NEVER KNOW.
(SIGHS)
SIMPSON:
YOU'RE MAKING
ALL THE RIGHT CHOICES.
THIS IS REALLY THE BEST WAY
FOR YOU TO FINISH
YOUR SCHOOL YEAR.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M REALLY PROUD OF YOU.
MIA: THANK YOU SO MUCH.
SIMPSON: GOOD LUCK! OKAY!
(EXCITED SQUEAL)
LOOKS LIKE YOU MADE
SIMPSON'S DAY.
OH, IT'S AWESOME.
HE FOUND ME A TUTOR IN PARIS,
SO I'LL BE ABLE TO FINISH
MY SEMESTER!
SOUNDS LIKE YOU'LL BE
PRETTY BUSY.
YEAH, I MAY HAVE TO MISS
A FASHION PARTY OR TWO,
BUT I'LL MAKE IT WORK.
PETER:
SPEAKING OF SKIPPING PARTIES,
I THINK YOU SHOULD GO
TO DECLAN'S THING TONIGHT
WITHOUT ME.
WHY?
DON'T YOU WANNA GO?
WHAT IS THAT?
IT'S JUST...
IT'S LIKE...
YOUR STUFF.
ARE YOU BREAKING UP
WITH ME?
NO! PETER, COME ON,
DON'T DO THIS!
MIA, YOU'RE GONNA BE
LIKE 5000 MILES AWAY,
SURROUNDED BY GUYS
FALLING IN LOVE WITH YOU.
AND THAT'S EXACTLY
WHY I NEED TO KNOW
THAT YOU'RE GONNA
BE HERE FOR ME.
BOTH:
(SIGH HEAVILY)
WHAT IF I MOVED TO PARIS
WITH YOU?
MIA:
WHAT ABOUT SCHOOL
AND YOUR PARENTS?
I'M EMANCIPATED, REMEMBER?
I STILL HAVE MONEY
FROM THE MOVIE.
I WOULD LOVE TO HAVE
MY BOYFRIEND THERE.
ALLI:
KC! WHERE'S CLARE?
I THOUGHT
SHE WAS WITH YOU.
NO! AND SHE WON'T
TEXT ME BACK!
HM. I JUST GOT ONE,
WISHING ME LUCK
WITH MY PROBATION OFFICER.
NOT THAT I HAVE ONE.
(KC'S PHONE BEEPS)
THIS IS WAY HARDER
THAN IT LOOKS.
THAT'S WHAT HE SAID!
(LAUGHS)
EW! JENNA!
SO, TONIGHT, MORE LESSONS,
OR SCIENCE ASSIGNMENT?
ALLI AND I USUALLY DO
A TV-SLASH-HOMEWORK NIGHT.
FRIENDSHIP PRIORITIES.
COOL.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
COME OVER,
IT'LL BE FUN.
YOU'RE SURE ALLI WON'T MIND?
OF COURSE NOT!
SHE'S NOT THE JEALOUS TYPE.
(CLARE'S PHONE RINGS)
(PHONE BEEPS)
(STRING QUARTET PLAYS
LIGHT JAZZ MUSIC)
(LOW DIN OF CHATTER)
(GASPS IN DISBELIEF)
THIS IS NO HIGH SCHOOL
DANCE.
HEY! THAT'S MY JA...
OH.
SORRY.
SHE JUST TOOK MY COAT!
GET USED TO IT.
IN EUROPE, MODELS GET INVITED
TO THIS KIND OF STUFF
ALL THE TIME.
PETER:
YEAH, MORE PROOF THAT THESE
RICH PEEPS AREN'T DUMB.
SO, NOW WHAT?
WELL,
IT IS A SCHMOOZEFEST...
I WONDER WHICH ONE'S
DECLAN'S MOM?
DECLAN:
SO, UH...
THIS IS OUR HUMBLE ABODE,
FOR THE NEXT SIX MONTHS OR SO.
ONLY SIX MONTHS?
AH... COULD BE MORE,
COULD BE LESS.
DIPLOMAT BRATS DO A LOT
OF BOUNCING AROUND.
HERE.
NEVER HAD RAW OYSTERS?
LOOKS LIKE A LOOGIE.
FI, DON'T YOU JUST LOVE
HOW PAROCHIAL
MIA'S BOYFRIEND IS?
WHAT IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
OH, PAROCHIAL?
UH...
LACKING WORLDLY EXPERIENCE...
BUT NOT IN A BAD WAY.
I LIKE TO SAY
HE KEEPS IT REAL.
LIKE, IN HIS BAND,
HE WRITES HIS OWN SONGS
AND LYRICS.
HMM...
YEAH, WE JUST SPENT
TWO WEEKS IN L.A.
AND THE PARTIES THERE
BLOW THIS SNOOZE-FEST
OUT OF THE WATER.
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU
SHOW EVERYONE
HOW YOU THROW DOWN
CALI-STYLE, THEN?
GET UP THERE!
PLAY THAT "WHOA" SONG.
NO. I DON'T EVEN HAVE
MY AXE.
OH, NO PROBLEM.
HEY, UH, SKIP?
CAN MY FRIEND BORROW
YOUR GUITAR?
SKIP:
SURE!
IT'S ALL YOURS THERE,
SIR.
NO, DECLAN, FORGET IT.
AW, COME ON.
HEY, EVERYONE.
HAVING A GOOD TIME?
GUESTS:
(SCATTERED APPLAUSE)
OKAY, IT'S TIME
TO TURN THIS SNOOZE-FEST
INTO A STUDZ-FEST!
HERE'S THE COOLEST GUY
AT MY NEW HIGH SCHOOL,
PETER...SOMETHING
OR OTHER.
GUESTS:
(POLITE APPLAUSE)
COME ON, SIR.
THEY'RE STARVED
FOR ENTERTAINMENT.
PETER:
HELLO, EVERYBODY.
(STRUMS GUITAR)
(STRUMS CHORDS TO "WHOA")
♪ I'M LIKE "WHOA!" ♪
♪ CALIFORNIA SUN ♪
♪ THIS RIDE HAS JUST BEGUN ♪
♪ I'M LIKE "WHOA!"
IT'S LIKE A... ♪
(LYRICS TRAIL OFF,
AWKWARDLY SINGS PARTIAL LYRICS)
(GUESTS RETURN
TO THEIR CONVERSATIONS)
SURE, WHY NOT?
JENNA:
MY NAILS GET TOTALLY TRASHED
PLAYING GUITAR.
IT'S ONE OF THE USEFUL THINGS
MY OLDER SISTER TAUGHT ME.
JENNA:
AT LEAST YOU HAVE A SISTER.
THREE HALF-BROTHERS
HERE.
OH, HEY!
AM I INTERRUPTING?
HEY, ALLI!
WE WERE JUST...
DOING SOME SCIENCE HOMEWORK,
AND THEN...
ALLI:
YOU ACTUALLY BECAME FRIENDS
WITH HER?
I'M SORRY, CLARE,
BUT THIS ENDS NOW.
SHOULD I GO?
I CAN GO.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
WHY ARE YOU SO AFRAID OF US
HANGING OUT?
I'M NOT. IT'S JUST...
IT'S JUST NOT FAIR
THAT SHE BREEZES INTO SCHOOL
AND STEALS MY BEST FRIEND.
I KNEW SHE'D DO IT
THE MINUTE I SAW HER.
SO I GUESS WHAT I WANT
DOESN'T MATTER?
THANKS, ALLI.
REAL NICE.
ACTUALLY, GUYS,
I'D LOVE TO BE FRIENDS
WITH BOTH OF YOU.
♪ This vibe is so amazing ♪
♪ Play it back,
this song is blazing ♪
PETER:
(EXHALES)
IT WASN'T THAT BAD.
WHATEVER. I SUCKED.
THIS WHOLE PARTY SUCKS.
LET'S JUST GO.
NOBODY CARES ABOUT
YOUR LITTLE PERFORMANCE, PETER.
THAT'S A LIE.
THOSE RICH SNOBS WERE
TRYING NOT TO LAUGH AT ME.
JUST TRY AND BE YOURSELF;
THE CHARMING
AND CONFIDENT GUY I KNOW.
I DON'T FEEL
LIKE THAT GUY.
YOU MUST BE MIA!
PLEASE,
COME MEET SOME PEOPLE.
THAT'S WHAT I'M HERE TO DO.
YOU'RE ALL BUSINESS,
AREN'T YOU?
MIA:
PETER!
WANT SOME COMPANY?
DON'T BOTHER.
YOU'LL JUST END UP
MOVING TO ANOTHER GALAXY,
LIKE ALL MY GIRLFRIENDS.
LUCKY FOR BOTH OF US,
DATING YOU ISN'T IN MY PLANS.
RIGHT.
THE BOYFRIEND.
I THINK HE KNEW I WAS GONNA
MAKE AN ASS OF MYSELF.
UH, THAT WOULD BE
MY BROTHER.
VICTORIA:
COMMON MISTAKE.
FIONA AND DECLAN
ARE VERY CLOSE.
SHUT UP, VICKI.
OH...
SO HE WAS HITTING ON MIA.
MIA AND GUESTS:
(LAUGHING)
WHERE'S MY STUPID
COAT TICKET?
YOU GUYS ARE LEAVING?
I AM.
THIS ISN'T FUN.
HEY,
I CAN'T STAND
THESE PARTIES EITHER,
BUT, UH...
NOW IT'S ALL GOOD.
REALLY, VICTORIA?
YOU'RE STILL DOING THAT?
WELL, WHAT IS THIS?
AN ESCAPE...
WITHOUT LEAVING.
DON'T THINK, SWEETIE.
JUST DO.
HOW DO YOU...?
YOU'LL FIGURE IT OUT.
(STAMMERS) AH...
MAYBE IN THE BATHROOM.
AH.
(LOW DIN OF PARTY CHATTER)
ALLI:
THERE. TO WELCOME YOU
TO DEGRASSI,
AND COMMEMORATE
OUR NEW FRIENDSHIP.
THANKS SO MUCH, GUYS.
IT'S SO HARD COMING
TO A NEW SCHOOL,
IN A NEW CITY,
WHERE YOU DON'T KNOW ANYBODY.
WE NINERS HAVE
TO STICK TOGETHER.
OKAY...
SO, TELL ME,
WHO'S OFF LIMITS?
"OFF LIMITS"?
JENNA:
AT MY OLD SCHOOL,
I WAS SUCH A BOYFRIEND STEALER,
ESPECIALLY WITH BAD-BOY TYPES.
THEY'RE TOTALLY MY WEAKNESS.
UM... I'M WITH JOHNNY.
HE'S A SENIOR.
JENNA:
ENH. TOO OLD FOR ME.
I'M WITH KC.
JENNA:
AW! HE IS SO CUTE!
BUT DON'T WORRY,
CLARE BEAR!
I WON'T EVEN LOOK AT HIM.
(AWKWARD LAUGH)
ALLI:
MM! YOU'RE RIGHT,
JENNA'S SO NICE!
(LOW DIN OF PARTY CHATTER,
MUSIC PLAYS QUIETLY)
MIA:
MM!
I GOT MY GROOVE BACK!
YEAH...
ALL OF A SUDDEN.
YEAH,
I HAD SOME HELP.
YOU'RE LOOKIN' SMOKIN',
BY THE WAY.
YOU WANNA GO FOOL AROUND?
UH, PETER, WHAT HELP?
DARE ME TO EAT
AN OYSTER?
ARE THERE DRUGS
GOING AROUND?
YEAH, I COULD PROBABLY
FIND YOU SOME...
NO, NOT FOR ME,
IT'S PETER.
(SLURPS OYSTER)
PETER:
MIA!
I DID IT!
HE DOES SEEM...
ENTHUSED.
MM-HM.
VICTORIA'S GIVING OUT
PARTY FAVOURS.
HE'S ON CRANK.
WHAT?!
PETER.
DID YOU TAKE SOMETHING
FROM THE VICTORIA?
SOME COKE, I THINK;
JUST A LITTLE.
SHHH!
PETER, COKE WOULD'VE BEEN
BAD ENOUGH,
BUT THAT WAS CRYSTAL METH!
METH?!
CRAZY!
HOW MUCH'LL YOU GIVE ME
IF I EAT THESE FISH EGGS?
WE'RE LEAVING.
COME ON, MIA!
(WARNING)
PETER?
NOW.
UGH...
(VIDEO GAME BUZZES,
PETER MIMICS GUN BLASTING)
VIDEO GAME:
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED!
WORLD DOMINATION!
MORNING, GORGEOUS!
MIA:
UGH! JUNGLE BREATH!
DID YOU SLEEP AT ALL
LAST NIGHT?
NO, BUT I'M THE MASTER
OF "TOXIC CONFLICT."
MIA:
PERFORMANCE ENHANCERS!
AWESOME.
I TOLD YOU,
IT WAS, LIKE, AN ACCIDENT!
RIGHT. YOU THOUGHT THE METH
WAS JUST COKE.
SO MUCH BETTER.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE LUCKY
THAT MY MOM BOUGHT
THE PETER-ATE-BAD-OYSTERS-
SO-I-HAD-TO-STAY-OVER STORY.
PETER:
YEAH, WELL, AT LEAST IT MADE
DECLAN'S SNOBBY PARTY MORE FUN.
I NEEDED SOMETHING.
MIA:
NEWS FLASH!
PETER,
LOTS OF METH ADDICTS
GOT THEIR START
AS "ONE-TIME THINGS."
HEY, WHOA.
I AM NOT A METH ADDICT,
OKAY?
DON'T FREAK OUT,
I'LL BE FINE.
MOVING TO PARIS
DOES FREAK ME OUT.
AND IF YOU'RE GONNA
COME WITH ME,
I NEED YOU TO BE GOOD.
PLEASE?
MIA, I PROMISE.
LET'S JUST GO TO SCHOOL.
(EXHALES)