THIS IS NOT A BIRD COURSE,
PEOPLE.
IT'S A LOT OF HOURS
AND HARD WORK
SO PICK A PRODUCTION
YOU LIKE!
MY COUSIN'S SCHOOL
DID PIPPIN.
OR, OOOH!
HMS PINAFORE!
JANE:
KILL ME NOW... PLEASE.
GUYS,
LET'S BE REAL!
PARENTS ARE COMING.
AT LEAST GIVE 'EM
SOMETHING SEXY,
LIKE CHICAGO.
OH, SEXY CONVICTS.
HIGH SCHOOL KIDS
ARE SUPPOSED TO IDENTIFY?
WELL,
YOU WANT MAMMA MIA?
OOOH!
CONDESCENDING, MUCH?
MAYBE IT TAKES MORE
THAN FIVE MINUTES
TO FIND A SHOW
THAT WORKS FOR EVERYBODY?
MAYBE YOU HAVE A POINT.
MR. LAVIGNE:
GLAD WE SORTED THAT.
ANYONE ELSE?
BIG PASSION
FOR HIGH-SCHOOL DRAMA?
ONSTAGE, KINDA.
OFFSTAGE, NO WAY.
HMM.
TOO BAD FOR ME.
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out
I know I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it,
I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, Woo-ooh ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
J?
JANE:
OH!
(LAUGHS)
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
OH, SORRY.
SPIN, YOU THINK YOU WANNA
MAYBE INVEST
IN SOME MORNING HELP?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHY BUY THE COW WHEN
SHE POURS THE MILK FOR FREE?
OH, AND SMELLS LIKE STALE
COFFEE
FOR HER TROUBLE.
FANTASTIC.
WHOO!
NICE... BEAUTIFUL.
NOW HUG.
(LAUGHS)
WHEN DID YOU TWO BECOME
SO INTIMATE, ANYWAY?
WE HAVE 52 SHARED
FACEBOOK FRIENDS.
AND FIVE COMMON
STALKERS. BLOCKED.
MANNY:
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
LOVE THE WALKING,
HATE THE FREEZING.
I'M ALL CONFLICT-Y.
DON'T THEY LET YOU
OUT IN L.A.?
L.A. SIDEWALKS
ARE FOR HAND-PRINTS ONLY.
BUT I LIKE THE PART
WHERE I ACTUALLY
GET PAID FOR ACTING, SO...
HEY, UM...
IS IT HARD BEING APART
FROM JAY?
(LAUGHS)
REALLY?
'CAUSE SPIN AND I ARE
ATTACHED AT THE HIP 24/7.
AND YOU DON'T WANT
TO KILL HIM YET?
HEY, JANE.
JANE'S FRIEND.
WHOA.
WHO'S JOHNNY EYEBROWS?
WHO DECLAN?
RICH-KID TRANSFER.
HE'S IN MY THEATRE
PRODUCTION CLASS.
WHAT?
IT'S A BIRD COURSE.
I NEEDED AN ARTS CREDIT.
YOU SURE YOU DIDN'T NEED
DECLAN'S UNDRESSING-YOU EYES?
(GROANS)
I THOUGHT MRS. SPINNER MASON
WAS OFF THE MARKET.
SANTOS, I'M ALLOWED
TO SAY HI!
(DISBELIEVING LAUGH)
AND FINALLY, THE CAFETERIA
WAS HALF-EMPTY AT LUNCH
BECAUSE IT'S FRESHMAN
TAKE YOUR KID TO WORK DAY.
ENJOY THE NINER-FREE ZONE
WHILE IT LASTS!
HEY,
I'M SORRY YOU'RE STUCK
HERE TODAY.
HOW YOU FEELING?
ABOUT NOT HAVING
ANY PARENTS AROUND
TO DRAG ME TO WORK?
I DON'T REALLY
FEEL ANYTHING.
BORED, MOSTLY.
WELL, IN THAT CASE,
I HAVE A WHOLE BATCH
OF PHOTOCOPYING
I COULD USE
HELP WITH.
IS IT OKAY
IF I JUST READ TODAY?
YEAH.
WELL, IF YOU GET
MORE BORED,
LET ME KNOW.
PETER:
SO THE TAPS DRIP,
AND YOU REALLY GOTTA
SLAM THE DOOR.
GIVE 'ER.
GOT IT.
YEAH. THANKS FOR TAKING UP
THE LEASE.
I NEVER WANNA SEE
THAT PLACE AGAIN.
NO PROBLEM, DUDE.
ALL RIGHT. LATER.
SEE YA, DUDE.
JANE!
HEY, COME HERE.
SPIN,
WHAT'S GOING ON?
JUST THE BEST NEWS
EVER!
YOU KNOW HOW
PETE DITCHED THE BAND
AND THE LOFT, RIGHT?
SO WE HAVE NOWHERE
TO PRACTICE?
I GUESS.
GO ON...
CHECK THIS OUT:
(KEYS JANGLE)
BOOM!
NOW IT'S MY LOFT.
(LAUGHS)
DECLAN:
JANE AND THE DOT GUY!
WHO KNEW?
UM...SPINNER,
THIS IS DECLAN.
HE'S IN MY THEATRE
PRODUCTION CLASS.
AND ACCORDING
TO YOUR LADY,
I'M CONDESCENDING.
AH! THAT'S JANE -
SWEET AND SUBTLE.
(SMOOCHES)
JANE:
UH, JUST A SEC.
LISTEN,
UH, WE SHOULD WORK
ON A PITCH FOR THE SHOW.
IF, IF YOU WANT,
IF YOU WANT,
I MEAN.
YEAH SURE, I'M IN.
DON'T KEEP THE DOT GUY
WAITING.
(BASKETBALL BOUNCING)
(BOUNCING)
NICE ONE.
LEFT-SIDE, HUH?
YEAH.
I WANNA GET
BOTH SIDES DOWN.
WELL,
LET'S SEE IT AGAIN.
ALL RIGHT, DON'T SECOND-GUESS
YOUR FOOTING.
ARE YOU SOME KIND
OF EXPERT?
THEY CALL ME
COACH CARSON.
I'M HELPING OUT
WITH THE MIDGETS.
YOU'RE ON THE TEAM?
I'M ON THE BENCH.
GRADE NINE.
GRADE NINE?
THE FACT THAT YOU'RE OUT
HERE MEANS-
I HAVE NO PARENTS
TO BUG AT WORK.
MORE TIME TO PRACTICE,
RIGHT?
GET YOU OFF
THAT BENCH
AND INTO
THE STARTING FIVE?
(SCOFFS)
AS IF THAT WOULD HAPPEN.
MAYBE.
LET'S SEE
A MIKAN DRILL.
(POLICE SIRENS WAILING)
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
MMM. BAD-ASS!
ALL RIGHT,
(LANDS WITH A THUD)
STEREO: PRECIOUS.
EVERYTHING ELSE? GO NUTS.
UNPACK YOUR BRAINS OUT.
HEY,
WIRELESS STILL WORKS!
NO-HOMEWORK ZONE,
VAUGHN.
UM, THIS HOMEWORK
IS IMPORTANT?
SPINNER:
A PARTY?
MY FIRST NIGHT!?
JANE:
WE GOTTA KICK IT OFF RIGHT, NO?
SO...I SHOULD PROBABLY
TEACH YOU THE NEW TUNE.
UNLESS YOU WANNA HUM.
I WAS TALKING
TO THE GUYS,
WE NEED
A NEW LEAD SINGER.
WE WANT YOU TO BE
THE NEWEST STUD.
WOW!
WAIT, WAIT-
BUT, SPIN,
BEING IN A BAND TOGETHER?
THAT'S PRETTY INTENSE.
WHAT?
YEAH.
NOOOO!
DON'T BE SO NEGATORY!
YOU HANG OUT WITH US
ALL THE TIME,
YOU'RE PRACTICALLY A DUDE,
IT'S PERFECT!
YOU...
...ARE THE BEST.
YEAH. I'M IN.
YES!
SWEET!
I'LL TELL THEM.
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
♪♪♪♪♪
HEY.
SEE, BABE?
YOU COME INTO TOWN
AND I DELIVER A PARTY.
THAT IS THE JAY HOGART
GUARANTEE.
HEY, DON'T BE STEALING
JANE'S LIGHTENING, OKAY.
THIS WHOLE PARTY
WAS HER IDEA!
(SELF-EFFACING CHUCKLE)
IT'S THUNDER!
(LAUGHING)
LOOK WHO HAPPENED
TO STOP BY!
SHUT UP!
OH, HEY.
HEY!
GOT THE E-VITE,
WAS IN THE AREA.
OH, I'M GLAD
IT WAS CONVENIENT.
DANNY:
JANE, LET'S GO!
YOU'RE UP!
WHAT ARE YOU,
THE STUDZ ROADIE, NOW?
NOT QUITE.
♪♪♪♪♪
JANE:
♪ I SLAM AROUND AND WASTE AWAY
WAITING FOR YOU ♪
♪ I'M STARIN' AT THE CEILING
LIKE I LIVE IN A ZOO ♪
♪ GOOD TIMES
GOOD TIMES ♪
♪ GOOD TIMES ♪
WHOO!
JANE:
♪ NO TIME TO WASTE ♪
♪ NO TIME TO WASTE
GOOD TIMES ♪
♪ COME ON,
DON'T STAND AROUND ♪
♪ MAKE A MOVE ♪
♪ I'M STARING AT THE CEILIN'
I GOT NOTHIN' TO DO ♪
♪ IT'S ALL GOOD TIMES
GOOD TIMES ♪
♪ GOOD TIMES
♪ NO TIME TO WASTE ♪
(MUSIC FADES, MELLOWS)
SPINNER:
WHAT'D YOU GUYS THINK?
SO WHAT'D YOU THINK?
YOU GUYS ARE
IN THE ZONE.
AND THE STUDZ ALWAYS HAVE
THOSE RAW LYRICS.
YEAH. NO HIDING THOSE
TEEN-BOY EMOTIONS.
RAGE AND HORMONES.
SEE NOW,
THAT'S OUR SHOW.
YEAH! TAKE SONGS
FROM DEGRASSI BANDS,
AND THEE LYRICS ARE,
LIKE, THE SCRIPT!
DO YOU THINK
THEY'LL GO FOR IT?
HMM. MAYBE.
YOU THINK YOUR
BOYFRIEND NOTICED
WHO YOU WERE
SINGING TO?
YOU SEE
WHAT YOU WANT TO SEE.
THAT WAS WHAT
I WANTED TO SEE.
AND I HAD
A GREAT VIEW.
THINK DOT MAN WOULD MIND
IF I WALKED YOU HOME?
SAW THE VIEW
IN THE DARK?
UH...
GOODNIGHT, DECLAN.
SWEET DREAMS.
SPINNER, MANNY:
OKAY. 'BYE.
SPINNER:
OKAY.
MANNY:
HEY, THANKS FOR HAVING US.
SPINNER:
YEAH. THANKS FOR COMING.
GUYS, GO!
GO.
GOOD JOB, JANE.
THANKS.
GIRL:
THANKS. ENJOYED THE SHOW.
SEE YOU.
GOOD NIGHT,
GOOD NIGHT.
THANKS FOR COMING!
(BANGS DOOR CLOSED)
(SIGHS)
YOU TOOK STUDZ TO A WHOLE
'NUTHER LEVEL TONIGHT!
THANKS.
IT WAS A RUSH.
I HAVE SOMETHING
TO SHOW YOU, OKAY?
OKAY.
IKEA'S FINEST?
I DON'T GET IT.
IT'S A DRAWER.
YOUR DRAWER.
I WANT YOU
TO MOVE IN WITH ME.
SPIN, WHA-
WHERE'S THIS
COMING FROM?
FROM MY HEAD!
LOOK,
WE BOTH KNOW I'M NOT GOIN'
TO COP COLLEGE ANYMORE.
THAT WAS A BEFORE-YOU
THING.
THIS?
THIS IS MY LIFE NOW.
WE'RE, WE'RE YOUNG,
THOUGH.
I, I THOUGHT WE AGREED
NOT TO RUSH THIS STUFF?
(SIGHS) IT'S -
IT'S NOT RUSHING IT'S-
IT'S KNOWING, JANE.
TONIGHT YOU AND I
KICKED ASS. TOGETHER.
I-
I'VE GOT UNIVERSITY.
MAYBE FAR AWAY.
BUT OUR HOME
WILL BE HERE.
I-I NEED SOME TIME
TO THINK.
I'M-
I'M SORRY.
I'M, I'M GONNA GO.
JANE. NEVER-
(SOBS)
JANE:
MOST BANDS SING ABOUT STUFF
WE ALL THINK ABOUT ANYWAY.
DECLAN:
SO JANE SAID,
LET'S MAKE THOSE LYRICS
THE ACTUAL STORY-LINE.
IN SHORT,
IT'S A ROCK OPERA.
WRITTEN BY
DEGRASSI BANDS.
PRODUCED BY US.
UH, YEAH GUYS.
THAT'S WICKED!
MR. LAVIGNE:
REALLY INNOVATIVE.
ORIGINAL MUSIC,
TELLING YOUR OWN STORIES,
YOUR WAY.
I THINK WE'VE FOUND OUR SHOW!
HMM?
(ENTHUSIASTIC APPLAUSE,
CHATTER)
MR. LAVIGNE:
I WILL NEED TO ASSIGN
POSITIONS. UM...
OUR PRODUCERS
ARE JANE AND DECLAN.
CONGRATULATIONS.
FOR THE REST OF YOU,
PLEASE WRITE OUT
THE TOP THREE POSITIONS
YOU'RE MOST INTERESTED IN.
AND SUBMIT THEM TO ME.
I'D ALSO LIKE A COUPLE
OF SENTENCES
ACCOMPANYING EACH POSITION
ENLIGHTENING ME-
JANE:
I'M GETTING MIXED SIGNALS.
WAIT, BACK UP!
WHO ARE WE
TALKING ABOUT?
THE BOYFRIEND
OR THE FLIRT?
SORRY. DECLAN.
MR. HOT AND COLD.
MMM. CLASSIC MOVE.
MAKES YOU PAY ATTENTION!
HE'LL BE BACK
FOR MORE.
THANK YOU!
I SO NEED THE GIRL-
TRANSLATION OF THIS STUFF!
I HAD SERIOUS FAMILY
STUFF THIS YEAR AND,
SPIN WAS SO GOOD.
YEAH, BUT WHEN WAS
THE LAST TIME
HE MADE
YOUR STOMACH FLIP?
REPETITION.
YOU'RE NERVOUS.
CONNOR, WE HAVE A GAME,
REMEMBER?
THE GRADE TENS
HAVE A GAME.
WE SIT ON THE BENCH
AND WAIT
UNTIL ONE OF THEM
GETS HURT.
SOME OF US WANT
TO MAKE AN IMPRESSION.
(BANGING LOUDLY)
JASON:
I LIKE THAT!
YOU GUYS YOU LOOK LIKE WINNERS.
DO YOU FEEL LIKE WINNERS?
BOYS:
(SHOUTING) YEAH, COACH!
JASON:
OKAY, LET'S DO THIS!
I GOT FIVE GUYS
WHO ARE GOING TO LEAD:
ELLIOT, NICK, SHAWAUGHN,
ETHAN AND ZACK.
THE REST OF YOU GUYS
BE READY.
LETS GO!
CONNOR:
I GUESS I'LL SAVE YOU A SEAT.
(HIGH-FIVING)
JANE!
(INDISTINCT VOICE OVER PA)
HANG ON,
I WANNA TALK!
OH,
IT MUST BE 3:30.
TIME FOR YOU TO SAY
SOMETHING CRYPTIC?
WHOA, IS THIS ABOUT
THIS MORNING?
LOOK, NOTHING HAPPENED
THIS MORNING, OKAY?
MY FOOT
HAD A SPASM.
GIMME A BREAK.
YOU KNOW I THINK
YOU'RE SMART,
AND DAMN CUTE.
BUT YOU'RE TAKEN,
SO...
I'LL TRY NOT TO MAKE IT
HARD ON YOU.
LISTEN,
WHY DON'T YOU
COME OVER TONIGHT?
WE'VE GOT A BIG
MUSIC ROOM,
WE'LL FOCUS
ON THE SHOW.
STRICTLY AS FRIENDS,
RIGHT?
FRIENDS, PEERS,
COLLABORATORS.
CALL IT WHAT YOU WANT.
WELL, WE'RE MATURE PEOPLE.
NO REASON WE CAN'T BE
ALONE IN A ROOM.
(LAUGHING)
RIGHT?
YEAH.
(LAUGHS)
PLAYER:
PASS HERE!
THOSE YOUR PARENTS
OR SOMETHING?
YEAH.
IF I EVER GET
A CHANCE TO PLAY
THEY'LL BUY ME
A SOLID GOLD FERRARI.
PLAYER:
OVER HERE!
PLAYER 2:
OKAY, LET'S GO. LET'S GO!
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
GUTHRIE! YOU'RE IN!
ALL RIGHT,
SET YOUR SCREENS.
FIND THE OPEN MAN.
SHOW ME WHAT YOU GOT.
GO. GO, GO.
PLAYER:
OKAY, COME ON.
♪♪♪♪♪
(TAKES DEEP BREATH, SIGHS)
JASON:
COME ON, GUTHRIE!
HEAD IN THE GAME!
REBOUND! REBOUND!
(BOARD BUZZER SOUNDS)
PLAYER:
OVER HERE! OVER HERE!
2-2!
JASON:
COME ON, WATCH IT!
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(BOARD BUZZER SOUNDS)
REFEREE:
FOUL!
1-1, BLUE.
SUB! ZACK!
GUTHRIE, TAKE A SEAT.
COACH, DON'T-
I CAN DO IT!
ENOUGH!
I'LL TALK TO YOU LATER.
COACH, I'M SORRY.
SIT DOWN.
I GET IT.
I SUCK!
(DOOR BELLS CHIME)
JANE.
YOU NEED A BURGER?
WHAT'S UP?
SOME AWESOMENESS.
DEGRASSI CHOSE OUR
ROCK OPERA IDEA
TO BE THE SHOW!
THAT'S GREAT.
YOU CAME ALL THE WAY HERE
TO TELL ME THAT?
WHY, DO I HAVE TO
ANNOUNCE MYSELF
OR SOMETHING?
AM I IN YOUR WAY?
JANE,
ARE WE FIGHTING?
NO.
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
I'M GOING TO DECLAN'S TONIGHT
TO DO SOME WORK FOR THE SHOW.
UNLESS, UNLESS YOU
HAVE STUFF HERE
YOU NEED HELP WITH?
I MEAN, I COULD STAY.
NO.
NO, NO, NO.
GO DO YOUR HOMEWORK.
I HAFTA CLEAN
THE GREASE TRAPS, AND....
REALLY?
YOU DO?
OKAY.
YEAH.
LISTEN UM...
ABOUT YESTERDAY?
THE MOVING IN THING?
THERE'S NO PRESSURE,
OKAY?
I'LL CALL YOU LATER.
OKAY.
(SMOOCHES)
BYE, SPIN.
(BANGING LOUDLY)
(LANDS WITH A THUD)
THE COACH WANTS YOU
BACK OUT THERE.
YEAH?
ON THE BENCH?!
WHY YOU SO MAD?
WE'RE WINNING!
HE PUT ME IN, CONNOR,
AND I SCREWED IT UP!
MASSIVELY.
HE TOLD ME TO GET YOU
SO I'M GETTING YOU.
COME ON.
LET'S GO.
WHY, SO HE CAN
YELL AT ME AGAIN?
SO WHAT?
COACHES YELL.
MY DAD
USED TO YELL AT ME.
I'M DONE WITH BASKETBALL.
WHAT?
WE HAVE PLAYOFFS!
FORGET IT!
I'M DONE!
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
DECLAN:
HERE'S THE REST OF THE HOUSE,
I GUESS.
AUSTRALIA.
UH, TANZANIA.
AND UH... OH!
WELL, HELLO PUBERTY,
I'M JUST FEEDING
A GIRAFFE, RIGHT NOW.
AMATEUR.
MY PICS BACK THEN?
SCABBY KNEES, BRAIDS,
THE END.
WHY DO GIRLS
HAVE THIS IDEA
THAT TOMBOYS
AREN'T HOT?
IT'S SO ODD.
SPEAKING OF ODD,
IT'S BEEN TWO HOURS
AND WE HAVEN'T DONE
ANY WORK YET.
GOOD POINT.
UM... HERE...
MY BEDROOM HAS
A HUGE KEYBOARD IN IT.
YOU'RE NOT EXACTLY
SUBTLE, ARE YOU?
SO THERE'S VIBES
HERE, RIGHT?
WELL, CAN VIBE
WITH A LOT OF PEOPLE BUT...
IT DOESN'T HAVE
TO MEAN ANYTHING.
THEN WHY AREN'T WE
AT THE LIBRARY
INSTEAD OF YOUR BIG
EMPTY HOUSE?
BECAUSE...
IN EXACTLY FIVE SECONDS
I'M GONNA KISS YOU.
FIVE...
FOUR...
THREE-
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
RETURNING TO THE SCENE
OF THE CRIME, HUH?
SORRY ABOUT THE MESS.
LOOK, SON.
I KNOW YOUR SITUATION.
GROUP HOME LIFE'S
GOTTA BE TOUGH.
BUT I'M NOT LETTING YOU
GET AWAY FROM ME
THAT EASILY.
EVEN AFTER I ALMOST
BLEW THE GAME?
LOOK, IT'S NOT
ABOUT THE GAME.
IT'S ABOUT
THE WHOLE SEASON.
AND MY ROLE IS
TO BRING OUT THE BEST
IN MY PLAYERS.
ON AND OFF THE COURT.
WE'RE IN THIS TOGETHER,
GOT IT?
EXCEPT FOR CLEANING UP
THE LOCKER ROOM.
THAT'S ALL YOU.
AND HEY, IF YOU
EVER DO WANT TO TALK TO ME,
BASKETBALL OR NOT,
YOU LET ME KNOW.
FOR SURE, COACH.
OKAY.
THANKS.
NOW, CLEAN IT UP.
MANNY:
SANTOS SCHOOL OF BREAKUPS.
ONE, DO IT FAST.
RIP THE BAND-AID.
TWO, DON'T MENTION
THE OTHER MAN.
AND THREE, NO HUGGING.
IT GETS MESSY.
I'M GONNA BE SICK.
COMMON SIDE EFFECT.
BUT IT'LL BE OKAY,
JANE.
PROMISE?
OKAY.
THANKS.
(POLICE SIREN WAILS)
MORNING, SUNSHINE.
SPIN,
WE HAVE TO TALK.
I JUST UM...
I THINK THAT-
NO.
LOOK, IF YOU'RE GOING
TO DO THIS,
DO IT QUICK, OKAY?
BUT REMEMBER
I LOVE YOU.
WHATEVER IT IS,
I CAN FIX IT.
I CAN'T...
I CAN'T MOVE IN.
A TOOTHBRUSH,
SWEATER MAYBE.
BUT I- IT'S JUST NOT
THE RIGHT TIME FOR ME,
AND I THINK-
DUDE,
I WAS SWEATING!
DO HAVE ANY IDEA WHAT
I THOUGHT YOU WERE GONNA SAY?
ARE YOU KIDDING?
DON'T BE CRAZY!
AWW, THE LOVEBIRDS.
JANE, WE UH,
DOWN FOR HOMEWORK?
TONIGHT? UM...
ABSOLUTELY.