RILEY:
PLANNING A QUICK GETAWAY?
YEAH, I GOTTA STOP
THE FRENCH GUYS
FROM MACKIN'
ON MY GIRL,
SO I'M GOING WITH HER.
YEAH, RIGHT.
WHAT'RE YOU GONNA DO IN PARIS?
PLAY MY AXE,
UH, EAT CRESCENT ROLLS,
MAYBE I'LL GO
TO FRENCH SCHOOL.
AND LEARN THE FRENCH WORD
FOR "CRESCENT ROLLS"?
DECLAN:
UGH! WI-FI HERE BLOWS.
PETER!
THIS GUY SURE MADE HIS MARK
AT OUR LITTLE DO YESTERDAY.
HAVEN'T SEEN ANYBODY SLURP
THAT MANY OYSTERS
SINCE MARDI GRAS.
YEAH, LAST NIGHT WAS FUN,
BUT RIGHT NOW,
NOT SO MUCH.
OH YEAH, THE CRASH.
METH'LL DO THAT.
METH?
IT WAS A MISTAKE.
IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
DECLAN, DO YOU EVER...?
OH, NO, SIR.
I COME BY CONFIDENCE
NATURALLY.
VICTORIA'S THE ONE
WITH THE PHARMACY IN HER PURSE.
YOU TWO DIDN'T...
YOU KNOW...?
NO. NO, NO, NO.
I'M WITH MIA!
AH, WELL, YOU DODGED
AN STI BULLET THERE, SIR.
MY COUSIN VICKI
WAS A BALLERINA.
NOW SHE JUST TWEAKS OUT
AND HOOKS UP WITH RANDOM GUYS.
IT'S A SHAME REALLY.
THIS COULD BE YOU
IN SIX MONTHS.
BAM!
(MOUSE CLICKS,
COMPUTER BEEPS)
DECLAN:
DON'T LOSE THAT PRETTY SMILE.
UH... ARE YOU OKAY?
DUDE, IF YOU KNOW
HOW I FELT RIGHT NOW...
NEVER GONNA DO IT AGAIN.
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out
I know I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it,
I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, Woo-ooh ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
KWAN:
HENRY HIGGINS MOLDS
ELIZA DOOLITTLE
INTO A SOPHISTICATED
UPPER CLASS WOMAN,
USING DIALOGUE
AND ETIQUETTE.
PSSST!
I MADE YOU SOMETHING.
KWAN:
...TOOK THE TITLE FROM THE MYTH
"PYGMALION AND GALATEA,"
A POPULAR SUBJECT OF SATIRE
AT THE TIME.
PYGMALION SPEAKS
TO THE NOTIONS OF CLASS,
POVERTY AND EDUCATION.
ANYA:
"SUPERHOLLY."
WHERE'S THE J?
OH.
BLUE JUST CALLS ME HOLLY.
I THOUGHT YOU HATED THAT.
KWAN:
...VULNERABILITY TO CHANGE
INTO SOMEONE ELSE.
NOW, IN THE CASE
OF ELIZA DOOLITTLE...
(WHISPERS)
THIS IS AMAZING, BLUE.
THANKS.
KWAN:
AND SHE'S NOT REALLY
INTERESTED IN...
SHEP:
SO, MRS. JONES,
WE'LL BE SEEING YOUR DAUGHTER
ON BILLBOARDS, HUH?
ANNA:
I AM VERY PROUD OF HER.
BUT SCHOOL COMES FIRST,
RIGHT?
YEAH, MOM, THAT'S WHY
THEY HAVE A TUTOR.
HI, MRS. JONES.
HEY, CUTIE.
PETER, YOU LOOK SICK!
YEAH, I GOTTA LAY OFF
THE SEAFOOD.
ANNA:
UH, WE'LL PACK TONIGHT
AFTER YOUR SHOOT?
FOR SURE.
BYE, MOM.
ANNA:
OKAY.
BYE, BELLS.
MUAH!
CONGRATS.
THANK YOU.
WHAT'S THAT?
TRANSCRIPT REQUEST.
MM, WOW.
HOW VERY OFFICIAL OF YOU.
I ALSO GOT THIS RUSH
PASSPORT THINGY ONLINE,
SO I'LL PROBABLY BE ABLE
TO BE THERE
BY, LIKE, TUESDAY.
SO YOU'LL HELP ME
MOVE IN!
THINK ABOUT IT,
WE'RE GONNA HAVE LIKE
FIVE MONTHS OF "US" TIME,
BEFORE YOUR MOM
AND IZZY COME.
YOU KNOW,
IF YOU KEEP THIS UP,
I MIGHT EVEN LET YOU MOOCH
MY TUTOR.
OOH LA LA!
BYE.
(SIGHS)
HOLLY J:
WHERE AM I SUPPOSED TO FIND
50 BAGS OF SAND,
PALM TREES
AND A STRAW HUT?
HEY, ARE WE GETTIN'
A HOT TUB?
THAT'D BE KILLER!
IMPOSSIBLE.
BUMMER.
WE STILL GETTIN' TACOS?
YEAH!
IMPOSSIBLE?
OKAY,
MAYBE NOT IMPOSSIBLE,
BUT I HAVE A SHIFT
AT THE DOT,
WHICH LEAVES LIKE TWO HOURS
TO TURN THE DEGRASSI GYM
INTO SANTA MONICA PIER.
WATCH THIS.
WHO WANTS TO HELP HOLLY
SET UP THE BEACH BASH?
(STUDENTS MURMUR "NO")
THERE'LL BE HOT TUBS!
(STUDENTS CHEER
AND APPLAUD)
BLUE:
SEE? YOU HAVE FANS.
SINCE THE INCIDENT,
PEOPLE KNOW
YOU'RE A CHANGED WOMAN.
SO BEING TAKEN HOSTAGE
WAS A GOOD THING?
SOMETIMES BAD SITUATIONS
ALLOW A PERSON'S INNER LIGHT
TO SHINE.
COME ON,
YOU CAN DO THIS!
WELL, I GUESS NOW
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO.
SAV:
HEY, WE GONNA PRACTICE
AT YOUR PLACE?
PETER:
OH, I CAN'T.
I HAVE PLANS TONIGHT.
SAV:
COME ON, DUDE!
IT COULD BE THE LAST TIME
WE PLAY DEGRASSI
BEFORE STUDZ TAKES OFF!
I WANT US TO BE TIGHT.
COULD BE THE LAST TIME
WE PLAY ANYWHERE.
I'M MOVING TO PARIS
WITH MIA.
YOU'RE GONNA DITCH
THE BAND?
I'M NOT GONNA LET
ANOTHER ONE SLIP AWAY.
IMAGINE IF ANYA
WAS LEAVING.
WOW.
SO YOU'RE MOVING TO FRANCE.
I'D BE SO FREAKED OUT!
HOW DO YOU EVEN, LIKE,
ASK FOR DIRECTIONS?
I DON'T KNOW,
HAND SIGNALS?
IT'LL BE FINE.
ARE YOU SURE?
I MEAN, MIA'S GONNA BE BUSY.
MAN, I COULD NEVER DATE
A MODEL.
IF ANYA WAS HALF-NAKED
IN ALL THESE MAGAZINES...
SAV, SHUT UP, MAN!
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
GUESS NOT.
SO, I GUESS...
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO FIND
A NEW SINGER, HUH?
DUDE, THERE'S NO STUDZ
WITHOUT ME.
THOSE SONGS ARE MINE.
THEY TEACH YOU ABOUT THAT
IN COPYRIGHT CLASS.
AH... WHATEVER.
IF TOMORROW'S
OUR LAST SHOW,
WE'D BETTER ROCK IT.
ROCK IT WE SHALL.
OKAY...
BINCE:
DEHYDRATION OF ALKENES...
GRAB YOUR APPARATUS,
COME SEE ME
FOR CHEMICALS.
("WHOA" BY STUDZ PLAYS)
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ I'm like "Whoa!"
The California sun ♪
This ride has just begun ♪
♪ I'm like "Whoa!"
Just like a submachine gun ♪
♪ With our guitars
and all our girls ♪
♪ Hey-Cali-hey-fornia-i-a ♪
OH MY GOD!
LOOK AT ALL THESE PEOPLE!
TOLD YA.
YOU'VE GOT FANS.
HOLLY TO THE J!
WHAT UP, PREZ?
I'M SORRY, YOU ARE?
DAVE?
FUTURE GRADE NINE CLASS REP.
FUTURE REP?
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU?
OKAY, I WAS THINKING,
WE NEED A TOGA DAY NEXT WEEK.
FOR FUN.
I'LL LOOK INTO IT?
(HUFFS)
BLUE:
DON'T WORRY.
SHE'LL MAKE IT HAPPEN.
DAVE:
UH HUH.
TOGA! TOGA!
TOGA DAY?
SERIOUSLY.
UH, I'VE HEARD
WORSE IDEAS.
ALL RIGHT!
TOGA... DAY.
HAPPY?
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ It's hot ♪
♪ I'm cranking up
the heat again... ♪
HEY, MIA,
WHERE'S THE SPARKLE?
ON NE VEND PAS L'ASSURANCE-VIE,
ON VEND LA MODE!
MIA! BREAK TIME!
UH...
DESOLEE. UN MOMENT,
S'IL VOUS PLAIT.
I'M SORRY, HON.
WE'RE RUNNING LATE.
I DON'T KNOW IF I'LL HAVE
A BREAK.
PETER:
WHOA!
(LIGHT BULB SHATTERS)
CREW MEMBER:
WHOA! HEY!
PETER:
HEY, SHOW SOME RESPECT
OR WHATEVER, DUDE!
RESET!
GET THIS KID AWAY!
I'M SORRY.
IT WAS JUST AN ACCIDENT.
THIS IS THE BOYFRIEND?
SERIOUSLY?
YEAH, AND SHE'S ON BREAK,
ALL RIGHT?
UH, CAREFUL, MY HAIR.
LOOK, MAYBE YOU SHOULD
JUST GO.
JEAN LUC:
LISTEN TO YOUR GIRLFRIEND,
GARCON.
WE BOTH KNOW THAT SHE CAN DO
A LOT BETTER.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE,
GUY.
SECURITY!
SECURITY GUARD:
OKAY, BIG GUY.
DON'T MAKE THIS HARD
ON YOURSELF.
PETER:
NO, LET GO OF ME, MAN!
M-MIA!
JEAN LUC:
LA MODE!
(GIVES COMMANDS TO MIA
AND MALE MODEL)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS LOUDLY)
MIA:
PETER?
PETER!
(MUSIC STOPS ABRUPTLY)
MIA:
HEY.
SORRY ABOUT JEAN-LUC.
PHOTO SHOOTS CAN GET...
REALLY TENSE SOMETIMES.
OH, WELL, THEN,
LET'S JUST STAY HERE.
WE CAN STILL GO TO SCHOOL,
WE CAN HANG WITH OUR FRIENDS,
I CAN STILL PLAY IN MY BAND.
IT'LL BE GOOD TIMES.
LOOK, DON'T WORRY,
OKAY? I...
WAIT, YOU HAVEN'T EVEN
STARTED PACKING YET?
YOU'RE SERIOUS?
OH, COME ON, MIA.
THIS WHOLE MODELLING THING
MAKES YOU CRAZY.
MIA:
(SCOFFS)
I'M CRAZY?
LOOK,
IT'S NOT UP FOR DEBATE.
HOW COME YOU GET TO DECIDE
WHAT HAPPENS, HUH?
WHAT ABOUT ME?
PETER, CALM DOWN.
NO.
YOU'RE SO SELFISH, MIA!
IT'S ALL ABOUT YOU,
YOU, YOU.
OH MY GOD!
IS THIS IT?
PETER, YOU PROMISED ME
THAT WOULD NEVER DO THIS AGAIN,
THIS MORNING!
MY OWN GIRLFRIEND
WATCHES ME GET DRAGGED OFF
HER STUPID PHOTO SHOOT.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO,
HUH?
YOUR DRUG USE
IS NOT MY FAULT.
YEAH?
WHAT ABOUT BEING SUPPORTIVE?
WHAT, OF A METH-HEAD?
YOU ARE NOT GOING
ANYWHERE WITH ME.
OKAY?
GET SOME HELP, PETER.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
PETER:
COOL!
HEY.
OH, SAV,
CHECK IT OUT!
THE SIDEWALK MAKES
A DIFFERENT SOUND
THAN THE STREET!
THAT'S GREAT, PETE.
OH, COME TO MY HOUSE!
WE GOTTA JAM!
NOW?
YEAH!
I WROTE A SWEET
NEW SONG!
WE GOTTA JAM IT OUT!
WHY, I THOUGHT
YOU WERE GOING AWAY?
WELL...
MIA BROKE UP WITH ME.
BUT IT'S ALL RIGHT
'CAUSE THEY ALWAYS DO, RIGHT?
BUT... COME ON,
STUDZ LIVES, MAN!
ARE YOU OKAY, MAN?
NO! CRAP!
I FORGOT MY GUITAR.
HOLLY J:
ALL RIGHT,
SEE YOU THERE.
DON'T FORGET TO WEAR
YOUR BEACH CLOTHES.
CONNOR:
WE HEARD YOU'RE TAKING
REQUESTS.
OKAY,
'CAUSE WE HAVE A REQUEST.
WE WERE WONDERING IF ATHLETES
COULD CUT THE CAF LINE,
SO WE CAN MAKE IT TO PRACTICE
AT LUNCHTIME.
WE'RE ON THE JUNIOR
BASKETBALL TEAM.
WE'RE ATHLETES.
I'LL ADD IT TO THE LIST.
I'M A WALKING
SUGGESTION BOX!
AND THE IDEA THAT ANY RANDOM
NINER CAN COME HASSLE ME,
SO NOT MY STYLE.
(SIGHS)
YOU'RE NEVER
GONNA BE HAPPY.
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
EVERYONE USED TO HATE YOU.
NOW, YOU'VE GOT BLUE,
YOU'RE SUPER-POPULAR...
WHERE'S THE PROBLEM?
SAV:
HE'S LIKE, "SHE'S GONE,
THEY ALL LEAVE ME,"
AND THEN HE TOOK OFF.
SERIOUSLY, HUH?
MIA DUMPED HIM?
SUPER-HARSH.
THAT'LL MESS A GUY UP.
DON'T TELL ME
MR. AND MRS. HIGH SCHOOL
ARE ON THE ROCKS!
MIA SMASHED HIS HEART
INTO A MILLION PIECES.
HE WAS FREAKING OUT,
LIKE...
HE WASN'T HIMSELF
OR SOMETHING.
UH, YOU SURE
IT WASN'T THE CRANK?
WHAT?!
DECLAN:
GUYS, YOUR LEAD SINGER'S
TAKEN A FANCY TO CRYSTAL METH.
HE MADE A PRETTY BIG ASS
OF HIMSELF AT OUR PARTY.
IT WASN'T PRETTY.
OKAY,
YOU BETTER CALL HIM.
YEAH.
(PHONE KEYS BEEP)
(PETER'S PHONE RINGS)
(PHONE CLATTERS ON FLOOR)
(GUITAR PLAYS)
JENNA:
♪ SINGING OUT LOUD,
LAUGHING OUT LOUD ♪
♪ IN THE BACKSEAT ♪
♪ EVERYBODY KNOWS THE WORDS ♪
♪ CLAPPING HANDS,
SWINGIN' HIPS ♪
♪ SHAKIN' IT
TO THEIR OWN BEAT ♪
♪ LISTEN TO THE MUSIC ♪
♪ HEAR THE MELODY,
FOLLOW THE BEAT ♪
♪ DA-DA DA DA ♪
♪ THAT'S HOW IT GOES, NOW ♪
♪ IT'S CONFUSIN' AND AMUSIN' ♪
♪ BUT IT'S MOVIN'
THE RHYTHM IS ALL AROUND ♪
♪ ON AND ON ♪
♪ JUMPIN' UP AND DO-O-OWN ♪
♪ SHINE, JUST BELIEVE ♪
♪ TOUCH THE SKY ♪
♪ OPEN YOUR HEART
AND TAKE IT ALL IN ♪
♪ SHINE, DREAM A DREAM... ♪
(SONG BECOMES MUFFLED)
PEOPLE LOVE THE HOT TUBS.
I KNEW YOU COULD DO IT!
YAY ME.
I'M SO READY FOR A NAP.
ANYA:
HERE, I BROUGHT YOU
SOME SNACKS.
THANK YOU!
I HAVEN'T EATEN ALL DAY.
IS THAT AVOCADO?
I'D LIKE TO FILE
A COMPLAINT.
YOU ALREADY HAVE YOUR
FRONT-OF-THE-LINE PRIVILEGES,
NOW WHAT?
BRUCE CUT THE LUNCH LINE,
AND FOOTBALL SEASON'S OVER!
SO? WHAT AM I,
THE CAF POLICE?
HEY, UH, SO WHEN EXACTLY
IS TOGA DAY?
MONDAY? WEDNESDAY?
NOT NOW, DARRYL, OKAY?
IT'S, IT'S DAVE.
CLARE:
HEY, HOLLY J?
UM, THERE'S THIS REALLY
WEIRD SMELL
COMING FROM
THE GIRLS' BATHROOM.
MAYBE BECAUSE
IT'S A BATHROOM?
WHAT'S NEXT?
IS THE SUN TOO BRIGHT?
YOUR ALLOWANCE TOO SMALL?
HEY, WHY DON'T I JUST DO
SOMETHING ABOUT GLOBAL WARMING
WHILE I'M AT IT!
SORRY.
UH, SHE'LL GET ON THAT.
YOU'RE REALLY HAVING TROUBLE
PRIORITIZING, HUH?
ACTUALLY, BLUE, I KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT MY PRIORITY IS RIGHT NOW:
THIS TACO.
GOT IT?
(JENNA FINISHES PLAYING,
STUDENTS CHEER AND APPLAUD)
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
ANYA:
AND NOW,
FRESH FROM THEIR HOLLYWOOD
MOVIE SHOOT,
THE ONE AND ONLY,
THE AMAZING STUDZ!
STUDENTS:
(CHEER AND APPLAUD)
GUYS?
WHO'S GONNA SING?
I DON'T KNOW
THE WORDS.
I'M A ONE-ARMED
DRUMMER!
(LOW DIN OF PARTY CHATTER)
(BAND PLAYS "WHOA")
(STUDENTS CHEER
AND APPLAUD WILDLY)
♪♪♪♪♪
SAV:
♪ I'M LIKE "WHOA!"
THE CALIFORNIA SUN ♪
THIS RIDE HAS JUST BEGUN ♪
♪ I'M LIKE "WHOA!"
JUST LIKE A SUBMACHINE GUN ♪
♪ WITH OUR GUITARS ♪
♪ AND ALL OUR GIRLS ♪
♪ HEY-CALI-HEY-FORN-HEY-I-A! ♪
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ I'M LIKE "WHOA!"
THE CALIFORNIA SUN ♪
THIS RIDE HAS JUST BEGUN ♪
♪ I'M LIKE "WHOA!"
JUST LIKE A SUBMACHINE GUN ♪
PETER:
HEY! THAT'S MY SONG!
AND ALL OUR...
(INSTRUMENTAL DIES OUT)
SAV:
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?!
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
THERE'S NO STUDZ WITHOUT ME!
YOU GUYS SUCK!
STUDZ:
(STRUGGLING GRUNTS)
OKAY! OKAY!
SHARED CUSTODY!
1, 2, 3, 4...
STUDENTS:
(LOW MURMURS OF CONFUSION)
PETER:
(STUTTERS)
(MIC SQUEALS)
SAV:
HEY, NO, DUDE.
ARE YOU TWEAKING?
PETER:
WHAT?! NO!
WE KNOW ABOUT
THE METH.
CHANTAY:
PETER, WHAT HAPPENED?
TELL THE FANS
ON THE VIDEO BLOG.
PETER:
GET OUTTA MY FACE!
STUDENTS:
(CONCERNED MURMURS)
(TRASH CAN CLATTERS)
(STUDENTS BOO ANGRILY)
HOLLY! IT'S, UH,
DEFCON FOUR IN THERE.
BOY BAND BREAK-UP?
BOO HOO.
CHANTAY:
LET'S TAKE A QUICK BREAK...
AREN'T YOU GOING
TO DO SOMETHING?
BLUE, I'M NOT ACTUALLY
A SUPERHERO.
I DEAL IN RAFFLE TICKETS,
NOT DRAMA.
BLUE:
WHAT ABOUT ALL YOUR FRIENDS
IN THERE?
THEY'RE NOT MY FRIENDS.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
HALF THEIR NAMES.
(SIGHS)
YOU KNOW, YOU SHOULD REALLY PUT
ALL THE HEADS ON THE MONEY
TO ONE SIDE.
THAT'S IT!
FIRST OF ALL,
YOU ARE NOT STUDENT COUNCIL
PRESIDENT.
AND I DIDN'T
BECOME PRESIDENT
SO THAT I COULD
MAKE FRIENDS
AND HAVE PEOPLE LOVE ME;
I DID IT SO I COULD
DO THINGS MY WAY.
SO JUST LEAVE ME ALONE!
(LOW DIN OF PARTY CHATTER)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
(LOUD RUSH OF TRAFFIC,
CELL PHONE RINGS)
HE'S STILL NOT ANSWERING.
(RILEY'S PHONE RINGS)
PETER?
WHAT?
SLOW DOWN.
GUYS! IT'S PETER!
SAV:
WHERE'D HE GO?
(HORNS HONKING)
I THINK I, LIKE, OD'D
OR SOMETHING.
RILEY:
WHERE ARE YOU?
I DON'T... I DON'T KNOW!
I'M BETWEEN TWO ROADS.
(PANICKED YELP)
PLEASE, JUST COME AND HELP ME!
COME FIND ME!
GUYS, COME ON.
RILEY:
'KAY, WE'RE COMING.
WHERE ARE YOU?
WHAT DO YOU SEE?
(TRAFFIC RUSHES BY)
(HORNS HONK LOUDLY)
♪ Where's your courage? ♪
♪ Where are they now? ♪
♪ Black versus white ♪
♪ Happened somehow ♪
RILEY:
PETER! PETER!
(CARS RUSH BY)
RILEY:
NO! PETER!
(TRUCK'S AIR HORN HONKS)
SPINNER:
WHOA, WHOA!
IT'S OKAY.
YOU'RE GONNA BE OKAY.
I'M FREEZING.
RILEY:
YOU'RE GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
PETER:
WOO!
(VEHICLE RUMBLES BY)
UH, WE SHOULD GO.
CURFEW.
TAKE IT EASY,
BUDDY.
CALL IF YOU NEED
ANYTHING.
WE'LL MAKE SURE
YOU'RE OKAY.
THANK YOU.
I HATE THIS STUPID LOFT.
I'M ALONE ALL THE TIME.
YEAH, NOT TONIGHT, DUDE.
CHUG THIS.
PROBABLY DEHYDRATED.
(EXHALES AND SNIFFLES)
(SHIVERING)
I'M LIKE MESSED UP,
GUYS.
(SHIVERING)
CAN YOU GET RID OF THIS?
ARE YOU SURE
THAT'S ALL OF IT?
(SHIVERING)
YEAH.
(PHONE BEEPS)
NEED TO MAKE A CALL,
DUDE?
LONG DISTANCE.
YOU KNOW IT'S LIKE 4 A.M.
IN PARIS, RIGHT?
I'M NOT CALLING MIA.
HEY, MOM, IT'S ME.
YEAH, I'M FINE.
WELL...
WELL, NOT REALLY, BUT...
CAN YOU COME HOME, PLEASE?
(BROOM SWISHES)
GUESS WHO?
YOU HAD A HARD NIGHT,
BUT I STILL BELIEVE
YOU CAN CHANGE.
SO IF YOU'RE READY
TO APOLOGIZE,
I'M READY TO LISTEN.
APOLOGIZE?!
FOR WHAT?
LOOK, BLUE,
I HAVE LOTS OF SIDES.
YOU CAN'T JUST PICK THE ONES
YOU LIKE.
BUT... I WANT TO LET
THE HOLLY I KNOW...
SHINE THROUGH.
NO, YOU DON'T.
YOU WANNA TURN ME INTO
SOMEONE THAT I'M NOT.
AND THAT'S NEVER
GONNA HAPPEN?
NO.
I'M SORRY, BLUE.
ME TOO.
BYE, HOLLY.
(SIGHING)
IT'S HOLLY FREAKIN' J!
(EXHALES, CONTENT)
AND THEN THEY GIVE YOU
THESE HOT TOWELS IN FIRST CLASS,
AND A LIMO PICKED ME UP.
ANNE MARIE FROM THE AGENCY'S
BEEN SO HELPFUL.
THAT'S AWESOME, MIA.
HOW ARE YOU?
YOU MEAN,
HOW'S MY DRUG PROBLEM?
I'M WORRIED ABOUT YOU,
PETER.
DON'T BE.
I BEGGED MY MOM
TO COME BACK FROM REGINA.
BONJOUR MIA!
MIA:
HI, MS. H!
PETER,
EVEN THOUGH WE BROKE UP,
I'M REALLY HAPPY
THAT YOU'RE NOT ALONE.
UM... I GOTTA GO,
BUT...
KEEP IN TOUCH, OKAY?
BYE, MIA.
I NEVER SHOULD'VE LEFT YOU.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT,
MOM.
I KNOW I CAN'T MAKE
YOUR CHOICES FOR YOU,
BUT JUST PROMISE ME...
IT'S OVER,
I PROMISE.
BECAUSE, PETER,
YOU CAN'T CONTROL THIS DRUG.
ONE RELAPSE,
JUST ONE,
AND IT'S STRAIGHT
TO REHAB.
PETER:
(SIGHS)
THANKS FOR COMING HOME,
MOM.