(SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYS)
I JUST THINK THAT
WE GOT INTO THIS SO FAST
THAT WE DIDN'T HAVE
TIME TO GROW.
THE THING IS
I DON'T WANT TO LIMIT YOU.
YOU'RE AN AMAZING GIRL.
SO WHAT DOES THIS MEAN?
RIGHT NOW I WANT YOU
TO FEEL FREE.
(SENTINMENTAL MUSIC CUTS OUT)
NICE LINE.
YOU'RE THE PLAYER
EVERYONE SAYS YOU ARE.
DON'T DO ME ANY FAVOURS.
SO, DID YOU DO IT?
DECLAN:
YEAH. I THINK SHE TOOK IT WELL.
SO, I GUESS
NOW WE'RE...OFFICIAL?
WHO KNEW A WEEK AGO
WE'D BE IN LOVE TODAY?
WE'D BE WHAT?!
(LAUGHS)
I JUST WANTED TO SEE
WHAT YOU'D SAY.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
WELL, HEY.
NO GOODBYE KISS?
SO MUCH FOR LOVE.
SCHOOL SINCLAIR
KICKS IN AT 8:01.
I'M SUPER BEHIND ALREADY.
IT'LL BE WORTH IT.
TRUST ME.
ALMOST.
DAVE:
HOLLY J,
LAST MINUTE ANNOUNCEMENT!
LEIA:
HOLLY J, UH, YOU CALLED
ABOUT A BABYSITTING JOB?
CHANTAY:
HOLLY J,
VIDEO BLOG INTERVIEW?
HOLLY J.:
THERE'S PLENTY OF ME
TO GO AROUND.
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out
I know I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, whatever ♪
(Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
CHANTAY:
YOU BETTER SPILL!
HOLLY J.:
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
ANYA:
MMM... RUMOUR HAS IT
THAT YOU AND DECLAN COYNE
ARE A THING.
NOT THAT IT'S A BIG A DEAL
OR ANYTHING.
IT'S A HUGE DEAL!
HE'S THE HOTTEST GUY
IN SCHOOL
AND YOU'RE...
YOU...
THERE BETTER BE A GOOD END
TO THAT SENTENCE, ANYA.
ATTENTION WOMEN LEADERS
OF THE FUTURE!
THE BUSINESS MENTORSHIP AWARD
FINALISTS ARE:
SASHA,
AMY,
HOLLY J,
AND EMILY.
GOOD LUCK
WITH YOUR INTERVIEWS, GUYS!
ANYA:
MENTORSHIP?
ON TOP OF YOUR JOB
AND BUSINESS
AND BEING PRESIDENT?
HOW'RE YOU GONNA
HAVE TIME TO DATE?
BEHIND EVERY POWERFUL WOMAN
IS A MAN WHO'D...
BETTER BE COOL WITH IT.
(SHARP EXHALE)
THAT'S MEGAN FOX
IN "TRANSFORMERS."
YEAH.
ALL THE SPECIAL EFFECTS ARE CGI
EXCEPT THE ONE
WHEN SHE'S IN SHORT SHORTS.
I LOVE THOSE
SHORT SHORTS.
ARE THERE MORE PICTURES?
YEAH.
(APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS)
CONNOR,
HAND IT OVER.
THIS MATERIAL IS NOT
APPROPRIATE FOR CLASS.
DETENTION.
DAVE:
NO, NO, NO.
IT'S JUST...
DO YOU WANT TO JOIN
YOUR FRIEND?
NO, IT'S JUST...
HE HAS BASKETBALL PRACTICE.
CONNOR SHOULD'VE THOUGHT
OF THAT.
BRO, WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
NOBODY'S GONNA MISS ME
AT PRACTICE.
HEY!
YOU BUSY RIGHT NOW?
WELL I HAVE SIX THINGS
TO DO
BEFORE THE BELL RINGS
IN THREE MINUTES, SO...
JANE:
HEY, YOU TWO.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
JUST TRYING TO CONVINCE
LA PRESIDENTA
TO SKIP CLASS.
AW! HE CAN'T WAIT
'TIL LUNCH!
YEAH.
NO DICE.
I HAVE MATH
TO HAND IN.
CAN YOU HAND THIS IN
FOR US?
THANKS, ANYA.
JENNA:
HOLLY J?
I HAVE THE BABYSITTING
MONEY BUT,
WHAT'S TWENTY PERCENT
OF $26.00?
HOLLY J.:
UM, JANE?
CAN YOU HANDLE THIS?
DECLAN AND I HAVE
AN IMPORTANT MEETING.
JANE:
FOR SURE.
ENJOY YOUR "MEETING."
(BELL RINGS)
SPINNER:
SKIPPING SCHOOL
TO HANG OUT AT WORK.
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH KIDS TODAY?
YEAH, UH,
PUT IT ON MY TAB.
YOU GOT IT, CHIEF.
SPONTANEOUS MEETINGS
ARE FUN!
SEE? I BRING
UNPREDICTABLE ROMANCE
INTO YOUR STRUCTURED WORLD.
HOLLY J.:
HEY! I'M NOT THAT STRUCTURED.
I MEAN, ARE PEOPLE
SAYING STUFF ABOUT ME?
IT'S JUST,
I USED TO BE DIFFERENT.
SOME MIGHT SAY...
HARSH.
HOLLY J, THIS IS US.
HIGH SCHOOL GOSSIP
DOESN'T MATTER.
SO, BACK HERE
AFTER SCHOOL?
OH, I CAN'T.
I HAVE MY MENTORSHIP
INTERVIEW.
OH, THAT'S MY MOTHER'S
PROJECT.
SHE'S ONE OF THE JUDGES.
WAIT. WHAT?
HOW DID YOU HANG ONTO
THIS PIECE OF INFORMATION
UNTIL NOW?
YOU SHOULD TELL HER
ABOUT US.
WHY WOULD I DO THAT?
BECAUSE IF SHE HAS
A PERSONAL STAKE
IN YOU AND YOUR SUCCESS,
SHE'LL WANT
TO MAKE IT HAPPEN.
BY TELLING HER
I'M DATING HER SON?
HELLO, NEPOTISM!
UH, IT'S CALLED POLITICS!
CONNECTIONS MAKE THINGS
HAPPEN.
HMM...
YOU WANNA BLOW
FOURTH PERIOD,
TAKE A WALK,
CLEAR YOUR MIND
BEFORE THE INTERVIEW?
♪ Forgot my cheque book,
it didn't... ♪
(LAUGHING)
YOU LOOK RIDICULOUS.
YUP. SO DO YOU.
♪ Time doesn't sympathize ♪
♪ Atlantic Boulevard ♪
♪ Won't you be my friend ♪
♪ Treat me as a friend ♪
ALL THAT TIME OVERSEAS
AND YOU NEVER DEVELOPED
A FASHION SENSE?
OH, HOW THE MIGHTY
HAVE FALLEN.
(LAUGHS)
'KAY, THIS ONE'S GOING
ONTO MY WALLPAPER.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
COACH:
OKAY, GUYS. THAT'S IT.
HOW WAS DETENTION?
PRETTY RELAXING,
ACTUALLY.
I INVENTED TRANSFORMERS
IN MY MIND.
BUT YOU KNOW YOU DIDN'T
NEED TO TAKE THE FALL.
IT WAS MY MAGAZINE.
IT'S FINE.
IN DETENTION,
I DON'T HAVE TO TALK TO PEOPLE
WHO THINK I'M WEIRD.
AH, COME ON, MAN.
YOU GOTTA GET OUT THERE,
ALL RIGHT?
SHOW PEOPLE
YOUR TRUE SELF,
GET NOTICED,
MAKE 'EM LAUGH.
HEY, GUYS!
CHECK IT OUT.
CONNOR WAS TELLING ME
ABOUT POP ROCKS
AND ROOT BEER DYNAMITE.
TELL 'EM.
THAT'S BEEN LITERALLY
DISPROVED.
POPULAR MECHANICS
DID A STUDY.
NOT THE POINT, MAN.
NOT THE POINT.
ANYWAY, SO WHAT HAPPENS
IS YOU GET A MOUTH FULL
OF POP ROCKS...
(SHOUTING)
IT DOESN'T WORK LIKE THAT!
(A FEW GUYS CHUCKLE)
OKAY, DORKS.
LET US KNOW
WHEN YOU GET TO THE BOTTOM
OF THE GREAT POP ROCKS DEBATE.
TEAM:
(LAUGHING)
CONNOR:
DAVE, WAIT UP!
DAVE!
HEY,
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
CONNOR:
JUST WONDERING IF YOU WERE
DOING ANYTHING AFTER SCHOOL.
DAVE:
YEAH, CONNOR.
I'M GOING TO THE BREAKROOM
WITH THE TEAM.
OKAY. LET'S GO.
YEAH.
NO, NO, NO.
I DON'T THINK
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
WHY NOT?
OKAY.
OKAY, LOOK, ALL RIGHT?
YOU WERE RIGHT,
I SHOULDN'T HAVE TRIED
TO BREAK YOU OUT OF YOUR
COMFORT ZONE, ALL RIGHT?
THAT WAS MY BAD.
SO NOW YOU'RE GONNA
AVOID ME?
OKAY, CONNOR, LOOK.
THE GUYS ON THE TEAM
ALREADY THINK
I'M LIKE 49% LAME-O...
AND BEING AROUND YOU
MIGHT TIP THE BALANCE.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
MY FRIEND.
GUY:
DAVE, HURRY UP!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
LARA:
I CAN'T TELL YOU
HOW IMPRESSED I AM, HOLLY J,
OR SHOULD I SAY
"MADAM PRESIDENT"?
YOUR CLASSMATES ARE VERY LUCKY
TO HAVE SUCH A LEADER.
HOLLY J.:
I'M NOT SURE THEY ALWAYS SEE IT
THAT WAY.
THEY THINK I'M MORE...
TYPE A?
DRIVEN?
THEY TEND TO USE
OTHER WORDS.
MMM. TYPICAL.
YOUNG WOMEN LIKE YOU
ARE RARE.
A MENTOR CAN BE INVALUABLE.
FEMALE PANELIST 1:
WE'LL BE MAKING
OUR DECISION SOON.
HOLLY J.:
WELL, THANK YOU.
AND I'M SURE I'LL SEE YOU
SOON REGARDLESS.
YOUR SON AND I ARE
KIND OF... DATING.
MY SON AND YOU ARE...?
YEAH. HE WANTED ME
TO MAKE SURE I MENTIONED IT.
LARA,
I'M QUITE CONCERNED
ABOUT THE OPTICS
OF THIS SITUATION.
HOLLY J...
(SIGHS)
THIS IS A HIGH-PROFILE PROGRAM
WE'RE LAUNCHING,
AND I'M AFRAID
IT WOULDN'T LOOK GOOD
TO AWARD IT
MY SON'S GIRLFRIEND.
WAIT.
BUT DIDN'T YOU JUST SAY
I'M THE BEST AT DEGRASSI?
UNFORTUNATELY,
IN SITUATIONS LIKE THIS,
POLITICS OFTEN
GET IN THE WAY.
WELL, I GUESS THESE ARE
THE REAL LEADERSHIP LESSONS
I NEED TO LEARN, HUH?
I WITHDRAW.
(ANGRY HUFF)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
(APPLAUSE)
AS STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT,
IT IS MY GREAT PLEASURE
TO INTRODUCE LARA COYNE
WITH A VERY SPECIAL
ANNOUNCEMENT.
LARA:
THANK YOU, MS. SINCLAIR.
BEING A BUSINESS MENTOR
MEANS OPPORTUNITY,
AND NOT JUST IN THE WORKPLACE.
BUT A PROFOUND OPPORTUNITY
TO MEET WOMEN
FROM DIFFERENT WALKS OF LIFE
WHOSE NARRATIVE...
(WHISPERED)
HOLLY J.!
LARA:
LIFE EXPERIENCES
AND PROFESSIONS
REMIND US OF A WOMAN'S STRENGTH
AND POWER...
HOLLY J.!
LARA:
TO OVERCOME IN A ONCE
MALE-DOMINATED WORLD.
THIS PROGRAM EMPOWERS
YOUNG WOMEN
TO UNITE WITH EACH OTHER.
TO CONNECT.
TO LEAD.
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
SHHH!
SO I GUESS I GAVE YOU
SOME BAD ADVICE, HUH?
MEH.
I'M GLAD I WAS HONEST.
SHE'D HAVE FOUND OUT
EVENTUALLY.
I'M SORRY IT COST YOU
THE MENTORSHIP, THOUGH.
SO, YOU'D BETTER
BE WORTH IT.
I'LL DO MY BEST.
LARA:
AND THIS IS WHY
OUR MENTORSHIP PROGRAM EXISTS.
TO UNITE YOUNG WOMEN
WITH PEOPLE LIKE
MRS. PERRIAGE...
THIS COULD GET DANGEROUS.
YOU'RE MY CONSOLATION PRIZE!
LARA:
WHEN I FIRST CAME TO DEGRASSI,
I WAS HONOURED TO MEET
THESE YOUNG WOMEN.
BUT ONE IN PARTICULAR
EXEMPLIFIED
WHAT WE WERE LOOKING FOR:
DRIVEN,
DETERMINED,
AND WITH THE INTEGRITY TO STAND
FOR WHAT SHE BELIEVES IN.
IS IT JUST ME
OR, UH, IS IT GETTING HOT
IN HERE?
LARA:
SHE HAS OUTSTANDING GRACE
AND HAS CLOCKED AN IMPRESSIVE
NUMBER OF WORK HOURS.
NO POINT
IN GOING HALFWAY.
LARA:
HER ABILITY TO BALANCE SCHOOL,
A PART-TIME JOB,
AND VOLUNTEER...
DECLAN, WE'RE GONNA
GET IN TROUBLE.
I HOPE SO.
AND NOW, I'D LIKE TO ANNOUNCE
THE WINNER.
PLEASE HELP ME CELEBRATE
MS. HOLLY J. SINCLAIR!
(CHEERING AND APPLAUDING)
MS. SINCLAIR?
HOLLY J.?
HOLLY J.:
(GASPS)
ETHAN:
SO, UH, AFTER THE ATHLETICS
BANQUET?
I'M GETTING A HOTEL ROOM
WITH TRISH.
DAVE:
SHEEYAH.
NO WAY.
WHAT'LL YOU AND TRISH DO?
UH, DO YOU WANT ME
TO DRAW YOU A PICTURE?
(CHUCKLES)
ETHAN:
WHO IS THIS GUY!
BRO, WHY DO YOU KEEP
FOLLOWING US AROUND?
ARE YOU EVEN ON THE TEAM?
ETHAN, LEAVE HIM ALONE.
ETHAN:
HE'S A GLORIFIED WATERBOY!
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
I DON'T THINK I'M THE ONE
WITH THE PROBLEM,
LITTLE DAVE.
YEAH, YOU KEEP LIPPING OFF
LIKE THAT,
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE ONE.
I'M SHAKING.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
APPARENTLY I SHOULD HAVE
ACCEPTED YOUR WITHDRAWAL,
MS. SINCLAIR.
HATZILAKOS:
IT SEEMS LIKE RIGHT NOW
WE'RE IN A DAMAGE CONTROL
SITUATION.
SO I'M...
MARY KATE SINCLAIR:
PLEASE!
MY DAUGHTER WAS HUMILIATED,
IF NOT ASSAULTED,
IN FRONT OF THE SCHOOL
AND WE'RE TALKING
DAMAGE CONTROL?
FOR WHOM?
MOM!
MS. SINCLAIR,
OUR FAMILY IS IN
THE PUBLIC EYE.
AND LET ME ASSURE YOU
THAT WHEN THOSE PHOTOS
HIT THE INTERNET,
IT WON'T LOOK GOOD
FOR ANYONE.
HOLLY J.:
OKAY, SO I LOSE THE MENTORSHIP.
FINE.
MARY KATE SINCLAIR:
YOU'RE GOING TO PUNISH
MY CHILD
FOR YOUR SON'S ACTIONS?
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
WE CAN'T HAVE IT SEEM AS THOUGH
THIS AFFECTED OUR DECISION.
HOLLY J. WILL ATTEND
ALL OF SESSIONS AS PLANNED.
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU WIN.
BUT...
YOU WILL NOT SEE EACH OTHER.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
GOT IT, MOM.
SO WE'RE JUST SUPPOSED
TO BE OVER?
LARA:
THE LESS WE DWELL ON THIS,
THE BETTER.
MARY KATE SINCLAIR:
I COULDN'T AGREE MORE.
(DISBELIEVING GASP)
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
KWAN:
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK
WITH YOUR PHOTOCOPIES.
READ QUIETLY.
HEY.
YOU WANT TO HIT UP
THAT WII TODAY, OR WHAT?
WHAT ABOUT PRACTICE?
NAH. I'D RATHER HANG OUT
WITH MY REAL FRIENDS,
YOU KNOW?
LISTEN, DAVE,
YOU'RE GOOD.
THE TEAM NEEDS YOU.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
I-I THINK I MIGHT QUIT.
I DON'T FIT IN
AND I SUCK.
NAH, YOU JUST HAD
A GROWTH SPURT.
YOUR SKILLS WILL CATCH UP.
WHAT'S THIS?
STATS.
I DO THEM
FOR EVERY GAME.
DAVE:
BLOCKS...
ASSISTS, REBOUNDS?
BRO, THIS STUFF IS AMAZING.
MAKES THE BENCH
LESS BORING.
COACH HAS TO SEE THIS.
REALLY?
LOOK, NEVERMIND FITTING IN,
ALL RIGHT?
PLAY TO YOUR STRENGTHS.
HEY! SO I GUESS
CHIVALRY IS DEAD.
THAT'S NOT FUNNY,
HOLLY J.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S
LESS FUNNY?
HOW YOU SAT THERE
AND SAID NOTHING
WHILE THEY SKEWERED ME!
MY HANDS WERE KINDA TIED,
OKAY?
YOU SAW MY MOTHER
IN THERE!
YEAH, I NOTICED.
ARE YOU SCARED
TO MAKE YOUR MOMMY MAD?
IN CASE YOU HAVEN'T NOTICED,
MY FAMILY'S ALL I HAVE,
HOLLY J.
SO NOW WHAT?
YOU CAN'T SERIOUSLY
BELIEVE
THAT THIS IS GONNA GET BETTER
IF WE SPLIT UP.
LOOK, WE BOTH KNOW
I'LL HAVE TO MOVE AWAY
EVENTUALLY.
AND IF WE'RE NEVER ALLOWED
TO SEE EACH OTHER...
WHAT'S THE POINT?
(SLAMS LOCKER SHUT)
ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION, DEGRASSI:
PLAY AN INSTRUMENT
OR JUST YOUR VOICE?
OPEN JAM SESSIONS...
TWO BRUISED REPS,
TWO ANGRY MOMS,
ONE DEAD RELATIONSHIP.
AWESOME.
AT LEAST YOU GOT
THE MENTORSHIP.
GREAT. SO I GET TO HANG OUT
WITH HIS MOTHER,
AND NOT HIM.
IT'LL BLOW OVER.
YOU'VE DEALT WITH WORSE.
HOW DO I MAKE
PEOPLE REALIZE
THAT THIS IS REALLY NOT
A BIG DEAL?
WHAT PEOPLE?
WHO DO YOU ACTUALLY CARE ABOUT
IN THIS SCENERIO?
LEIA:
I'M REALLY SORRY,
BUT...
THE MURPHYS DON'T GET HOME
'TIL 11.
I HAVE TO CANCEL.
MY CURFEW.
CALL ANYA,
TELL HER YOU'RE TAKING
HER JOB AT THE DANES'.
SHE'LL HIT THE MURPHYS.
THEY'VE GOT
THREE DOCILE KIDS,
WE'RE NOT LOSING THEM.
(LAUGHS)
ARE YOU REALLY LAUGHING
AT MY MISFORTUNE RIGHT NOW?
WELL,
I'VE NEVER SEEN YOU
WITH A PROBLEM
YOU CAN'T SOLVE.
(TRAFFIC HUMS ALONG,
HORNS HONK)
(TUMBLER CLICKS IN PLACE)
(KEYS JANGLE)
THANKS FOR SHOWING UP.
DECLAN:
YOU HAD ME
AT "BREAKING INTO THE SCHOOL."
IT'S NOT BREAKING IN
IF YOU HAVE THE KEY.
THIS IS THE ONLY PLACE
I COULD THINK OF
FOR US TO BE ALONE.
I THINK WE SHOULD
MAKE THIS WORK.
AND YOU WOULDN'T BE HERE
IF YOU DIDN'T THINK SO TOO.
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
COME ON.
♪♪♪♪♪
THIS IS KIND OF INCREDIBLE.
HOLLY J.:
WELL, IT'S NOT LIKE WE CAN HAVE
A ROMANTIC DINNER
ANYWHERE ELSE.
(HALF LAUGHS)
(TRAY COVERS CLATTER)
GUESS THE DOT
DOESN'T DO LOBSTER?
(HALF LAUGHS)
YOUR SMOOTH MOVES
DISAPPEAR FASTER
BY THE DAY.
I GET NERVOUS!
EAT YOUR BURGER.
I CAN'T.
I'M JUST TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT
HOW SOMETHING SO GOOD
WENT SO BAD.
IT'S LIKE EVERYTHING
IS AGAINST US.
DECLAN,
WE HAVE EVERYTHING
GOING FOR US.
WE...TALK,
WE...LAUGH.
WE MAKE EACH OTHER HOT.
SEE, THIS IS WHAT WE NEED
TO MAKE THINGS WORK.
SO YOU'RE SAYING
WE SHOULD JUST DO IT.
YEAH.
LIVE OUR LIVES.
WE'RE LIKE THE MODERN
ROMEO AND JULIET.
SNEAKING AROUND
HAS DEFINITE APPEAL.
NO. I'M...
I'M NOT SNEAKING.
COME ON!
THIS WAY WE GET WHAT THEY WANT
AND WHAT WE WANT.
IT'S DRAMATIC,
IT'S ROMANTIC...
IF WE CAN'T BE
UP FRONT ABOUT THIS,
I DON'T...
I DON'T WANT
TO DO IT AT ALL.
IT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
THEN NEITHER ARE WE.
(KEYS JANGLE)
LOCK UP.
♪ You're the one for me... ♪
(BALL BOUNCING)
ETHAN:
HEY, WHAT'S THIS ALL ABOUT?
CARSON:
EVERYBODY HERE?
GOOD.
YOUR TEAMMATE'S BEEN KEEPING
STATS ALL SEASON.
WHAT'S IN THIS BINDER
IS PURE GOLD.
IT'S GOING TO PUT US
OVER THE TOP.
THAT, AND MAKE SURE CONNOR
STAYS ON THE BENCH.
SHUT UP, ETHAN!
EASY, PONY.
ETHAN,
YOUR STATS ARE SOFT.
NEXT GAME,
YOU'LL KEEP CONNOR COMPANY.
DAVE, YOU'RE STARTING
AT POINT GUARD.
SEE Y'ALL AT PRACTICE.
CAN'T KEEP ME OFF THE COURT,
DORK.
HEY,
NUMBERS DON'T LIE.
NICE.
JUST PLAYING
TO MY STRENGTHS.
NICELY DONE.
THANKS.
HATZILAKOS:
THERE ARE CAMERAS
THROUGHOUT THE SCHOOL.
DO YOU WANT TO EXPLAIN
TO YOUR MOTHERS
WHAT'S ON THEM?
I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M HERE
FOR THE SECOND TIME
IN TWO DAYS, DECLAN.
MARY KATE SINCLAIR:
HOLLY JEANNETTE,
WHAT DID HE DO TO YOU?
LARA:
EXCUSE ME?
WHAT ARE YOU ACCUSING
MY SON OF, EXACTLY?
IT'S PRETTY OBVIOUS
HE'S NEVER BEEN TAUGHT
TO CONTROL HIMSELF.
HOLLY J.:
OKAY!
WE SPENT SOME TIME HERE
LAST NIGHT,
WORKING ON
DECLAN'S PLAY.
THAT'S IT.
HATZILAKOS:
NEEDLESS TO SAY,
KEYS ARE A PRIVILEGE
YOU NO LONGER HAVE.
DO YOU PARENTS HAVE TO PUT
YOU TWO ON A LEASH?
THIS IS REALLY STUPID.
I MEAN, WE LIKE EACH OTHER,
RIGHT?
WELL, MOM,
YOU SAID YOURSELF
THAT SHE'S THE BEST GIRL
IN THE SCHOOL.
I'M NOT DISPUTING
HER TALENTS!
WELL, WE WOULDN'T HAVE
TO SNEAK AROUND
IF YOU DIDN'T
KEEP US APART!
SO THE NEW PLAN IS
WE'RE DOING THIS.
YEAH.
YOU WERE AWESOME!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I JUST DID THAT.
NOW YOU KNOW
HOW IT FEELS!
PLUS, THEIR FACES?
(LAUGHS)
PRICELESS.
SO, UH...
HOLLY JEANNETTE, HUH?
SHUT UP.
♪ Are you still wondering? ♪
♪ We are... ♪
♪ We are who we are... ♪
♪ We are who we are ... ♪