(STUDENTS CHEERING, APPLAUSE)
OKAY, PEOPLE,
LET'S HEAR IT!
HERE THEY COME!
WOOOO!
(STUDENTS CHEER WILDLY)
EMMA:
AAH!
(LAUGHS)
QUITE THE WELCOMING COMMITTEE!
WELL, IT'S NOT EVERY DAY THAT
MY STEP-DAUGHTER'S
ON A CHARITY BIKE-A-THON,
HUH? COME ON.
EMMA:
OH! FIVE DAYS,
500 KILOMETERS.
KELLY:
AND FIVE-ALARM
SADDLE SORES.
EMMA:
AW, POOR BABY!
OKAY, GUYS,
WE'LL SEE YOU IN A FEW DAYS.
MAKE CENTENNIAL HIGH
COUGH UP THOSE BIKES!
MR. SIMPSON:
GREAT. OKAY,
WE'LL SEE YOU IN A BIT.
GUYS, THANKS SO MUCH, LET'S GO
BACK TO CLASS, ALL RIGHT?
EMMA, AS STUDENT COUNCIL
PRESIDENT,
IT'S MY JOB TO WELCOME
YOU TO DEGRASSI.
SO, ARE YOU READY
TO GO MAKE AN ANNOUNCEMENT
FOR YOUR ALMA MATER?
YOU GO AHEAD,
YOU'RE THE TALKER,
I'M MORE OF A NUTS
AND BOLTS GUY,
I'LL GO TALK
TO YOUR DAD.
I WON'T TELL HIM ABOUT THAT!
EMMA:
KELLY!
WE'RE A TEAM.
COME ON.
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, whatever ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
EMMA:
MANY PEOPLE IN DEVELOPING
COUNTRIES
HAVE TO WALK FOR HOURS
TO GET TO SCHOOL, WORK,
OR TO THEIR FIELDS.
KELLY:
RIGHT. AND HAVING A BIKE
CAN CUT THAT TIME IN HALF.
WITH ZERO CARBON EMISSIONS!
THAT'S WHAT THE RECYCLING
TOUR IS ALL ABOUT!
BRING YOUR OLD, UNWANTED
BIKES HERE ON THURSDAY,
AND KELLY THE TOOL MAN
AND I,
WILL SHOW YOU
HOW TO TURN YOUR JUNK
INTO SOMEONE ELSE'S TREASURE.
SEE YOU THEN!
WHAT A CAUSE.
THAT'S IT FOR NOW.
QUITE THE CRUSADERS,
YOU TWO.
MR. SIMPSON,
I MEAN YOUR DAD,
KEEPS MAKING US WATCH
YOUR VIDEO BLOGS.
ADDICTIVE,
AREN'T THEY?
I CAN'T HELP BUT BECOME ENGAGED
IN AN ACTIVE ONLINE COMMUNITY.
I'M SORRY. I GUESS
MY SOCIAL CONSCIENCE
IS A LITTLE BIT
UNDER-DEVELOPED.
WELL, THAT'S WHY
WE'RE HERE.
HEY, HOW'S SMITHDALE?
IT'S ONE OF MY TOP FOUR
PICKS FOR UNIVERSITY.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
WELL,
WHAT'S YOUR MAJOR?
WOW, LOT OF QUESTIONS.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE SHOULD GO.
HER MOM'S BOUNCING OFF
THE WALLS WAITING FOR US.
KELLY:
I'M SO LOOKING FORWARD
TO SPENDING THE NIGHT
UNDER A ROOF.
EMMA:
CHATEAU SIMPSON NELSON'S
ALL BOOKED UP.
WE'LL BE IN THE LIVING ROOM
PULL-OUT COUCH SUITE.
KELLY:
IT'S BETTER THAN THE TENT.
WE'LL BE ALONE,
RIGHT?
EMMA:
UH FIRST, WE HAVE TO POSTER
THE NEIGHBOURHOOD.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
IT'S ALWAYS ABOUT THAT!
WOULD YOU LIKE SOME CHEESE
WITH THAT WHINE?
COME ON KELLY,
IT'S THE WHOLE POINT
OF THE BIKE-A-THON!
WHAT ABOUT HAVING FUN?
POSTERING IS FUN!
(HALF LAUGHS)
OKAY!
WHAT DID YOU HAVE IN MIND?
INVITE SOME FRIENDS,
FRIENDS BRING REFRESHMENTS...
WELL, MY PARENTS ARE TAKING
JACK TO A BIRTHDAY PARTY.
I GUESS WE COULD HAVE
A BARBECUE?
TELL MS. UNDERDEVELOPED
SOCIAL CONSCIENCE
TO BRING SOME FRIENDS.
SO, ARE YOU A FOOD SHARER
OR NOT?
MY CAESAR SALAD
IS YOUR CAESAR SALAD.
TASTE TEST
ALL YOU WANT.
HOPE THE GARLIC BREATH
WILL WEAR OFF BEFORE OUR DATE.
SEVEN HOURS, ELEVEN MINUTES,
AND... 45 SECONDS.
SHOULD BE ENOUGH TIME.
COUNTING DOWN,
ARE WE?
I'VE ONLY BEEN WAITING
TWO WEEKS!
(HOLLY J GIGGLES)
THINK WE COULD GIVE
THOSE TWO A RUN
FOR "DEGRASSI'S HOTTEST COUPLE"
ON THE ANTI-GRAPEVINE?
I SUPPOSE I COULD
LOOK INTO THAT.
LET ME KNOW HOW
I CAN BRIBE THE BLOGGER.
(VIDEO GAME WHOOSHES AND BLIPS)
KELLY:
COME ON!
YOU'RE GOING DOWN!
EMMA (ON BLOG):
A HUNDRED KILOMETERS TO GO,
AND THEN WE'LL END
DAY FIVE WITH MY FAMILY.
KELLY:
CAN'T WAIT FOR SOME
HOME COOKIN'!
SPIKE:
YOU TWO SURE LOOK COZY.
WELL, WE'D BETTER BE,
IF WE'RE GOING TO SURVIVE
A CROSS-COUNTRY ADVENTURE.
BUT THAT'LL TAKE
ALL SUMMER,
WHAT ABOUT
GETTING A JOB?
THIS IS OUR JOB, SNAKE.
IT'S JUST A VOLUNTEER ONE.
DID KELLY TALK YOU INTO THIS?
WHY WOULD YOU
SAY THAT?
WELL, YOU SOMETIMES
GO TO EXTREMES FOR A GUY.
SINCE WHEN?!
SO, HOW ABOUT EXAMS?
WE'VE BEEN WAITING ALL WEEK
FOR THE DETAILS.
WELL, COMPARED TO 12 HOURS
A DAY ON A BIKE,
EXAMS WERE NOTHING.
SMITHDALE IS JUST PEACHY.
KELLY AND EMMA:
(RELAXED SIGHS)
I'M A CORPSE!
CAN WE JUST PHONE IN
THE LAST 2000 CLICKS?
HEY!
WE ARE NOT QUITTING.
YOU JUST NEED SOME
POSITIVE REINFORCEMENT.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(EXASPERATED SIGH)
IS YOUR DAD STILL TELLING YOU
TO GET A "REAL JOB?"
I'M RUNNING OUT OF ARGUMENTS
FOR NOT GETTING ONE.
HEY.
WE'RE HELPING PEOPLE.
WE'RE TOGETHER, AND...
WE ARE FAR AWAY
FROM SMITHDALE.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO TELL YOUR
FOLKS ABOUT SCHOOL EVENTUALLY.
BUT I HAVE SO MANY MORE
IMPORTANT THINGS TO DO!
LIKE THIS!
(EMMA HALF LAUGHS)
(SIGHS)
SO MUCH FOR OUR
ALONE TIME!
GOODNIGHT.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
(SOUNDS OF DOG BARKING,
ALARM CLOCK, MIXED IN A SONG)
NICE SOUNDSCAPE!
I LOVE HOW YOU PITCH-SHIFTED
THE HOWLING DOG.
YEAH, CHANTAY AND I
CAME HERE AT LUNCH,
WE FOOLED AROUND.
WITH THE AUDIO LEVELS!
SO, YOU TWO ARE OFFICIAL, HUH?
YEAH, WE'RE OUT AND PROUD.
REALLY?
LET'S CHECK...
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
SAV:
"AT LUNCH WITH ANOTHER STUDENT,
I COULDN'T HELP BUT NOTICE
ALL EYES TURNED TO POWER COUPLE
HOLLY J AND DECLAN..."
IT'S BASICALLY
JUST ABOUT THEM...
UH... WAIT.
"LUNCH WITH ANOTHER STUDENT?"
ANOTHER STUDENT!
THAT WAS ME!
THAT'S ALL I AM?!
WELL, TECHNICALLY,
IT'S TRUE.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
(BLENDER WHIRRS)
♪♪♪♪♪
KELLY:
WHAT HAVE WE HERE?
LOCALLY-GROWN
STRAWBERRY SMOOTHIES!
FOOD TASTES WAY BETTER
WHEN IT DOESN'T TRAVEL
FOR A WEEK
TO GET TO YOUR TABLE.
YEAH WELL, I DON'T KNOW WHERE
THESE BABIES CAME FROM,
BUT I DO KNOW
WHERE THEY'RE GOING!
WHO WANTS A STRIP LOIN?
JANE:
RIGHT HERE!
DUDE.
COME ON.
I'M KINDA VEGAN.
EMMA SHOWED ME THE ERROR
OF MY MEAT-EATING WAYS.
EMMA:
YEAH, GRILLED PORTOBELLOS
FOR US!
MMM! WHO NEEDS STEAK,
WHEN YOU COULD HAVE
A GREAT BIG MUSHROOM, RIGHT?
IT'S A GOOD SOURCE
OF... ZINC.
OH YEAH,
YOU GOTTA HAVE ZINC.
(GIRLS GIGGLING)
CHANTAY:
SO, DID SAV LIKE THE BEAUTIFUL
SOUNDSCAPE WE MADE TOGETHER?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
THIS IS OUR FIRST DATE,
AND YOU'VE BARELY SAID A WORD.
AH, SO,
SO IT IS A DATE, THEN.
YOU'RE NOT ASHAMED
TO BE WITH ME?
WHY WOULD YOU SAY THAT?
I WAS KIND OF EXCITED TO READ
YOUR FIRST BLOG POST ABOUT US.
BUT APPARENTLY,
I'M JUST ANOTHER STUDENT.
DANNY...
BEING IN THE SPOTLIGHT
ISN'T EASY.
C'MON, I'M A ROCK STAR,
REMEMBER?
THANKS.
(SIGHS)
SO, FOUR BUCKS EACH?
UH, HOLD ON.
YOUR LATTE WAS MORE
THAN MY MACCHIATO...
SO, PLUS TAX, YOU OWE...
FIVE-TWENTY-FIVE.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
IT'S ONLY FAIR, RIGHT?
OH, MAN!
THAT'S GOOD!
EMMA DOESN'T KNOW
WHAT SHE'S MISSING, DOES SHE?
IF CARNIVORISM'S WRONG,
WHY ARE COWS SO TASTY?
YEAH?
AND YOU GAVE IT UP FOR HER.
AH, IT'S NOT THE ONLY THING
I GAVE UP...
WELL, SHE MUST BE
WORTH IT, THEN.
EMMA:
KELLY?
SORRY, BABE!
I CAVED!
EMMA:
DID YOU OPEN THIS?
MY PARENTS HAVE BEEN SAVING
THIS SINCE THEY GOT MARRIED!
I THOUGHT WE WERE
MAKING OURSELVES AT HOME!
CALM DOWN.
EMMA: CALM DOWN?!
WE NEED TO TALK.
I GOTTA GO...
FEED MY TURTLE.
I KNOW PASSIVE-AGGRESSIVE
WHEN I SEE IT, KELLY.
OH, COME ON.
EVER SINCE WE STARTED
THIS TRIP,
YOU'VE BEEN MAKING
THESE LITTLE POINTED REMARKS,
AND I AM SICK OF IT!
WELL, SO AM I!
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I TALKED TO MY DAD.
THERE'S A SUMMER JOB
AT AN ENGINEERING FIRM.
I'D BE CRAZY
TO TURN IT DOWN.
PLANE TICKET'S
IN MY INBOX.
UNBELIEVABLE.
THIS WAS SUPPOSED TO BE FUN,
EMMA.
BUT IT'S WORK.
UNPAID AT THAT.
KELLY, YOU CAN'T JUST
BACK OUT OF A COMMITMENT!
OH, RIGHT! YOU FLOATED
THROUGH A SEMESTER OF SCHOOL,
AND YOU'RE LECTURING ME
ON COMMITMENT?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN MY ROOM?
WE ARE NOT TELLING THEM
ABOUT THIS.
HIDE THE BOTTLE,
I'M GONNA SLEEP
ON THE COUCH.
TOMORROW,
CATCH YOUR PLANE.
I NEVER WANT
TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ I've been waiting
a lifetime ♪
♪ For nothing ♪
♪ Taking my time with this ♪
♪ From something ♪
♪ With no prize
to speak of for me ♪
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
SPIKE:
DID KELLY LEAVE?
HE QUIT, MOM.
WE BROKE UP,
HE'S GOING HOME.
WHAT HAPPENED?
CAN YOU JUST CALL SNAKE,
AND CANCEL THE WORKSHOP?
IT'S IN AN HOUR!
I CAN'T GIVE A BIKE-FIXING
DEMONSTRATION
WITHOUT A MECHANIC!
WELL, HOW IS SNAKE
SUPPOSED TO EXPLAIN THAT
TO HALF THE SCHOOL?
♪ What's become of me ♪
P.A. ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION, DEGRASSI:
IT'S HOT DOG DAY IN THE CAF!
(BOOKS LAND WITH A THUD)
SAV:
MAN, THANKS.
WHAT DO I OWE YOU?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
HAVEN'T YOU SEEN
CHANTAY'S BLOG?
IT'S ALL ABOUT YOUR DATE.
SWEET!
I'LL GO CHECK IT OUT.
NO, SHE ALSO MENTIONED THAT YOU
DIDN'T WANNA SPLIT THE BILL.
NOW PEOPLE ARE CALLING YOU
CHEAP.
(FRUSTRATED SIGH)
WELL, THAT'S JUST GREAT!
MR. SIMPSON:
HONESTLY GUYS, I... I DON'T
KNOW HOW TO FIX THESE THINGS,
YOU'RE GONNA JUST HAVE TO WAIT
UNTIL THEY SHOW UP.
IF YOU COULD JUST LIKE,
WAIT OVER THERE FOR NOW.
COULD YOU JUST WAIT OVER THERE!
I'M SURE OUR SPECIAL GUESTS
WILL BE HERE SOON, FOLKS. OKAY?
EMMA:
SORRY!
AND HERE'S ONE OF THEM NOW.
AND SHE'S... ALONE.
UM, TAKE IT AWAY, EMMA.
UM, WHERE'S YOUR BOYFRIEND?
NOT HERE, IS HE?
OKAY, WITH AN OLD BIKE,
AND A LITTLE EFFORT,
AND A FEW TOOLS, YOU CAN HELP
PEOPLE ALL OVER THE WORLD.
WHEN WE... WHEN I FIRST BEGAN
THE RE-CYCLING TOUR...
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
CAN WE JUST
WATCH THE VIDEO?
SURE.
GUYS, WHY DON'T WE WATCH
THIS EXCITING VIDEO OVER HERE
FOR A SECOND?
MR. PERINO:
SO, I TRUST YOU'VE ALL
COME UP WITH DEBATE TOPICS
FROM VARIOUS MEDIA?
DANNY:
SIR? I FOUND SOMETHING
IN OUR VERY OWN ANTI-GRAPEVINE.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S HEAR IT.
"DEAR READERS,
WHO SHOULD PAY ON A FIRST DATE?
SHOULD EACH PAY THEIR SHARE,
OR SHOULD THEY SPLIT 50/50?"
MALE STUDENT:
EACH PAYS THEIR SHARE.
SEE, THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
IT WAS A BUCK TWENTY-FIVE,
DANNY!
WHAT'S SO WRONG
WITH SPLITTING?
IF I COVERED A PORTION
OF YOUR COSTS,
ISN'T THAT PATRONIZING?
ISN'T MATH
THE ENEMY OF ROMANCE?
(CLASS LAUGHS)
HERE I THOUGHT FEMINISM
WAS ALIVE AND WELL.
WHAT ABOUT SAME-SEX COUPLES?
CHANTAY:
GUYS! I DON'T CARE
ABOUT THE MONEY!
I JUST ASKED A QUESTION!
MALE STUDENT:
SOUNDS LIKE YOU DON'T
LIKE THE ANSWER.
♪♪♪♪♪
(STUDENTS APPLAUD)
EMMA:
OKAY, UM, BEFORE WE
GET COVERED IN BIKE GREASE,
ARE THERE ANY QUESTIONS?
ALLI:
UM, YOU GO TO SMITHDALE,
RIGHT?
I MEAN, WHAT'S IT LIKE?
SCHOOL, WHATEVER,
BUT WHAT ABOUT LIKE,
FROSH WEEK?
AND DORM PARTIES!
DO YOU HAVE A QUESTION
ABOUT THE RE-CYCLING PROJECT,
OR ARE YOU ONLY CONCERNED
WITH MY SOCIAL LIFE?
ALLI:
FIX BIKES,
AND GIVE THEM TO THE POOR.
I GET IT! SO, DOES YOUR REZ
HAVE LIKE, COED WASHROOMS?
OKAY, YOU WANNA TALK
UNIVERSITY?
FIRST OF ALL,
IT'S NOT FUN.
ALLI:
UM, EXCUSE ME?
NO PARENTS, NO CURFEW,
NO RULES?
HOW CAN IT NOT BE FUN?
YOU'RE BROKE,
...STRESSED,
LONELY,
YOU SKIP 18TH CENTURY LIT
TO TRY AND MAKE FRIENDS,
THEN YOU MEET A GUY WHO SAYS
HE'S TOTALLY COMMITTED,
BUT HE BAILS WITHOUT WARNING
TO GET A REAL JOB-
THE LESSON HERE IS,
IS THAT UM,
UNIVERSITY'S HARD WORK,
BUT SO WORTH IT,
RIGHT?
I'M FAILING, SNAKE.
YOU'RE FAILING?
I DON'T WANT TO GO BACK.
WE'LL DISCUSS THIS AT HOME.
SO, WHO WANTS
TO FIX SOME BIKES?
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
CHANTAY:
HOLD ON.
I GUESS THE CHANTAY-DANNY
EXPERIMENT IS A BUST.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
IF YOU HAVE A PROBLEM,
TALK TO ME IN PERSON,
NOT IN FRONT
OF THE WHOLE CLASS.
YOU BLOGGED THAT I WAS CHEAP
TO THE WHOLE WORLD!
DANNY, I POSED
AN ETHICAL QUESTION,
SO READERS WOULD COMMENT.
GOSSIP NEEDS CONTROVERSY,
DUMMY!
SO YOU DON'T THINK
I'M CHEAP?
NO. BUT YOU MIGHT BE
A JERK.
SO, YOU'RE GONNA HIDE OUT
HERE ALL DAY?
NO, I'M GONNA HIDE OUT
HERE FOREVER.
WELL, WOULD YOU AT LEAST
LIKE SOMETHING
TO GO WITH THAT SELF-PITY?
MORE COFFEE, TEA?
SORRY, WE DON'T SERVE
THE STRONG STUFF.
GET ME...
A DOUBLE-DOT BURGER.
WITH BACON.
WHAT, SERIOUSLY?!
THERE'S NO POINT
TO BEING VEG.
OR TO ANYTHING ELSE
THAT I DO.
I MIGHT AS WELL SEE
WHAT I'VE BEEN MISSING.
REBOUND EATING?
THAT'S NO WAY TO END UP
IN THE WONDERFUL WORLD OF MEAT.
NO, NO, NO.
NO DEAL.
CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
YES.
WHEN YOUR FRIENDS
WENT AWAY TO UNIVERSITY,
DID YOU FEEL LIKE YOU DIDN'T
LIVE UP TO EXPECTATIONS?
WHOSE EXPECTATIONS?
YEAH, MAYBE A LITTLE.
BUT NOW,
I HAVE MY JOB,
MY LOFT, MY BAND.
JANE.
SO, STAYING HERE
WAS JUST... ME.
AND YOU'RE HAPPY?
YEAH.
I'M JEALOUS.
HOLLY J:
SORRY I'M LATE!
SPINNER:
AGAIN.
HEY, I'VE GOT TWO JOBS,
TAE-KWON-DO,
AND MEETINGS,
MEETINGS, MEETINGS!
DROWNING YOUR SORROWS?
JUST PUTTING THEM OFF.
I'M SORRY ABOUT
THE OUTBURST.
MEH. IT WASN'T
THE WORST THING
YOU'VE DONE IN FRONT
OF THE ENTIRE SCHOOL.
'LEAST YOU KEPT
YOUR CLOTHES ON!
HEY!
(LAUGHS)
WHAT WAS WRONG
WITH ME BACK THEN?
HOLLY J:
I KINDA THOUGHT IT WAS AMAZING
HOW YOU'D DO ANYTHING
FOR YOUR BELIEFS,
EVEN IF THEY WERE INSANE.
I WAS PRETTY BAD-ASS,
WASN'T I?
SPIKE:
YOU'RE DROPPING OUT?!
MR. SIMPSON:
LOOK, LOOK. YOU'RE IN A FRAGILE
EMOTIONAL STATE RIGHT NOW,
MAKING RASH DECISIONS.
MANNY WENT TO HOLLYWOOD,
LIBERTY JOINED A SORORITY,
MY MARKS SUCK!
WHY WOULD I GO BACK?
TO GET A WELL ROUNDED
EDUCATION? HMM?
TO GET A JOB?
EMMA, THIS IS YOUR FUTURE
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT!
UNIVERSITY'S NOT FOR EVERYONE!
I MEAN, YOU DROPPED OUT MOM,
AND YOU DID OKAY.
YEAH, FOR SOMEONE
WHO GOT PREGNANT AT 14!
BUT YOU KNOW, EM,
I DIDN'T ALWAYS DREAM
OF BECOMING A HAIRDRESSER!
WELL, SORRY,
I CRAMPED YOUR STYLE.
I ALWAYS WANTED YOU
TO HAVE MORE.
MORE CHOICES.
MORE OPPORTUNITIES.
BUT NOBODY WANTS YOU
TO BE UNHAPPY.
EMMA,
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
I WANT TO HELP PEOPLE.
SOUNDS NAIVE, I KNOW.
SOUNDS LIKE THE EM
WE USED TO KNOW.
I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT
MAYBE TAKING A GAP YEAR.
JUST TO FIGURE OUT
IF SMITHDALE'S RIGHT FOR ME.
AND, I WANNA GO TO UNIVERSITY
SOMEWHERE, SOMEDAY, I JUST...
AT SMITHDALE, I WAS ONLY HAPPY
WHEN I WAS WITH KELLY.
AND, I DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN DO
THE RE-CYCLING TOUR
WITHOUT HIM.
EM, IF YOU REALLY WANT
TO HELP PEOPLE,
DO YOU HAVE TO BE
WITH A GUY TO DO IT?
DANNY:
CHANTAY!
CHANTAY, WAIT!
THIS IS FOR FRITZ HELDER
AND THE PHANTOM'S
SOLD OUT SHOW!
IN TWO MONTHS.
AND, UH, I HOPE
WE'RE STILL TOGETHER FOR IT.
OKAY.
SO WHAT DO I OWE YOU?
FORTY BUCKS,
PLUS SERVICE CHARGES.
UH, MINUS THE COST
OF ONE LATTE.
I UH, I GUESS
YOU WERE RIGHT.
I'M NOT MUCH FOR BEING
A PUBLIC FIGURE.
THE BLOG'S A REFLECTION
OF MY LIFE, DANNY.
AND YOU'RE A PART OF THAT.
BUT NEXT TIME I MENTION US,
I'LL RUN IT BY YOU FIRST.
SOUNDS GOOD.
WALK YOU TO CLASS?
RIGHT AFTER THIS.
(SMOOCH)
PICK UP THE PACE!
EMMA:
UH...
WHERE DID ALL THESE
BIKES COME FROM?
I THOUGHT YOU
ONLY HAD 12 DONATIONS?
I MADE SOME CALLS.
WHAT CAN I SAY,
I WAS INSPIRED.
AND, A SISTA' WAS IN NEED.
THANK YOU, HOLLY J.
HEY!
THE GANG'S HERE.
LISTEN,
KEEP IN TOUCH, OKAY?
YEAH, THAT'S WHAT
THE INTERNET'S FOR.
YOU NEVER KNOW, I MIGHT BE
AROUND TO BOTHER YOU
DURING YOUR SENIOR YEAR.
WELL, WE CAN ALWAYS USE
AN INTERESTING GUEST-SPEAKER.
MR. SIMPSON:
EMMA! YOUR FRIENDS ARE WAITING!
BE CAREFUL. PLEASE.
CALL IF YOU NEED ANYTHING,
ALL RIGHT?
I'LL BE FINE ON MY OWN.
I LOVE YOU.
♪ Strugglin' to work it out ♪
♪ Here I am now ♪
♪ Work it out ♪