(GROUP OF BUSKERS PLAY
UPBEAT MUSIC)
MAN:
HEY! FEED THE CASE!
IT'S HUNGRY FOR CASH.
JUST LIKE US!
(BAND SINGS)
BAND MEMBER: HUNGRY!
BAND MEMBER:
♪ OH... ♪
♪ YEAH-EAH YEAH! ♪
BAND:
♪ WHERE WE'RE GOING
I DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ OH... OH, OH, OH! ♪
(DOG BARKS)
GO! GO!
MAN:
WHOA! WHOA!
MARLEY! MARLEY!
MAN: MARLEY, COME HERE!
JANE: OH HEY!
MARLEY, WAIT!
NO, NO, NO, MARLEY!
MARLEY, GET OUTTA THERE!
HEY!
I'M SO SORRY.
OH... NO, IT'S COOL.
I'M A DOG PERSON.
AND HE HAS GOOD TASTE
IN WOMEN.
SO, UM...
CHECKING OUT THE BUSKERS?
OH YEAH, UM...
THE TALENT IN THIS CITY...
MAKES ME ASHAMED
TO CALL MYSELF A SINGER.
YOU SING?
YEAH.
LIKE, IN A BAND?
UNTIL RECENTLY.
LONG STORY.
YEAH, IT OFTEN IS.
I'M GEORGE.
ANE.
HI.
I.
WELL, JANE. UM...
YOU WOULDN'T HAPPEN TO BE
LOOKING FOR YOUR NEXT GIG,
WOULD YOU?
ALL RIGHT, MY BAND,
UH, FRIDAY,
WE GOT THIS LIVE TV GIG
THING.
IT'S THE BREAK
WE'VE BEEN WAITING FOR.
AND YOU GOT ALL THIS
WITHOUT A SINGER?
(LAUGHS)
OUR, UH, LEAD SINGER
DECIDED TO PURSUE
A SOLO CAREER.
I GUESS NOW I KNOW
HOW NO DOUBT FELT.
SO LOOK, UH, I MEAN WE'VE
BEEN AUDITIONING PEOPLE
FOR LIKE A WEEK.
IF YOU WANNA, WHY DON'T YOU
COME BY TOMORROW
AND SHOW US YOUR STUFF.
SURE. OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
CLUB ON FOURTEENTH.
UH, WAIT!
HOW WILL I KNOW YOUR SONGS?
MYSPACE.
FLASHIN' MIDNIGHT.
SWEET! UH, NICE TO MEET YOU,
GEORGE.
RIGHT PLACE,
RIGHT TIME.
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know
I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ I know
I can make it through ♪
♪ Woo-oo-oo-ooo ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever
Woo-oo-oo-ooo ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know
I can make it through ♪
(SIRENS WAIL IN THE DISTANCE)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
WELL, THERE GOES MY SUMMER
CLOTHING BUDGET.
STYLISH AND BROKE.
VERY MANHATTAN.
FIONA:
THOUGHT YOU'D BEEN KIDNAPPED
BY ROCKETTES.
TAKES TIME TO COVER
A HUNDRED CITY BLOCKS.
YEAH. LUISA WANTS TO KNOW
WHAT WE WANT FOR DINNER.
UH, WE HAVE RESERVATIONS
AT TAILOR FOR DESSERT.
OOH, MANCHEGO CHEESECAKE.
YUM!
UH, RESERVATIONS FOR TWO.
I'M GONNA GO CHANGE.
J'ADORE THAT CHEESECAKE.
COME ON, FI.
HOLLY J STARTS WORK TOMORROW.
AND SHE'S REALLY BEEN LOOKING
FORWARD TO THE STAY.
ARE YOU TWO GONNA COUPLE-OUT
ALL SUMMER?
IT'S KINDA THE POINT.
SO WHAT AM I SUPPOSED
TO DO?
I'M SURE YOU'LL FIND SOMETHING
TO KEEP YOURSELF BUSY.
(STREET BUZZES WITH CHATTER,
TRAFFIC RUMBLES ALONG)
(EXHALES)
OH, CUTE SHOES!
OH, THANKS.
JAY MANUEL?!
WOW, DO YOU WORK HERE?
BECAUSE IF YOU DO I...
I GUESS WE'RE CO-WORKERS.
I'M JUST AN INTERN,
BUT...
LET ME GUESS.
FIRST DAY ON THE JOB?
YUP. TVM.
I'M REPORTING TO KRISTIN.
(TIGHT INHALE)
OOH...
WHAT? WHY'RE YOU MAKING
THAT FACE?
NO REASON.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'LL DO GREAT,
AS LONG AS YOU AVOID
BREATHING WITH YOUR MOUTH
AND EYE CONTACT.
GOOD LUCK.
(OFFICE BUZZES WITH CHATTER)
KRISTIN:
OKAY, WHEN I SAY NOW,
I MEAN NOW!
GOT IT, INTERNS?
HI. KRISTIN?
I'M HOLLY J SINCLAIR.
NEW INTERN?
HOLLY J? LITTLE INITIAL.
THAT'S CUTE.
I'M KRISTIN, NO INITIAL,
BUT YOU KNOW THAT.
JOB NUMBER ONE:
BANANA.
I HAVE A THING
FOR POTASSIUM.
GOT IT?
OTHER THAN THAT,
PHOTOCOPY, GET COFFEE,
STAY OUTTA THE SHOTS.
KRISTIN, HAVE YOU SEEN
MY DEMO REEL?
OH...
'COURSE NOT, SWEETIE.
OTHER PEOPLE
TAKE CARE OF THAT.
OH.
I WAS JUST WONDERING,
BECAUSE AT SCHOOL I USED TO DO
THE ON-AIR ANNOUN-
UH, OKAY, WALK
BEFORE YOU CAN RUN, INTERN.
FI-FI!
FIONA:
HEY, KRISTIN.
(KISSES)
PUT ME TO WORK!
EVERYBODY!
(SNAPS FINGERS)
FIONA COYNE.
YOU KNOW HER
FROM THE SOCIETY PAGES.
SHE'LL BE HELPING OUT.
WAIT, YOU'RE AN INTERN?
HERE?
SORT OF.
DECLAN SAYS
I SHOULD KEEP BUSY.
SO YOU JUST WALKED IN?
THE COYNE NAME OPENS
A LOT OF DOORS.
WARDROBE CONSULT?
SOME BAND INTERVIEW FRIDAY.
GOTTA LOOK INDIE!
FIONA:
SURE, KRISTIN.
ANYTIME!
(HUFFS)
♪♪♪♪♪
(GIRL SINGS,
AUDITIONING FOR THE BAND)
(BAND ENDS AUDITION DEMO)
WELL, THAT WAS GREAT.
THANKS.
WE'LL, UH...
WE'LL LET YOU KNOW.
JANE:
HEY, GUYS. HEY.
UM, YOU STILL LOOKING
FOR A NEW SINGER?
JANE! GUYS, THIS IS THE GIRL
I WAS TELLING YOU ABOUT -
ATTACKED MY DOG
TO GET AN AUDITION.
NO. NO,
I DID NOT DO THAT!
MM. YOU KNOW THE SONGS?
NO. UM, I JUST STOPPED BY
SO I COULD GET YOUR AUTOGRAPH.
SASSY! I LIKE THAT!
BUT I AM EXPECTING YOU
TO TAKE US TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
COME ON.
OKAY. NO PRESSURE.
NO PRESSURE.
(BAND STARTS A SLOW TEMPO INTRO)
(CYMBALS CHING)
(DRUMS BEAT LIGHTLY)
(TEMPO OF SONG PICKS UP)
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ THE SUMMER NIGHT
IS CLINGING TO US ♪
♪ LIKE BREATH
AGAINST MY SKIN ♪
♪ A STREAM MOVES
LIKE A RUMOR ♪
♪ YOU CAN HEAR IT SPIN ♪
♪ I WANNA JUMP ACROSS
THE ROOFTOPS ♪
♪ FROM HERE TO WAY DOWNTOWN ♪
♪ SAIL ABOVE THE CITY
NEVER LOOKING DOWN ♪
♪ I'M NOT THE ONLY ONE
WHO HEARS THE BELLS ♪
♪ OR THE MUSIC
FROM A NEARBY CAROUSEL ♪
♪ EVERY BREATH
IS A THING OF WONDER ♪
♪ SO LIGHT
THAT IT FLOATS AWAY ♪
♪ LIFE'S A SPELL THAT
WE'VE FALLEN UNDER ♪
♪ IT'S HERE TODAY ♪
♪ EVERY MOMENT'S A REVELATION ♪
♪ MAKE IT UP
AS WE GO ALONG ♪
♪ LET ME SPEND THIS ONE
WITH YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE IT'S HERE TODAY ♪
♪ GOOD TODAY ♪
♪ EVERY BREATH
IS A THING OF WONDER ♪
♪ SO LIGHT
THAT IT FLOATS AWAY ♪
♪ LIFE'S A SPELL
THAT WE'VE FALLEN UNDER ♪
♪ IT'S HERE TODAY ♪
♪ EVERY MOMENT'S A REVELATION ♪
♪ MAKE IT UP
AS WE GO ALONG ♪
♪ LET ME SPEND THIS ONE
WITH YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE IT'S HERE TODAY ♪
♪ IT'S GOOD TODAY ♪
♪ ONLY HERE TODAY ♪
♪ AND GONE ♪
HOLLY J:
I EARNED THAT INTERNSHIP.
AND THEN FIONA JUST WALTZES IN,
AND VOILA!
SHE'S KRISTIN'S
GIGGLY LAPDOG!
MAYBE FIONA JUST WANTED
TO SPEND SOME TIME WITH YOU.
SHE DOESN'T HAVE
MANY FRIENDS.
WELL, DID SHE HAVE
TO STEAL MY THING?
CAN'T IT BE BOTH
YOUR THING?
JANE:
GUYS! GUYS-GUYS-GUYS!
YOU ARE LOOKING
AT THE NEW SINGER
FOR FLASHING MIDNIGHT!
(JANE AND HOLLY J
GIGGLE HAPPILY)
HOLLY J:
CONGRATS!
WHEN CAN WE COME WATCH YOU?
I'M COMING TO YOU,
FRIDAY.
WE'RE PLAYING LIVE AT TVM!
THAT'S YOU?
KRISTIN'S DOING AN INTERVIEW!
HOLLY J AND JANE:
(GIGGLE EXCITEDLY)
I LOVE NEW YORK!
(EXCITED SQUEALS
AND LAUGHTER)
(SIRENS WAIL IN THE DISTANCE,
TRAFFIC RUMBLES ALONG)
COULDN'T FIND THE DOOR
OUT OF YOUR ROOM?
UH, WE OVERSLEPT.
FIONA:
SURE.
WE NEED TO BE WELL RESTED
FOR "LA TRAVIATA" TONIGHT.
MMM.
THAT WOULD BE TWO
OPERA TICKETS, I ASSUME?
DECLAN:
SORRY, FI. IT'S JUST HOLLY J'S
BEEN TALKING ABOUT IT.
IT'S FINE, DECLAN!
DON'T LET ME CRASH
YOUR LOVE PARTY.
THANKS, FI.
READY TO GO MAKE SOME TV?
MM, LET'S DO IT!
PICK YOU UP AFTER WORK?
(EXHALES)
(SPINNER EXHALES)
EMMA:
HEY.
SO... I HEAR JANE LEFT.
DO YOU WANNA TALK?
REALLY DON'T.
I'M DOING MY BEST
TO FORGET HER.
SO...
WE PLAY HORSE INSTEAD.
GIMME THE BALL.
(BALL CLUNKS)
YOU PLAY BASKETBALL?
ONLY IF I CAN BE SKIN.
YEAH, THAT, I'D LIKE TO SEE.
(HALF LAUGHS)
I MADE YOU SMILE!
LET'S SEE WHAT YOU GOT.
(SHOES SCUFF ON PAVEMENT)
EMMA:
AH! I GOT IT IN!
I GOT IT IN!
(EMMA LAUGHS PLAYFULLY)
SPINNER:
AW!
EMMA:
(EXCITED SQUEAL)
(LAUGHS)
ALL RIGHT, MAN.
BE GOOD.
SEE YA.
THANK YOU.
BYE, GUYS.
GOOD REHEARSAL.
GEORGE:
WHAT'S WITH THE WARPAINT?
I MEAN, EVERY TAT
HAS A STORY, RIGHT?
YEAH, UM....
ACTUALLY, I ALMOST FORGOT
IT WAS THERE.
OUTTA SIGHT, OUTTA MIND.
RIGHT?
SOME THINGS ARE BETTER
THAT WAY.
(TRAFFIC HUMS,
HORNS HONK)
OKAY...
OKAY!
(SNAPS FINGERS)
TOMORROW -
FLASHIN' MIDNIGHT.
INDIE BAND,
LOTS OF BUZZ.
APPARENTLY THEY HAVE
A NEW LEAD SINGER.
YEAH, JANE VAUGHN.
MY FRIEND.
OH.
YOURS TOO?
THAT'S RANDOM.
HUH?
I SPILLED.
I TOLD KRISTIN ABOUT HOW JANE
AND I ARE TOTES BFFS.
KRISTIN:
AND WE THOUGHT IT WOULD BE NEAT
FOR OUR RESIDENT CELEBUTANTE
TO INTERVIEW THE NEW SINGER!
FIONA:
I'D LOVE FOR YOU TO DO
THE RESEARCH, HOLLY J.
I MEAN...
YOU KINDA KNOW JANE.
I'VE NEVER HEARD
OF THE BAND.
WELL, GOOD THING YOU HAVE
ALL NIGHT, INITIAL!
OKAY, YOU ALL KNOW
WHAT TO DO.
(SNAPS HER FINGERS
AT THE INTERNS)
SO SORRY ABOUT
YOUR OPERA PLANS.
TA!
DECLAN:
HOW GOES "DA BIZ,"
AS WE SAY IN DA BIZ?
I'VE HAD BETTER DAYS.
DIDN'T YOU GET MY TEXT?
I WON'T BE NEEDING
THE DRESS.
I KNOW.
FIONA:
DECLAN!
THANK YOU!
FIONA ASKED ME
TO TAKE HER.
I DIDN'T WANT THE TICKET
TO GO TO WASTE.
YOU TWO HAVE FUN.
OPERA IT UP.
THANKS, HOLLY J.
(SIGHS IN DISBELIEF)
(TRAFFIC WHIRS)
MAN: (ON TV)
...PRACTICAL REPRODUCTION.
SO, THE GRADE NINES ARE GETTING
THIS TREMENDOUS EXPERIENCE
OF COMING OUT HERE,
ACTUALLY SEEING THE PROCESS
IN THE STREAM,
COLLECTING THE EGGS,
BRINGING THEM BACK TO STUDY
THEIR DEVELOPMENT IN THE...
WHAT?
JAY:
ALL RIGHT, OFF THE COUCH,
DRUMMER BOY!
EMMA: COME ON.
SPINNER: WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
WE'RE KIDNAPPING YOU.
EM SAID YOU NEEDED FUN,
SO FUN IT IS!
LIKE IT OR NOT!
YOU SAID THAT?
EMMA:
YOU THINK A COUPLE GAMES
OF HORSE
WERE GONNA CUT IT?
WH-WHERE ARE WE GOING?
COME ON.
WE CAN'T TELL YOU.
HAVEN'T YOU EVER BEEN
HELD HOSTAGE BEFORE?
SPINNER:
YES, I HAVE!
CAN I GRAB PANTS, PLEASE?
I'M ALL OVER IT.
(BUZZ OF EXCITED CHATTER,
TELEPHONES RING)
LAINEY!
KRISTIN!
THAT LAST BLIND ITEM
ON YOUR BLOG?
LOVED IT!
, I'M GLAD YOU WERE
"BORROW" IT
FOR THE GOSSIP MINUTE.
SOMEDAY YOU'LL HAVE
YOUR OWN SHOW, SWEETIE.
LAINEY:
WHY? SO I CAN BE
JUST LIKE YOU?
PLAGIARISTA.
KRISTIN:
PARASITE.
INITIAL!
TRAVEL FI TO SET.
HOLLY J:
IT'S HOLLY J, AND SURE.
KRISTIN WANTS YOU ON SET.
FIONA:
IS THERE ANY COFFEE?
DECLAN AND I GOT IN SO LATE
LAST NIGHT.
AND I GOT IN
TWO HOURS LATER,
SO, FETCH YOUR OWN COFFEE.
WE HAD SUCH A BLAST
AT THE MET.
IT WAS JUST LIKE
OLD TIMES.
HOLLY J:
AS IN, BEFORE MY TIME?
HOLLY J, I PUT UP WITH YOU
AT DEGRASSI,
BUT YOU'RE IN MY CITY NOW.
EXCUSE ME?!
YOU DON'T FIT IN HERE,
AND I THINK IT'S TIME
YOU WENT HOME.
HUH. WELL, I WONDER
WHAT MY BOYFRIEND
WOULD THINK ABOUT THAT?
BOYFRIENDS ARE TEMPORARY;
BROTHERS ARE FOREVER.
YOU'RE NOT GETTING RID
OF ME.
AND WHAT'RE YOU GONNA DO
ABOUT IT, MS. INTERN?
♪ If you don't like
how I talk ♪
YOU'LL BE NEEDING YOUR RESEARCH
FOR THE INTERVIEW.
♪ Just know I'm walking
my walk ♪
♪ And baby you can k-i-s-s
my derriere ♪
LOOK!
WHAT?
(KEYPAD BEEPS)
HOLLY J!
DON'T YOU DARE LOCK ME
IN HERE!
BYE-BYE, FIONA.
THIS IS NEW YORK HOLLY J,
BITCH.
I'M SORRY,
MAYBE I WASN'T CLEAR.
I TOLD YOU TO FIND HER
IN THE BUILDING.
YOU- NO- NOTHING.
BLANK.
YOU'RE JUST GONNA
LOOK AT ME BLANKLY?
ARE YOU GONNA GIVE ME
A BANANA?
I DON'T WANT IT,
BUT YOU COULD GIVE IT TO ME.
IS THERE A REASON I SHOULD BE
KEEPING YOU AROUND?
HOLLY J!
HEY.
NAMES, PROFILES,
INFLUENCES, REVIEWS.
PLUS A SPECIAL SECTION
ON THE NEW LEAD SINGER.
I'M SORRY,
WHERE THE HELL IS FIONA?
I'VE BEEN LOOKING
ALL OVER FOR HER.
FLAKY SOCIALITE INTERNS!
THERE'S NO WAY YOU CAN GET
THROUGH ALL THIS RIGHT NOW!
HOW'RE YOU GONNA DO
THE INTERVIEW?
OH MY GOD.
KRISTIN, I WAS UP
ALL NIGHT RESEARCHING.
I KNOW THIS.
I'M SORRY,
YOU WANNA DO THE INTERVIEW?
JANE:
UM, ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
SHE WAS BORN FOR THIS.
ONE MINUTE,
CHATTY CHAT CHAT,
THEN THE BAND PLAYS.
GOT IT?
♪ Yeah, we're ready for this ♪
♪ 'Cause we're ready
Are you we're ready? ♪
♪ Yeah, we're ready for this ♪
♪ 'Cause we're ready ♪
KRISTIN:
AND WE'RE BACK
WITH FLASHING MIDNIGHT!
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
KRISTIN:
AND THEY'RE NOT THE ONLY ONES
MAKING THEIR TV DEBUT.
TURNS OUT, OUR INTERN IS BFFS
WITH THEIR LEAD SINGER,
JANE VAUGHN.
IT'S ALL YOURS, HOLLY J.
HOLLY J:
SO, JANE, TELL ME,
HOW DOES A HIGH SCHOOL SENIOR
WITH A BABYSITTING BUSINESS
BECOME LEAD SINGER
IN A BREAKOUT INDIE BAND?
WELL, SOMETIMES GOOD THINGS
DO COME OUT OF A BREAKUP...
(TITTERS)
(THE FALLS THUNDER LOUDLY)
JAY:
I CAN'T BELIEVE
WE MADE IT HERE.
(MANNY GIGGLES)
SPINNER:
WHOA!
JAY:
WELCOME TO GAMBLER'S PARADISE!
HUH?
SPINNER:
THIS IS AWESOME!
I'VE NEVER BEEN TO A CASINO!
MANNY:
EMMA THOUGHT YOU'D LIKE IT.
EMMA:
REMEMBER, GUYS,
WHAT HAPPENS IN NIAGARA FALLS,
STAYS IN NIAGARA FALLS.
SPINNER:
ALL RIGHT, SO WHAT FIRST?
SLOTS?
OH, PLEASE!
YOU WANNA WIN,
YOU GOTTA PLAY
WITH THE BIG BOYS.
SPINNER:
HOLY COW! WHERE'D YOU LEARN
TO PLAY LIKE THIS?
IN THE DORMS.
A LOT OF LATE-NIGHT
CARD TOURNAMENTS.
SO MUCH FOR HIGHER
EDUCATION.
WHO NEEDS EDUCATION
WHEN YOU HAVE LUCK?
I WOULDN'T KNOW.
ACTUALLY, YOU HAVE HEARD
ABOUT MY LIFE LATELY?
WELL, SOMETIMES YOU GOTTA
MAKE YOUR OWN LUCK.
HIT.
DEALER:
21! BLONDIE WINS!
GOING AGAIN?
SEE, THE KEY IS TO TAKE
BIG RISKS.
YOU'RE SOME CARD-PLAYING YODA,
YOU KNOW THAT?
EXCEPT...
WAY BETTER LOOKING.
WHOA!
SOMEONE'S ON A ROLL.
IT'S ALL THANKS
TO MY GOOD LUCK CHARM.
CHEERS.
GIVE IT UP
FOR FLASHING MIDNIGHT!
(AUDIENCE CHEERS WILDLY)
(BAND BEGINS SONG)
OH, I'M SORRY.
IN!
LOOK WHO DECIDED
TO SHOW UP!
NO, IT'S NOT MY FAULT!
HOLLY J LOCKED ME IN...
(KRISTIN YELLS AT FIONA,
FIONA CONTINUES TO PLEAD)
♪ DEAR DIARY,
DEAR RELIGION ♪
♪ DEAR VANITY
AND ADDICTION ♪
AND I DON'T WANNA SEE YOU
HERE EVER AGAIN!
THANK YOU!
JANE:
♪ YOUR MEMORY
AND SUPERSTITION LIE ♪
♪ ARE YOU TRYING TWIST
MY MIND ♪
♪ WHAT'S THE ANSWER? ♪
♪ MAYBE LOVE, MAYBE LOVE ♪
♪ MAYBE LOVE
WILL MAKE YOUR DAY ♪
♪ MAYBE LOVE, MAYBE LOVE ♪
♪ MAYBE LOVE
WILL SAVE YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ FROM DISASTER ♪
DEALER:
21! AGAIN!
(SQUEALS HAPPILY)
JAY:
HEY.
LOOKS LIKE PROJECT CHEER-UP
IS A SUCCESS.
WHICH IS WHY WE NEED
TO LEAVE THEM ALONE.
(CHUCKLES)
WE ARE UP ALMOST 2500!
DOLLARS?!
YOU ARE AMAZING!
HOW DO WE CELEBRATE?
DUDE, TONIGHT COULD NOT
GET ANY BETTER.
I'M... I'M SORRY.
DON'T BE.
JANE:
♪ MAYBE LOVE, MAYBE LOVE ♪
♪ MAYBE LOVE
WILL MAKE YOUR DAY ♪
♪ MAYBE LOVE, MAYBE LOVE ♪
♪ MAYBE LOVE
WILL SAVE YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ FROM DISASTER ♪
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ OOH, OOH, OOH ♪
♪ MAYBE, MAYBE LOVE ♪
DECLAN:
WHAT HAPPENED?!
(CRIES AND SNIFFLES)
HOLLY J...
JANE:
♪ OOH, OOH, OOH ♪
♪ MAYBE LOVE ♪
♪ MAYBE LOVE, MAYBE LOVE ♪
♪ MAYBE LOVE
WILL MAKE YOUR DAY ♪
♪ OOH, OOH, OOH ♪
♪ MAYBE LOVE, MAYBE LOVE ♪
♪ MAYBE LOVE
WILL SAVE YOUR LIFE ♪
DECLAN!
YOU MADE IT!
DID YOU SEE MY INTERVIEW?
WHAT DID YOU DO
TO MY SISTER?
WHAT DID I DO?
YOU'RE SISTER'S THE ONE-
DECLAN, CAN WE PLEASE
JUST GO HOME?
IS THAT HOW YOU GET YOUR WAY,
HOLLY J?
WHAT THE HELL'S
WRONG WITH YOU?
JANE:
♪ MAYBE LOVE WILL SAVE US ALL ♪
♪ FOREVER AFTER ♪
(BAND PLAYS FINAL NOTES
AND ENDS SONG)
(AUDIENCE CHEERS WILDLY)