WHAT'S PARIS
WITHOUT LIGHTS?
ANYA:
WHERE DID YOU GET THOSE?
AH, MY MOM WON'T NEED THESE
'TIL CHAAND RAAT.
THEY'RE PERFECT!
(GIGGLES)
SO... YOU READY FOR
OUR ENCHANTED EVENING?
YEAH! THE LIMO
WILL PICK YOU UP AT 7:00,
AFTER MY "OFFICIAL" DATE,
FARRAH, AND I
PICK UP DANNY, CHANTAY,
AND HER "UNOFFICIAL" DATE,
PETER.
I'M SORRY IT HAS TO BE
SO COMPLICATED.
IT'S OKAY,
IT'S JUST MORE TIME
TO MAKE MYSELF BEAUTIFUL
FOR YOU.
YOU'RE ALWAYS BEAUTIFUL.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
AS LONG AS WE'RE TOGETHER
AT THE END OF THE EVENING,
NOTHING ELSE MATTERS.
ABOUT THAT...
I STILL WANT TO,
BUT WITH FARRAH
AND HER FAMILY AT MY PLACE,
WE CAN'T BREAK CURFEW.
I'M SORRY.
THAT'S OKAY.
CAN YOU HELP ME STRING THESE
OVER THE ARC DE TRIOMPHE?
SURE.
OKAY.
'RE OKAY?
YEAH, I MEAN,
WHAT'S THE RUSH, RIGHT?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out
I know I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, whatever ♪
(Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
ALLI:
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE'RE HERE
ON A SATURDAY!
(SCOFFS) OKAY,
NINER CLASS REPS:
GYM DECORATING THIS AFT
AND PUNCH DUTY TONIGHT.
UH, WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
TONIGHT?
AT THE SPRING FORMAL?!
YOU AND DAVE WILL WORK
THE DRINKS TABLE.
IN FRONT OF EVERYONE?
HOLLY J:
NOT EVERYONE,
JUST ALL OF GRADE 11 AND 12.
DRESS NICE!
AS FOR THE SKIP-A-THON,
PLEDGE SHEETS ARE AVAILABLE
ONLINE.
THE MINIMUM TOTAL FOR EACH...
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
PET DIE?
THIS ISN'T EXACTLY
HOW I PICTURED GOING TO FORMAL.
HUH! YOU PICTURED
GOING TO FORMAL?
(SIGHS)
IT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
ONE OF THE POTENTIAL BENEFITS
OF DATING UP!
DIDN'T THAT JOHNNY GUY
TURN OUT TO BE A SLEAZEBAG?
YEAH, AND HE'S GONNA BE
THERE TONIGHT,
AND NOW I'M STAFF!
IT'S SUPER EMBARRASSING!
MAYBE I CAN
CALL IN SICK!
(SCOFFS)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
WILL YOU BE ACCESSORIZING
FOR THE FORMAL?
WHAT'S THE POINT?
SAV'S ALREADY GOT HIS GORGEOUS,
PARENT-APPROVED ACCESSORY.
YOU SAID YOURSELF
HE'S ONLY TAKING FARRAH
SO HE CAN GO WITH YOU.
(SIGHS)
NO MATTER WHAT,
SAV AND I ARE ALWAYS GOING
TO BE A STRUGGLE.
LOOK, PARENTS JUST WANT
THEIR KIDS TO BE HAPPY, RIGHT?
WHAT IF HE'S HAPPIER
WITH...
FARRAH?
YOU LOVE HIM, RIGHT?
HE'S WORTH FIGHTING FOR?
THEN HONEY,
WHAT DOES FARRAH HAVE
THAT YOU DON'T?
OTHER THAN HIS...
FAMILY'S APPROVAL?
(SIGHS)
NOTHING.
THEN GO TO THE FORMAL
AND PROVE IT!
(EARRINGS JANGLE)
(SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
♪ Boys and girls
are all fired up ♪
VA-VA-VA-VOOM!
YOU LIKE IT?
PETER:
HEY.
YOU LOOK NICE!
SAV:
LET'S GO!
(SHUTTER CLICKS)
♪ Boys and girls
are all fired up ♪
PETER:
WORK IT!
♪ Whole world's shaking, baby ♪
♪ Baby, I'm a rock idol ♪
YOU GUYS LOOK SO CUTE!
AWWW!
THAT'S AWESOME!
(GIGGLES)
OKAY, SAV,
NOW A FEW PHOTOS
FOR THE BHANDARI/HASSAN
FAMILIES?
YEAH, I GUESS I SHOULD
TAKE SOME PICTURES
WITH MY SO-CALLED "DATE."
MM-HM!
OH, OUR FIRST
PHOTO TOGETHER.
(AFFECTING AN ACCENT)
WHAT WILL OUR CHILDREN THINK?!
(CLEARS THROAT)
KIDDING!
(ANYA AND FARRAH LAUGH
UNCOMFORTABLY)
PETER:
OH. ANYA,
COULD YOU, UH...
UH, YOU'D BETTER
GET OUT OF THE PICTURE.
(LAUGHS UNCOMFORTABLY)
SAY "GHEE!"
SAV AND FARRAH:
GHEE! (LAUGHING)
ANYA:
GREAT!
THE LIMO'S WAITING.
OH! HOLD ON!
I JUST WANNA GET
A FEW SHOTS OF SAV
FOR MY COUSINS
BACK IN INDIA.
SAV:
OKAY...
DAVE:
YOU KNOW WHAT?
OUR DRINKS TABLE
NEEDS A SIGNATURE COCKTAIL.
WE'LL CALL IT...
THE BHANDURNER.
BHANDARI PLUS-
TURNER.
I GET IT.
RIGHT. OKAY,
SO, GINGER ALE...
UM...
CRANBERRY, LIME...
YOU ARE SO DORK-TASTIC!
NICE WORK,
MINOR NINERS!
DOES SHE HAVE
TO CALL US THAT?
HEY!
WHILE I GOT YOU,
YOU WANNA PLEDGE FOR
THE PLAN CANADA SKIP-A-THON?
ALLI AND I ARE IN IT.
UM, IT'S A FUNDRAISER
FOR GIRLS' EDUCATION
IN TOUGH PLACES.
COOL...
PUT ME DOWN
FOR $100.
RIGHT ON!
THANKS.
THE SKIP-A-THON?!
DID YOU HAVE TO TELL DECLAN,
OF ALL PEOPLE?
SEE, THIS IS WHY
I DON'T LIKE YOU.
HOW CAN YOU
NOT LIKE ME?
'CAUSE YOU'RE TOO COOL
FOR SCHOOL.
ALL RIGHT?
YOU'RE KIND OF A SNOB.
HOW AM I A SNOB
JUST BECAUSE
I DON'T WANNA SKIP ROPE?!
WHY DON'T YOU
WANNA?
SERIOUSLY,
GET OVER YOURSELF.
(GASPS)
♪ Hey hey-oh ♪
♪ When you're an army of one ♪
♪ You're ahead of the game
♪ Always second to none ♪
♪ And never one in the same ♪
(FABRIC RIPPING)
♪ You can be a radical ♪
FARRAH,
YOUR DRESS!
FARRAH:
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WAIT.
(LAUGHING)
YOU KNOW?
I LIKE IT BETTER
THIS WAY.
OKAY, SURE!
♪ Hold your head high ♪
♪ Hey hey ♪
♪ You're an individual ♪
♪ You can be invincible ♪
♪ Hey hey ♪
♪ Steppin' to the beat
of your drum ♪
♪ When you're an army of one ♪
♪ Hey hey ♪
♪ You're an individual ♪
♪ You can be invincible ♪
HELLO,
FUTURE MRS. BHANDARI!
I MEAN,
HYPOTHETICALLY.
(SCOFFS) PLEASE.
IT'S JUST AS LIKELY
I'LL MARRY YOU.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
UH, THE NATIVES CALL HIM
"PUTS-FOOT-IN-MOUTH."
(EVERYONE LAUGHS)
I WAS JOKING.
SAV'S LUCKY TO HAVE ANYA.
SHE'S SUCH A HOTTIE.
FARRAH:
MR. FOOT-IN-MOUTH IS RIGHT!
YOU LOOK AMAZING.
FRANKLY, I DON'T THINK SAV
DESERVES EITHER ONE OF US.
ANYA:
HE'S UH...
NOT EXACTLY THE MOST SUAVE.
(ANYA AND FARRAH LAUGH)
TWO COKES,
ONE PUNCH,
TWO VIRGIN CRANTINIS,
SHAKEN, NOT STIRRED.
JOHNNY, HEY.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
JOHNNY:
MAN!
THE SERVICE HERE
IS TERRIBLE.
BRUCE:
(SNICKERING)
AWFUL.
JOHNNY:
TWO COKES,
AND DON'T SPIT IN THEM.
HAVE YOU TRIED
THE BHANDURNER?
ALLI BHANDARI,
DAVE TURNER -
IT'S OUR HOUSE SPECIALTY.
100% SPIT-FREE.
A NICKEL
FOR YOUR TROUBLE.
BUY YOUR NINER FRIEND
SOME CANDY.
(SNICKERING)
TOO SNOBBY FOR YOU?
ANYA:
HEY!
HAVING FUN?
IT'S A LITTLE WEIRD,
BUT SAV'S FRIENDS ARE COOL.
COULD BE WORSE.
(SIGHS)
LOOK, FARRAH,
THANKS FOR GOING ALONG
WITH THIS WHOLE
"PRETENDING TO BE
SAV'S DATE" THING.
I WON'T HAVE TO PRETEND
FOR LONG.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
SEEMS TO ME YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO'S PRETENDING.
WE BOTH KNOW HOW
THIS IS GONNA WORK OUT.
I'M NOT SURE WE DO.
LET ME PAINT YOU
A PICTURE.
I LIKE SAV.
OUR FAMILIES WANT US
TO BE TOGETHER.
RIGHT NOW,
HE'S JUST BEING A GOOD GUY,
KEEPING YOU HAPPY.
BUT SOMEDAY SOON
YOU'LL BE HISTORY.
(SCOFFS)
BUT SAV WANTS TO BE
WITH ME.
HE HAS PLENTY OF TIME
TO CHANGE HIS MIND.
WHAT MAKES YOU
SO SURE?
(LAUGHS)
I JUST AM.
AND THERE'S NOTHING
YOU CAN DO ABOUT IT.
ENJOY THE DANCE!
SAV:
COME ON, HOLLY J!
CAN'T YOU JUST DO ME
THIS ONE FAVOUR?
UH, BUT WHAT ABOUT
THE SANCTITY OF THE VOTE?
RIGGING IT WOULD BE
DISHONEST, DECEITFUL...
DELICIOUSLY SCHEMEY!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE NOT SUPPORTING THIS.
♪ Look around, look around ♪
♪ Do you like what you see ♪
♪ Or is your world
a little wasted ♪
WOW!
WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
COME ON.
IT'S TIME.
FOR WHAT?
!
(GIGGLES)
UM, NOW?
BUT WHERE?
ANYA:
THIS WAY...
♪ Everybody say hey yeah ♪
♪ We're gonna raise
a little hell now ♪
♪ Hell now ♪
♪ Hey yeah ♪
♪ We're gonna raise
a little hell now ♪
♪ Hell now ♪
♪ Ready or not ♪
♪ Baby here we come ♪
♪ Gonna go all night
'til the morning sun ♪
♪ Everybody say hey yeah ♪
HEY FARRAH, HOW ABOUT A DANCE
WITH YOUR DATE?
OKAY!
MAYBE NOT.
♪ Feel the vibe
taking over the street ♪
♪ There's a new intoxication ♪
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT!
I MEAN WITH...
WITH FARRAH HERE,
I NEVER THOUGHT
THIS WOULD HAPPEN.
I DIDN'T BRING
ANY PROTECTION.
I'VE TAKEN CARE OF IT.
IT'S...
WHAT?
LIKE, LIKE, THE PILL?
COME HERE, YOU.
♪ We're gonna raise
a little hell now ♪
♪ Hell now ♪
♪ Hey yeah ♪
♪ Gonna raise a little
hell now, hell now ♪
(CROWD TALKING AND LAUGHING)
♪ You can't explain ♪
♪ Why it all seems so strange ♪
♪ You are rockin' this place ♪
♪ That you just can't escape ♪
♪ You know who they are ♪
♪ But you don't know
their names ♪
♪ And it's driving you insane ♪
CHECK IT!
THE BHANDURNER SLIDE.
(MAKING BEAT NOISES)
OH MY GOD,
NEVER DO THAT AGAIN!
ALL RIGHT,
CHECK IT, ALL RIGHT?
IN A FEW YEARS,
WE'LL BE HERE
AT FORMAL FOR REAL.
DO YOU KNOW HOW LONG
THAT SOUNDS?
WHAT'S THE RUSH?
DAVE!
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU,
BUT SOME PEOPLE
WANT TO GROW UP!
YEAH? MEANWHILE,
ALL THE FUN IN YOUR LIFE'S
PASSING YOU BY.
HAVE ANOTHER BHANDURNER.
ITS ACTUALLY
A GOOD DRINK!
YOU KNOW,
I'VE BEEN THINKING.
IT'S NOT JUST A DRINK,
ALL RIGHT?
IT'S A STATE OF MIND,
IT'S A DANCE MOVE.
A CLUB!
HELL, YEAH!
BHANDURNER'S A CLUB!
(GIGGLES)
NOW SHOW ME
THAT DANCE MOVE.
YOUR TURN!
YOU.
HEY...
(DISSOLVES INTO GIGGLES)
CHANTAY:
THERE YOU ARE!
I WAS BEGINNING TO THINK
THAT WE'D LOST YOU FOR GOOD!
ANYA:
OH...
WALK.
PHONE CALL.
(TAPS ON MIC)
HOLLY J:
HEY, DEGRASSI!
IT'S TIME TO ANNOUNCE
YOUR SPRING FORMAL ROYALTY.
(CHEERING AND APPLAUDING)
WHAT A SURPRISE!
YOUR "SPRINGTIME IN PARIS"
KING AND QUEEN ARE...
SAV BHANDARI
AND ANYA MCPHERSON!
STUDENTS:
AWWW!
(CHEERING AND APPLAUDING)
HOLLY J:
AND NOW,
I'D LIKE TO INVITE
THE KING AND QUEEN
TO THE FLOOR
FOR THEIR ROYAL DANCE.
♪ All these stars around ♪
♪ Let them shine on down ♪
♪ Shine all over you ♪
♪ The future isn't planned ♪
♪ Now I understand ♪
♪ What you're going through ♪
♪ But have no fear ♪
♪ I am here ♪
TIME TO GO.
OUR RIDICULOUSLY EARLY
CURFEW IS UP.
I'M SORRY, BABE.
NO, IT'S OKAY,
WE CAN DANCE ANY TIME.
THANKS,
YOU'RE THE BEST.
♪ I promised ♪
♪ To catch you
if you fall again ♪
♪ And I'll save you ♪
♪ Always ♪
(CELL PHONE BEEPING)
(PHONE BEEPS OFF)
(SIGHS) WELL,
THAT'S JUST GREAT.
(DECORATIONS RUSTLE VIOLENTLY)
TEXTING AND TIDYING,
A LETHAL COMBINATION.
SORRY.
SAV'S SUPPOSED
TO MEET ME HERE.
WE'LL BE OKAY.
THE NINERS GOT MOST
OF THE TRASH LAST NIGHT.
IT'S NOT THE POINT!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I DID SOMETHING
VERY STUPID LAST NIGHT.
OTHER THAN THE MACARENA?
I HAD SEX WITH SAV
IN THE LIMO.
IT'S CLICHE,
BUT...
NOT THE END
OF THE WORLD!
(SIGHS)
WE DIDN'T USE
PROTECTION.
WHAT?!
ANYA, THERE'S A CONDOM MACHINE
IN THE BATHROOM!
WHAT IF I'M PREGNANT?
HON...
YOU HAVE OPTIONS.
THE MORNING AFTER PILL?
RIGHT, BECAUSE INSTEAD
OF SPENDING
THE "MORNING AFTER"
WITH ME,
HE'S AT A "FAMILY BRUNCH"
WITH HIS FUTURE WIFE.
SOUNDS LIKE YOU TWO
HAVE A BIG TALK COMING.
OH, SURE, I'LL JUST GO WALTZ
RIGHT OVER TO HIS HOUSE.
YOU KNOW, HIS PARENTS
DON'T EVEN KNOW
WE'RE STILL TOGETHER?
IF SAV IS GROWN UP
ENOUGH TO HAVE SEX,
HE'S GROWN UP ENOUGH
TO TELL HIS PARENTS
HE HAS A GIRLFRIEND.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
HI.
HEY, UM...
I KNOW I SHOULDN'T
BE HERE,
BUT I NEED TO TALK
TO YOUR BROTHER?
UH,
HE WENT WITH MY DAD
TO TAKE THE HASSANS
TO THE AIRPORT.
BUT, UH, CALL HIM.
I NEED TO TALK TO HIM
FACE TO FACE.
YOU GUYS ARE SO INTENSE!
IT'S LIKE HIGH SCHOOL
DRAMA 24/7!
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT, ALLI.
IS THIS ABOUT
THE WHOLE FARRAH THING?
MRS. BHANDARI:
ALLI, WHO'S AT THE DOOR?
UH, NO ONE, MOM!
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE!
LOOK, I GOTTA GO!
BUT I'LL TELL SAV
TO CALL YOU.
(CELL PHONE BEEPING)
(SIGHS)
(BELL RINGS)
CHANTAY:
AND ONE LAST QUESTION
FOR OUR KING AND QUEEN:
WHERE DO YOU LOVEBIRDS
SEE YOURSELVES IN FIVE YEARS?
I DUNNO, ROCK STAR?
CHANTAY:
WITH ANYA,
QUEEN OF THE GROUPIES?
(GIGGLES)
SURE, WHY NOT?
I MIGHT EVEN BUY HER A CROWN
WITH ALL MY CASH.
AND A CASTLE?
SKY'S THE LIMIT, BABY.
WITH LITTLE PRINCES
AND PRINCESSES
RUNNING AROUND?
(SCOFFS)
YEAH, RIGHT!
I THOUGHT THIS WAS SUPPOSED
TO BE A FUN FANTASY!
WE BETTER GET TO CLASS.
(CAMERA BEEPS OFF)
WOULD IT REALLY BE
THE WORST THING?
WHAT?
YOU KNOW... A KID?
UH, YEAH, IT WOULD!
WHY ARE YOU SO OBSESSED
WITH KIDS ALL OF A SUDDEN?
WE MIGHT HAVE A PROBLEM.
ANYA. ANYA, YOU SAID
YOU WERE ON THE PILL.
YEAH, NOT SO MUCH.
YOU LIED!
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
(SIGHS)
IT WAS A MISTAKE!
I WASN'T...
I WASN'T THINKING!
OH MY GOD!
W ELSE AM I SUPPOSED
KEEP YOU
AWAY FROM FARRAH?!
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
I DON'T KNOW.
ALLI:
AND THE LITTLE PIGGY
WENT "WEE, WEE, WEE,
I'M A RUSSIAN DICTATOR!"
DAVE:
FOUR LEGS GOOD,
TWO LEGS BETTER!
(ALLI GIGGLES)
JOHNNY:
WAY TO PICK UP ON
THE POLITICAL SUBTEXT.
THOUGHT YOU WERE SMARTER
THAN THAT.
AND, UH, HOW DOES
YOUR OPINION COUNT?
YOU GOT A PROBLEM,
LITTLE MAN?
ALLI:
JOHNNY, STOP IT.
STOP WHAT? YOUR LITTLE NINER
BOYFRIEND GOT IN MY FACE.
ALLI:
HE'S NOT MY BOYFRIEND.
WE'RE IN A...
WE'RE IN A CLUB.
(LAUGHING)
A CLUB?
WHAT, DO YOU COLLECT
COMIC BOOKS?
DO YOU HAVE A TREE FORT?
(BRUCE LAUGHS MEANLY)
JOHNNY:
I KNOW I'M NOT ONE TO TALK,
BUT I NEVER THOUGHT
YOU WERE THIS LAME.
ANYWAYS, SO I WAS THINKING
A SECRET HANDSHAKE...
NO! I'M SORRY,
I TRIED,
BUT THE DRINK,
THE DANCE,
AND NOW THE HANDSHAKE?
JOHNNY'S RIGHT!
YOU'RE TURNING ME
INTO A LAME-O!
SORRY I CRAMPED YOUR STYLE.
(BAG RUSTLES)
THIS IS NOT THE PILL
I HAD IN MIND IN THE LIMO.
I KNOW.
MAYBE WE DON'T NEED IT.
IT WASN'T THE WORST TIME
IN MY CYCLE...
SAV:
CYCLE, SHMYCLE!
THIS PILL ONLY WORKS
UP TO 72 HOURS AFTER SEX.
YOU'D BETTER-
IT CAN MAKE ME
BARF FOR DAYS.
YOU KNOW WHAT BARFS
FOR MONTHS?
A BABY!
YOU'RE MAD,
I GET IT.
BUT I'M THE ONE
THAT HAS TO GO THROUGH THIS!
OKAY, I'M SORRY.
I'LL KEEP AN EYE ON YOU.
CAN I COME BACK
TO YOUR PLACE?
MAYBE WATCH SOME MOVIES
ON THE BLU-RAY?
YOU KNOW THAT YOU CAN'T!
(SIGHS) SO,
YOU CAN SLEEP WITH ME,
BUT YOU STILL CAN'T TELL
YOUR PARENTS ABOUT ME.
I WILL... EVENTUALLY.
EVENTUALLY OR NEVER?
I DON'T KNOW!
JUST... HERE.
DON'T TURN BOTH OUR LIVES
UPSIDE DOWN.
(RELIEVED SIGH)
(STUDENTS YELL ENCOURAGEMENT)
DOES THIS MEAN
YOU'RE BACK IN THE CLUB?
(SIGHS)
UM, MAYBE WE CAN
JUST BE FRIENDS INSTEAD?
(LAUGHS)
ALL RIGHT.
NO CLUB.
GOT IT.
LET'S SEE WHAT'CHA GOT!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(BELL RINGS)
HOW'RE YOU FEELING?
I'M OKAY.
BIT GROSS,
BUT I'M OKAY.
I'M SORRY, SAV.
FOR EVERYTHING.
YEAH, ME TOO.
DO YOU WANNA HAVE LUNCH
AND TALK?
I DON'T REALLY FEEL
LIKE TALKING.
WOULD YOU RATHER
TALK TO FARRAH?
SAV:
(SIGHS)
RIGHT NOW, I'M NOT SURE
I WANNA TALK TO ANYONE.
(SNIFFS)
SAV, ARE YOU BREAKING UP
WITH ME?
I CAN'T TRUST YOU
ANY MORE, ANYA.
I'M SORRY.
(CRYING)
HOLLY J:
ALL EYES WERE ON SAV BHANDARI
AND ANYA MACPHERSON
AT SPRING FORMAL.
DEGRASSI BLOGGER CHANTAY
CAUGHT UP WITH THE KING
AND QUEEN YESTERDAY.
CHANTAY:
"WHERE DO YOU LOVEBIRDS SEE
YOURSELVES IN FIVE YEARS?"
SAV:
"I DUNNO, A ROCKSTAR?"
CHANTAY:
"WITH ANYA,
QUEEN OF THE GROUPIES?"
SURE, WHY NOT?
I MIGHT EVEN BUY HER A CROWN
WITH ALL MY ROCK STAR CASH.
AND A CASTLE?
SKY'S THE LIMIT, BABY.
(HEARTBROKEN SIGH)