MATCHMAKER FORMS, PEOPLE!
FIND YOUR SECRET SWEETHEART
AT DEGRASSI.
GIRL:
THANKS.
DECLAN!
DO YOU WANT ONE?
ALL PROCEEDS GO
TO THE MUSICAL!
OH YEAH, I BOOKED THE MUSIC
ATRIUM AFTER SCHOOL.
SONGWRITER SHOWCASE.
YEAH, I SAW THAT.
I MOVED IT TO LUNCH.
ALL BOOKINGS GO THROUGH
"LA PRESIDENTA."
THAT WOULD BE ME.
PUNISHMENT FOR
DISOBEYING PROTOCOL?
IS DEGRASSI A DICTATORSHIP?
HOLLY J:
A BENEVOLENT ONE.
IF YOU COME AFTER SCHOOL,
YOU'RE DOUBLE-BOOKED
WITH THE STEEL DRUM BAND.
SEE YA.
NOW THAT'S A GIRL
WORTH FIGHTING FOR.
HOLLY J SINCLAIR?
YOU HAVE HEALTH INSURANCE,
RIGHT?
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out
I Know I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, whatever ♪
(Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever)!
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
SAV:
WHAT'CHA GOT?
MATCHMAKER FORMS!
FILL IN YOUR PROFILE
AND FIND YOUR SOUL MATE.
BEST TWO BUCKS
I'LL EVER SPEND!
SO...
WOULD I PICK A PENNY UP
OFF THE FLOOR?
YES, NO,
OR ONLY IF
NO ONE SAW ME.
UM...
YES?
ME TOO!
WHY ARE YOU ALL
FILLING THEM OUT
IF YOU'RE ALREADY
A COUPLE?
TO SEE IF WE'RE DESTINED
TO BE TOGETHER?
COME ON, DANNY!
YOU'RE JUST PICKING "C"
FOR EVERYTHING!
'CAUSE I HAVE AN ACTUAL
STANDARDIZED TEST!
I STILL CAN'T FIGURE OUT
NOUN DECLENSIONS.
CHANTAY:
LATIN A.P.?
KILLING ME TOO.
WHO NEEDS A DEAD LANGUAGE,
ANYWAY?
I DUNNO,
EVERYONE IN PRE-LAW?
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
OKAY.
LEX TEMPUS!
LATER, DUDES.
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
HOLLY J:
PAY TWO DOLLARS FOR MATCHMAKER
RESULTS THIS FRIDAY,
AKA DATE NIGHT!
(ECHOING OVER PA)
SPEAKING OF,
IF ANY OF YOU HAVE
LITTLE BROTHERS OR SISTERS,
THE PREMIUM BABYSITTING AGENCY'S
DATE NIGHT DROP-IN
OFFERS CHILD-CARE
FOR MOMS AND DADS
LOOKING FOR A NIGHT OUT.
DEGRASSI GYM FRIDAY,
FORTY DOLLARS A HEAD.
(SONG PLAYS IN HALLWAY)
♪ Every lover needs another ♪
♪ It's no wonder
you and I have found... ♪
WHAT THE...?
(HALF LAUGHS)
THE TESSAS ARE GIVING
A PRIVATE CONCERT
THIS FRIDAY,
I'VE GOT TWO
BACKSTAGE PASSES.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
THEY JUST PLAYED SNL,
AND IT'S THEIR LAST
SMALL VENUE GIG
BEFORE THE STADIUM TOUR.
STRINGS WERE PULLED!
THANKS,
BUT I'M BUSY.
(ASTONISHED SCOFF)
WHAT?
EARTH TO PLANET DECLAN,
I HATE THE TESSAS.
AND I'M WORKING FRIDAY
SO THAT EVERYONE ELSE
CAN GO ON A DATE!
DON'T YOU LISTEN?
COULDN'T YOU GET
SOMEONE TO COVER?
PLEASE, DECLAN.
YOU BARELY KNOW ME.
I'M...NOT YOUR TYPE.
IS THAT A CHALLENGE?
MORE OF AN OBSERVATION.
YOUR SO-CALLED
GIRLFRIENDS
HAVE EITHER BEEN ATTACHED
LIKE JANE,
OR...DITZY.
HEY!
TRISH IS VERY SWEET.
SHE'S A HOUSEPLANT.
YOU LIKE LOW-MAINTENANCE.
DATE A HONDA!
(LOCK CLICKS ON STALL DOOR)
DID YOU HEAR
HOW DANNY TALKS TO ME?
CHANTAY:
I'M SURE HE'S JUST STRESSED
ABOUT THE TEST.
(SIGHING HEAVILY)
DO YOU THINK
I'M LOSING HIM?
UH...
WHY WOULD YOU SAY THAT?
WE HAVE NOTHING
IN COMMON!
WE GO FOR COFFEE
AND JUST SIT THERE, MUTE.
SOUNDS LIKE HE TAKES YOU
FOR GRANTED.
IT'S LIKE I'M NOT EVEN THERE
SOMETIMES.
BUT...
I BET HE'D MISS YOU
IF YOU WERE GONE!
I WAS JUST READING
IN "SIZZLE TEEN,"
WHERE IS IT...
AHA!
"TEN WAYS TO RE-IGNITE
THE SPARK!"
NUMBER THREE:
"THE PRE-EMPTIVE STRIKE."
WHAT'S THAT?
IT'S WHERE YOU BREAK UP
WITH A GUY FIRST,
TO SHOW HIM WHO'S BOSS.
BUT THEN I'LL HAVE
NO BOYFRIEND!
ONLY 'TIL HE SEES
WHAT HE'S MISSING.
Y-YOU REALLY THINK
THAT'LL WORK?
IT'S A CLASSIC MOVE,
TRUST ME.
PRE-EMPTIVE STRIKE,
HUH?
I'LL GIVE IT A TRY.
THANKS, CHANTAY!
911 TEXT?
YOU HAVE TO HELP ME.
I NEED THE DEETS
ON HOLLY J SINCLAIR.
THE DRAGON LADY
OF DEGRASSI?
WHY?
BECAUSE SHE SAYS
I DON'T KNOW HER.
(SCOFFS)
WHATEVER THAT MEANS.
I HAVE HER ON FACEBOOK,
HER TWITTER ID...
FIONA:
YOU'RE DIGGING UP INFO
ON THE INTERNET?
BIT PATHETIC, FOR YOU.
WHAT?
SHE'S AMAZING, FI.
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
LOOK.
SHE'S A YELLOW BELT
IN TAE-KWAN-DO!
(SIGHING)
OH, NO.
THIS NEVER ENDS WELL
FOR YOU.
REMEMBER SOPHIE?
DECLAN:
(SCOFFS)
GIMME SOME CREDIT.
FIONA:
YOU WERE A WRECK
FOR SIX MONTHS!
I CAN'T LISTEN
TO ANY MORE COLDPLAY.
(TAKES A DEEP BREATH)
PLEASE, FI?
I KNOW YOU GIRLS
LIKE TO SHARE.
WHAT HAVE YOU HEARD?
LEIA:
NO! I JUST...
I THINK WE'RE BETTER OFF
AS FRIENDS.
CHANTAY:
HEY, HOW'D IT GO?
UH...IT WAS HARD,
BUT I DID IT.
PERFECT.
NOW, YOU JUST WAIT FOR HIM
TO COME CRAWLING BACK.
(LAUGHS)
WHO CAN TELL ME
THE RHYME SCHEME
OF A SPENSERIAN
LOVE SONNET?
(PANICKING)
THIS BETTER WORK!
(SIGHS)
I AM BLOWING YOUR MINDS, FOLKS.
AN M.I. CLASS OUTSIDE.
OKAY, FORM A LINE!
QUICKLY,
LET'S FORM A LINE!
OKAY,
SINCE IT IS MATCHMAKER WEEK,
WE'RE GONNA LEARN HOW COMPUTERS
USE BINARY SETS
TO CREATE UNIQUE USER PROFILES.
OKAY, STEP FORWARD
IF YOU ARE MALE.
AND ANOTHER
IF YOU ARE 17 AND OLDER.
(CLASS MUTTERS)
AND ONCE AGAIN
IF YOU HAVE A SIBLING
THAT'S YOUNGER THAN YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
AND ONCE AGAIN
IF YOU WATCH...
GUITAR SOLO TUTORIALS
ON YOUTUBE.
(CLASS MUTTERS)
SEE? WE JUST CREATED
A PROFILE FOR SAV.
ALL RIGHT,
WHO WANTS A SHOT?
DECLAN.
FLOOR'S ALL YOURS.
ALL RIGHT,
BACK IN LINE.
STEP FORWARD IF YOU'RE FEMALE.
STEP FORWARD AGAIN...
IF YOU LOVE
MUSHROOM PIZZA.
STEP FORWARD AGAIN
IF YOU'VE WON
A PUBLIC SPEAKING COMPETITION.
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
STEP FORWARD
IF YOU'RE AFRAID OF SPIDERS.
ONCE MORE IF YOU KNOW
ALL THE WORDS TO MAMMA MIA.
GUY:
THINK YOU'RE IN LOVE!
(GIGGLES)
AND...THAT'S WHAT WE CALL
NICHE MARKETING!
PA ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION, DEGRASSI!
BRING AN INSTRUMENT
OR LIFT YOUR VOICE...
WOULD THE LADY
CARE TO JOIN ME?
(SELF-CONSCIOUS LAUGH)
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU WENT TO THE TROUBLE
TO FIND ALL THAT OUT.
WELL, I DO HAVE GOVERNMENT
INTELLIGENCE CONTACTS.
BUT... (WHISPERING)
IT WAS MOSTLY FIONA
BRIBING ALL YOUR FRIENDS
FOR ME.
SO, I DON'T KNOW
MUCH ABOUT YOU.
OH, YOU KNOW,
JUST YOUR AVERAGE
NOMAD CHILDHOOD
ON FOUR CONTINENTS.
BOO-HOO!
SOUNDS AMAZING.
IT HAS ITS DOWN SIDE.
YOU KNOW,
MOVING ALL THE TIME,
MALARIA PILLS,
NOT SPEAKING
THE LANGUAGE.
NO WILD BEACH NIGHTS
IN CAPRI?
UH...
NOT SO MUCH.
(CHUCKLES)
BUT WHEN WE LIVED
IN THAILAND,
I DID MEET THE DALAI LAMA.
THE DALAI LAMA!
SERIOUSLY?
YEAH,
I WAS ABOUT EIGHT.
TRISH:
DECLAN?
TRISH!
WE'RE STILL ON
FOR TONIGHT?
(SARCASTIC LAUGH)
LET ME GUESS:
"I MET THE DALAI LAMA
WHEN I WAS EIGHT-YEARS-OLD."
UH... YEAH, ACTUALLY.
TRISH:
NEXT HE'LL TELL YOU
HE MADE LIFELONG FRIENDS
WITH AN ELEPHANT HE RODE.
IT'S A TEARJERKER.
AND HERE I THOUGHT
THIS WAS A CONVERSATION,
NOT A SCRIPT!
DECLAN:
HOLLY J, WAIT.
I ALMOST FELL FOR IT.
HOLLY J!
STUDENTS:
(SURPRISED CHATTER
AND LAUGHTER)
(DISBELIEVING SIGH)
ANYA:
COME ON!
IT'S OUR ANNIVERSARY!
SPILL!
WHAT'S THE BIG SURPRISE?
NO WAY!
I'M NOT TELLING!
MR. PERINO:
HELEN OF TROY,
SHE OF "THE FACE THAT LAUNCHED
A THOUSAND SHIPS."
WE'RE GONNA START
WHAT I CALL
THE CLASS DISCUSSION!
AND I'M EXPECTING SOME
PRETTY ENGAGING...
A WHOLE YEAR, HUH?
MAYBE IT IS JUST FINDING
THE RIGHT GIRL.
SAV: (WHISPERING)
YOU MEAN HOLLY J?
THERE'S SOMEONE
FOR EVERYONE,
I GUESS.
SMALL PROBLEM,
(INHALES SHARPLY)
I KINDA...
MESSED UP?
YEAH.
SHE DOESN'T TRUST ME
AT ALL.
WELL, MAYBE...
TALK TO HER.
JUST TELL HER
HOW YOU FEEL;
GIRLS LOVE THAT.
MR. PERINO:
AND HE WAS ALSO THE RULER
OF MOUNT OLYMPUS.
DECLAN:
LISTEN, HJ,
ABOUT THE CAF THING?
HONESTLY, IT WASN'T
WHAT IT SOUNDED LIKE.
YES, I STILL HAD PLANS
WITH TRISH, BUT...
DUDE! YOU'RE STILL
WITH TRISH?
MR. PERINO:
(CLEARS THROAT)
OKAY. LET'S BEGIN
OUR LITTLE CHAT HERE...
BUT PLANS WERE TO BREAK UP
WITH HER FACE-TO-FACE.
MR. PERINO:
...THE ABDUCTION OF HELEN
BY PARIS.
SILENT TREATMENT?
SERIOUSLY?
GIRL:
LET'S GO FOR THE TOP!
NICE PASS!
STUDENTS:
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
ALL RIGHT! YEAH!
WHY ARE YOU BEING
SO HELPFUL?
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE
WITH A NOSE FOR GOSSIP.
(GRUNT OF EFFORT)
I SAW LEIA
AND MR. DANNY VAN ZANDT EARLIER,
AND SOMETHING WAS UP!
MIND YOUR OWN BUSINESS,
DAVE.
OH, COME ON.
YOU'VE HAD A CRUSH
ON THIS GUY FOREVER!
(WHISPERING)
SHUT UP! I HAVE NOT!
CHANTAY,
DID I IMAGINE
THAT YOU BEDAZZLED
THE INITIALS C-V-Z
ON YOUR BACKPACK
IN GRADE SIX?
(LAUGHS)
OH MY GOD!
(GIGGLING)
(SHARP INDRAWN BREATH)
I TOLD LEIA TO DUMP DANNY!
MM!
TOTALLY SLY, CUZ!
I'M IMPRESSED.
WHY?
I'M A TERRIBLE PERSON!
YEAH, BUT YOU GOT YOURSELF
IN THERE!
SO YOU GONNA
GO OUT WITH HIM?
NO!
I CAN'T GO OUT
WITH HIM EVER!
LEIA WOULD KILL ME!
YOU GONNA TELL HIM THAT?
(LOW HUM OF STUDENT CHATTER)
HEY! UH...
WHAT ARE YOU UP TO
FRIDAY NIGHT,
CONDISCIPULUS?
(THINKING)
CONDISCIPULUS...
(REMEMBERING)
FELLOW STUDENT.
LATIN A.P. TEST?
UH, THE DOT'S SERVING
LAVA CAKES -
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE MEET UP
AND GO OVER SOME NEW VERBS?
UH, JUST TO STUDY,
RIGHT?
OF COURSE.
YEAH.
CHOCOLATE AND TRANSLATION.
SEE YOU AT 8:00?
GREAT.
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
CHANTAY:
INSIDE YOUR RESULT FORM
IS A STICKER
WITH YOUR NAME ON IT.
STICK IT TO YOUR BEST MATCH!
SEE? I KNEW WE WERE
A PERFECT FIT!
(LAUGHS)
YOU DIDN'T FILL
ONE OUT?
WHY WOULD I?
HOW 'BOUT YOU?
PLEASE, LET THIS BE ANYONE
BUT...
(PAPER RUSTLES)
NUMBER ONE MATCH:
DECLAN COYNE.
DAMMIT!
IF YOU NEED A FRIEND
TO PICK UP THE PIECES
AFTERWARDS,
I WILL BE THERE.
(LOW HUM OF INDISTINCT CHATTER)
HEY, HE CAN'T HELP
BEING POPULAR.
HOLLY J:
I HAVE TO LET HIM
INTO THE SOUND BOOTH
AFTER LUNCH.
(KEY CLICKS IN LOCK)
I'M RECORDING THREE
SOLO MUSICIANS'
ALIENATION THEME.
HOLLY J,
WE NEED TO TALK.
(SCOFFS) I'M JUST HERE
TO UNLOCK DOORS.
(BLOWS OUT BREATH)
DID SOMEONE LEAVE
A SANDWICH IN THERE?
(SIGHS)
BLOODY GLEE CLUB!
(DOOR THUDS SHUT,
LOCK CLICKS)
LET ME OUT!
IF YOU...
(INAUDIBLE THROUGH GLASS)
...AND JUST LET ME OUT!
(INTERCOM CLICKS ON)
I THOUGHT YOU WEREN'T
TALKING TO ME ANYMORE!
I'M STILL NOT TALKING
TO YOU!
AND I'M NOT GONNA LISTEN
TO YOUR CRAP EITHER WAY,
SO YOU BETTER
SAVE US SOME TIME
AND JUST LET ME OU...
(INTERCOM CLICKS OFF)
(INTERCOM CLICKS ON)
ARE YOU DONE?
(SIGHING HEAVILY)
YOU'RE RIGHT,
I'M A PLAYER.
OR HAVE BEEN.
I'VE NEVER LIVED
ANYWHERE LONG,
AND THE ONE TIME
I HAD AN ACTUAL GIRLFRIEND,
I GOT MY HEART SMASHED.
IT GOT UGLY.
(HALF LAUGHS)
I WROTE A POEM CALLED
"MELANCHOLY TURTLE."
BUT ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED
IN THE CAF,
YOU'RE WRONG.
YOU HAVE TO TRUST ME,
HOLLY J.
I DON'T NORMALLY
TRY THIS HARD,
AND I AM TERRIFIED
RIGHT NOW.
SO COULD YOU PLEASE
GIVE ME ANOTHER CHANCE?
GIRL:
I'M HERE TO RECORD
FOR THE MUSICAL.
SURE,
LET'S DO IT.
(LOCK CLICKS)
SO?
YOU WANTED ME
TO LISTEN.
I LISTENED.
(CHUCKLES TO HERSELF)
AMA...
AMOS...
AMAT!
LEIA:
(RELIEVED SIGH)
THERE YOU ARE!
YOU HAVE TO HELP ME!
THIS ISN'T WORKING
AT ALL!
HE, UH, HASN'T COME
CRAWLING BACK?
NOT EVEN CLOSE!
HE LOOKS HAPPY!
THIS WAS YOUR IDEA,
CHANTAY!
I KNOW.
(SIGHS)
I MISS HIM SO MUCH!
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT I HAD
UNTIL I DUMPED HIM.
I'M SORRY,
I'LL TALK TO HIM,
OKAY?
COME BY THE DOT
TONIGHT.
WE'RE STUDYING
FOR THE LATIN A.P.
ALONE?
ON A FRIDAY NIGHT?
LOOK, DO YOU WANT
MY HELP OR NOT?
WHATEVER!
YOU HAVE TO FIX THIS!
(BATHROOM DOOR SLAMS)
SAV!
HELP A GUY OUT?
HOLLY J'S...
NOT LIKE THE USUAL GIRLS
I DATE.
SHE'S A BIG FISH;
I NEED BIG IDEAS.
AND KEEP IN MIND,
I HAVE ACCESS
TO A HELICOPTER.
UM... BIG GESTURES
FREAK GIRLS OUT.
YOU SHOULD JUST TRY
AND FIND A WAY
TO SPEND TIME WITH HER.
LIKE, UH, PICK HER UP
FROM THE BUS STOP,
OR WALK HER TO SCHOOL.
ARE YOU TAKING NOTES,
HONEY?
MM-HM
MM-HM.
SPEAKING OF BIG GESTURES,
WHAT'S THE ANNIVERSARY
SURPRISE?
A HOMEMADE
"SANYA" SCRAPBOOK.
FOR A ONE-YEAR
ANNIVERSARY?
YEAH, I'M SCREWED.
YEAH.
(LAUGHS)
HOW 'BOUT TWO BACKSTAGE PASSES
TO THE TESSAS PRIVATE CONCERT?
YOU DON'T WANT THESE?
I GOT SOMEWHERE
TO BE TONIGHT.
MAN!
THANK YOU!
AH!
HEY!
PA ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION, DEGRASSI:
THE SIXTH ANNUAL
INTERNATIONAL...
OOOH!
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ We've had enough fun... ♪
(SONG BECOMES MUFFLED)
JANE:
AWW!
WELL, THANKS FOR BEING HERE
TONIGHT.
WELL, A WORK-DATE'S BETTER
THAN NOTHING AT ALL!
I AGREE!
DANNY:
AB IMO PECTORE.
UH, WHAT'S THAT,
"FROM UNDER
MY PECS"?
(LAUGHS)
"FROM THE BOTTOM
OF MY HEART."
(LAUGHS UNCOMFORTABLY)
SO, NEXT VERB:
ABSTINEO!
(SOUNDING OUT)
AB-STIN-EO...
UH, WHAT'S LEIA DOING HERE?
HERE'S THE THING.
YOU NEED TO GET
BACK TOGETHER WITH HER.
BUT WHY?
SHE DUMPED ME.
IT WAS MY IDEA...
SORT OF.
I CONVINCED HER TO...
BREAK IT OFF WITH YOU
SO YOU'D MISS HER
AND COME BACK.
(SHARP INDRAWN BREATH)
WHO DOES THAT?
SIZZLE TEEN MAGAZINE READERS.
SHE DIDN'T REALLY
WANT TO DUMP YOU,
AND SHE'S REALLY SORRY
AND SO AM I.
♪ Step up and sing ♪
♪ He smiled at me! ♪
♪ 'Cause I would do
most anything ♪
♪ To be closer to you ♪
♪ All the time... ♪
(NOISY CLATTER OF TOYS,
KIDS SHOUTING)
HOLLY J:
BYE!
OKAY, UH...
SO WE'VE GOT TWO ADHDS,
THREE PEANUT ALLERGIES,
AND ONE SUGAR-BUZZED GAME
OF DUCK-DUCK-GOOSE.
WE'RE ON IT,
BOSS.
(KIDS SHOUTING)
OKAY!
EVERYONE IN A CIRCLE!
(SCUFFLING NOISES)
READY?
TYLER, GO!
DUCK, DUCK,
DUCK, DUCK, DUCK, DUCK,
DUCK, DUCK, DUCK, DUCK...
GOT ROOM
FOR ONE MORE DUCK?
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
SUPPOSED TO BE
AT THE TESSAS CONCERT.
I COULDN'T WAIT.
FOR WHAT?
TO SPEND EVERY POSSIBLE MOMENT
WITH YOU.
TYLER:
DUCK, DUCK, DUCK, DUCK...
LITTLE KID:
(IMPATIENT)
GOOSE!
TYLER:
DUCK...
GOOSE!
AHOY MATEY!
I'M GONNA GET YA!
(KIDS LAUGH AND HOLLER)
WHO WANTS
TO CLIMB ON ME?
(KIDS SHRIEKING AND LAUGHING)
(DOOR SQUEAKS,
BELLS JINGLE)
I SHOULD MIND
MY OWN BUSINESS, HUH?
YES, YOU SHOULD.
ARE YOU GUYS GONNA BE OKAY?
UH... NO.
WHAT? I'M SO SORRY!
IT'S PROBABLY BETTER.
LEIA AND I WEREN'T...
WORKING OUT,
I JUST...
COULDN'T GET IT TOGETHER
TO END IT.
REALLY?
I FEEL RELIEVED,
LIKE A...
A HUGE WEIGHT'S
OFF MY SHOULDERS.
DANNY,
TONIGHT,
WAS THIS...?
NOT JUST A STUDY DATE?
(LAUGHS)
SO WHAT DOES
SIZZLE TEEN MAGAZINE
HAVE TO SAY ABOUT
THE GIRLFRIEND CROSS-FADE?
IT SAYS A GUY SHOULD WAIT
TO DATE ANOTHER GIRL
FOR AT LEAST A MONTH.
MAKE IT TWO WEEKS
AND YOU'VE GOT A DEAL!
(GIGGLES)
OKAY.
(BOTH LAUGH)
♪ Let's talk about love ♪
HOLLY J:
(LAUGHING)
SO, DO YOU THINK PIRATE KID
WAS TRYING TO KISS
THE PRINCESS GIRL?
NO, I THINK HE WAS TRYING
TO SLAY HER.
BUT THAT'S WHAT
SAMMY TOLD ME.
OH! THE KID
WHO TALKED IN BURPS?
YOUR TABLE IS READY,
MR. COYNE.
(LIGHT JAZZ MUSIC PLAYS)
SOURCES TELL ME
IT'S THE BEST
MUSHROOM SLICE
IN ALL OF TORONTO.
YOUR PIZZA QUATTRO FUNGI
AS YOU ORDERED.
CAN I GET THE LOVELY LADY
A BRIO?
MM-HM.
MMM!
(SIGHS)
KNOW WHAT?
THIS IS A GOOD
FIRST DATE.
FIRST DATE, HUH?
DOES THIS MEAN I'M IN?
(CHUCKLING)
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
(GROANS)
JUST A SEC.
(BUTTON BEEPS)
WHO'S THAT?
IT'S NOBODY.
(CHUCKLES LIGHTLY)
NOW, WHERE WERE WE?
I THINK...
YOU WERE ABOUT TO DO
SOMETHING SPONTANEOUS.
SOUNDS ABOUT RIGHT.
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Let's talk about love ♪
♪ Let's laugh about life ♪
♪ Let's sing about the stars ♪