DECLAN:
FIONA'S UPSTAIRS PACKING.
SOON IT'S JUST YOU, ME,
AND MANHATTAN,
LIKE IT WAS MEANT TO BE.
WHERE TO?
MMM...
STATUE OF LIBERTY?
AH, STICK WITH THE CLASSICS.
NICE.
JANE:
YOU GUYS! WAIT!
HEY. WE THOUGHT YOU WERE
SLEEPING IN.
HOW'S GEORGE?
HE'S BACK TOGETHER WITH HIS EX.
I NEED TO ASK A HUGE FAVOUR.
IF YOU NEED TO STAY LONGER-
NO, NO, NO,
WE NEED TO DRIVE HOME NOW!
SPINNER IS MARRYING EMMA.
HOLLY J AND DECLAN:
WHAT?!
I KNOW!
I NEED TO STOP IT!
HE'S MAKING A BIG,
FAT REBOUND MISTAKE,
JUST LIKE I DID.
BUT IT'S HOLIDAY WEEKEND -
NO FLIGHTS.
I AM DESPERATE.
YEAH, I GUESS A ROAD TRIP
WILL GIVE ME TIME
TO DIGEST THE NEWS.
THANK YOU.
WELL, WE MIGHT AS WELL
TRAVEL IN STYLE.
(ENGINE ROARS)
(POP SONG BEGINS)
DON'T TELL MY DAD.
HANG ON.
IT'S GONNA BE A WILD RIDE.
(ENGINE REVS,
TIRES SQUEAL)
♪ You keep blaming me forever ♪
♪ Hey, sunshine ♪
♪ We're burning down together ♪
♪♪♪♪♪
JANE:
WE HAVE TO STOP HIM!
CAN'T THIS THING
GO ANY FASTER?
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, Woo-ooh! ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
WELL?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
(SIGHS)
IT'S NOT TOO LATE
TO GET AN ANNULMENT?
CAREFUL.
IT'S NOT TOO LATE
TO REVOKE YOUR MAID OF HONOUR
STATUS.
HAVE YOU EVEN TOLD
YOUR PARENTS YET?
THEY'LL BE HOME
FROM CAMPING SOON.
EMMA, REALITY CHECK:
YOU TEND TO RAILROAD PEOPLE
INTO FOLLOWING YOUR LEAD.
IT'S CALLED
HAVING CONVICTION.
AND BESIDES,
IT WAS BOTH OUR IDEAS.
SO YOU'RE GONNA
GIVE IT ALL UP
FOR A GUY WHO MANAGES
A COFFEE JOINT?
GIVE WHAT UP?
NOT EVERYONE WANTS TO BE
A HOLLYWOOD STARLET, YOU KNOW?
FINE.
JUST... PLEASE,
TALK TO SPIN ONE LAST TIME,
MAKE SURE
YOU'RE BOTH READY.
IF IT WILL MAKE YOU HAPPY,
I WILL MAKE TEN THOUSAND
PERCENT SURE.
I LIKE THE DRESS.
(CAR ENGINE RUMBLES)
(GAS BAR DINGS)
JANE:
OKAY. HUH...
WE JUST MIGHT MAKE IT IN TIME.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT HE'S DOING THIS.
HOLLY J:
TO BE HONEST,
I CAN'T REALLY BELIEVE WE'RE
RACING BACK HOME TO STOP HIM.
HELLO?
SPINNER IS YOUR FRIEND, TOO.
BUT YOU MUST REALIZE
HE'S MAKING A HUGE MISTAKE.
(SIGHS)
OKAY.
YEAH, ONE CONDITION.
UH, KETTLE CHIPS.
I'M ON IT.
THIS IS GONNA BE
A DISASTER.
NORMALLY, I'M ALL FOR
CRASHING A WEDDING,
BUT THE GROOM ALREADY
PUNCHED ME IN THE FACE.
WHAT DO WE DO?
I GUESS WE COULD MAKE
THIS ROAD TRIP
TAKE A WHOLE LOT LONGER
THAN IT SHOULD.
OKAY... ENOUGH KETTLE CHIPS
TO LAST ALL NIGHT.
LET'S MOTOR!
HOLLY J.:
YEAH, OF COURSE.
OOH! STRAWBERRIES!
JANE:
WHAT?
(STAMMERING)
WE NEED TO GO!
HOLLY J.:
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW SHORT STRAWBERRY SEASON IS?
IT'S NOW OR NEVER!
WHAT?
UH...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
SPINNER:
(GRUNTS)
A DRAWER FOR MY LADY'S
DELICATES.
OH, HOW THOUGHTFUL!
DID YOU CHOOSE A DRESS?
I-I'M WORKING ON IT.
UM...
SO THIS IS ALL REALLY FAST,
RIGHT?
YEAH, I'LL SAY.
YOU WOULD?
WOULD YOU?
(LAUGHS,
SLIGHTLY UNCOMFORTABLE)
I AM GONNA LOVE YOU FOREVER,
YOU KNOW?
SPINNER:
ME TOO! ME...
UH, LOVE YOU.
YOU KNOW.
BUT WE DON'T HAVE
TO MAKE THIS BIG
PUBLIC ANNOUNCEMENT TOMORROW.
N... NO.
NO, NO.
UH...
WE'LL SEE HOW IT GOES,
AND THEN WE'LL TELL OUR FRIENDS
AND FAMILY.
AND THEN IF IT DOESN'T
WORK OUT...
WHAT'S THE RUSH,
RIGHT?
NO RUSH.
NONE.
HUH. OKAY, WELL...
I'M GONNA GO.
OKAY.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
EMMA:
OKAY.
BYE!
(BAT CLINKS AGAINST BALL)
JANE:
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, I GET IT.
I GET IT,
YOU'RE STALLING.
HOLLY J:
DARN, YOU TOTALLY BUSTED US.
JANE:
YOU GOT SOMETHING TO SAY,
JUST SAY IT.
OKAY, SO YOU SHOW UP,
EVERYBODY'S THERE,
SPINNER AND EMMA ARE READY
TO DECLARE THEIR LOVE...
THEN WHAT?
I HAVE TO KNOW, HOLLY J.
HOLLY J:
JANE,
HE'S MARRYING SOMEONE ELSE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THIS IS A MISTAKE.
(BAT CLANKS AGAINST BALL)
LET'S GO BACK TO NEW YORK,
OKAY?
I'M GONNA JUST WAIT
IN THE CAR.
KEYS?
TO LISTEN TO THE RADIO.
THANK YOU.
(KEYS JINGLE)
IT WAS FUN WHILE IT LASTED.
THINK I WAS I TOO HARSH?
YOU ARE A BALL-BUSTER!
(CAR DOOR CLOSES,
ENGINE REVS AND RUMBLES)
MY CAR!
DECLAN AND HOLLY J:
JANE?!
(CAR RUMBLES)
HOLLY J:
JANE!
(CAR ZOOMS OFF)
(BAT CLANKS)
(HAMMER SLAMS HEAVILY,
METAL CLATTERS)
(DOOR CREAKS OPEN,
SPINNER HEAVES AND GRUNTS)
(LOUD THUDDING)
IT'S HAMMER TIME!
(LAUGHS)
(SANDWICH MAKER CLUNKS)
(SPINNER GRUNTS,
LOUD SMASHING)
(PANTS HEAVILY)
DUDE, YOU ALL RIGHT?
I'M GOING NOWHERE IN LIFE,
OKAY?!
JANE WAS RIGHT.
YOU'RE LISTENING TO HER?
SHE CHEATED ON ME
FOR A REASON, DUDE, OKAY?
I'M A LOSER!
NO WONDER EMMA
WANTS A DIVORCE.
WHAT?!
WE GOT MARRIED
IN NIAGARA FALLS, OKAY?
AND WE WERE GONNA THROW
THIS BIG PARTY
TO SHOW EVERYONE
HOW HAPPY WE WERE,
AND THEN...
I THINK... WE AGREED
IT'S NOT GONNA WORK OUT.
SO...
THERE'S MY GUYS!
OH, YOU BEGAN THE RENO?
EXCELLENT!
INSURANCE CAME THOUGH!
THE DOT'S GOING TO BE BETTER
THAN EVER!
THAT'S GREAT, GAMAL.
THAT'S GREAT.
GAMAL:
YOU KNOW, THIS FIRE
WAS A BLESSING IN DISGUISE.
SOMETIMES GOOD THINGS
COME FROM ACCIDENTS!
YEAH.
♪♪♪♪♪
YOU WANNA HELP
THROW A PARTY?
CALL JAY,
RIGHT NOW.
I GOT SOMEWHERE TO GO,
OKAY?
GAMAL, YOU...
MUAH!
NO, IT'S OKAY.
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Oh take me away ♪
♪ I'll be your passenger ♪
♪ I'm coming after ya ♪
♪ How does it feel? ♪
SPINNER:
EMMA, I KNOW THIS IS CRAZY...
♪ Gotta leave,
find a way outta here ♪
OH.
♪ Suddenly,
everything seems so clear ♪
UH, DO YOU WANNA TALK
ABOUT THIS OUTSIDE?
NO.
NO, I NEED THEM ALL
TO HEAR THIS.
EMMA, I WANT THE REST
OF OUR LIVES TOGETHER
TO START NOW.
I DON'T CARE IF IT STARTED
AS AN ACCIDENT.
WHAT'S WITH THE FLOWERS?
WH-WHAT'S GOING ON?
I'M ASKING YOUR DAUGHTER
TO MARRY ME, SIR.
HOW PREGNANT ARE YOU?
NOT EVEN A LITTLE BIT.
SIMPSON:
HOLD ON.
YOU JUST MOVED HOME,
AND NOW YOU WANNA
MARRY...
SPINNER MASON?
ACTUALLY, WE ALREADY HAVE.
AT A CASINO.
MR. SIMPSON,
MRS. NELSON,
I'VE BEEN THROUGH STUFF.
I KNOW HOW PRECIOUS TIME IS.
AND SOMETIMES YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE LOOKING FOR
UNTIL...
IT BURNS DOWN
YOUR PLACE OF WORK.
BOTH:
(LAUGH)
ARE YOU SURE
ABOUT THIS?
YEAH. WE'LL MAKE IT OFFICIAL
TOMORROW!
SPIKE AND SIMPSON:
TOMORROW?!
UM...
I WAS HOPING THAT YOU WOULD
BOTH WALK ME DOWN THE AISLE?
WELL, IN THAT CASE...
(TEARING UP)
YEAH...
WE'D BE HONOURED.
♪ Take me away ♪
SAV:
HEY YO, PETER!
PETER:
OH HEY, GUYS!
LIBERTY!
YOU GOT THE EVITE?
NO, I JUST HAPPENED TO BE
STROLLING ALONG THIS BEACH.
WHERE'S EMMA?
OH, I'M SHE'S AROUND
SOMEWHERE.
PUNCH?
SURE.
UH, WHAT KIND OF PARTY
IS THIS?
THANKS, MOM.
EM'S GONNA LOVE IT.
I AM SO PROUD OF YOU,
GAVIN.
AND I KNOW YOUR DAD
WOULD BE, TOO.
(CAR SPEEDS ALONG)
(RADIO PLAYS ROCK SONG)
(HUM OF LIVELY CHATTER)
RELAX!
AS A MINISTER ORDAINED BY
THE ONLINE CHURCH OF DECADENCE,
I HAVE SEEN MANY
A NERVOUS GROOM.
I'M NOT.
SERIOUSLY, MAN,
WHY HAVEN'T YOU EVEN TRIED
TO TALK ME OUT OF THIS?
I'M GONNA BE YOUR BUD
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS.
BUT IF I THOUGHT THAT EMMA
WAS A STONE-COLD HEARTBREAKER
LIKE JANE,
I WOULD PHYSICALLY PREVENT YOU
FROM GOING THROUGH WITH IT.
(CALMING BREATH)
THANKS, MAN.
(HALF LAUGHS)
CAN I GET A MINUTE?
YEAH.
RUN...
AND MANNY WILL KILL US
BOTH.
(BLOWS A CALMING BREATH)
(CAR RUMBLES
AND SKIDS TO A HALT)
♪♪♪♪♪
I'M NOT GETTING
INVOLVED.
SPINNER:
SEE, JAY?
I'M STILL HERE.
SPIN, YOU HAVE TO...
YOU HAVE TO...
(EXHALES, CALM)
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
NOTHING, SORRY.
IT'S JUST...
IT'S WEIRD SEEING YOU
IN A SUIT.
(HALF LAUGHS)
YEAH.
TOO FORMAL?
ACTUALLY, YOU...
YOU LOOK HAPPY.
(TIGHT INHALE)
I WAS GONNA TRY
TO CONVINCE YOU
TO COME BACK WITH ME
TO NEW YORK, BUT...
IT WOULDN'T WORK.
YOU BELONG HERE.
AND I'M GETTING MARRIED
IN LIKE TWO MINUTES.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
I JUST REALLY HAVE
TO ASK YOU SOMETHING.
ASK.
I AM SO, SO SORRY
THAT I BROKE YOUR HEART.
CAN YOU EVER FORGIVE ME?
PLEASE?
COME HERE.
I FORGIVE YOU, OKAY?
MARRY EMMA AND BE HAPPY,
OKAY?
YEAH.
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
DOING HERE?!
NOTHING.
WE'RE JUST TALKING.
MANNY, IT'S OKAY!
LIKE HELL IT IS.
GET OUT!
JANE:
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
NO ONE IS GOING TO RUIN
EMMA'S WEDDING!
JANE:
OW!
(JANE GRUNTS,
MANNY YELPS)
WELL, I'M NOT TELLING SPINNER
THAT JANE IS HERE.
MAN, IF I TELL HIM,
HE WILL BREAK ME.
(MANNY YELPS INSIDE TENT)
YOU'RE OVERREACTING.
I...
MAN, I'M LIKE A TWIG!
(MANNY SQUEALS)
GIRLS! STOP IT!
STOP!
MANNY!
COME... COME ON!
WELL, WHAT WAS THAT KISS
ALL ABOUT?
IT WAS ABOUT GOODBYE.
AND I WAS JUST LEAVING.
REALLY?
YES.
OKAY.
HOW'S MY HAIR?
NEVER LOOKED BETTER.
LET'S DO THIS, THEN.
GO.
(LAUGHS)
YEAH.
(WEEPING QUIETLY)
OKAY...
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
DANNY:
WHY'RE YOU SO WORRIED, MAN?
SAV:
I'M, I'M NOT WORRIED.
PETER:
(WHISTLES)
WELCOME, EVERYBODY...
TO EMMA AND SPINNER'S
POST-IMPULSIVE
CASINO WEDDING
COMMITMENT CEREMONY!
GUESTS:
WEDDING? WHAT?
(CONFUSED MURMURS)
IT'S A WEDDING, GUYS!
(STUNNED CHATTER)
WELL, THAT'S UNUSUAL.
PETER:
SO, UH, IF EVERYONE COULD JUST
SPLIT DOWN THE MIDDLE.
(PETER PLAYS
"HERE COMES THE BRIDE")
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
♪♪♪♪♪
LADIES AND GENTS,
WE ARE GATHERED HERE TODAY
TO CELEBRATE
SWEET, SPONTANEOUS LOVIN'.
GAVIN, DO YOU STILL TAKE EMMA
TO BE YOUR WIFE,
NO MATTER WHAT CURVEBALLS
FATE CHUCKS AT YOUR HEAD?
YEAH, I DO.
AND EMMA,
KINDA THE SAME DEAL?
YOU KNOW I DO.
JAY:
(CLEARS THROAT)
THE RING.
WELL, THEN BY THE POWER
INVESTED IN ME -
BY THE FACT THAT YOU TWO
ARE ALREADY ACTUALLY MARRIED -
I NOW PRONOUNCE YOU
MR. AND MRS. GAVIN MASON
AND EMMA NELSON.
(GUESTS APPLAUD AND CHEER)
(CHEERING AND CLAPPING)
(HUM OF CHATTER)
(BOAT WHIRS)
(SIGHS)
DON'T TELL ME,
ARE WE TOO LATE?
YOU WERE RIGHT.
UM...
I'M AN ASS.
JANE, WHAT HAPPENED?
JANE: I KISSED HIM-
HOLLY J: YOU KISSED HIM?
I TOLD YOU WE SHOULD'VE
TAKEN THE HELICOPTER!
I KISSED HIM GOODBYE.
(CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICK,
LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
SPINNER:
HOLLY J? DECLAN? WHAT?
HOLLY J:
DON'T WORRY,
WE'RE GOING!
JANE SHOWED UP
'CAUSE SHE NEEDED CLOSURE.
WE TALKED.
IT'S ALL GOOD.
SURE IS.
GOT YOU, DIDN'T I?
YEAH.
EMMA:
HEY, GUYS!
COME JOIN THE PARTY!
(WAVES CRASH ASHORE)
MANNY:
THIS IS A SPECIAL SONG I WROTE
FOR MY BEST FRIEND,
THE BEAUTIFUL BRIDE.
♪♪♪♪♪
MANNY:
♪ I TRUST YOU WITH MY TEARS ♪
♪ AND MY SECRETS NEVER TOLD ♪
♪ I TRUST YOU
WITH MY HOPES AND FEARS ♪
♪ AND THIS HAND TO HOLD ♪
♪ I KNOW YOU'LL BE TRUE TO ME ♪
♪ WHENEVER WE'RE APART ♪
♪ IN A WORLD FILLED
WITH UNCERTAINTY ♪
♪ I TRUST YOU ♪
♪ I TRUST YOU WITH MY HEART ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN HOLDING BACK
SO LONG ♪
♪ AFRAID TO GIVE IT ALL ♪
♪ LOOKING FOR A PLACE TO LAND ♪
♪ TRYING NOT TO FALL ♪
♪ YOU SHOWED ME HOW TO GIVE ♪
♪ LET ME TAKE MY TIME ♪
♪ WISHES SOMEHOW
WE'LL JUST KNOW ♪
♪ BUT WE'LL NEVER FIND ♪
♪ I TRUST YOU WITH MY TEARS ♪
♪ AND MY SECRETS NEVER TOLD ♪
SO...
BACK TO NEW YORK.
WHERE WE'LL HAVE THE PLACE
ALL TO OURSELVES,
AS LONG AS MY MOM'S
IN THE HAMPTONS WITH FIONA.
EVEN AFTER EVERYTHING,
I FEEL SORRY FOR HER.
SHE'S SO LONELY.
DECLAN:
SHE'S WITH MY MOM.
SHE'LL BE OKAY.
MANNY:
♪ IN A WORLD FILLED
WITH UNCERTAINTY ♪
♪ I TRUST YOU ♪
♪ I TRUST YOU WITH MY HEART ♪
HOLLY J:
QUITE A WAY TO KICK OFF
THE SUMMER.
FROM GRAD, TO FALLING IN LOVE
WITH NEW YORK,
TO WATCHING THE FORMER LOVE
OF MY LIFE GET MARRIED...
IT'S BEEN WILD.
IT WAS A REALLY NICE
WEDDING.
EVEN KIND OF FAIRY-TALE,
IN A WEIRD WAY.
THAT FAIRY-TALE
WAS NEVER MY STORY.
HELL, YOUR ADVENTURE
HASN'T EVEN STARTED YET.
ANY IDEA
WHAT IT MIGHT BE?
(EXHALES)
I CAN'T WAIT TO FIND OUT.
LET'S GO!
MANNY:
♪ I TRUST YOU ♪
♪ O-O-OH ♪
♪ I TRUST YOU WITH MY HEART ♪