(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
THE NIGHT IS ENDING SOON.
WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME.
(GASPS)
(EXHALES)
(SIGHS)
♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it,
I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, Woo-ooh ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
CLARE:
SORRY. I WAS UP 'TIL 3 A.M.
READING "FORTNIGHT."
DO YOU HAVE THE NEXT ONE?
ALLI:
SO ADDICTIVE, HUH?
I'M TOTALLY CAUGHT UP.
STUCK WITH READING LAME-O
FAN FICTION
UNTIL THE NEXT ONE
COMES OUT.
HEY, DOESN'T DECLAN
KIND OF REMIND YOU OF EDMUND,
ALL BROODING
AND SEXY?
GET YOUR MIND
OUT OF THE GUTTER!
I READ FORTNIGHT BOOKS
FOR THE PLOT.
YO YO, PROPMASTER CLARE
IN THE HOUSE!
HEY, DECLAN!
SEE YOU AT REHEARSAL!
(BELL RINGS)
AH, LET'S GO PARK OUR BUTTS
INSIDE.
HE VANTS TO SUCK
YOUR BLOOD.
(LAUGHS)
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
PA ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION, DEGRASSI.
WOULD DUNCAN GRANT
PLEASE REPORT
TO THE FRONT OFFICE?
CHANTAY'S LATE AGAIN.
CLARE!
CAN YOU GET UP HERE
AND READ SOME LINES?
I'M A BEHIND-THE-SCENES
PERSON.
SCENE SIX,
ALIEN MEETS GREG.
(READING)
UH, GREG.
TEAM'S WAITING.
WHO'S THIS FREAK?"
NOBODY.
COMING, TESS!
AH! STOP.
YOU'RE BLOCKING HER FACE.
LIKE THIS.
TILT BACK, CHIN UP...
(GASPS)
WHOA.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
I'M FINE.
THAT'LL TEACH ME
NOT TO SKIP BREAKFAST!
MOST IMPORTANT MEAL
OF THE DAY!
OKAY... LET'S TAKE IT
FROM THE TOP.
CHANTAY:
SORRY, SORRY...
AH.
TAKE IT FROM SCENE SIX -
ALIEN MEETS GREG.
CHANTAY:
OKAY.
PA ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION, DEGRASSI.
TICKETS ARE ON SALE NOW
FOR THE DEGRASSI DANCE
AND SCHOOL PLAY.
HEY!
SO, WE GOT OUR REPORT BACK.
B-PLUS.
LEIA:
ONE UPSIDE TO YOU TWO
BREAKING UP -
ANYA'S A GREAT STUDY PARTNER.
UH, SO HOW'S IT GOING?
SO BUSY!
UM, I JUST STARTED
DRIVER'S ED,
UM...
WARDROBE FOR THE MUSICAL,
LARPING LIKE... 24/7.
YOU?
UH, I'VE BEEN, UH...
YOU KNOW,
I'VE BEEN PRETTY BUSY TOO.
CLIFF WANTS US TO SLAY
A LARP DRAGON MID-INVASION.
(LAUGHS)
HE'S CRAZY!
I'LL TEXT HIM BACK.
CONNOR! YOU'RE FRIENDS
STILL COMING OVER TOMORROW?
YEP. WESLEY'S IN CHARGE
OF THE CHIPS.
KETCHUP AND DILL PICKLE!
CHIPS, GREAT.
OKAY, GUYS, YOU'RE EXAM
IS A TAKE HOME.
NOW I WANT YOU TO DESIGN
AN INTERACTIVE
COMMUNITY WEBPAGE.
YO, SPACE CADET,
WHATCHYA TYPING?
NOTHING. IT'S PERSONAL.
OH, LET ME SEE,
PLEASE?
FORTNIGHT FAN FICTION?
WOW, CLARE,
THIS IS PRETTY STEAMY!
I WAS JUST GOOFING AROUND.
LIKE, WHAT IF THE GIRL
WAS THE VAMPIRE?
THIS IS WAY BETTER THAN
THE STUFF ON FAN BOARDS.
YOU SHOULD POST IT.
ONLINE?
ARE YOU INSANE?
DO IT ANONYMOUSLY!
BESIDES, IT'S NOT LIKE
DECLAN'S GONNA READ IT.
FORTNIGHT BOOKS
ARE A GIRL THING.
SO, WHAT'S MY PEN-NAME?
"MISS DEGRASSI?"
HOW ABOUT "MADAME DEGRASSI?"
(KEYS CLACK)
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
HEY!
YOU GUYS READY TO HEAR
OUR LATEST TRACK?
OH, YOU FINISHED THE MIX?
YEAH.
I STAYED LATE LAST NIGHT.
NOTHING BETTER TO DO.
HERE, LISTEN!
JANE:
♪ HOUSE ARREST,
HOUSE ARREST ♪
♪ PUT MY RECORD TO THE TEST ♪
♪ HOUSE ARREST,
HOUSE ARREST ♪
WOW! THAT SOUNDS AMAZING,
SAV!
AND TVM'S VIRAL VIDEO CONTEST
IS THIS WEEKEND!
WAIT, IT'S THIS WEEKEND?
SAV:
YEAH, IF WE SHOOT SATURDAY,
WE CAN MAKE THE DEADLINE!
I GOT FINALS.
YEAH, SAME HERE.
SORRY.
RIGHT.
NEVER MIND.
JANE:
SEE YOU.
SORRY, DUDE.
(PHONE TRILLS)
(BEEP, PHONE DIALS)
(PHONE BEEPS OFF)
OH MY GOD, CLARE,
DID YOU SEE YOUR REVIEWS
ON THE FORTNIGHT SITE?
SO MANY PEOPLE READ IT!
EVERYONE GAVE YOU
4 STARS,
AND AN M FOR MATURE,
MISS "PURITY RING"!
I WROTE ANOTHER ONE
LAST NIGHT...
HOLLY J:
"DECLAN'S EYES HELD MINE
AS MY HEART RACED!
WHY MUST I BE A VAMPIRE?"
YOU'RE A FORTNIGHT FREAK?
HOLLY J:
IT'S MY THING, OKAY?
YOU READ PEREZ,
I READ VAMPIRE FAN FICTION.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD'VE CHANGED
DECLAN'S NAME TOO.
HOLLY J:
"I TREMBLED IN ANTICIPATION,
WANTING WHAT
I COULD NOT HAVE."
WHO IS THIS
MADAME DEGRASSI?
(PLAYFUL SNARL)
DELICIOUS HUMAN BLOOD!
(LAUGHS)
ARE YOU DONE OBSESSING,
HOLLY J?
'CAUSE I GOT A REHEARSAL
TO RUN.
I'M GOING, I'M GOING.
(EXHALES)
ALLI:
SO, HAVE YOU READ THE STORIES?
HJ READ BOTH OF THEM
TO ME LAST NIGHT,
EVERY SINGLE WORD.
COULD YOUR NAME
JUST BE A COINCIDENCE?
COULD BE.
BUT WHOEVER MADAME DEGRASSI IS,
SHE SURE CAN WRITE.
GOT QUITE THE IMAGINATION,
TOO.
UH...
DON'T WORRY,
I CAN TAKE IT IN.
PETER:
HEY, DUDE.
STILL TWEAKING THE MIX?
YEAH. KIND OF.
NO.
DON'T DO IT, MAN.
WHAT?
YOU'RE TOTALLY STALKING
YOUR EX.
MAN, IT'S NOT FAIR.
I'M THE DUMPER,
NOT THE DUMPEE.
SHE'S ALL HAPPY TWEETS,
AND DRIVING SCHOOL,
AND LARPING,
AND I'M THE ONE
WHO CAN'T GET OVER IT.
YOU ARE NOT GETTING BACK
TOGETHER WITH HER, DUDE.
NOT AGAIN.
I DON'T WANT TO.
I JUST DON'T GET WHY
SHE'S HAPPY AND I'M NOT.
WELL, IT'S 'CAUSE
SHE'S DOING STUFF.
IT'S ALL ABOUT DISTRACTIONS.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'LL FIND SOMETHING.
(EXHALES)
OKAY. I'LL TALK TO THE GUYS
ABOUT MAKING THE VIDEO.
REALLY?
YEAH, ONE MUSIC VIDEO
CAN'T RUIN FOUR YEARS
OF HIGH SCHOOL, RIGHT?
THANKS, MAN.
WE'LL GET STARTED
SATURDAY MORNING.
WHOA, MORNING?
YEAH. IF WE'RE GONNA
MAKE A VIDEO,
IT'S GOTTA BE GOOD.
THERE YOU ARE!
CONNOR'S E-VITE
SAID 4:30 SHARP.
CLARE:
I THINK I'M GONNA PASS.
MORE FORTNIGHT
FAN FICTION?
YOU HEARD DECLAN.
HE LOVES IT.
DECLAN IS SOMEONE ELSE'S
BOYFRIEND,
AND IF HOLLY J KNEW
YOU WERE MADAME DEGRASSI,
SHE'D MURDER YOU.
IS THIS HIS SWEATER?
I COULDN'T HELP IT.
OKAY, YOU ARE OFFICIALLY
OBSESSED.
TIME TO GO OUT
IN THE DAYLIGHT
AND INTERACT WITH
REAL LIVE HUMANS.
BUT I WANNA WRITE!
NOT RIGHT NOW,
MADAME DEGRASSI!
I'M IN CHARGE OF GAMES
FOR CONNOR'S PARTY -
YOU KNOW,
"SPIN THE BOTTLE,"
"ROCK, PAPER, KISSES."
MMM, SOUNDS GREAT.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO.
COME ON.
One, two, three, four!
♪♪♪♪♪
IMPRESSIVE CHIP BUFFET.
WELL, WHERE DO YOU STAND
ON THE GREAT PRINGLES
VS. PRETZELS DEBATE?
ALLI:
ATTENTION, EVERYONE!
TIME FOR "SEVEN MINUTES
IN HEAVEN!"
TWO NAMES ARE PICKED
TO GO IN THE CORNER
AND MAKE-OUT
FOR SEVEN MINUTES.
HA HA, THIS PARTY JUST
GOT INTERESTING!
DO WE HAVE TO MAKE OUT?
UM, YOU CAN DO THE TIMER.
SO WHATEVER HEAVEN MEANS
TO YOU, DO IT.
FIRST UP IS...
CLARE...
AND...
WESLEY!
KIDS:
OOH!
(LAUGHS)
GIRL:
HAVE FUN, GUYS!
SEVEN MINUTES, STARTING...
NOW!
SO... THIS IS HEAVEN?
NOT EXACTLY
HOW I PICTURED IT.
OH, WELL, THAT'S PRETTY.
WHAT'S IT SAY?
PURE HEARTS WAIT.
IT'S AN ABSTINENCE RING.
OH.
ARE YOU EVEN ALLOWED
TO DO THIS?
I'M PRETTY SURE
I CAN KISS!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS)
CLARE, WE CAN'T.
WE MUSTN'T.
I LONGED FOR THIS MOMENT.
CLARE!
(EXHALES SHAKILY)
I'M SORRY.
CLARE:
I'M GOING HOME.
BUT YOU'RE ONLY AT 1:42!
(DOOR CHIMES JINGLE)
OH. THAT WAS THE BEST MINUTE
AND 42 SECONDS OF MY LIFE.
DO YOU WANNA GO
FOR GELATO LATER?
NOT INTERESTED.
TELL THAT TO MY NECK!
YOU COULD HAVE CALLED
TO TELL ME WESLEY WAS HERE.
(SIGHS)
JUST IGNORE HIM.
FORTNIGHT BOOKS.
ALL OF THEM.
YOU READ THEM ALREADY?
NO. AND I'M NOT READING
ANY MORE.
THEY'RE TURNING ME
INTO A PERVERT.
SURE, BLAME THE BOOKS.
I'M ALSO DELETING
ALL MY FAN-FIC POSTS.
THEY'RE MAKING A MOCKERY
OF MY ABSTINENCE PLEDGE.
BECAUSE YOU WROTE SOME STORIES
AND GAVE A GUY A HICKEY?
SEXUAL ACTS BEGIN
IN THE MIND.
CLARE, IT'S NORMAL
TO THINK ABOUT SEX. JEEZ!
FOR YOU, MAYBE.
BUT EVENTUALLY I'M GONNA DO
SOMETHING I'LL REGRET.
LIKE YOU DID WITH JOHNNY.
(GASPS,
TAKEN ABACK)
SO JUDGY CLARE IS BACK,
HUH?
YOU SAY JUDGY,
I SAY PRINCIPLED.
I HAVE TO GET TO REHEARSAL.
(DOOR CHIMES JINGLE)
(STUDZ PLAY)
JANE:
♪ HOUSE ARREST!
HOUSE ARREST! ♪
♪ PUT MY RECORD TO THE TEST ♪
♪ HOUSE ARREST,
HOUSE ARREST ♪
♪ HOUSE! A-RREST! ♪
AND CUT!
OH THAT LOOKED AWESOME!
UM, LET ME GET ONE
WHERE I CAN SEE
ALL YOUR ANKLE BRACELETS!
UH, HOW MANY TIMES
ARE WE GONNA DO THIS?
D-DIDN'T YOU SEE
MY STORYBOARDS?
YOU STILL GOTTA CLIMB DOWN
THE FIRE ESCAPE,
AND RUN FROM THE POLICE.
I RAIDED THE SCHOOL COSTUME
STASH!
OH SWEET!
I ALWAYS WANTED TO BE A COP.
HEY, UM, I THOUGHT YOU SAID
THIS WAS ONLY GONNA TAKE
A COUPLE HOURS?
SAV:
ALL RIGHT. ONE MORE TIME,
FROM THE TOP!
HERE WE GO.
OKAY.
(RECORDER BEEPS,
SPINNER TAPS IN TIME)
("HOUSE ARREST" PLAYS)
JANE:
♪ HOUSE ARREST,
HOUSE ARREST
♪ PUT MY RECORD TO THE TEST ♪
♪ HOUSE ARREST... ♪
CLARE:
DECLAN?
I, UH, FOUND THIS BACKSTAGE.
OH, COOL.
HEY, UH, THANKS FOR COMING
IN ON A SATURDAY.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
I COULDN'T SLEEP AT ALL
LAST NIGHT.
ME NEITHER!
CLARE, CAN I GET YOU
TO TELL ME SOMETHING,
STRAIGHT-UP?
DO YOU THINK I'M DOING
A GOOD JOB?
OH! YOU'RE DOING
AN AMAZING JOB!
'CAUSE I'VE NEVER DIRECTED
A MUSICAL BEFORE
AND I WANT TO NAIL IT.
LIKE, REALLY SINK MY TEETH
INTO IT, YOU KNOW?
WELL, I'D SAY MISSION
ACCOMPLISHED!
THANKS, PROPMASTER CLARE.
ANY TIME YOU WANNA TALK...
("HOUSE ARREST" PLAYS)
MUSIC
SAV:
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA,
WHOA-WHOA-WHOA-WHOA!
CUT! CUT! CUT! CUT!
OKAY, ONE MORE TIME!
DANNY:
THAT ONE WAS GOOD!
YOU LOOKED RIGHT AT THE CAMERA.
FOCUS!
JANE:
WE ARE FOCUSED, SAV -
ON FINALS!
IS ANYBODY ELSE STARVING?
YES.
SAV:
NO-NO-NO-NO-NO-NO.
WE CAN EAT WHEN WE'RE DONE.
UM, OKAY.
UH, SHOT 14, TAKE 17,
ACTION!
I THINK WE SHOULD WRAP IT UP
FOR THE DAY, MAN.
N-NO. WE CAN'T STOP NOW!
WE'LL NEVER FINISH IN TIME
FOR THE TVM DEADLINE!
THAT'S NO REASON FOR ME
TO FAIL PHYSICS.
YEAH, I'M SORRY, DUDE.
I'M GOING HOME.
CAN YOU GIVE ME A LIFT,
SPIN?
YES. I HAVE TO BE AT THE DOT
IN AN HOUR ANYWAY.
DUDE, UH,
CAN I KEEP THE UNIFORM?
I'M SORRY, BRO.
LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN.
(DOOR OPENS)
(EXHALES)
(PHONE BEEPS)
(KEY BEEPS)
SAV:
THANKS FOR MEETING ME.
ANYA:
YOU'RE LUCKY
I COULD SQUEEZE YOU IN.
SAV:
IT'S AMAZING
HOW FAST YOU MOVED ON.
I MEAN, SOMETIMES I WONDER
IF I MADE A MISTAKE.
(RELIEVED SIGH)
WHEW!
THAT'S GOTTA BE
A NEW RECORD!
RECORD?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL...
YOU REALLY HAD ME GOING, SAV.
I THOUGHT YOU ACTUALLY
MEANT IT THIS TIME.
I-I DID MEAN IT...
EVERYBODY SAID IF YOU ACT
LIKE YOU DON'T CARE,
HE'LL COME CRAWLING BACK,
AND HERE YOU ARE!
WHOA! SO THIS WHOLE THING
WAS SOME KIND OF GAME
TO GET ME BACK?
NOT A GAME.
UH...
MORE LIKE A STRATEGY.
AND A DAMN GOOD ONE,
IF I DO SAY SO.
(HALF LAUGHS)
THANKS, ANYA.
YOU KNOW, I ALMOST FORGOT
WHY I BROKE UP WITH YOU.
SAV, YOU NEED ME.
IT'S OKAY.
I DON'T NEED ANYONE
WHO CAN'T BE HONEST WITH ME.
THEN WHY DID YOU
CALL ME HERE?
I DON'T KNOW,
'CAUSE I'M A MORON?
NO TAKEBACKS.
THIS TIME IT'S FINAL.
PFFT! FINE BY ME.
I'D RATHER BE ALONE.
DECLAN:
HOLLY J, I JUST WANT SOMEONE
WITH IMAGINATION!
SOMEONE WITH PASSION!
HOLLY J:
OH, YOU MEAN LIKE
MADAME DEGRASSI?
I KNEW IT!
TYPICAL!
YOU'RE SO UPTIGHT!
(HALF LAUGHS)
CAN I TAKE YOU UP
ON THAT TALK?
CLARE, SOMETIMES
I LOOK AT YOUR FACE
AND IT'S LIKE...
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
THAT UNDERSTANDS.
(DRAMATIC, OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS)
DECLAN:
CLARE!
HEY, SLEEPYHEAD.
READY TO SHOW ME
YOUR PROPS?
PROPS TABLE.
FLATS.
TREES.
NICE WORK.
IS THAT ACTUAL MOSS?
CLARE, THIS IS AMAZING.
DID YOU JUST KISS MY NECK?
OH, GOD.
ARE YOU...?
MADAME DEGRASSI?
WOW.
OKAY, UM...
(LOW HUM OF STUDENT CHATTER)
ALLI:
YOU KISSED DECLAN COYNE'S NECK?
WELL, CLARE,
NEXT THING YOU KNOW,
YOU'LL BE DOING SOMETHING
YOU REGRET.
I AM SO SORRY
I SAID THAT.
IT WAS A CRIME OF PASSION.
SO, UH...
WHAT'RE YOU GONNA DO?
OBVIOUSLY I'M GONNA QUIT
THE MUSICAL.
STUDZ:
♪ IT WAS WORTH IT! ♪
JANE:
♪ SOME PERFECT TIME ♪
♪ GOTTA SERVE IT ♪
♪ MY LIFE OF CRIME ♪
STUDZ:
♪ IT WAS WORTH IT! ♪
(GUITAR RIFF PLAYS)
♪♪♪♪♪
JANE:
♪ HOUSE ARREST,
HOUSE ARREST ♪
♪ PUT MY RECORD TO THE TEST ♪
♪ HOUSE ARREST,
HOUSE ARREST ♪
♪ HOUSE A-RREST! ♪
HOLLY J:
"HOUSE ARREST" BY OUR VERY OWN
"JANIE AND THE STUDS"
FEATURING PETER STONE
AND SAV'S CAT.
VOTE FOR IT ON THE TVM WEBSITE!
AND ALSO, IF YOU'RE LOOKING
FOR TICKETS...
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU FINISHED IT!
SAV:
YEAH, I HAD FUN.
SO YOU WANNA HIT THE BREAK ROOM
AFTER SCHOOL TO CELEBRATE?
I CAN'T.
I'M MAKING MORE VIDEOS.
WOW. FOR OTHER BANDS?
NO, CATS.
YEAH, ONE OF THEM'S
GOT A PERSIAN CAT
WHO CAN SING
"HAPPY BIRTHDAY."
(WITH A LAUGH)
OKAY. SEE YOU.
(EXHALES)
HELLO, MADAME DEGRASSI.
HOLLY J,
PLEASE DON'T KILL ME!
I THOUGHT ABOUT IT.
AND THEN DECLAN AND I TALKED,
LUCKY FOR YOU.
SO, I SEE YOU TOOK
YOUR STORIES DOWN
FROM THE FORTNIGHT WEBSITE.
WHY?
I'M NEVER WRITING AGAIN.
I'M SICK.
I'M TRYING TO MAKE THESE
STUPID FEELINGS GO AWAY.
AND HOW'S THAT WORKING
FOR YOU?
NOT WELL.
STILL A PERVERT.
IT'S CALLED PUBERTY.
AND IF WRITING FAN FICTION
STOPS YOU FROM SUCKING
MY BOYFRIEND'S NECK,
THEN PLEASE CONTINUE.
YOU THINK I SHOULD
KEEP WRITING?
YOU'RE REALLY GOOD.
I CAN'T STOP READING
YOUR POSTS.
ARE YOU GOING TO TELL
EVERYONE AT SCHOOL IT'S ME?
NO.
BUT IF YOU EVER TRY
KISSING MY BOYFRIEND AGAIN,
I WILL DESTROY YOU.
CLEAR?
YOU TWO ALL DONE
YOUR LADY-TALK?
I THINK WE HAVE
AN UNDERSTANDING.
DECLAN,
I'M REALLY SORRY.
HOW ABOUT THIS?
NEVER HAPPENED.
REALLY?
SEE YOU AT REHEARSAL.
FOUR O'CLOCK.
(RELIEVED BREATH)
HOLLY J:
(HALF LAUGHS)
(KEYS CLACK)
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS)
(HISSES)