VELOCITY EQUALS
DISTANCE OVER TIME -
VERY LITTLE OF WHICH YOU HAVE
BEFORE FRIDAY'S EXAM.
COME ON, SPIN.
LOOK, I KNOW HOW MUCH
YOU HATE THIS CLASS, OKAY?
BUT TO COME BACK NEXT YEAR
IS GONNA REALLY SUCK.
OH, YEAH?
MORE THAN STILL HAVING CANCER?
GET MY TEST RESULTS TOMORROW,
MAN;
I NEED GOOD NEWS.
BINCE:
BUT I HAVE GOOD NEWS.
YOU CAN WRITE THE EXAM
OR YOU CAN DO THE MAKEUP;
BUILD A PASTA BRIDGE
USING THE ENGINEERING
PRINCIPLES WE STUDIED.
ONLY CATCH?
IT MUST SUPPORT THIS
TEN KILO WEIGHT.
(STUDENTS GRUMBLE)
DUDE,
WE COULD DO THAT.
JUST FOCUS ON PASSING
AND GETTING THE HELL
OUT OF HERE, OKAY?
I AM, MAN.
THAT'S WHY I NEED YOU
TO HELP ME.
MY MARK IS CRAP.
BINCE:
IT REALLY IS.
YOU NEED TO ACE THIS,
GAVIN.
IF YOU NEED ANY EXTRA HELP...
SIR, HE'LL ACE
THE TAKE-HOME
IF WE CAN WORK ON IT
TOGETHER.
THIS IS YOUR MARK TOO,
JIMMY.
YOU SURE?
YEAH.
BINCE:
OKAY.
REALLY, MAN,
YOU'D DO THIS FOR ME?
I GOT YOUR BACK, SPIN.
WE CAN ACE THIS.
I HOPE YOU'RE RIGHT.
♪♪♪
JANE?
JANE, I'VE BEEN LOOKING
ALL OVER FOR YOU!
I'M IN A GLASS ROOM,
SPIN.
YOU GOTTA DO
SOME OF THE WORK HERE.
I'M IN REMISSION;
NO MORE CANCER.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
JANE, I JUST GOT THE NEWS,
I HAD TO SEE YOU!
(CHUCKLES)
I MET YOU AT THE WORST TIME
IN MY LIFE.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW MUCH MORE KICKASS
IT'S GONNA BE NOW?
I HAVE A PRETTY DECENT GUESS,
YEAH.
SO WHAT NOW?
NEW LEASE ON LIFE?
BIG PARTY?
NO. FIRST, JIMMY AND I HAVE
TO BUILD A BRIDGE
OF NOODLES...
FOR PHYSICS.
I ACE THE TAKE-HOME
AND THEN WE PARTY.
OKAY.
(GIGGLES)
PETER:
DUDE! OUR VIDEO, MAN,
IT'S VIRAL MANIA.
DUH! WE ROCK, MAN.
YEAH, AND IF 500 PEOPLE
VOTE ON OUR MYROOM PAGE,
WE GET TO GO TO THE BANDS
OF THE BLOGOSPHERE SHOWCASE
TO PLAY LIVE!
DUDES, THIS IS THE BEST DAY
OF MY LIFE.
EMMA:
SIX YEARS OF SCHOOL,
ONE CRAZY ROAD TRIP,
AND IT ALL COMES DOWN
TO THIS.
WHAT IF IT'S NO?
(MIMICKS PARENTS)
MANUELA,
I TOLD YOU NOT TO PUT ALL
YOUR EGGS IN ONE BASKET.
LET'S JUST DO IT.
(DEEP INHALE)
ONE...
TWO...           TWO...
(ENVELOPES TEAR)
(LETTERS RUSTLE)
MANNY AND EMMA:
WE ARE PLEASED TO OFFER YOU
ACCEPTANCE INTO THE SMITHDALE
POLI-SCI PROGRAM!
DRAMA PROGRAM!
MANNY AND EMMA:
(JOYOUS LAUGHTER)
SMITHDALE HERE WE COME.
OH, HERE'S THE APPLICATION
FOR REZ.
(READING)
DOUBLE OCCUPANCY ROOMS
ARE LIMITED.
WE'D BETTER SEND THESE IN FAST
IF WE WANNA BE ROOMIES.
MANNY AND EMMA:
(GIGGLE)
SPINNER:
HEY-HEY,
JIMMY, JIM, JIMBO.
WHAT'S UP?
YOU TELL ME,
YOU'RE THE ONE
WITH THE NEWS.
AND BY THE LOOKS OF IT,
I'M GUESSING IT'S GOOD?
CANCER-FREE HIGH FIVE,
MY FRIEND.
NOT UNTIL YOU WASH THAT THING,
BUT...
DEFINITELY A CANCER-FREE
THROWDOWN
IN OUR NEAR FUTURE.
SPINNER:
OH, YOU KNOW IT!
JIMMY:
YEAH, AFTER WE PUT
GLUE TO PASTA -
YOU ARE GONNA PUT IN ON THAT,
RIGHT?
(WATER SPLASHES)
DAMMIT!
SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN, DUDE.
JIMMY:
NO, MORON,
I DROPPED MY PHONE.
(HALF LAUGHS)
(CHUCKLES)
OH, HO, HO.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
IT'S A PERFECTLY GOOD
CELL PHONE, MAN.
WHAT? HERE,
AT LEAST TAKE MY GLOVES.
AWW!
YOU'RE INSANE.
(WATER SLOSHES)
(DISGUSTED BREATH)
WELL, WHAT CAN I SAY?
I'M NOT AFRAID
TO GET MY HANDS DIRTY.
OKAY. UGH!
(GIGGLES)
MR. SANTOS:
UGH, ALL OF THESE?
ARE YOU TRYING TO TAKE ME
TO THE DRY CLEANERS?
YOU ARE THE DRY CLEANERS,
DAD.
(LAUGHS)
LUCKY GIRL.
HEY, WHO'S GONNA CLEAN YOUR
CLOTHES AT UNIVERSITY, HUH?
DON'T LOOK AT ME.
OH, BY THE WAY,
WHO IS BERNICE?
ISN'T THAT YOUR AGENT?
YEAH, THE ONE
WHO NEVER CALLS.
WELL, SHE CALLED.
LEFT A MESSAGE
WITH YOUR MOTHER
FOR AN AUDITION.
REALLY?
DID SHE SAY WHAT FOR?
WELL, ARE YOU GONNA
CALL HER BACK?
NAH,
I'M A SMITHDALE GIRL NOW.
(LAUGHS)
THAT'S MY GIRL.
WHO NEEDS
RAZZLE-DAZZLE SHOWBIZ
WHEN YOU HAVE SCHOOL,
HUH?
(CHUCKLES)
STUDZ RULES, MAN.
BLOGGERS LOVE US.
WE GOT THE GIG.
WE GET TO PERFORM LIVE?
YEAH, BUT THE B.O.B. SHOWCASE
IS TOMORROW NIGHT.
TOMORROW NIGHT?
IT'S NOT A LOT OF TIME
TO PRACTICE.
WHOA, WHOA, PRACTICE?
WE HAVE EXAMS.
DUDES, COME ON,
THIS IS A CHANCE TO PLAY
IN FRONT OF A REAL AUDIENCE.
HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE.
YEAH,
AND WEBCAST TO THOUSANDS.
SAV:
THOUSANDS?
JOHNNY:
WE KNOW ALL ABOUT YOU GUYS.
HEY, JOHNNY,
DIDN'T I ALREADY
KICK YOUR ASS, MAN?
JOHNNY:
PHYSICALLY,
BUT MUSICALLY?
YOU GUYS JUST KEEP KICKING IT.
YOU GUYS OWE US,
BIG TIME.
WHO DO YOU THINK VOTED YOU
INTO THE B.O.B. SHOWCASE?
MANUELA SANTOS!
HI! KISSY!
HONEY, YOU HAVE BEEN
ON OUR RADAR
SINCE YOUR LAST AUDITION.
WALK.
I LOVE "WEST DRIVE",
SO THANK YOU.
OH, THIS ROLE
WILL BE PERF FOR YOU.
NOW THERE ARE
A COUPLE THINGS.
WE'RE SHOOTING IN THE SUN
ON LOCATION.
THOUGHTS?
SUN? NOT AN ISSUE.
LOVE IT.
OKAY, ONE MORE THING
AND I'M SORRY,
BUT YOU MIGHT HAVE TO SHARE
A VILLA WITH BRETT.
BRETT? (STAMMERS)
AS IN "BRAD WEST" BRETT?
THE STAR ON THE SHOW?
YEAH, I'M SORRY,
IT'S A BUDGET THING,
YOU KNOW.
BRETT?!
ROOMMATE.
I CAN'T SEE
HOW THAT'D BE A PROBLEM.
I KNOW, I LOVE HIM.
DON'T YOU LOVE HIM?
I LOVE HIM.
YEAH.
NOW, HONEY,
YOU'RE GRADUATING, RIGHT?
UH... YEAH.
YEAH, OKAY.
NOW THIS ROLE WILL BE
FULL-TIME FOR EIGHT MONTHS,
SO IF YOU HAD
ANY COLLEGE PLANS...
UH... NO,
I DEFINITELY DON'T
HAVE ANY PLANS.
OKAY, NICE, NICE.
WELL, YOUR WARDROBE SESH
IS MANANA.
OKAY.
(SCOFFS)
EXCUSE ME! NO.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
WHAT, YOU DON'T CHECK
YOUR PHONE?
WHERE THE HELL WERE YOU
LAST NIGHT?
SORRY, DUDE,
I FORGOT.
YOU FORGOT?
THIS, THIS BRIDGE
IS YOUR FUTURE
AND YOU FORGOT?
I'M REALLY SORRY, MAN,
BUT YOU'RE DOING REALLY WELL
BY YOURSELF.
YES, KEY WORDS:
"BY MYSELF".
I DID TWICE THE WORK
AND I'M STILL NOT DONE.
DUDE,
I'M NO SCIENCE BRAIN ANYWAY.
I PROBABLY JUST WOULD'VE
HELD YOU UP.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT'S WHY YOUR NAME'S NOT GONNA
GO ANYWHERE ON THIS PROJECT.
GOOD LUCK ON THE EXAM.
UH, DUDE,
YOU SAID YOU WOULD HELP ME?
HELP YOU,
NOT DO THE ENTIRE PROJECT
FOR YOU,
BECAUSE YOU CONTINUE
TO RELY ON ME
TO GET YOU OUT OF TROUBLE
AND I'M SICK OF IT.
SO, WHAT THE HELL AM I SUPPOSED
TO DO NOW?
JIMMY:
I DON'T KNOW.
FLUNK, AGAIN.
HANG OUT WITH YOUR BAND DORKS
NEXT YEAR.
I KNOW ABOUT "STUDZ".
(SMIRKS)
YEAH, DID YOU KNOW
WE HAVE A GIG TONIGHT?
VOTED IN BY OUR FANS.
SOME PEOPLE ACTUALLY
APPRECIATE ME FOR WHO I AM.
WHO? (LAUGHS)
KING OF THE BURNOUTS?
WHAT TYPE OF LIFE
IS THAT, MAN?
MINE.
YOU KNOW,
UP UNTIL YESTERDAY,
I DIDN'T KNOW
I WAS GONNA HAVE A LIFE,
AND NOW THAT I DO,
I'M GONNA DO STUFF
THAT MATTERS TO ME.
SPINNER:
SO, ARE YOU GONNA COME
THROW YOUR PANTIES
AT THE STAGE TONIGHT?
HOLY,
YOU MADE THE SHOWCASE.
AWESOME, EH?
STUDZ RULES.
WELL, YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO RULE WITHOUT ME.
MY GEOGRAPHY EXAM'S
TOMORROW.
SO,
HOW'D THE BRIDGE GO?
JIMMY GOT ALL NAGGY
ON MY ASS,
SO I BAILED.
WAIT, SPIN,
YOU NEED TO PASS.
REALLY?
'CAUSE I WAS THINKING
THAT IF I FAIL...
I'LL JUST BE BACK HERE
NEXT YEAR...
WITH YOU.
UH, NO YOU WON'T.
LOOK, I DON'T WANNA
BE WITH A GUY
WHO TRIES TO FAIL.
IT'S LAME.
THE EXAM'S TOMORROW,
RIGHT?
SO...
YOU BETTER GO STUDY.
YEAH, OKAY.
OKAY, I'LL STUDY.
OKAY, I PUT THAT
OUR SECOND CHOICE
IS A QUAD DORM.
IS THAT OKAY?
I AM SO GLAD THAT
I'M GONNA HAVE YOU.
DAMIAN JUST TOLD ME
HE'S GOING TO BANTING.
OH.
BABE, I'M SORRY.
ARE YOU GUYS BREAKING UP?
UH, WE'RE NOT SURE.
IT'S JUST SO WEIRD
THAT EVERYTHING'S CHANGING,
EXCEPT FOR ME AND YOU.
OKAY, JUST SIGN HERE
TO BE ROOMIES!
EM, I CAN'T.
WHAT? WHY?
I'M NOT SURE ABOUT THE WHOLE
SMITHDALE THING ANYMORE.
BUT, MANNY,
THIS WAS OUR DREAM.
HOW COULD YOU DO THIS?
THERE'S A ROLE FOR ME
ON "WEST DRIVE".
IT'S AN AMAZING
OPPORTUNITY.
BUT I THOUGHT SMITHDALE DRAMA
WAS WHAT EVERY ACTOR WANTS.
YEAH, BUT EM,
THERE'S SOMETHING TO BE SAID
FOR HAVING THE JOB
THAT EVERYONE
AT SMITHDALE DRAMA WANTS.
I GUESS I CAN'T COMPETE
WITH THAT.
(EXHALES)
(FINGERS TAP AGAINST DESK)
(DEEP INHALE)
(EXHALES)
(THINKS OF DRUM BEATS PLAYING)
(TEXTBOOK PAGES FLAP)
(DRUM BEATS PLAY)
(EXHALES)
(TEXTBOOK THUDS ONTO FLOOR)
(PLAYS DRUMS)
(SYMBOLS CRASH,
DRUMS PLAY)
DOUG:
(BAND PLAYS)
♪ COME ON! ♪
♪ GET READY ♪
♪ ALL RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ COME ON, YEAH ♪
♪ GET READY ♪
(LOUD WAILING)
♪ AAAHHH!! ♪
THANK YOU!
WE ARE THE LEDER-HOSERS.
(AUDIENCE CHEERS AND HOLLERS)
FINALLY!
WHERE WERE YOU GUYS?
CRAMMING.
EXAMS, REMEMBER?
THIS IS THE FANCY-ASS
SHOWCASE?
I'M NOT READY.
OH, COME ON, GUYS,
FOCUS.
WE'RE ON NEXT.
(STUDZ BEGIN TO PLAY)
♪ SHARED CUSTODY
SHARED CUSTODY ♪
♪ ALTERNATE WEEKENDS
AND HOLIDAYS ♪
♪ TWICE THE GIFTS
TWICE THE GIFTS ♪
♪ BUT ONLY EVER HALF
THE LOVE ♪
♪ SHARED CUSTODY
SHARED CUSTODY ♪
LAME!
♪ TWICE THE GIFTS
TWICE THE GIFTS ♪
(MIC FEEDBACK SQUEALS
OVER SLURRED LYRICS)
(AMPLIFIERS AND SPEAKERS
ARE TURNED OFF)
JOHNNY AND FRIENDS:
(LAUGH)
(DRUMMING CONTINUES
AND HALTS SUDDENLY)
(MIC FEEDBACK SQUEALS)
NICE.
AUDIENCE:
(LAUGHING)
WARDROBE STYLIST:
SO, STARLET,
LET'S HAVE A LOOK.
WOW.
(LAUGHS)
DO YOU REALLY SEE
LARA COLLETT IN THIS?
AW, YEAH,
IT'S PERFECT.
DROP DEAD SEXY, GIRL.
(CHUCKLES)
WARDROBE STYLIST:
OKAY, NOW LET'S TRY THIS TOP ON.
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
UM, WITH PEOPLE AROUND?
WARDROBE STYLIST:
(CHUCKLES) FORGOT YOU'RE NEW.
WE'RE LIKE FAMILY HERE,
YOU KNOW.
IT'S OKAY,
JUST PUT IT ON.
OKAY.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT A SET
WOULD BE LIKE A SECOND HOME.
BRETT:
MORE LIKE A FIRST HOME.
MY BOYFRIEND HATES IT.
HE NEVER SEES ME.
HAVE YOU TOLD YOUR FRIENDS
YOU'LL BE DISAPPEARING?
MY BEST FRIEND
WILL BE BUSY
WITH HER FIRST YEAR
AT SMITHDALE.
WARDROBE STYLIST:
SMITHDALE U?
WOW, SMART GIRL!
WE BOTH GOT IN.
HER FOR POLI-SCI
AND ME FOR DRAMA.
BRETT:
EXCUSE ME?
SMITHDALE DRAMA?
WOW, I AUDITIONED
LIKE THREE TIMES.
YOU DIDN'T GO EITHER?
ARE YOU KIDDING?
THEY WOULDN'T HAVE ME.
WHAT ARE YOU EVEN
DOING HERE?
WELL, LIVING THE DREAM,
BEING A WORKING ACTRESS
ON "WEST DRIVE".
COME ON,
IT CAN'T BE THAT BAD.
YOU'VE BEEN ON THIS SHOW
9 SEASONS.
BRETT:
EXACTLY!
I CAN'T GET ANYTHING ELSE.
YOU KNOW, EVERYONE JUST SEES ME
AS BRAD WEST.
PLUS HE'S GOT THE RANGE
OF A BAG OF HAIR.
HE COULD USE SOME SMITHDALE.
(TRAFFIC HUMS,
LOW BAR CHATTER)
DOUG:
DUDE, MAN,
YOU CAN REALLY POUND.
BUT THOSE OTHER GUYS?
THEY'RE NOT REAL ROCKERS.
YEAH, TELL ME ABOUT IT.
HEY, DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT, MAN.
OKAY,
YOU'LL OUTGROW 'EM.
HEY, I DROPPED OUT OF SCHOOL
TO PLAY WITH MY BAND.
YOU DID?
SO WHAT HAPPENED?
IT'S STILL HAPPENING,
MAN!
NINETEEN YEARS
WITH THE LEDER-HOSERS!
IF YOU PLAY YER CARDS RIGHT,
YOU COULD BE LIKE THE DOUG'ER.
SPINNER:
NINETEEN YEARS?
SO YOU NEVER GOT THAT
PIECE OF PAPER?
WHAT,
HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA?
OH, MAN, LIFE AIN'T ABOUT
A PIECE OF PAPER, OKAY?
IT'S ABOUT WHAT YOU
ROLL IN IT.
(CHUCKLES)
SORRY, I DON'T TOUCH
THAT STUFF ANYMORE.
YOU SURE?
IT'S 4:20 SOMEWHERE,
MAN.
ALL RIGHT.
(DRUMSTICKS CLATTER)
PA ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION STUDENTS...
JANE:
HEY. HEY.
I SAW THE WEBCAST
LAST NIGHT.
I THINK EVERYBODY DID.
TOUGH BREAK.
SO ROCK AND OR ROLL
MAY HAVE TO WAIT,
BUT AT LEAST YOU STUDIED,
RIGHT?
YEAH, TOTALLY.
YEAH.
YOU DIDN'T,
DID YOU?
GOOD LUCK, SPIN.
JIMMY!
JIMMY, MAN, YOU...
(SIGHS)
BRIDGE ROCKS, DUDE.
(EXHALES)
YUP, A PLUS.
COULD'VE BEEN YOURS TOO,
NUMBNUT.
I KNOW I'M AN IDIOT,
BUT, DUDE,
YOU GOTTA HELP ME
PASS THIS EXAM.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
JUST GONNA FLUNK,
COME BACK AND "RULE"
NEXT YEAR?
JIMMY, YOU HAVE LIFE PLANS,
RIGHT?
STEM CELL SURGERY
IN THE SUMMER
AND THEN NEW YORK CITY.
I HAVE NO PLANS.
NOTHING.
I'M TERRIFIED, MAN.
YOU'LL FIND YOUR WAY, MAN.
NOT IF I DON'T PASS
THIS EXAM.
JIMMY, COME ON.
JUST TELL ME EVERYTHING
YOU KNOW ABOUT PHYSICS.
(CHUCKLES)
SPINNER,
THE EXAM STARTS ANY SECOND.
HATZILAKOS:
FIVE MINUTES TO GEOGRAPHY-011
AND PHYSICS-012 EXAMS.
MAKE YOUR WAY TO THE GYM,
PLEASE.
DUDE, YOU'RE THE SMARTEST GUY
I KNOW.
JUST DO SOMETHING?
WHEN IN DOUBT,
PICK "C".
YUP.
I KNOW.
HEY.
I CALLED LAST NIGHT;
YOU WERE AT
A WARDROBE FITTING.
SO I GUESS
YOU GOT THE PART?
ANY CHANCE YOU WANT
A JOB AS A PA?
WHAT AM I GONNA DO
WITHOUT YOU?
BORE MY NEW ROOMMATE
WITH MY LONELINESS?
CALL AND BORE ME INSTEAD,
PLEASE?
YOU'LL BE BUSY WITH
YOUR OWN PROBLEMS.
LIKE HOW TO DEAL WITH
ALL YOUR FAME AND MONEY.
EMMA'S SO GROWN UP.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
SHE'S GOING TO UNIVERSITY.
DO YOU THINK
I SHOULD BE TOO?
YOU'VE ALWAYS WANTED
TO BE AN ACTRESS.
GOOD MONEY,
A GOOD OPPORTUNITY...
I DON'T WANT TO MAKE
THE WRONG DECISION.
THE ONLY WRONG DECISION
IS INDECISION, MANUELA.
WHO ARE YOU?
WHERE'S THE PERSON
WHO USED TO TELL ME WHAT TO DO?
YOU'RE AN ADULT NOW,
REMEMBER?
I KNOW YOU'LL DO
WHAT'S BEST FOR YOU.
(EXHALES)
(SNIFFS)
COME ON, BRAIN,
ANSWERS.
(FIRE ALARM RINGS)
FILE OUT, PEOPLE.
USE BOTH EXITS.
LEAVE YOUR PAPERS BEHIND!
THANK YOU!
(WATER SPRAYS,
STUDENTS YELP)
(FIRE ALARM RINGS
AS WATER SPRAYS)
(CHAIR CLATTERS)
SO GLAD I CAUGHT YOU.
I JUST ABOUT TO MAIL
MY RESIDENCE APPLICATION.
LAST CHANCE.
(ENVELOPE TEARS)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
(EXHALES)
NOW IT'S YOUR TURN.
THIS IS THIS YOUR
"WEST DRIVE" CONTRACT?
HOLLYWOOD CAN WAIT.
WE MAKE GREAT ROOMMATES,
REMEMBER?
JUST... DO IT.
I CAN'T WATCH.
OKAY.
HERE GOES...
(NERVOUS GROAN)
(MANNY AND EMMA GIGGLE)
SMITHDALE HERE WE COME!
YAY!
SO WHAT'S THE DEAL
WITH THE HANDS?
WHEN SOMEONE PULLS
THE ALARM
IT SPLATS PURPLE INK
ON YOUR HANDS.
MS. H, WHAT HAPPENS
WITH OUR EXAMS?
MAKEUPS ARE GONNA BE
RESCHEDULED
AT THE END OF THE EXAM
PERIOD.
YOU ARE ONE LUCKY GUY.
I KNOW.
I KNOW, I REALLY AM.
OH, THERE'S JIMMY.
UH...
LET ME CATCH UP
WITH YOU LATER, OKAY?
OKAY.
DUDE!
DUDE, TALK ABOUT
SAVED BY THE BELL, HUH?
SAVED BY THE...
THE WHAT NOW?
YOU...?
(NERVOUS BREATH)
(SHOCKED LAUGH)
DUDE, I OWE YOU
SO HUGE!
I GET FOUR EXTRA DAYS TO STUDY
FOR EVERYTHING PHYSICS, NOW.
(TIGHT INHALE)
YUP.
WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
IT'S YOUR FIRST LESSON.
OBJECTS IN MOTION
STAY IN MOTION.
ALL RIGHT.
(PLAYFUL JAB)
I'M IN MOTION,
ALL RIGHT?
NOTHING'S GONNA
STOP ME NOW.
(LAUGHS)