HEY, HEY, PANTHER FANS,
YELL IT OUT
AND ROCK THE STANDS!
D-C-S!
ON YOUR FEET,
CLAP YOUR HANDS!
GO PANTHERS!
(EXHALES)
WELCOME TO THE SQUAD.
FINALLY.
YOU SHOULD'VE BEEN HERE
MONTHS AGO.
HOLLY J:
HELL-O! I THOUGHT THIS
WAS A CHEEROCRACY.
AS NEW CO-CAPTAIN,
I THINK I GET A SAY.
UM, THIS WHOLE TRYOUT
WAS A FORMALITY,
THANKS TO YOU,
HOLLY J.
MANNY, SHE'S A MOM.
ISN'T DOING THE SPLITS
WHAT GOT HER INTO
THIS WHOLE MESS
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
MANNY:
SHUT UP, HOLLY J.
SOMETIMES I ENVY DARCY
FOR LEAVING THE SQUAD.
I KNOW I HAVE ISABELLA,
BUT IT WON'T INTERFERE.
I PROMISE.
FINE,
LET'S SEE HOW YOU DO
PLANNING FOR THE SPIRIT SQUAD
DANCE THIS WEEK.
CAN'T WAIT!
8 A.M. TOMORROW,
STUDENT COUNCIL MEETING.
NO EXCUSES.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
SO, YOU FINALLY
HAVE IT ALL:
CHEERLEADING,
FAKE FRIENDS...
ONLY ONE THING MISSING.
BYE BYE, LUCAS.
YOU CAN'T AVOID ME
FOREVER.
THAT'S THE PLAN.
♪♪♪
ANNOUNCEMENT:
DO-RE-MI-FA-SO!
TICKETS FOR THE DEGRASSI
MUSICAL PREMIER
WILL BE ON SALE...
I'D GIVE YOU A HAND,
BUT ALL I'VE GOT
IS A FOOT.
I, I SEE YOUR FOOT
AND UH, RAISE ONE HIP.
OKAY.
OW.
WATCH MY LEG.
MIA:
SPIRIT SQUAD DANCE COMMITTEE?
YEAH, HOW'D YOU KNOW?
MIA:
I... (LAUGHS)
TYLER AND MIA:
(LAUGH)
(CAR WHIRS BY)
MANNY:
THANKS FOR WALKING ME.
SO ROMANTIC.
I'D WALK YOU TO CLASS
IF I HADN'T BEEN BANNED.
FORBIDDEN LOVE
BRINGS PEOPLE TOGETHER.
SO, YOU WANNA
MEET FOR LUNCH?
CAN'T.
GOING TO HOOTERS
WITH YOUR DAD.
(SARCASTIC LAUGH)
WHEN AM I GOING SHOE SHOPPING
WITH YOUR MOM?
(SARCASTIC)
OH, YEAH.
I'M NOT KIDDING.
WHEN?
WHAT?
WE'RE ENGAGED.
NEXT STEP:
MEET THE PARENTS.
UH, YEAH, MANNY,
I, I TOLD YOU...
I KNOW THERE'S A REASON
WHY YOU NEVER WANT
TO TALK ABOUT THEM,
BUT YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO,
EVENTUALLY.
OKAY, I'LL TELL YOU
ONE THING.
UM...
THEY'RE IN MALTA.
MALTA, THE COUNTRY?
WHAT'RE THEY DOING THERE?
THEY GOT DEPORTED,
YEARS AGO.
BUT I WAS BORN HERE,
SO I STAYED BEHIND.
WOW.
SO... WHAT HAPPENED?
MAYBE SOME OTHER TIME,
BABE.
SADLY, IT'S ALMOST
IMPOSSIBLE TO VISIT.
FLIGHTS ARE MUCHO DINERO.
SO...
YOU'RE REALLY
ALL ALONE HERE?
WELL, I HAVE YOU;
THAT'S ENOUGH.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
GO.
(HEAVY SIGH)
LIBERTY:
AND TO PREVENT A REPEAT
OF THE LAST DANCE FIASCO,
THE DJ WILL NOT BE
TAKING REQUESTS.
ANYONE WISHING TO APPROACH
THE DJ MUST BE VETTED BY
A OFFICIAL MEMBER
OF THE SPIRIT SQUAD.
UH, "SPRING FEVER"
PASSED AS THEME
FOR THE SPIRIT SQUAD
FUNDRAISER DANCE.
(GAVEL BANGS)
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
UH, LIBERTY?
WOULD IT BE OKAY IF I TOOK HOME
SOME DECORATIONS
AFTER THE DANCE?
AKA...
SIPHON SCHOOL RESOURCES?
ISABELLA'S BIRTHDAY'S
COMING UP AND...
KID'S PARTIES
CAN BE EXPENSIVE.
SAY NO MORE.
OH, AND FYI,
THERE ARE MORE ALLOONS-BAY
IN THE OSET-CLAY.
AH-HA!
THANKS,
YOU'RE AN IFESAVER-LAY.
ANNOUNCEMENT:
THE DONNIE OSMOND GOAL,
DEGRASSI.
THE HARDEST PART
STAYING IN TV...
COME ON, MIA,
I JUST WANNA TALK.
I'M LATE FOR CLASS,
OKAY?
STUDENT:
HEY!
(LOCK RATTLES,
DOOR BANGS OPEN)
(ENVELOPE RUSTLES)
MR. BINCE:
NOW, DON'T BE FOOLED BY
THE ROCKS THAT YOU'VE GOT
OR THE ICE.
ONLY A REAL DIAMOND
CUTS GLASS.
SO, YOU STILL FOOLING PEOPLE
WITH THAT RING, MRS. HOGART?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL,
FOR A FAKE ENGAGEMENT,
YOU SEEM TO BE
WEARING THAT RING A LOT.
ANYONE GOT SOME BLING
THEY WANT TO TEST?
UH... (SIGHS)
(DIAMOND SCRAPES
AS IT CUTS GLASS)
MR. BINCE:
WELL, WELL, LOOKS LIKE MANNY'S
GOT A REAL DIAMOND.
STUDENTS:
OOH!
MANNY:
MMM... (CHUCKLES)
I MUST'VE HIT THE JACKPOT
WITH MOM'S JEWELRY BOX.
WHO KNEW?
MR. BINCE:
OF COURSE, THERE ARE OTHER
MINERALS THAT CUT GLASS,
BUT IF YOU WANT
TO KNOW FOR SURE...
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
MIA:
SORRY.
OKAY, SO, EVERYONE WILL
GET STAMPED AND THEN-
MOMMY, I'M HUNGRY.
NOT RIGHT NOW, IZZY.
OKAY, UM...
HAVE WE DECIDED ON DEEJAYS?
YUPPIE MOM:
LOOK ETHAN, IT'S ISABELLA!
ETHAN'S LOOKING FORWARD
TO ISABELLA'S BIRTHDAY PARTY!
OH, DID YOU RENT
PLAYGROUND PARADISE?
ETHAN LOVED HIS PARTY THERE.
UH... NO.
UM, I THINK...
YEAH, NO, I THINK WE'RE GONNA
HAVE IT AT MY MOM'S HOUSE.
YUPPIE DAD:
OH, GREAT!
YEAH,
THAT'LL BE FUN TOO.
OKAY.
SORRY.
UH, WHERE WERE WE?
I WANT
A CHOCOLATE COOKIE.
(SIGHS) YOU KNOW,
MAKING DECORATIONS
WOULD BE A WHOLE LOT EASIER
WITHOUT YOU-KNOW-WHO.
JUST ONE, MOMMY,
PLEASE?
IZZY, WE'VE GOT COOKIES
AT HOME, OKAY?
ISABELLA:
I WANT A COOKIE!
(BANGING TANTRUM)
MIA:
NO, IZZY, STOP.
PLEASE.
I'M SORRY, UM...
WHAT'S THE NEXT ONE?
(CLEARS THROAT)
IZZY.
(BIKE WHIRS BY,
STUDENTS CHATTER)
MR. BINCE:
I WOULD GUESS...
THIS IS PROBABLY
JUST ABOUT A CARAT.
WHAT?
I MEAN... WOW.
HOW MUCH WOULD SOMETHING
LIKE THAT BE WORTH?
A GREAT CUT LIKE THIS?
HMM, MAYBE FIVE G'S?
FIVE-ZERO-ZERO-ZERO?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
$5000 DOLLARS
FOR YOUR RING?
DEPENDING ON
THE PAWN BROKER.
NOT THAT I'M SUGGESTING
HOCKING YOUR MOM'S BLING,
ERR, JEWELRY.
(UNCOMFORTABLE EXHALE)
SO, JAY GAVE YOU
AN ACTUAL DIAMOND
FOR YOUR FAKE
ENGAGEMENT?
JAY, GAVE ME A REAL DIAMOND
FOR OUR REAL ENGAGEMENT.
OH MY GOD,
YOU'RE SERIOUS.
SURPRISE?
REAL RING,
REAL ENGAGEMENT.
SHOULD I BE PLANNING
A REAL BABY SHOWER?
NO! IT JUST...
IT JUST WORKS.
I AM GOING TO NEED
A MILLION YEARS
TO GET USED TO THIS.
YOU AND JAY HOGART?
I HAVE THE $5000 DOLLAR RING
TO PROVE IT.
ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION DEGRASSI STUDENTS,
YOU WANNA GET GOOD GRADES?
VOLUNTEER FOR
THE DEGRASSI SOUP KITCHEN
THIS SATURDAY MORNING.
LUCAS:
SO YOU'LL TAKE MY MONEY...
(CHUCKLES)
BUT YOU WON'T TALK TO ME?
MIA:
WHY NOW, LUCAS?
HUMOUR ME, PLEASE.
WHAT'S CHANGED?
I SEE YOU EVERY DAY.
MAKES ME WISH THAT UH...
THINGS HAD WORKED OUT
BETTER...
BETWEEN US.
OH, OKAY.
SO YOU WISH YOU HADN'T
DECIDED TO BAIL ON ME
WHEN I WAS PREGNANT?
I WAS FOURTEEN, OKAY?
I GOT SCARED.
I WAS THIRTEEN!
YOU THINK THAT
I WASN'T SCARED?
YOU THINK THAT I DIDN'T
WANT TO WALK AWAY?
SOME DAYS I STILL DO.
THAT WAS A LONG TIME AGO.
I'VE GROWN UP.
WE BOTH HAVE.
HOW 'BOUT
A SECOND CHANCE, HUH?
TO SPEND SOME TIME WITH YOU?
AND ISABELLA?
YEAH, SURE.
TRAILER PARK
FAMILY REUNION?
SWEET.
WE'RE PAINTING LEAVES TONIGHT,
MAMA MIA.
YOU BETTER BE THERE,
AND NO RUG RAT,
GOT IT?
(EXHALES)
YOU REALLY WANT
TO HELP ME?
BABYSIT AFTER SCHOOL.
(TRAFFIC HUMS)
(KEYS JINGLE)
HEY, YOU'RE UP LATE.
YEAH, I STAYED LATE WITH
SPIRIT SQUAD AFTER SCHOOL.
THE DANCE IS TOMORROW.
ANNA:
AFTER SCHOOL?
WHAT ABOUT ISABELLA?
SHE WAS...
SHE WAS WITH HER DAD.
LUCAS?
HE WANTS TO BE
IN OUR LIVES MORE.
ANNA:
AND YOU'RE GONNA LET HIM?
MIA, WHEN YOU HAD IZZY,
WE AGREED...
MIA:
MOM, IT'S BEEN THREE YEARS
AND THINGS ARE FINALLY
ON TRACK FOR ME.
I MADE THE SPIRIT SQUAD
AND I HAVE THE DANCE
TOMORROW...
MIA, I HAVE TO WORK
A LATE SHIFT
AT THE RESTAURANT TOMORROW.
YOU HAVE TO LOOK AFTER IZZY.
I'M SORRY.
WHAT? OKAY, NO...
MOM, CAN'T YOU SWITCH SHIFTS
OR SOMETHING?
YOU HAVE TO ROLL
WITH THE PUNCHES, KIDDO.
(PEN TAPS ON BINDER)
(STUDENT CHATTER)
(PAYPHONE CLICKS,
CHANGE JINGLES)
OH-HO-HO.
SO...
HEY, UM...
YOU DID A GOOD JOB
YESTERDAY.
ISABELLA WAS
A HAPPY CAMPER.
YOU KNOW, UH...
ARE YOU GOING
TO THE DANCE TONIGHT?
SCHOOL DANCE?
NOT EXACTLY MY THING,
BUT IF YOU WANTED ME TO-
PERFECT!
SO YOU CAN TAKE CARE
OF ISABELLA AGAIN.
'CAUSE I HAVE TO GO
TONIGHT,
OH, FOR SPIRIT SQUAD.
(LAUGHS)
IT'S GONNA COST YOU.
OKAY, SO I'LL, UH,
DROP HER OFF TONIGHT,
'KAY?
(DISGUSTED CHUCKLE)
("See You Run" performed by
The Scenario plays)
♪♪♪
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
(EXCITED CHATTER)
DO I GET YOUR SEAL
OF APPROVAL?
I MEANT THE STAMP,
BUT THAT WAS NICE.
♪ I don't watch you
all time ♪
♪ Well I know
and I know and I know ♪
♪ What's right for you
is right for me ♪
YOUR DISGUISE IS PERFECT.
THE SACRIFICES
I MAKE FOR MY GIRL.
I KNOW.
AND THAT'S WHY I HAVE
A SURPRISE FOR YOU.
I BOUGHT US TICKETS.
TICKETS?
GREAT. WHAT KIND?
PLANE TICKETS.
TO MALTA!
MALTA?
RIGHT, MY PARENTS.
YEAH.
I KNOW THINGS
ARE REALLY COMPLICATED,
BUT I WANT TO MEET THEM.
THEY'RE GONNA BE
MY IN-LAWS.
MANNY, CAN YOU JUST DROP
THE PARENTS THING, PLEASE?
OH GOD.
THEY DON'T LIVE IN MALTA.
WHAT? YEAH!
(NERVOUS SNORT)
SORT OF.
NO.
JAY, WHAT THE HELL?!
I DIDN'T THINK YOU WERE
GONNA BUY TICKETS!
THAT'S NOT THE POINT!
YOU LIED.
♪ You know it's,
you know it's true ♪
OH, GUYS,
SORRY, YOU NEED TICKETS.
I'LL TAKE THAT
INTO CONSIDERATION.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
EVERYTHING'S FINE.
FINE, JUST GO IN.
MACKING ON GOLDEN BOY
WHILE LUCAS IS WITH THE KID?
BRAVO.
CLASSY.
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER,
MUSIC PLAYS)
HEY.
♪ You know its,
you know its true ♪
MANNY!
DIMPLES?
NOT NOW!
GO LIE TO SOMEONE ELSE.
FROM NOW ON, HONESTY.
STRAIGHT UP.
YOU LIE ABOUT
YOUR OWN PARENTS!
HOW CAN I BELIEVE
ANYTHING YOU SAY?
(TIGHT CHUCKLE)
I DIDN'T LIE.
OKAY, FINE, I DID.
MANNY:
I NEVER KNOW WHAT'S REAL
AND WHAT'S FAKE.
WHICH WAS FINE
WHEN EVERYTHING WAS FAKE,
BUT NOW THAT EVERYTHING'S
REAL...
MANNY, MANNY,
IT'S ALL REAL.
LOOK, THIS RING
IS A SYMBOL OF...
WHERE'S THE RING?
UH, NEVERMIND THE RING.
OF COURSE!
THE PLANE TICKETS.
YOU HOCKED IT,
DIDN'T YOU?
NO I DIDN'T!
OKAY, FINE, I DID.
AND YOU'RE LECTURING ME?
I DID IT FOR YOU!
MANNY,
THAT RING WAS SPECIAL.
IT BELONGED TO MY MOTHER,
MY REAL ONE.
THE ONE WHO DIED
WHEN I WAS LITTLE.
♪ ...take the pain away ♪
♪ Too late to take
the pain away ♪
THIS IS AWESOME!
I HAVEN'T BEEN "OUT" OUT
IN SUCH A LONG TIME.
REALLY?
WHY'S THAT?
YOU KNOW,
JUST BEEN BUSY.
HEY, SURFER BOY!
THINK YOU GOT WHAT IT TAKES
TO BE A GOOD STEPDAD?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHO HAS ISABELLA?
MY MOM.
I JUST WANTED
ONE DANCE,
BUT I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN
YOU MOVE FAST, JONESEY.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
THIS LITTLE LADY
ASKED ME TO BABYSIT
HER KID
SO SHE COULD HOOK UP
WITH YOUR DWEEBY LITTLE SELF.
ISABELLA IS YOUR KID, TOO.
AND YOU SAID THAT
YOU WANTED TO?
HOLD UP.
YOU TWO HAVE A KID?
(LAUGHS)
YOU'RE GONNA
WANT TO GET LOST
RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
(MOUTHS)
GOODBYE.
THANKS,
YOU'VE BEEN A GREAT HELP.
AND YOU'VE BEEN
A GREAT SCAMMER.
I'M GONNA GO PICK UP
MY DAUGHTER NOW.
MMM.
HOLLY J:
MOVING OUT? FINALLY.
YOU DIDN'T HAPPEN TO FIND
AN ENVELOPE IN HERE, DID YOU?
MONEY FROM BABY-DADDY?
NOT TODAY,
SWEETHEART.
(SIGHS)
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOUR PROBLEM IS?
HE'S A HOTTIE.
YOU COULD DO WORSE.
HE LEFT ME PREGNANT
AND ALONE.
YEAH,
THREE YEARS AGO!
NEWSFLASH, MAMMA MIA:
CHOOSY WENT OUT THE WINDOW
WHEN YOUR WATER BROKE.
MY ADVICE...
TAKE WHAT YOU CAN GET.
STUDENTS:
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
(LADDER CREAKS)
FORGET HIM.
YOU DON'T NEED HIM.
IT'S LONELY,
LIBERTY.
AND THE ONLY GUY THAT'S GONNA
LOOK AT ME IS LUCAS.
FIGHT-PICKING-BULLY LUCAS?
YOU CAN DO BETTER,
BELIEVE ME.
HE'S ISABELLA'S DAD.
I WAS A LOT DIFFERENT
BACK THEN.
OKAY, SO,
YOU MADE A MISTAKE,
BUT YOU GREW UP;
THAT'S A GOOD THING.
AND STILL I DON'T FIT IN
WITH OTHER PARENTS,
I DON'T FIT IN HERE,
I CAN'T DO ANYTHING RIGHT.
MIA, YOU'RE DOING
A GREAT JOB.
JUGGLING SPIRIT SQUAD
AND PICKS-UPS FROM DAYCARE?
CRAP!
WHAT TIME IS IT?
OH CRAP.
(PARTY ITEMS RUSTLE)
(DOOR OPENS)
I'M SORRY!
KIDS ARE ARRIVING
IN HALF AN HOUR.
GO PUT YOUR DRESS ON.
WHAT HAPPENED?
I WAS LATE PICKING UP
ISABELLA FROM DAYCARE.
AGAIN?
NEXT TIME THEY CALL
CHILDREN'S AID, MIA.
I KNOW, MOM.
I'M JUST TRYING TO HAVE A LIFE.
I'M ONLY GONNA BE 16 ONCE.
AND ISABELLA'S
ONLY GONNA TURN THREE ONCE.
YOU HAVE TO MAKE
ALL YOUR DECISIONS
WITH HER IN MIND.
THAT'S WHAT BEING
A MOTHER IS.
(WRAPPING PAPER RUSTLES)
(CHILDREN GIGGLE)
MIA:
OH, IT'S A DOLL!
OKAY, C'MON, ISABELLA,
SAY THANK YOU
AND GIVE ARIANA A HUG.
ANNA:
OH, VERY NICE.
(KNOCKING)
(CHILDREN GIGGLE)
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
IT'S MY DAUGHTER'S BIRTHDAY.
(HEAVY SIGH)
LUCAS:
HEY, IZZY,
REMEMBER ME?
IT'S MY BIRTHDAY.
LUCAS:
(LAUGHS) YEAH.
BOY:
WHAT IS THIS?
MOMMY, COME SEE.
MIA:
WOW, I...
WHAT DO YOU SAY,
ISABELLA?
THANK YOU.
NO PROBLEM, SWEETIE.
(LAUGHS)
ISN'T IT SICK?
♪ Yum-yum-yum yum yum ♪
♪ Yum yum yum yum ♪
MANNY:
JAY, IF YOU GET THIS MESSAGE,
I AM SO SORRY ABOUT THE RING.
I HAD NO IDEA...
I, I HATE YOUR VOICEMAIL.
OKAY, CALL ME,
CALL ME, CALL ME.
WE HAVE TO GET IT BACK.
I COULD SELL THE TICKETS
ON EBAY OR...
I DON'T KNOW,
I JUST THINK THAT...
(THUMP)
WHOA!
UGH.
UH, HERE,
I HAVE SOMETHING FOR YOU.
OH.
IT'S UM...
IT'S YOUR FAKE MUSTACHE.
WOW.
NO MORE DISGUISES,
NO MORE ACTING.
BECAUSE WITH YOU,
I DON'T NEED TO.
THAT'S BEAUTIFUL, JAY.
IT'S UM...
IT'S KINDA GROSS,
BUT IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
WHEN MY FATHER MET
HIS THIRD WIFE,
I FELT LIKE HE CHOSE HER
OVER ME
AND I GOT SUCKY,
I MADE A SCENE
AT THE WEDDING,
AND I KINDA LOST TOUCH.
AND THAT'S THE TRUTH?
MM-HMM.
YUP.
I DIDN'T WANT TO TELL YOU
'CAUSE...
IT WAS SUCH A LOSER-Y
THING TO DO.
I LOVE ALL OF YOU,
DUMMY!
EVEN THE LOSER-Y PARTS.
SO, YOU STILL WANT TO MEET
THE IN-LAWS?
AS LONG AS WE DON'T
HAVE TO GO TO MALTA.
NO, THEY'RE...
THEY'RE A LITTLE CLOSER.
WHERE IS MALTA ANYWAY?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
(BIKE WHIRS)
MIA:
SHE REALLY LOVES IT.
LUCAS:
OF COURSE.
I AM HER DAD, MIA.
WE GONNA TELL HER?
SOMEDAY.
LET'S JUST TAKE THIS
ONE STEP AT A TIME.
IT'LL BE GOOD FOR HER
TO KNOW HER DAD.
SO THAT YOU CAN TELL HER
BEDTIME STORIES
ABOUT ALL THE PEOPLE
THAT YOU BULLY AND HARASS?
YEAH, SOUNDS GREAT.
I'M OVER THAT STUFF.
HEY, I'LL PROVE IT.
AND I'VE GOT A JOB
THAT COULD BE PERMANENT
AFTER GRADUATION.
I'LL HAVE MONEY.
YOU'D HAVE TO SPEND IT
ON DAYCARE,
NOT "SICK" TOYS.
LUCAS:
YOU GET A GUY,
ISABELLA GETS A DAD.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS GIVE ME ANOTHER SHOT.
OKAY.
OKAY, WE CAN,
WE CAN DO THIS.
(SIGH OF RELIEF)