(SINGS HAPPILY)
YOU WOKE ME...
BY SINGING.
WHAT CAN I SAY?
I'M BLISSFUL.
THINGS ARE GREAT AT WORK,
I HAVE YOU GUYS,
AND ANDREA
GAVE ME A RAISE.
TIME TO REDECORATE!
MARCO:
THIS MEAN YOU'RE GONNA BE
PAINTING?
UH, IT MEANS
WE'RE GONNA BE PAINTING.
OOH, I'D LOVE TO,
BUT I HATE PAINTING.
MARCO:
MM-HM. ME TOO.
YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN, PAIGEY.
COME ON, GUYS.
COULD BE FUN.
ELLIE:
ANY EXCUSE TO SPEND TIME
IN PAIGE MICHALCHUK'S BEDROOM,
HUH?
PAIGE:
CAN YOU BLAME HIM?
I'M FABULOUS.
SO ARE YOU GUYS IN?
FINE.
YEAH, FINE.
EH, PAIGE, ARE WE STILL ON
FOR THE BED LATER?
MMM! ABSOLUMENT.
BED?
UH, YEAH,
ROOMMATE-ETIQUETTE?
YOU DIDN'T EVEN CHECK WITH US!
RELAX, ELEANOR.
WE'RE GOING TO IKEA.
HE'S HELPING ME
GET IN BED.
A BED.
I SWEAR.
♪♪♪
PAIGE:
(SMALL LAUGH)
SO, ANY BROTHERS?
SISTERS?
GRIFFIN:
(GRUNTS WITH EFFORT)
NO, JUST ME
AND MY DAD.
HE'S REALLY AMAZING.
DO YOU SEE YOUR MOM
A LOT?
GRIFFIN:
NOT REALLY.
WHAT ABOUT
THE MICHALCHUKS?
UH, MY PARENTS ARE GRADUALLY
GETTING OVER THE FACT
THAT THEIR SON MOVED TO EUROPE
TO PLAY HOCKEY.
AND LEFT POOR MARCO
BEHIND.
MARCO'S FINE.
HE FINALLY CUT THE CORD,
MOVED THE LAST OF HIS THINGS
FROM DYLAN'S FORMER ROOM,
AND NOW I HAVE
A BLANK SLATE!
HOW'D YOUR PARENTS DEAL
WITH HAVING TWO GAY KIDS?
I MEAN, YOU AND...
ALEX?
AKA THE ONLY GIRL
I WAS EVER INTO?
YEAH,
MAKE THAT ONE GAY KID
AND...
ONE UNDECIDED.
ELLIE:
OKAY, YOU HAVE TWO HOURS,
STARTING RIGHT NOW.
SO WE READY
TO PAINT THIS TOWN...
"TRUFFLED MINT"?
♪♪♪
(HUM OF OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
(BALLS CLACK)
CHECK IT OUT.
SPINNER:
DECENT...
BIT OF A BUTTERFACE.
(LAUGHS)
WHAT'S THAT?
IS THAT LIKE SOME WEIRDO
GUY THING?
SPINNER:
OKAY. EVERYTHING'S GOOD
ABOUT HER,
BUT HER FACE.
GET IT?
BUTTERFACE.
LAME. LAME.
FOCUS ON THIS INSTEAD,
OKAY?
SERIOUSLY, GUYS,
THE SAUSAGE FEST
IS GETTING KIND OF TIRED.
YOU KNOW,
WITH AIM LIKE THAT,
YOU'D DO AWESOME
IN THE ARCHERY CLUB.
LIKE BOWS-AND-ARROWS
ARCHERY?
THE CLUB JUST STARTED
AT SCHOOL.
FLYING ARROWS ARE STRANGELY
THERAPEUTIC.
YOU SHOULD COME.
SOUNDS MEDIEVAL.
I'M IN.
BOTH:
(LAUGH)
♪♪♪
OW. MY ARMS ARE DYING.
CAN WE JUST BE DONE?
SURE, HON.
THANK YOU.
GRIFFIN:
(CLEARS THROAT)
SO...
YOU LIKE WHAT YOU SEE?
UM...
I'M NOT SURE.
IT'S A SMIDGE MINTIER
THAN I EXPECTED.
WHEN YOU HAVE VISITORS?
YEAH?
THEY'RE NOT GONNA BE
LOOKING AT THE WALLS.
OKAY,
SPEAKING OF VISITORS,
LET'S NOT OVERSTAY
OUR WELCOME.
WE HAVE SO MUCH
CLEANING UP TO DO.
ALL RIGHT.
(HUM OF CHATTER)
REMIND ME NOT TO MESS WITH YOU,
LIKE EVER.
YOU ARE DANGEROUS!
IT'S A NEWFOUND TALENT.
(LAUGHS)
ARMSTRONG:
THAT'S GOOD, DARCY.
BUT REMEMBER TO KEEP
YOUR ELBOW UP.
JANE, YOU READY?
MM-HM.
ARMSTRONG:
HERE YOU GO.
(LAUGHS)
WOW!
FROM NOW ON,
I'M PACKING A BOW.
PLUS IT'S, UH, NICE TO HAVE
A BOYFRIEND-FREE ZONE
EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE.
PETER'S MY PARTNER
FOR ENGLISH.
DOES HE NEED A TALKING TO?
OR AN ARROW, MAYBE?
(CHUCKLES) NO, HE'S GREAT.
IT'S JUST...
EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE...
FORGET IT.
NO, COME ON,
YOU CAN TELL ME!
IT'S LIKE...
OKAY, WITH SPIN?
IF IT WEREN'T
FOR HIS PIT STAINS,
HE'D BE PERFECT.
WOW. YOU GUYS WERE
MADE FOR EACH OTHER.
I WAS ONLY GONNA TELL YOU
ABOUT PETER'S BREATH.
(LAUGHS)
FORGET I SAID THAT.
KID:
SORRY, MAN.
HEY, CAN YOU TOSS THAT
BACK TO ME?
LUCAS:
THIS?
OOPS!
(FRIENDS SNICKER)
GO GET IT.
AS LONG AS WE'RE
TELLING SECRETS,
UM... THAT ASS
IS MY BROTHER.
DARCY:
THAT CREEP?
YEAH,
NOT EXACTLY PROUD OF IT.
BUT YOUR LAST NAME-
OH, I CHANGED IT.
UM, MY REAL NAME
IS ACTUALLY...
ANASTASIA VALIERI.
THAT'S A BIG ONE,
ANASTASIA.
SHOOT IT OUT, GIRL.
LET ME GUESS.
ESSAY DUE AND YOU'RE WAITING
FOR THE CAFFEINE TO KICK IN?
WAITING FOR YOU,
MOSTLY.
YOU GOT A MINUTE?
YEAH,
JUST CAME INTO FIFTEEN.
WHAT'S UP,
CAPTAIN LONGFACE?
NOTHING. I JUST...
I WANTED TO RUN SOMETHING
BY YOU.
TOTES.
EVERYTHING OKAY?
IT'S KIND OF SCARY
TO TALK ABOUT
AND I DON'T REALLY WANT
TO FREAK YOU OUT, BUT...
WELL, YOU'RE STARTING TO.
COME ON,
JUST SPILL IT ALREADY!
(SIGHS)
MARCO, I HAVE...
UH, FEELINGS FOR PAIGE.
(LAUGHS)
WHAT? THAT'S IT?!
OH MAN! COME ON.
YOU HAD ME SCARED
FOR A SECOND THERE.
YEAH.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I LOVE THAT GIRL.
SO, IF YOU HURT HER,
I'D TAKE DRASTIC MEASURES.
TOTALLY. I GET THAT.
MS. KWAN:
IMPROV SCENES CONTINUE!
PETER AND JANE AS HARLEQUIN
AND COLUMBINE.
LOOKS LIKE COMMEDIA DELL'ARTE
ARE NEXT.
CLASSMATES:
(CHEER AND APPLAUD)
PETER:
(CLEARS THROAT)
(READING SCRIPT)
FAIR MISS, I BESEECH YOU,
LOVE ME!
JANE:
BUT MY FATHER
WILL BE DISPLEASED!
LET ME WHISPER A SECRET.
OH, DAMN!
NO KEEPING THAT
JUNGLE BREATH A SECRET.
RIGHT, DARCE?
(CLASS LAUGHS)
KWAN:
LET'S GET BACK ON TRACK,
PLEASE!
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
DARCY:
PETER, WAIT UP.
I HAVE TO GET TO CLASS.
LATER.
WHO KNEW PETER
COULD BE SO POUTY?
YOU SO DON'T GET IT,
JANE.
WHY DO YOU HAVE TO BE
SUCH A GIRL?
(UNCLEAR PA ANNOUNCEMENT)
PAIGE:
HELLO? GUYS?
(SIGHS)
OH MAN, I'M HUNGRY.
GRIFFIN:
PAIGE?
HEY.
I HAVE A SURPRISE
FOR YOU.
YOU READY?
UH HUH...
(LAUGH OF DISBELIEF)
GRIFFIN:
SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
THIS IS GORGEOUS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU DID THIS.
HOW DID YOU DO THIS?
FAST.
LOOK,
ALLAN KEY CALLOUS.
(SYMPATHETIC)
OH.
SO DO YOU LIKE
YOUR ROOM?
SEE IF YOU CAN GUESS.
PAIGE, HOLD ON.
ARE YOU SURE?
OH GOD. UH...
YOU DON'T WANT THIS.
NO, I DO.
A LOT.
EVER SINCE THE FIRST
ROOMMATE INTERVIEW.
SO THEN WHY ALL THE TALKING
AND NOT THE KISSING?
JUST CHECKING.
YOU LEAVING?
SO SOON?
I WAS TRYING TO BE QUIET.
SO YOU COULD
SNEAK OUT?
SO I COULD LET YOU SLEEP.
MM. SO ORDER ANOTHER
WAKE-UP CALL?
CAN'T. I GOTTA MEET
WITH MY PROF.
MARCO:
YOU'RE GONNA BE LATE, EL!
DON'T YOU WANT TO GET
THE GOOD SEATS?
ELLIE:
IT'S LINGUISTICS CLASS, MARCO.
NOT A MOVIE.
MARCO:
HERE'S YOUR COFFEE MUG.
GOT YOUR BAG?
ELLIE:
I'M GOING! BYE!
(DOOR SHUTS)
ALL RIGHT,
I SHOULD JET TO CLASS
WHILE THE COAST IS CLEAR.
SEE YOU TONIGHT?
(DOOR SHUTS)
(FRONT DOOR SHUTS)
PAIGE:
WHAT'S WITH ALL THE PILLS?
IT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS,
HON.
(PILLS RATTLE)
BOTH:
(LAUGHING)
SPINNER:
HEY, FUNNY GIRL!
I WAS JUST TELLING JIMMY
ABOUT HOW YOU TOTALLY
BURNED PETER IN CLASS.
HILARIOUS.
TOO BAD DARCY'S
IN A SNIT ABOUT IT.
HOW COME?
I GUESS I WASN'T SUPPOSED
TO SAY ANYTHING
ABOUT HER HATING
HIS STANK BREATH.
BUT WHATEVER,
SHE'LL GET OVER IT, RIGHT?
SPINNER:
DARCY EDWARDS?
NO SHE WON'T.
WELL, MAYBE.
DID YOU APOLOGIZE AT LEAST?
WELL, I TOLD HER
SHE WAS MAD OVER NOTHING,
AND TO STOP BEING
SUCH A GIRL.
(LAUGHS) OOH.
SPIN, THIS IS WHY
I CAN'T DEAL WITH GIRLS!
THEY'RE JUST SO SENSITIVE,
YOU KNOW?
I DEFINITELY THINK YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE TO DO SOME DIGGING
TO GET OUT OF THIS ONE.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
MARCO:
I FEEL WEIRD
GOING THROUGH HIS STUFF.
LOOK, IT'S NOT LIKE
I WENT LOOKING FOR IT!
BUT I CAN'T UN-KNOW THIS NOW.
I TOLD HIM IF HE HURT YOU,
I'D KILL HIM.
PAIGE:
3TC? ABC?
MAYBE IT'S VITAMINS,
OR WEIGHT-LIFTING STUFF.
YEAH, AND HE PACKS THEM IN
LITTLE PRESCRIPTION BOTTLES
JUST TO BE QUIRKY?
(SIGHS) OH GOD,
WHAT IF HE'S SICK?
WHAT IF HE HAS GOT CANCER
OR SOMETHING?
I DON'T KNOW WHY
HE'D HIDE THAT.
(SIGHS)
(PILLS RATTLE)
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT THIS IS?
EFAVIRENZ. AZT.
WHERE HAVE I HEARD THAT
BEFORE?
OH MY GOD.
MARCO...
WHAT?
IT'S THE HIV COCKTAIL.
MARCO:
HE CAME TO MY WORK
TO ASK IF YOU TWO COULD...
BUT IF I HAD KNOWN THIS... WOW.
(DOOR CLOSES)
ELLIE:
'KAY, I GOT AN EMERGENCY TEXT
MINUTES BEFORE CLASS.
WHY?
GRIFFIN HAS HIV.
WE FOUND HIS DRUGS.
WHAT?!
ARE YOU GUYS SURE?
YES, ELLIE!
IS THAT EMERGENCY ENOUGH
FOR YOU?
MARCO:
PAIGE, CALM DOWN.
I CAN'T CALM DOWN.
HOW COULD HE NOT TELL ME?
WELL...
PAIGE:
WELL?
THERE IS NO "WELL",
MARCO.
UGH!
WE ALL DRANK
FROM THE SAME OJ CARTON.
ELLIE, YOU CAN'T-
ELLIE:
I KNOW, I KNOW.
THERE'S NO WAY
TO PASS IT LIKE THAT.
BUT STILL,
IT'S... DISTURBING.
(SIGHS)
WELL, SINCE I SLEPT
WITH HIM,
I THINK I CAN RELATE
TO YOUR CONCERNS.
IT JUST KINDA HAPPENED.
YOU USED PROTECTION
THOUGH, RIGHT?
OF COURSE!
BUT THERE'S NO GUARANTEES.
AND I SWORE I WOULD NEVER
BE OUT OF CONTROL
WITH A GUY AGAIN.
MARCO:
PAIGE, IF HE USED A CONDOM...
HE STILL TOOK A RISK,
MARCO!
HE TOOK A RISK WITH MY LIFE.
GRIFFIN:
PAIGE? GUYS?
EH, HAS ANYBODY SEEN MY WALLET?
WHEN WERE YOU
GONNA TELL ME?
YOU CAN'T RUN AWAY FROM THIS,
GRIFFIN!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU WENT THROUGH MY STUFF?
UH, I THINK YOURS
IS THE BIGGER FAUX PAS HERE!
I MEANT TO TELL YOU,
THE TIME JUST NEVER
SEEMED RIGHT.
WELL, IT DOESN'T MATTER!
BECAUSE NOW I HAVE TO SUFFER
YOUR STUPID CHOICES
AND LIFESTYLE.
LIFESTYLE?
YOU JUST ASSUME
IT'S MY LIFESTYLE?
WELL, ISN'T IT?
GO TO HELL.
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
(HUM OF CHATTER)
WOULD IT MAKE IT EASIER
IF YOU PRETEND MY FACE
IS ON THE TARGET?
KIND OF, YES.
SO UNLESS YOU WANT TO BE
THE TARGET, MOVE.
DARCY, LISTEN,
PLEASE?
I'M SORRY I BUSTED YOU
ON PETER'S HALITOSIS.
OKAY. BUT I GOT
SUPER STRONG MINTS, SO.
(CHUCKLES)
ARE YOU FOR REAL?
I DIDN'T TELL YOU ABOUT THIS
SO YOU COULD FIX IT.
THERE'S A PROBLEM,
I'M OFFERING YOU
A SOLUTION.
I DIDN'T WANT A SOLUTION,
I WANTED YOU TO LISTEN.
WHAT IF I TOLD
ALL THESE EAVESDROPPERS
ABOUT YOUR EVIL
BROTHER?
WOULD THAT HELP
TO FIX THINGS?
MAKE YOU FEEL BETTER?
DARCY, PLEASE-
JANE, RELAX.
I'M NOT GOING TO.
NO FRIEND - GIRL OR GUY -
WOULD DO THAT.
WHICH IS WHAT MAKES YOU AND I
VERY DIFFERENT.
HOW LONG AGO DO YOU THINK
YOU MAY HAVE BEEN EXPOSED?
LAST NIGHT.
WE USED A CONDOM,
BUT I STILL WANNA CHECK.
WHAT?
HIV ANTIBODIES TAKE UP
TO 6 MONTHS TO SHOW UP.
WE'LL KNOW MORE THEN.
I WON'T KNOW
FOR SIX MONTHS?
NURSE:
BUT THE GOOD NEWS IS
YOU TOOK PRECAUTIONS.
(COMPUTER KEYS CLACK)
(MONITOR BEEPS)
PAIGE:
(SCOFFS LIGHTLY)
"BUT YOUR PARTNER MIGHT ALSO BE
A WONDERFUL SOURCE OF SUPPORT."
(SPOON CLINKS)
GRIFFIN:
YOU'RE NOT GONNA TALK TO ME?
MAYBE IN SIX MONTHS.
GRIFFIN:
THAT'S GREAT.
YOU'RE NOT EVEN GONNA ASK
HOW I GOT IT?
WHAT, TOO MANY GIRLS,
TOO FEW CONDOMS?
OOPS!
I WAS BORN HIV POSITIVE.
WHAT IS THIS?
GRIFFIN:
MY MOTHER'S OBITUARY.
SHE WAS A JUNKIE.
TRIED TO STOP
AFTER I WAS BORN,
BUT COULDN'T.
I NEVER EVEN MET HER.
I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T KNOW.
YOU DIDN'T ASK.
WELL, EVEN IF I HAD,
WOULD YOU HAVE HAD
THE GUTS TO TELL ME?
I'VE BEEN IN A HEALTHY
SEXUALITY PROGRAM FOR YEARS.
THEY TEACH YOU HOW TO HAVE
THESE CONVERSATIONS,
BUT IT DOESN'T MAKE IT
ANY EASIER.
I AM NOT WRONG TO BE SCARED.
I KNOW.
NEITHER AM I.
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
DARCY:
HEY.
'KAY. GO.
FOR THE RECORD,
WHAT YOU DID WAS NOT COOL.
I KNOW.
DARCY, I'M AN IDIOT.
BUT THANKS.
KISSING PETER DID GET
A LITTLE BIT MORE FUN.
HMM. LOOK, UM...
CAN WE MAKE ME LIKE,
A FRIENDSHIP TRAINEE?
'CAUSE CLEARLY
I'M AN IGNORAMUS.
WILL YOU HELP ME?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT IF I SAY SOMETHING'S
SACRED
AND YOU SAY THAT'S STUPID?
THEN WHAT?
MMM...
ARROW TO THE HEAD?
BOTH:
(LAUGH)
LOOK, I...
I GUESS I WANT A FRIEND
MORE THAN I THOUGHT.
KIND OF A LOT MORE.
OKAY, YOU NUTBAR,
WE CAN TRY.
THAT'S RAD.
OKAY, LESSON ONE?
FRIENDS CAN HUG.
PAIGE:
MARCO SAYS YOU'RE LEAVING.
YOU SHOULD'VE TOLD ME.
(SIGHS)
THINGS WERE GOING SO WELL.
I DIDN'T WANNA RUIN IT.
YOU'D BE SURPRISED
HOW QUICKLY THE TRUTH
MAKES PEOPLE RUN AWAY.
YEAH, WELL, SO DO LIES.
EVERYTHING'S ALWAYS
SO COMPLICATED WITH ME.
THE HIV MAKES EVERYTHING
COMPLICATED.
YOU WEREN'T HONEST
WITH ME.
YOU DIDN'T LET ME CHOOSE.
BUT I'M NOT MAD
YOU HAVE HIV.
YOU KNOW, SOME DAYS,
I FORGET THAT I HAVE IT.
I'VE NEVER EVEN BEEN SICK.
THE DRUGS WORK.
WE HAVE A LOT
TO TALK ABOUT.
WHICH'LL BE HARDER
IF YOU GO.
DON'T MOVE OUT,
PLEASE.
IT'S NOT GONNA BE WEIRD
IF I STAY?
(SIGHS)
LET'S BE HONEST,
IT'S GONNA BE WEIRD
EITHER WAY.
BUT I WANT TO TRY
TO WORK THROUGH THIS.
YOU ARE AMAZING.
THIS IS NOTHING.
WAIT 'TIL
YOU GET TO KNOW ME.
(CHUCKLES)