(BIRDS CHIRP)
WHAT TIME IS IT?
PETER?
UGH!
PETER.
PETER, WHAT HAPPENED
LAST NIGHT?
(GROANS)
I THINK I BECAME
FLUENT IN KEG DRAFT.
BUT DID WE...?
OH MY GOSH, WE DID.
DID WHAT?
ARE YOU SURE?
YES, I'M SURE
AND YOU SHOULD BE TOO,
YOU WERE KINDA THERE.
MY BODY WAS, I GUESS,
BUT NOT MY MIND.
DARCY,
I WAS TOTALLY WASTED.
(SARCASTIC GASP)
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE.
I'VE GOT THE THRASHING HEADACHE
TO PROVE IT.
(PAINFUL INHALE)
WE HAD SEX?
WHEN DOES THE NEXT
BUS LEAVE?
IF I DON'T GET HOME
BEFORE MY PARENTS,
I'M DEAD.
(EXHALES)
DARCY, UH...
I KNOW THIS ISN'T
HOW YOU PICTURED IT.
LOOK,
LET ME GET DRESSED.
JUST GET OUT.
PETER:
NO, I MEAN,
(EXHALES)
I WISH IT HAD BEEN
MORE MEMORABLE.
I KNOW HOW MUCH
IT MEANT TO YOU,
LOSING YOUR VIRGINITY,
YOU KNOW.
NO,
YOU DON'T, PETER,
NOT EVEN A LITTLE.
NOW PLEASE,
LET ME GET DRESSED!
♪♪♪
(EXHALES)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
♪♪♪
AND 5, 6, 7, 8.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5
AND 6, 7, 8.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5...
AH, HOLLY,
TRY TO KEEP UP.
(GASPS)
IT'S HOLLY J
AND I'M TRYING.
IT'S JUST HARD
TO MEMORIZE MEDIOCRITY.
HMPH, PLEASE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
PRACTICE IS OVER.
EVERYONE HIT
THE SHOWERS.
WAY TO END PRACTICE
ON A HIGH NOTE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHAT?
OH, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU KNOW,
AT MOUNT HURON?
AFTER YOU GOT ALL JUDGY
ON ME AND I LEFT?
MANNY,
I AM REALLY SORRY
ABOUT THAT.
WHAT WAS IT AGAIN?
"NO VALUES,
NO SELF-RESPECT".
UH OH.
'RENTS CAUGHT YOU
SNEAKING BACK IN,
DIDN'T THEY?
NO, THEY DIDN'T.
IT'S NOT THAT,
IT'S PETER.
I HAD A FEELING WHEN YOU GUYS
WEREN'T ON THE BUS HOME.
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
(EXHALES)
EVERYTHING...
AND I BARELY
REMEMBER IT.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU SAID YES?
YOU'RE SURE PETER DIDN'T
TAKE ADVANTAGE?
MANNY,
DON'T GO THERE.
I GOT DRUNK
AND I MADE A MISTAKE.
END OF STORY.
YOU'RE NOT THE FIRST ONE,
HONEY.
WHAT IF PEOPLE
FIND OUT?
WHAT IF THEY TALK?
AND SAY I'M LIKE THIS
BIG NYMPHO.
I SWEAR I'D DIE.
YOU'LL BE FINE.
SO LONG AS
YOU MAKE SURE
PETER HASN'T
TOLD ANYONE.
(INHALES)
BUT... I KNOW.
AND EVERY GIRL
IS ENTITLED TO A SECRET.
OR TWO. OR THREE.
(THEY CHUCKLE)
IT'LL BE FINE.
♪♪♪
MARCO:
MORNING.
SLEEP OKAY?
YEAH, YOU WEREN'T LYING
ABOUT THAT COUCH.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO LIE,
ALEX,
I KNOW YOU AND PAIGE
ARE PLAYING HOUSE
IN DYLAN'S ROOM.
IT'S NOT LIKE
HE'S GONNA CARE,
HE'S IN SWITZERLAND.
(MUG CLANKS ON TABLE)
KEYS TO THE STORE?
THEY'RE ON THE FRIDGE.
PAIGE:
OH, THANKS, HON.
WITHOUT YOU,
I'D BE SAD,
LONELY AND
WITH MANY CATS.
MARCO:
YOU KNOW WE HAVE
A NO PETS RULE.
PAIGE:
WELL, ONCE I CLOSE DOWN
SQUATCH DESIGNS FOR GOOD?
I'LL LEAVE
THE RATS BEHIND.
BYE GUYS.
MARCO:
BYE.
HEY, EL, DON'T FORGET
STUDY GROUP AT FOUR.
I MADE NOTES.
THANKS!
YOU'RE TOO PERFECT.
TELL THAT TO DYLAN.
WHAT'S WITH DYLAN?
IT'S OUR ANNIVERSARY
AND...
YOU'D THINK I WOULD HAVE
HEARD FROM HIM BY NOW,
BUT NADA.
MARCO,
THE BOY IS CHECKED OUT!
I GOTTA GET TO CLASS.
SORRY!
I'M SURE
HE'LL CALL.
(CHUCKLES)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
(STUDENT CHATTER)
DEREK:
C'MON, YOU CAN TELL US!
DANNY:
TOTALLY!
WE'RE PRACTICALLY FRIENDS.
PETER:
ALL RIGHT,
BUT YOU GUYS
CAN'T TELL ANYONE.
ALL RIGHT,
I THINK DARCY
AND I HAD SEX.
WHAT?!
NO WAY!
SHHHH!
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
"THINK YOU HAD SEX"?
WELL, YOU KNOW,
WHEN YOU THINK YOU HAD SEX,
BUT YOU'RE NOT TOTALLY SURE
IF YOU DID OR NOT?
UH, NO.
C'MON DUDE,
YOU'RE ASKING US?
SO WHAT IS IT?
DID YOU DO IT OR NOT?
(GLEEFUL SIGH)
I KNEW IT, HE DID.
SCORE!
SHHH! IT'S A SECRET.
YOU, GUYS,
CAN KEEP A SECRET, RIGHT?
TOTALLY, WE'RE NOT LIKE
IMMATURE OR WHATEVER.
YEAH!
SO DID YOU SEE
HER BARE-NAKED?
KWAN:
SEATS, EVERYONE!
TODAY WE BEGIN STUDYING
A NEW NOVEL.
THE MID-19TH CENTURY CLASSIC,
"THE SCARLET LETTER".
WRITTEN BY
NATHANIAL HAWTHORNE.
THE BOOK IS A STORY OF A WOMAN
WHO MUST PERMANENTLY BARE
THE MARK OF HER SINS,
IN THE FACE OF PUBLIC SCRUTINY.
♪♪♪
THANKS.
(KEYBOARD KEYS CLICK)
HELLO, NASH.
ERIC:
MARCO.
HEY, HOW ARE YA?
WHAT BRINGS YOU
TO THE CORE?
MARCO:
AH, JUST GETTING
A TEXT BOOK FROM EL.
HOW GOES THE JOURNALISM?
ERIC:
IT'S GOING REAL WELL.
MAKES NO SENSE.
WHAT YOUR
JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE REVIEW?
(SARCASTIC TONE)
HA HA.
IT'S MARCO.
HE KEEPS HOLDING
ON TO A GUY
WHO TREATS HIM
LIKE CRAP.
WELL, HE'S SURE GOT
A FAN IN ERIC.
REALLY?
WE SHOULD SET THEM UP.
WE SHOULD
MIND OUR OWN BUSINESS
AND BY WE I MEAN YOU.
LOOK, YOU KNOW MARCO;
UNLESS SOMEONE INTERVENES
HE'S GONNA LET DYLAN
KICK HIM AROUND FOREVER.
NO DOUBT.
MARCO'S LOYAL TO A FAULT
WHICH IS WHY
HE'S NEVER GONNA LET YOU
SET HIM UP WITH ERIC.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
JUST MEANS WE'RE GONNA
HAVE TO BE SNEAKY.
STILL WITH
THE "WE", HUH?
(BIRDS CHIRP,
STUDENTS CHATTER)
HEY,
STILL MAD AT ME?
I WASN'T MAD AT YOU.
I WAS FREAKED OUT.
YEAH, I GET IT.
I DO.
I WAS FREAKED TOO.
I'M JUST SURPRISED,
I GUESS.
YEAH, I KNOW.
WASN'T HOW YOU THOUGHT
IT WOULD HAPPEN.
(SIGHS)
SO WE AGREE
THAT IT WAS A MISTAKE?
I MEAN,
IT CAN'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
DARCY,
I DON'T WANT TO DO ANYTHING
TO MAKE YOU UNHAPPY.
EVER!
SO WHATEVER YOU
SAY GOES.
AND YOU DIDN'T
TELL ANYONE ABOUT...
ABOUT WHAT WE DID,
DID YOU?
NO. OF COURSE NOT.
GOOD BECAUSE IF ANYONE
FOUND OUT?
PETER:
DON'T WORRY
NO ONE WILL.
I'M JUST GLAD
WE'RE COOL.
CAUSE IF YOU'RE
MAD AT ME?
MAN,
I COULDN'T TAKE IT.
(GIGGLE)
(EXHALES)
(DOOR SHUTS)
SO DYLAN JUST SENT
THE LAMEST TEXT.
IT SAYS,
"HAP ANNIV,
M LOVE" L U V, "D".
COULD THAT BE
ANYMORE ABBREVIATED?
WHY DOES IT SMELL
LIKE PIZZA?
BECAUSE WE HAVE GUESTS.
JESSE:
HEY, MARCO.
UH, ERIC AND I WERE UH,
JUST...
DOING SOME WORK.
HEY, MARCO.
(INHALES)
JESSE, I WANTED
TO SHOW YOU THAT... THING,
REMEMBER?
OH, RIGHT.
THE THING.
I LOVE THINGS.
WELL, THAT WASN'T AWKWARD.
(EXHALES)
ERIC:
HEY, I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T KNOW
THEY WERE GOING TO MAKE IT
SUCH AN OBVIOUS SET-UP.
BUT YOU DID KNOW
IT WAS A SET-UP?
WELL, I, I GUESS
I KINDA THOUGHT
THERE WAS SOMETHING
BETWEEN US.
MARCO:
YEAH, THERE IS SOMETHING
BETWEEN US.
HIS NAME'S DYLAN.
HE'S MY BOYFRIEND!
OKAY.
I WONDER IF AH, ELLIE
CAN SHOW ME THAT,
THAT "THING".
ENJOY THE PIZZA.
♪♪♪
(EXHALES)
PETER:
I TOOK THAT WHEN YOU WERE
WITH THE SPIRIT SQUAD.
(DOOR CHIMES OPEN)
EH, MIND IF WE INTERRUPT
THIS LOVE-FEST?
WE'VE GOT ALL THE TIME
IN THE WORLD FOR FRIENDS.
WE CAN ALL BE FRIENDS,
RIGHT?
NO RECENT REASONS WHY NOT;
PEOPLE CHANGE, RIGHT?
THEY SURE DO.
GET A ROOM YOU TWO.
OH, WAIT A SEC,
YOU ALREADY DID THAT,
YOU SLY DOGS.
YOU TOLD HER?
NO. I DIDN'T.
JANE:
WELL, THOSE TWO
FUZZ-HEAD TWINS
WON'T SHUT UP
ABOUT IT.
(HUFFS)
(DOOR CHIMES JINGLE)
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
THANKS A LOT.
DARCY, I'M SORRY.
OH, GREAT,
YOU'RE SORRY.
THAT'S REALLY
GOING TO HELP ME
GET MY REPUTATION BACK.
I ONLY TOLD
DANNY AND DEREK
'CAUSE I'M SO FREAKING
CONFUSED.
ABOUT WHAT?
ABOUT THE FACT
THAT YOU SAY WE HAD SEX,
BUT I DON'T THINK WE DID.
I REALLY DON'T.
I KNOW WHAT HAPPENED
THAT NIGHT.
I KNOW
THAT WE HAD SEX.
PETER:
LISTEN,
THE LAST TIME I SAW YOU
YOU WERE PASSED OUT
AND THERE WERE A LOT
OF PEOPLE AROUND.
PEOPLE WE DON'T KNOW.
IT WAS OUT OF CONTROL.
STOP IT, PETER.
I REALLY HOPE
IT'S NOT TRUE,
BUT WHAT IF SOMETHING
HAPPENED?
IT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
I'M NOT THE SORT OF PERSON
THAT HAPPENS TO.
YOU'RE SURE
YOU HAD SEX,
BUT I'M SURE
IT WASN'T WITH ME.
(POLICE SIREN SOUNDS)
DON'T TALK TO ME.
WHAT?
YOU HEARD WHAT I SAID.
DON'T TALK TO ME!
EVER!
(CAR HONKS)
(CAR WHIRS BY)
♪♪♪
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
(NERVOUS EXHALE)
DEREK:
DARCY, YOU LITTLE THIEF!
YEAH, WE HEARD YOU STOLE
PETE'S VIRGINITY,
MADE HIM A MAN.
YOU LITTLE MINX!
EMMA:
OUT OF THE WAY, DORKS.
(STUDENT CHATTER)
DON'T LET THEM BUG YOU,
WE'VE BOTH BEEN
HERE BEFORE.
IT'S LIKE BEING A SHEEP
AND THE HALLS ARE FILLED
WITH WOLVES WITH ACNE.
GUESS ALL THOSE YEARS
IN FRIENDSHIP CLUB
DIDN'T MEAN MUCH.
HEY, KIM.
KIM:
I SEE YOU'RE STILL WEARING
YOUR ABSTINENCE RING.
DON'T YOU THINK
YOU SHOULD TAKE OFF?
THIS ISN'T THE TIME,
KIM.
NO, IT'S FINE.
SATISFIED?
VIRGINITY IS GOD'S
MOST PRECIOUS GIFT,
HMPH, AND YOU JUST
GAVE IT AWAY.
♪♪♪
ELLIE:
YUM, FROZEN TOASTER TARTS.
EH, YOU'RE STILL
IN THE DOG-HOUSE, NASH.
I WAS ONLY TRYING
TO HELP YOU.
AND BY THE WAY,
IT WAS REAL NICE OF YOU
TO CRUSH POOR ERIC'S
FEELINGS.
I KNOW,
I GOT FREAKED.
MAYBE I'M ATTRACTED
TO ERIC.
(CHUCKLES)
MAYBE?
OKAY, HE'S HOT!
AND IN ANOTHER TIME
AND PLACE
IT MIGHT HAVE WORKED,
BUT DYLAN IS-
IS IN EUROPE,
WHICH IS EUROPEAN
FOR...
FAR FAR AWAY!
HE'S LIVING HIS LIFE,
MARCO,
BUT WHAT ARE YOU
DOING?
FINE!
I'LL TAKE ERIC OUT
FOR ONE CUP OF COFFEE.
JUST PROMISE
TO GET OFF MY BACK.
PROMISE.
(TOASTER POPS)
NO,
THEY HAVE TO BE HOT.
(SMIRKS) (GROANS)
PETER:
DARCY, CAN I TALK TO YOU?
I THINK YOU'VE DONE
ENOUGH TALKING.
YOU'VE MADE MY LIFE
HERE A HELL.
MANNY:
SHOO!
GO ON!
GET!
PETER:
I'M GONNA MURDER DANNY
AND DEREK.
HEY, UM,
YOU GUYS HEAR
ABOUT THAT
MOUNT HURON THING?
THERE'S A POLICE WARNING
ABOUT SOME "ROOFIE RAPIST"
ON THE LOOSE.
SOMEONE'S GOING AROUND
AND SPIKING RANDOM...
(MUFFLED SPEAKING)
DARCY:
WE CAN GO DO IT
IF YOU WANT?
JUST NOW IN THE BEDROOM,
PETER WAS TRYING TO MAKE
ME DO THINGS.
PETER:
HOW WASTED ARE YOU?
DARCY:
I ONLY HAS ONE DRINK,
JACK-ASS.
JANE:
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
SOMEONE'S GOING AROUND
AND SPIKING RANDOM GIRLS'
DRINKS AT PARTIES.
CRAZY-SCARY.
TOTALLY.
SO LUCKY IT WASN'T
ONE OF US.
YEAH.
WHAT?
YOU SAID YOU WERE
OUT-OF-YOUR-MIND DRUNK.
I HAD ONE DRINK.
IT JUST HIT ME.
ONE DRINK DOESN'T HIT YOU
LIKE THAT, ROOFIES DO,
AND THEY ALSO
MAKE YOU FORGET.
I REMEMBER ME AND PETER
HAVING SEX.
I REMEMBER THE WHOLE THING,
IT WAS BEAUTIFUL.
THAT'S NOT WHAT
YOU SAID YESTERDAY.
WELL,
MY MEMORY CAME BACK.
DOCTOR ROTMAN:
SO, WE'LL SEND THIS OFF
TO THE LAB
ALONG WITH YOUR URINE.
WE'LL TEST
FOR THE USUAL STIS,
JUST BEND YOUR ARM UP,
AND WE'LL HAVE RESULTS
IN A FEW HOURS.
AND THERE'S
ABSOLUTELY NO WAY
YOU CAN TELL
IF I'M PREGNANT?
NOT THIS SOON.
I'M SORRY.
YOU AH, SAID YOU WERE
VERY INTOXICATED
WHEN YOU HAD SEX.
ARE YOU SURE
IT WAS CONSENSUAL?
(STAMMERS)
ABSOLUTELY.
MY BOYFRIEND RAMON'S
CONDOM BROKE.
OOPS.
MISS AH... EDWARDS?
I KNOW AN EXCELLENT PERSON
YOU CAN TALK TO, IF...
(HUFFS)
NO NEED, DOCTOR.
I'VE GOT MY BOYFRIEND,
MY FAMILY, MY FRIENDS,
ALL SORTS OF SUPPORT.
(NERVOUS INHALE)
OKAY.
ERIC:
(LAUGHS)
THAT'S WHY I LOVE
THE SUMMER CAMP.
I THINK ALL KIDS SHOULD HAVE
ACCESS TO THE OUTDOORS.
YEAH, AND ALL THE MOSQUITO
BITES THEY CAN SCRATCH.
DON'T KNOCK IT,
CITY-BOY.
MAYBE SOMEDAY
I'LL TAKE YOU TO THE WOODS.
LOOK, ERIC, UM...
YOU'RE GREAT
AND I'M TRYING,
BUT I HAVE A BOYFRIEND.
(EXHALES)
LOOK, YOU HAVE A CRUTCH.
WHAT ARE YOU AFRAID OF,
MARCO?
NOTHING!
IT'S LONG DISTANCE
AND IT'S DIFFICULT,
BUT I'M COMMITTED.
LOOK, YOU'RE HIDING
UNDER A SAFETY BLANKET.
THERE'S A WHOLE WORLD
OUT THERE
AND DYLAN'S NOT THE ONLY
GAY MAN IN IT.
WELL, THANKS
FOR THE ADVICE.
YOU SURE SEEM
TO KNOW
A LOT ABOUT MY
LOVE LIFE.
(CHUCKLES)
I KNOW YOU DESERVE SOMEONE
WHO'S GOOD TO YOU.
WELL, I HAPPEN
TO HAVE THAT GUY.
MANNY:
HEY, GOT YOUR IM.
WHATS' GOING ON?
I USED TO PLAY HERE
WHEN I WAS LITTLE.
AND I USED TO DREAM
ABOUT MY PRINCE
WHO'D SWEEP ME OFF
MY FEET
AND OUR PERFECT WEDDING.
(INHALES AND EXHALES)
I JUST FOUND OUT...
I HAVE CHLAMYDIA.
(SNIFFS)
GOT ANY ANTIBIOTICS?
(SARCASTIC LAUGHS)
IS PETER
GETTING TESTED?
(DEEP BREATHS)
(SIGHS)
I REMEMBER FEELING
SOMEONE ON ME...
AND HE SMELT BAD.
NOT LIKE PETER.
I JUST WANTED
IT TO BE HIM SO BAD.
OH, MY GOD,
DARCE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO,
MANNY.
I'M TERRIFIED.
EVERY WHERE I LOOK,
I THINK, IS THAT HIM?
IS THAT THE GUY WHO-
DARCY, WE GOTTA TALK
TO SOMEONE,
YOU GOTTA TELL.
YOU SAID, MANNY,
YOU SAID EVERY GIRL
IS ENTITLED TO A SECRET.
I DIDN'T MEAN
GETTING RAPED.
BABE, YOU GOTTA TO TALK
TO YOUR PARENTS, OKAY?
AND DARCE,
YOU'RE STILL GONNA
HAVE YOUR PRINCE
AND YOUR
PERFECT WEDDING.
YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE IT ALL.
OKAY?
IT'S OKAY.
MRS. EDWARDS:
DADDY AND I ARE OFF
TO CHOIR PRACTICE.
HEY,
EVERYTHING OKAY, HONEY?
AWE, DON'T TELL ME THAT
COLD OF YOURS
IS COMING BACK.
I'M STILL FEELING
A LITTLE UNDER THE WEATHER.
HAVE FUN AT CHOIR.
(SCHOOL DOORS CLANK)
(CAR WHIRS AWAY)
MANNY:
OKAY, BRING IT DOWN.
CHEERLEADERS:
UGH!
MANNY:
HOLLY J, CAN YOU TAKE OVER
FOR A SEC?
(SIGHS)
OKAY, BACK IN FORMATION.
(DOOR CLICKS OPEN)
(WATER RUNNING)
DARCY?
DARCY!
(SHOWER KNOBS SQUEAK)
OH MY GOD!
HOLD THIS.
PRESS.
I'M CALLING 911.
(BLOOD GURGLES INTO DRAIN)
(DEEP INHALE)
(EXHALES)
(INTERCOM BEEPS)
PA:
(PAGING DOCTOR)
DO THEY KNOW?
I DON'T THINK DARCY
TOLD THEM YET.
SOMEONE'S GOT TO.
NOT US, NOT NOW.
WHY NOT?
I GOT THIS PAMPHLET...
OH GREAT,
A PAMPHLET.
IT SAYS RAPE VICTIMS
NEED TO HEAL AT THEIR OWN PACE.
IT'S IMPORTANT.
THE CUT WASN'T DEEP,
SHE'LL BE OKAY.
BUT CAN YOU TELL ME
WHY MY PERFECT DAUGHTER
WOULD'VE DONE THIS?
MRS. EDWARDS...
I REALLY DON'T KNOW.
(MONITOR BEEPS)
(INHALES)
PAIGE:
KEEPING SUMATRA IN BUSINESS,
HON?
I HAVEN'T SLEPT MUCH;
BEEN WAITING FOR DYLAN
TO CALL FOR TWO DAYS.
OH, WELL, LUCKILY
I'VE GOT JUST THE THING
TO CHEER YOU UP.
SQUATCH DESIGN TEES
IN EVERY SINGLE COLOUR.
SORRY ABOUT THE STORE
GOING UNDER.
NO BIG.
WE DID EVERYTHING WE COULD.
C'EST LA VIE, QUE CERA
AND ALL THAT.
IT'S NO USE CRYING.
HMPH...
I GUESS WHEN
IT'S TIME IT'S TIME.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
DYLAN...
HEY, LISTEN, UM,
WE NEED TO TALK.
YEAH.
IT'S THE TALK...
DARCY:
I JUST DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHY I'M HERE.
SAUVE:
YOU'RE HERE BECAUSE
YOU HURT YOURSELF
ON SCHOOL PROPERTY.
DARCY, I KNOW THERE'S A REASON
FOR WHAT YOU DID
AND IF YOU EVER DO
WANT TO TALK
I COULD BE
A PRETTY GOOD LISTENER.
BUT IN THE MEAN TIME,
WE'RE GONNA CREATE
A SAFETY PLAN
AND MAKE SURE YOU HAVE
THE BEST SUPPORT SYSTEM AROUND.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
AND IF THERE'S
ANYTHING ELSE YOU NEED
YOU KNOW WHERE
TO REACH ME.
(STUDENT CHATTER)
HEY, HOW'D IT GO?
I COULDN'T TELL HER.
NOT YET.
WE GOT YOU SOMETHING.
AN ABSTINENCE RING.
MANNY:
WHAT HAPPENED?
IT DIDN'T COUNT,
DARCY.
♪♪♪