(ELATED BREATH)
...TO BE CONFIRMED.
ABSOLUTELY.
THANK YOU!
ERIC, PULL THE TUITION HIKE
STORY!
YOU SURE? THAT'S YOUR
GIRLFRIEND'S STORY...
I DON'T CARE
IF IT'S ELLIE'S STORY.
IT NEEDS TO BE PULLED.
WHAT NEEDS TO BE PULLED?
SORRY, FROSH, YOUR STORY
GOT THE KIBOSH.
SOMETHING CAME UP WITH OUR
"SUBTEXT" LECTURE SERIES.
WHAT-WHAT-WHAT? HUH?
WHY? THE WHAT?
ERIC:
LOOK, EVERY YEAR THE CORE HOSTS
A SPEAKER
TO INSPIRE US ON "THE NEWS
THAT'S NOT BEING COVERED"
TYPE STUFF.
UH, THE PRESS COMES,
EDITOR HOSTS A Q & A.
IT'S KIND OF A BIG DEAL.
AND I JUST GOT OFF THE PHONE
WITH BILL NYE.
YOU YANKED MY FRONT-PAGE STORY
FOR THE SCEANCE GUY?
YEP. AND HE'S CONFIRMED
FOR THE LECTURE.
I SLAVED OVER THAT REPORT!
YOU PROMISED ME THE LEAD!
I KNEW THAT WAS
A BAD IDEA...
I HEARD THAT.
OKAY, WHO HERE THINKS
JESSE'S RIGHT
ON PULLING MY STORY?
GIRL:
SORRY.
RATHER NOT GET INVOLVED
IN ANY DOMESTIC DISPUTES.
ELLIE:
GUYS, THIS ISN'T ABOUT ME
AND HIM.
THIS IS A PROFESSIONAL MATTER.
SO BE PROFESSIONAL,
OKAY.
I NEED YOU
TO TAKE THIS HIT.
FOR ME. YOUR BOSS.
NOW COME ON.
(SOFT EXHALE)
FINE.
ALL RIGHT. GOOD.
AH, YOU'RE ON HOROSCOPES.
♪♪♪
JESSE:
KIM. IS THAT WITH A "Y"
OR AN "I"?
KYM:
"Y" ACTUALLY.
JESSE:
COOL. IT'S SO UNIQUE.
HM. WELL, I'LL SEND YOU
OVER THOSE QUOTES,
KYM WITH A "Y".
THANKS,
JESSE WITH AND "E".
(SMIRKS)
(MIMICKING KYM)
"THANKS, JESSE WITH AN "E"."
YOU HAVE TWO SETTINGS:
OFF AND FLIRT.
SHE WAS THE ONE TRYING TO FLIRT
HER WAY INTO DISCOUNT AD RATES.
COULD HAVE FOOLED ME.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU HAD A THING
FOR OLDER WOMEN.
I DON'T.
I HAVE A THING FOR WOMEN.
YOU KNOW I LIKE MY RED HEADS
WITH BLUE EYES.
I HAVE GREEN EYES!
EVERYTHING OKAY?
NO. I WANT PEOPLE AROUND HERE
TO TAKE ME SERIOUSLY -
AS A JOURNALIST
AND NOT YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
WHAT?
YOU CAN'T BE BOTH?
NINE-ONE-ONE!
BILL NYE JUST BAILED
ON THE LECTURE.
WHAT?
OH, THIS IS BAD!
YEAH. AND WE HAVE
NO LEAD STORY.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
RUN ELLIE'S PIECE!
TUITION HIKES IT IS.
THERE YOU GO, FROSH.
THANK YOU.
BUT WHAT ABOUT THE LECTURE?
CAN I HELP?
YEAH, IF YOU HAPPEN TO KNOW
SOMEONE FAMOUS.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
HEY.
YOUR LOCKER PARTNER AROUND?
YOUR BFF, HOLLY J?
SHE'S NOT HERE.
HEY, GREAT JEANS.
THESE?
ANYA:
YEAH.
THANKS.
SCOOTCH, MAMMA MIA.
WAS ANYA BOTHERING YOU?
NO. SHE WAS JUST WAITING
FOR HER BOSS TO ARRIVE.
WHO, LITTLE OLD ME?
I'M FLATTERED.
LOVE THE JEANS, BY THE WAY.
ACTUALLY, YEAH.
I WAS JUST COMMENTING ON THEM.
I THOUGHT
THEY LOOKED REALLY-
YEAH, THEY REALLY HIGHLIGHT
YOUR CELLULITE.
(SNICKERS)
HOLLY J:
ANYA'S TOO BUSY NERDING OUT
TO NOTICE.
VERY FUNNY. TRULY.
SEE, ANYA GIVES MUCH BETTER
COMPLIMENTS THAN YOU DO.
THEY MIGHT BE A BIT TIGHT.
ANYA, DON'T LISTEN TO HER.
ANYA, WE'RE GOING.
LET'S GO.
ELLIE:
CAITLIN.
ELLIE NASH?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I HEARD YOU MIGHT BE IN TOWN
AND I THOUGHT I'D DROP BY.
AND YOU JUST HAPPEN TO KNOW
THAT I'D BE RIGHT HERE
RIGHT NOW?
A LITTLE INVESTIGATIVE
JOURNALISM PERHAPS?
YOU TAUGHT ME
EVERYTHING I KNOW.
JESSE:
A CAFFEINATED TOAST.
TO CAITLIN RYAN.
JOURNALISTIC ROYALTY AMONG US.
AND TO ELLIE, FOR HAVING
THE CHUTZPAH
OF A GREAT JOURNALIST.
JESSE:
HOW THE HECK DID YOU PULL THIS
OFF, HUH?
WITH ONE OF THE MOST INFLUENTIAL
ENVIRONMENTALISTS AROUND?
WELL, CAITLIN WAS MY ADVISOR
BACK AT DEGRASSI.
I LOVE TO SUPPORT
MY ALMA MATER.
ELLIE WAS SO YOUNG,
BUT SO DETERMINED!
AND SHE JUST SOAKED EVERYTHING
UP LIKE A SPONGE!
SOUNDS LIKE OUR FROSH.
AND WHEN I HEARD SHE'D BE
IN TOWN FOR THE PREMIERE
OF "STORM OF CONTROVERSY"-
CAITLIN:
SHE CONVINCED ME
TO SCREEN THE DOC
FOR YOUR LECTURE SERIES.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M GONNA
GET TO INTERVIEW
"THE" CAITLIN RYAN.
OH, ACTUALLY UM...
CAITLIN THOUGHT IT'D BE GREAT
IF I DID THE Q&A.
MENTEE-MENTOR?
I THINK WITH OUR HISTORY
TOGETHER IT WOULD BE FANTASTIC.
AH, I GUESS I CAN'T ARGUE
WITH THAT, CAN I?
MR. BINCE:
YOU MAY BE ASKING YOURSELF
"MR. BINCE, WHAT KIND OF CRAZY
GAME ARE YOU TRYING TO PLAY?"
DEREK?
THERE'S SOMETHING
ON YOUR FACE.
DEREK:
WHAT IS IT?
UGLINESS.
(SNICKERS)
MR. BINCE:
ANYA?
MAYBE YOU COULD CONTINUE
READING FOR US?
"AT WHICH POINT
IS THE TENNIS BALL
PULLED TOWARDS THE BLOWING...
UM, PULLED INTO THE BLOWING
BALL?
COME ON, ANYA.
CLAP IT OUT.
YOU'VE ONLY
READ THE CHAPTER TEN TIMES.
HEY, JUST LET
HER FINISH, OKAY?
WITH HER DYSLEXIA?
WE'LL BE HERE
UNTIL LABOUR DAY.
MR. BINCE:
ENOUGH.
THE TENNIS BALL GETS PULLED
INTO BOWLING BALL'S GRAVITY.
YOUR LAB WILL SHOW THE RESULTS
OF THIS EXPERIMENT.
PARTNER UP.
HEY, ANYA?
DO YOU WANT TO?
EXCUSE ME?
(HUFFS)
WE'RE ALWAYS PARTNERS.
WHAT? EVERYONE ALREADY KNOWS
YOU'RE DYSLEXIC.
DON'T BE SO TOUCHY.
YOU'RE RIGHT, HOLLY J.
SORRY.
ELLIE:
ONE DOG, PLEASE.
NO... A SAUSAGE.
WHY AM I SO HUNGRY?
WELL, YOU'VE HAD A BUSY DAY.
TRACKING DOWN CAITLIN,
POACHING MY Q&A.
I DID NOT POACH
THE Q&A FROM YOU.
CAITLIN WANTED ME
TO DO IT.
OH, IT'S GREAT
YOU HAVE A PRO
TO TAKE YOU
UNDER HER WING.
YOU KNOW HOW RARE
THAT IS?
SHE'S NOT LIKE A FAIRY
GODMOTHER, JESSE.
SHE JUST WANTED TO GIVE ME
A CHANCE, I GUESS.
NO, CAITLIN'S AMAZING.
YOU'LL HAVE TO TELL ME HOW
SHE LIKES THE HORS D'OEUVRES
AT THE DEAN'S RECEPTION
FOR HER.
OKAY, POUTY VON POUTMEISTER.
GO TO THE RECEPTION.
TELL CAITLIN I CAN'T WAIT
TO SEE HER TOMORROW.
WELL, COME WITH ME.
OKAY.
I'LL SNEAK YOU IN.
HONESTLY?
I'VE GOTTA PREPARE
FOR PRETTY MUCH THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING I'VE EVER DONE.
PLUS, IT'D BE GOOD FOR YOU
TO GET TO KNOW CAITLIN.
WELL, THANKS.
YOU NEVER FAIL
TO SURPRISE ME, FROSH.
LIFE IS FULL OF SURPRISES,
BOSSMAN.
(KISS)
(LOUD PARTY CHATTER)
YOU PICKED A FINE NIGHT
TO TRY TO STUDY.
REMIND ME AGAIN WHY WE CHOSE
AN ENGINEERING ROOMMATE?
MUCHO MARVELOUS MARGARITA?
I'M TRYING TO GET
SOME WORK DONE.
BUT... WHAT THE HECK.
MMM!
GRIFFIN:
WOO!
(CHOKED SMIRK)
COASTERS, PEOPLE!
COASTERS!
OKAY, MOM.
YEAH, SPEAKING OF...
HOW IS YOUR MOM DOING
THESE DAYS?
OH, COME ON.
YOU, TEQUILA,
YOUR FAMILY HISTORY.
ELLIE:
SHE'S FINE.
SHE'S BEEN SOBER
FOR 17 MONTHS NOW,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
JUST ASKING.
AND JUST BECAUSE
SHE CAN'T DRINK
DOESN'T MEAN I CAN'T.
OKAY.
"PLANET FARTH IN CRISIS"?
AND THAT'S JUST AFTER
ONE SLURP.
OKAY! IT'S NICE AND QUIET
AT THE CORE RIGHT NOW.
BYE.
SHALL I CALL WALKSAFE?
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
(GIGGLING AND LAUGHTER
FROM WITHIN THE OFFICE)
JESSE?
ELLIE!
CAITLIN?
SURPRISE?
OH MY GOD.
UGH.
OH MY GOD!
ELLIE, CAN WE TALK?
PLEASE.
MY BOYFRIEND-SLASH-BOSS
MAKING OUT WITH MY MENTOR,
WHAT'S TO DISCUSS?
WE HAD A LOT TO DRINK
AT THE RECEPTION.
OKAY, WE FLIRTED A BIT.
BUT I DIDN'T MEAN
FOR IT TO HAPPEN.
WHAT? TO GET CAUGHT?
WHY CAITLIN?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA HOW
AWKWARD THIS MAKES THE Q&A?
HOW AM I GONNA FACE HER?
YOU'RE MORE CONCERNED
ABOUT THAT THAN ABOUT US.
OH, THERE'S NO MORE "US",
JESSE.
LOOK, I KNOW
I'M NOT PERFECT,
'KAY,
THAT I MAKE MISTAKES.
WITH A FAMOUS JOURNALIST
TEN YEARS OLDER THAN YOU.
AND I HATE MYSELF FOR IT.
BUT I WON'T JUST WALK AWAY.
(SIGHS)
FINE. FINE, THEN...
I QUIT THE NEWSPAPER.
(SCOFFS) COME ON,
DOESN'T THAT SEEM
A LITTLE DRASTIC TO YOU?
YOU'RE JUST DONE?
WELL, IT'S NOT LIKE
I WANT TO QUIT.
BUT YOU KNOW
WHAT PEOPLE SAY ABOUT US
AROUND THE OFFICE
AS IT IS.
I CAN'T DATE THE BOSS.
SO LEAVING THE CORE
IS THE ONLY WAY
THIS IS GONNA WORK.
AND IT DOESN'T MEAN
I'M NOT STILL MAD AT YOU.
HOLLY J:
DO YOU WANNA HANG OUT
WITH SAV AND THE GUYS AT LUNCH?
BUT WE HAVE
OUR SCIENCE PROJECT.
AND I THOUGHT YOU NEEDED
AN "A" THIS TIME?
OH, ANYA, YOU GIVE ME
SO LITTLE CREDIT.
MY SISTER'S OLD LAB.
FOR ANOTHER A-PLUS,
ALL WE HAVE TO DO IS RE-TYPE,
RE-USE, RE-CYCLE.
YOU MEAN CHEAT?
H-HOLLY J, I DON'T THINK
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
HEY, IF MR. BINCE IS TOO LAZY
TO PUT THE EFFORT
INTO CHANGING THE PROJECT,
THEN WHY WOULD WE PUT
THE EFFORT INTO DOING IT?
BECAUSE IT'S NOT THAT HARD?
AND WHAT IF WE GET CAUGHT?
WE WON'T.
LOOK, I'M JUST TRYING
TO GET AN "A" FOR ONCE.
(SIGHS) YEAH,
BUT I'M NOT A CHEATER.
DON'T GET ALL EXCITED.
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANNA DO?
IT'S FINE WITH ME.
UM...
DON'T MAKE FUN OF ME
IN CLASS.
I DON'T TELL PEOPLE
THAT YOUR PARENTS
GOT YOU A PRIVATE TUTOR.
HEY, ROCHELLE!
YOU WANNA HAVE LUNCH?
OKAY, I'LL DO IT.
SEE?
YOU'RE NOT THAT DUMB.
LUCKILY I DOUBLE-BAGGED
EVERY OUTFIT I OWN
BEFORE GRIFFIN'S
ENGINEERING SOIREE.
AND HE LEFT US THE MESS.
NICE.
WE NEED SOMETHING THAT SAYS
PROFESSIONAL, TALENTED...
HOW ABOUT SOMETHING
LIKE THIS?
GREAT.
JESSE KISSED CAITLIN.
EXCUSEZ MOI?!
JESSE AND CAITLIN?!
SAW THEM MAKING OUT
AT THE CORE.
EW, I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU WERE EVER WITH THAT GUY
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I WAS EVER WITH THAT GUY.
STILL WITH HIM.
PAIGE:
(SIGHS) HUN,
PARDON MY FRENCH,
BUT WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
TRY THIS ON.
CAITLIN WAS ON HIS FREEBIE
FIVE LIST.
AND WHEN YOU'RE IN
A MATURE RELATIONSHIP
YOU CAN'T JUST WALK AWAY.
HON, SOMETIMES WALKING AWAY
IS THE MATURE THING TO DO.
(SIGHS)
WHAT AM I DOING?
I CAN'T DO THIS Q&A
WITH CAITLIN.
THAT, HON, IS SOMETHING
YOU CAN'T WALK AWAY FROM.
IT'S A HUGE OPPORTUNITY
FOR YOU.
NO, IT SHOULD'VE BEEN
JESSE'S OPPORTUNITY.
MAYBE THIS IS KARMA.
(SIGHS)
SOMETIMES YOU HAVE TO CHOOSE
BETWEEN YOUR PROFESSIONAL LIFE
AND YOUR LOVE LIFE.
DON'T MAKE
THE WRONG CHOICE.
(SIGHS)
I THINK I ALREADY DID.
YELLOW'S A BAD IDEA.
STAY RIGHT THERE.
MR. BINCE:
IF YOU DID YOUR LAB
CORRECTLY...
HEY, I REALLY LIKE
THOSE EARRINGS.
THEY'RE NICE.
(SMIRKS)
MR. BINCE:
...THE FURTHER THE TENNIS BALL
GOT FROM THE BOWLING BALL.
MR. BINCE?
YES, MS. SINCLAIR?
THAT ASSIGNMENT ANYA
JUST HANDED IN.
IT'S PLAGIARIZED.
THAT'S A SERIOUS ACCUSATION.
HOLLY J:
RIGHT. THAT'S WHY,
EVEN THOUGH WE'RE PARTNERS,
I WENT AHEAD
AND DID MY OWN.
IS THIS TRUE,
MS. MACPHERSON?
ER NO, UM,
HOLLY J. WAS THE ONE WHO-
HOLLY J:
SHE'S RIGHT.
IT'S MY FAULT.
SOMEHOW SHE GOT HER HANDS ON
MY SISTER HEATHER'S
OLD PROJECT?
BUT I NEVER THOUGHT
SHE'D HAND IT IN.
CAN YOU COME SEE ME PLEASE?
CLASSMATE:
OOHHH...
♪♪♪
THANK YOU.
(PARTY CHATTER)
I'M SO EMBARRASSED
AND SORRY YOU SAW THAT.
NEVER LET A COLLEGE GUY
TALK YOU INTO A DRINKING GAME.
UM, CAITLIN,
BEFORE WE START...
DON'T BE NERVOUS!
YOU'RE GONNA BE GREAT!
REMEMBER, WHEN WE'RE
SITTING OUT THERE,
IT'S JUST US,
HAVING A CANDID CONVERSATION.
EASIER SAID THAN DONE.
YOUR EDITOR HAD
SOME PRETTY NICE THINGS
TO SAY ABOUT YOU
LAST NIGHT.
HE DID?
P.A.:
EXCUSE ME?
I'M GONNA NEED
TO GET YOU MIC'D UP.
I'LL GIVE YOU ALL
THE MORTIFYING DETAILS LATER,
OKAY?
DETAILS. GOODY.
JUST WHAT I WANT.
I NEED YOU IN TWO MINUTES.
OKAY.
UH, SORRY...
THANK YOU.
(GLASSES CLINK)
(PARTY CHATTER)
OW. (SMIRKS)
ELLIE:
AN ASPIRING JOURNALIST OFTEN
WORSHIPS HER IDOLS FROM AFAR.
BUT I'VE BEEN LUCKY ENOUGH
TO SIT ALONGSIDE
A WORLD-CLASS REPORTER
WHO WAS HAPPY TO SHARE
HER INSIGHTS
INTO THE WORLD OF MEDIA.
(TENSE EXHALE, CLEARS THROAT)
PLEASE WELCOME,
THE FILMMAKER,
THE ACTIVIST,
AND... (SMIRKS)
MY MENTOR, CAITLIN RYAN.
AUDIENCE:
(APPLAUDS)
UH...
UH, CAITLIN,
(CLEARS THROAT)
WE ARE HONOURED TO HAVE
A SCREENING
OF "STORM OF CONTROVERSY"
HERE TONIGHT.
WELL, THANK YOU
FOR HELPING ME
TO BRING ATTENTION
TO THIS ISSUE.
AND YOU'VE BEEN RAISING
QUITE THE CONTROVERSY
WHILE ON YOUR CROSS-COUNTRY
TOUR,
HAVEN'T YOU?
CAITLIN:
WELL, I DEFINITELY
TRY TO MAKE PEOPLE THINK.
AND I THINK CONTROVERSY
IS A PART OF CHANGE.
YEAH, YOUR FILM
SEEMS TO ENCOURAGE
RESPONSIBLE CONSUMPTION,
BUT DOES THAT APPLY
TO ALCOHOL CONSUMPTION?
(CROWD CHUCKLES)
I SUPPOSE IT WOULD.
I'M NOT SURE WHAT THAT
HAS TO DO WITH CLIMATE CHANGE.
ELLIE:
RIGHT.
(SMIRKS)
UM, SORRY.
I THINK WHAT YOU'RE
GETTING AT IS THAT,
RATHER THAN SOBERLY
ACCEPT THE FACT
THAT WE'RE BRINGING THIS PLANET
TO THE BRINK,
HUMANITY IS WANDERING AROUND
IN A DRUNKEN STATE-
NO, WHY'D YOU HOOK UP
WITH JESSE?
WHY?
ELLIE,
DON'T...
AND HOW WAS IT, JESSE?
WAS IT WORTH IT?
(HUM OF CONFUSED CHATTER)
SLUT.
(SHOCKED GASPS
THROUGHOUT THE CROWD)
OH BOY.
UM...
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
CAN WE, CAN WE ROLL THE FILM
PLEASE?
(DOCUMENTARY MUSIC BEGINS)
WHAT'S THE STORY,
MORNING GLORY?
JUST TAKE IT DOWN
A FEW NOTCHES, PLEASE.
YOU'RE HUNGOVER!
ELLIE, I THOUGHT
WE TALKED ABOUT THIS?
(KNOCK AT THE DOOR)
HELLO?
HI, FAMOUS CAITLIN RYAN
IN MY HOUSE!
UH, CAN I HAVE A SEC
WITH ELLIE?
HAVE A BUNCH OF SECS.
UH, OH, NOT SEX.
I'M JUST GONNA GO.
WELCOME TO MY ABODE.
SO, I'M HERE TO ASK
WHY YOU HUMILIATED ME
IN PUBLIC?
WHAT RIGHT DO YOU HAVE
TO COMMENT ON MY PRIVATE LIFE?
(SMIRKS)
UM, JESSE IS MY BOYFRIEND.
AH...
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
I'M SLEEPING WITH THE BOSS.
I THOUGHT THAT MIGHT LOOK...
UNPROFESSIONAL.
ELLIE,
IF I'D HAD ANY IDEA...
UM, JESSE DIDN'T SAY
ANYTHING.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
AND THAT'S WHY I QUIT
THE PAPER.
YOU WHAT?
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
I WANTED ME AND JESSE
TO WORK SO BADLY.
YOU COULD BE
A GREAT JOURNALIST.
DON'T LET A FRESHMAN ROMANCE
STAND IN THE WAY
OF YOUR CAREER.
I LEARNED THAT
THE HARD WAY.
AND UM, I SMELLED BOOZE
ON YOUR BREATH LAST NIGHT.
(SMIRKS)
(INAUDIBLE P.A. ANNOUNCEMENT)
HEY.
AT LEAST NOW YOU'LL
HAVE YOUR INDEPENDENCE
FROM THE EVIL HOLLY J!
"THE EVIL HOLLY J".
UNTRUE, BUT IT HAS
A NICE RING TO IT.
HEY, ANYA?
ADAM'S FRIEND SAV'S
BIRTHDAY BASH TONIGHT.
YOU WANNA COME?
SOUNDS GREAT.
CAN WE GO TOGETHER?
OF COURSE!
LATER.
ARE YOU CRAZY?
COME ON, I MEAN...
YOU NEED TO BREAK FREE
OF HER!
SO I'M FREE TO BE ALONE -
LIKE YOU -
ON A FRIDAY NIGHT?
I'D RATHER TAKE THE ZERO
ON MY ASSIGNMENT.
(COMPUTER KEYS TAP)
SURPRISED TO SEE YOU HERE.
I MADE A MISTAKE.
JUST TRYING TO FIX IT.
(SMIRKS)
WELL, I'M JUST GLAD
YOU'RE BACK, FROSH.
AND I PROMISE I WILL NEVER
CHEAT ON YOU AGAIN.
I'M BACK AT THE CORE.
NOT WITH YOU.
AND FROM NOW ON?
CALL ME ELLIE.
(SMIRKS TO HERSELF)