♪♪♪
WHY?
WHY ARE THESE
LAKEHURST GUYS
ALL NOISE AND ALL CHAOS
ALL THE TIME?
I CAN'T BLAME THEM.
DON'T KNOW HOW I'D BE
IF MY SCHOOL BURNED DOWN.
ONLY ONE GOOD THING ABOUT
LAKEHURST COMING HERE.
THEY DID BRING WITH THEM
A CERTAIN JE NE SAY WHAT.
BY JE NE SAY WHAT
YOU MEAN...
GUILTY AS CHARGED.
MAN, I JUST NEED TO FIGURE OUT
A WAY TO TALK TO HER.
IT'S LIKE A ZOO IN HERE
EVERY SINGLE LUNCH.
ASHLEY:
IT'S NOT JUST THE CAF,
IT'S IN THE HALLS TOO.
THERE'S A FIGHT
ALMOST EVERY DAY.
IT'S ANARCHY.
SPINNER:
YOU KNOW WHO WE NEED?
SOMEONE LIKE RUDY GIULIANI
OR GEORGE W. BUSH.
SOMEONE WHO'S GONNA TAKE NAMES
AND KICK BUTT.
ASHLEY:
OH, THAT'S OKAY.
I'LL TAKE ANARCHY.
I WON'T.
JOHNNY:
YEAH? CAN I HELP YOU?
JUST PUT THE BOWL DOWN,
MAN.
STOP ACTING LIKE
AN IMMATURE IDIOT.
LOOK,
I DON'T WANT TROUBLE, OKAY?
I JUST WANT YOU GUYS
TO STOP ACTING LIKE
A BUNCH OF MONKEYS.
YEAH. SURE.
YEAH,
WE'LL GET RIGHT ON THAT.
♪♪♪
(BONES CRACK)
THANKS, MAN.
(APPLAUSE AND CHEERING)
♪♪♪
ASHLEY:
SPINNER, YOU ARE A ROCK STAR.
JIMMY:
YEAH, SERIOUSLY.
WHEN ARE YOU GONNA GET
YOUR OWN COMIC BOOK?
SPINNER:
JUST TRYING TO KEEP
THE PEACE.
ASHLEY:
DIDN'T YOUR CAREER
GUIDANCE EXAM SAY
YOU SHOULD GO INTO
LAW ENFORCEMENT?
SPINNER:
YEAH. ALSO SAID I COULD
CONSIDER BEING A CLOWN.
AT LEAST I GOT OPTIONS.
HATZILAKOS:
GAVIN?!
I NEED TO SPEAK WITH YOU.
WHAT IS THE SCHOOL'S POLICY
TOWARDS VIOLENCE?
UH...
KEEP IT TO A MINIMUM?
ZERO TOLERANCE.
YOU KNOW THAT.
WHY DID YOU GET INTO
AN ALTERCATION
WITH JOHN DIMARCO?
ALL I DID WAS STEP IN
AND DE-ESCALATED
THE SITUATION.
LOOK, I APPRECIATE YOU
WANTING TO TAKE
A LEADERSHIP ROLE,
BUT YOU CAN'T RESPOND WITH
FORCE OR INTIMIDATION.
SO WHAT DO YOU SUGGEST,
STOMP THE YARD?
THE PEACE COMMITTEE?
COME ON, MS. H.
I DON'T EVEN WEAR SANDALS.
IF YOU'RE SERIOUS ABOUT
HELPING THE SCHOOL,
THEN GET SERIOUS.
FINE. I'LL GO.
I'LL TRY TO HELP.
JANE, ARE YOU LATE
FOR CLASS... AGAIN.
CAN YOU GIVE ME
ONE REASON
NOT TO GIVE YOU
A DETENTION?
SHE JUST VOLUNTEERED TO JOIN
THE PEACE COMMITTEE.
ACTUALLY.
I DID?
BEATS DETENTION.
GET TO CLASS,
BOTH OF YOU.
CONSIDER IT
MY THANK YOU GIFT.
FOR ALL THAT
YOU'VE DONE FOR ME.
DARCY,
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
BUT THIS SOUNDS LIKE
YOU'RE SAYING GOODBYE.
IT'S JUST THAT MY
AFTER-SCHOOL SESSIONS,
THREE TIMES A WEEK?
IT'S REALLY CUTTING
INTO MY STUDY TIME.
DARCY, WHEN SOMEONE HURTS
THEMSELVES THE WAY YOU DID,
WE HAVE TO TAKE IT
SERIOUSLY.
AND WE'VE TALKED ABOUT IT,
MS. SAUVE.
OVER AND OVER.
AND OVER.
ARE YOU READY
TO TALK ABOUT
WHAT WAS GOING ON
IN YOUR MIND
BEFORE YOU CUT
YOUR WRIST?
YOU KNOW,
ANY SUICIDE ATTEMPT-
I WASN'T TRYING
TO KILL MYSELF,
I WAS SAD.
WELL, THAT KIND OF SAD
DOESN'T OFTEN JUST GO AWAY.
IT STAYS WITH US.
HONESTLY,
I'M MUCH BETTER NOW.
I WANT TO FEEL HAPPY.
I MEAN,
I AM FEELING HAPPY.
THIS HAS HELPED.
ONCE A WEEK.
AT LUNCHTIME?
THANK YOU,
THANK YOU, THANK YOU!
(EFFORT GRUNTS)
THANKS MAN.
EASY JET LI.
GONNA HURT YOURSELF.
AGH!
NO PAIN, NO GAHHH!
SEE,
I'M NOT AN EXPERT?
BUT I'M PRETTY SURE
YOUR KICKS
ARE SUPPOSED TO HURT
THE OTHER GUY.
UGH, I THINK
I PULLED SOMETHING.
WELL,
YOU'RE IN LUCK -
DOCTOR JIMMY'S
IN HIS OFFICE
AND HE'S SEEING PATIENTS.
OH YEAH?
IS HE A GROIN
SPECIALIST?
JIMMY:
OKAY.
SORRY, THE DOCTOR
JUST STEPPED OUT.
(CHUCKLING)
NO SERIOUSLY, DUDE.
I THINK I'M LIKE
BACKED UP OR SOMETHING
IN THE JUNKULAR AREA.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
BACKED UP LIKE A TOILET?
NO, LIKE I'VE HAD NO ACTION,
IDIOT.
IT'S JAMMED UP.
BOYS.
GAVIN JR. AND-
OKAY!
I DO NOT NEED TO KNOW
THE NAMES OF YOUR NADS.
SO, I DON'T KNOW...
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE
SOMETHING?
NO, THE ONLY MEDICINE
I NEED
IS OF A LOVE VARIETY.
FROM SWEET SWEET JANE.
(GROANS)
DARCY:
SO, SHOULD WE SEE
A MOVIE THIS WEEK?
PETER:
SWEET. CLOWN ACADEMY 3?
DARCY:
UH, THEY'RE STILL MAKING
THOSE?
I WAS THINKING SCALPEL!
SAY, THURSDAY AFTERNOON?
PETER:
DON'T YOU HAVE SAUVE?
DARCY:
NOPE.
I CONVINCED HER
TO SPRING ME.
PETER:
IS THAT A GOOD IDEA?
COULD YOU LET ME
DECIDE THAT? GOD!
I MEAN, GOSH.
UGH, I'M SORRY.
I'M JUST DONE WITH
THE PRYING QUESTIONS.
I WANT TO FORGET.
NOT SO EASY TO DO
IN THERAPY, HUH?
WHATEVER,
IT'S OVER.
NOW I CAN GET BACK
TO MY LIFE
AND MY BOYFRIEND
AND SCHOOL,
LIKE A NORMAL
HUMAN BEING.
GLAD YOU'RE
FEELING BETTER.
I AM. TOTALLY.
LIBERTY:
3:12. CHAIR L. VAN ZANDT,
THAT'S ME,
PROPOSES WE MOVE MONDAY
MORNING MEETING TO AFT.
3:14. VICE CHAIR T. ISSACS
SECONDS THE MOTION.
TOBY:
DEMOCRATIC PROCESS
AT WORK.
JANE:
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU DRAGGED ME INTO THIS.
YOU MUST REALLY
HATE ME.
MAYBE I JUST WANTED
AN EXCUSE
TO HANG OUT WITH YOU.
YOU COULD'VE COME UP WITH
A BETTER EXCUSE THAN THIS.
EXCUSE ME!
CAN WE FOCUS ON THE ISSUE
AT HAND,
IE: HOW TO INCREASE
THE PEACE AT DEGRASSI.
SPINNER:
OH I KNOW!
HOW ABOUT WE JUST BORE
EVERYONE INTO SUBMERSION!
SUBMISSION.
AND HE'S RIGHT,
WHY ARE WE TALKING?
LET'S DO SOMETHING!
DEREK:
LIBERTY!
COME ON,
YOUR BROTHER'S IN A FIGHT!
(ENCOURAGING SHOUTS)
LIBERTY:
DANNY!
WHAT ON EARTH
IS DOING ON HERE?!
DANCING.
WHAT'S IT LOOK LIKE?
LIBERTY:
LISTEN.
WHATEVER THE ISSUE
IS HERE,
CAN WE NOT JUST
TALK IT THROUGH?
DANNY:
BUTT OUT, LIBERTY.
I GOT IT.
OH, YOU GOT AN ANGER
MANAGEMENT PROBLEM.
ALL I SAID WAS,
THAT DEGRASSI KID WHO DIED-
JT YORKE.
HIS NAME WAS JT YORKE.
YEAH, HIM.
I HEARD
HE ASKED FOR IT.
LIBERTY:
HOW DARE YOU!
OKAY LIB-
LIBERTY!
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY!
COME ON!
STOP!
GET OFF ME SPINNER!
(PAINED GRUNTS)
YOU, GO HOME
AND GET OUTTA HERE!
MAKE ME.
(PAINED GRUNT)
JIMMY:
GLADIATORS!
HATZILAKOS IS COMING!
COME ON ROCKY,
LET'S ROLL.
YEAH!
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
JIMMY:
KEEP BEING A HERO
ALL THE TIME
AND WE'RE GONNA HAVE
TO GET YOU A CAPE.
RIGHT.
THINK JANE
WAS IMPRESSED?
YEAH, FOR SURE.
SHE'S NOT GONNA BE IMPRESSED
WHEN YOU'RE IN THE ICU.
POINT?
THERE'S SOMETHING WRONG,
THAT'S MY POINT.
AND YOUR THEORY ABOUT
BEING BACKED UP?
IT'S STUPID, OKAY?
YEAH.
YOU'RE STUPID.
SHUT UP.
LOOK, SPIN.
I'VE HAD MY ISSUES
WITH THE JUNKULAR AREA.
IT'S NO FUN.
AND YOU NEED
TO GET IT CHECKED OUT.
I KNOW YOU HATE DOCTORS
'CAUSE OF WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR DAD-
LOOK, I DON'T WANNA
TALK ABOUT IT, OKAY?
THAT'S FINE.
IT'S YOUR CHOICE.
YOU CAN EITHER IGNORE
AN OBVIOUS PROBLEM
OR YOU CAN BE A MAN
AND FACE IT...
HEAD-ON.
IT'S UP TO YOU.
SIMPSON:
I HOPE YOU'VE ALL
STUDIED HARD.
NO TALKING,
EYES ON YOUR MONITORS.
AND... BEGIN!
CAN'T BELIEVE YOU
NEEDED SPINNER
TO BAIL YOU OUT
OF THAT FIGHT.
DARCY:
SHHH!
SO, GONNA TAKE YOUR
NEW GIRLFRIEND SPINNER
NO, BUT I MIGHT
ASK YOUR MOM.
DARCY:
MAYBE YOU TWO DON'T CARE
ABOUT YOUR GRADES,
BUT SOME OF US WANT TO STAY
OUT OF THE GUIDANCE OFFICE.
SIMPSON:
YOU KNOW THE RULES ABOUT
TALKING DURING EXAMS.
AUTOMATIC DETENTION,
AND I'M DOCKING 20%
FROM EACH OF YOU.
DARCY:
MR. SIMPSON,
I WAS JUST TRYING TO STOP
THESE TWO FROM TALKING!
FINE.
YOU CAN KEEP YOUR 20%.
BUT I'LL SEE YOU
IN DETENTION TOMORROW.
WHAT?
THAT IS SO UNFAIR!
DARCY,
DON'T PUSH YOUR LUCK.
BITE ME.
I'M SORRY!
I'M SO COMPLETELY SORRY.
WELL,
I'M SURE YOU ARE.
YOU'RE ALSO ON YOUR WAY
TO THE FRONT OFFICE. NOW.
RELAX,
I'M NOT GOING TO HURT YOU.
SPINNER:
YEAH. THAT'S WHAT DOCTORS
ALWAYS SAY.
(WINCES)
OKAY.
FEELING A LITTLE
TENDERNESS THERE?
YEAH.
NOT JUST THERE THOUGH.
LOWER TOO.
LIKE...
A HEAVINESS?
THEN IT'S IMPORTANT
I TAKE A LOOK.
WHOA, WHOA!
I COME IN FOR STOMACH PAIN
AND YOU WANNA GRAB MY JUNK?
WHAT KIND OF DOCTOR
ARE YOU?
THE KIND THAT DOES THIS
30 TIMES A WEEK.
JUST RELAX.
LET ME DO MY JOB.
STAND UP FOR ME.
(INHALES)
WE JUST LOOKING FOR ANY
SWELLING IN THE TESTICLE
OR ANY CHANGE
IN THE WAY IT FEELS-
HM-HM.
OKAY.
HOW LONG HAVE YOU
HAD THAT LUMP?
I DIDN'T KNOW
I HAD ONE.
YOU DIDN'T NOTICE
ANYTHING ODD?
YEAH. I DID.
BUT I DIDN'T...
WANT TO-
THAT LUMP COULD BE
A NUMBER OF THINGS.
A CYST, INFECTION,
TUMOUR.
TUMOUR?
YOU MEAN LIKE...
CANCER?
DOCTOR ROTA:
DON'T BE ALARMED.
WE WON'T KNOW ANYTHING
UNTIL WE'VE RUN SOME TESTS.
SPINNER:
HEY-HEY MAN!
DID YOU CATCH THE RAPTERS
LAST NIGHT?
HOW ABOUT
THAT BOSH, UH?
YEAH,
HOW ABOUT HIM.
SO IS YOUR
PHONE BROKEN?
CAUSE I CALLED YOU
LIKE, FIVE TIMES.
WHAT HAPPENED
AT THE DOCTOR'S?
IT WAS A TOTAL
FREAK SHOW, MAN.
THIS LARDASS ATE
A BOX OF DONUTS
REALLY?
AND THEN THERE WAS
THIS OTHER DUDE?
HE REEKED OF ONIONS
AND HORSE PEE.
THAT'S NASTY!
SO THE DOCTOR HAD NOTHING
TO SAY THOUGH?
SHE SAID I COULD
MAYBE POSSIBLY
HAVE CANCER OF THE NUTS.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
AS SERIOUS AS CANCER.
WHICH I TOTALLY
DON'T HAVE, MAN.
I MEAN, IT COULD BE
A LOT OF THINGS.
YEAH.
WHO GETS CANCER
AT 18 ANYWAY, RIGHT?
EXACTLY.
OOOPS.
WRONG GUY,
WRONG DAY, MAN.
BACK OFF.
OR WHAT?
SPIN, BEHIND YOU.
WHAT HAPPENED TO KEEPING
THE PEACE, MAN?
HE GOT IN MY FACE,
DUDE.
LOOK, AS MUCH AS I WANT
TO SEE YOU KICK HIS ASS?
I ALSO WANT TO SEE YOU
ON THE GRADUATION PODIUM
WITH ME.
RISE ABOVE, MAN.
RISE ABOVE.
COME ON, GUYS,
PICK IT UP.
RELAX, LOVELY.
DARCY:
DON'T TELL ME TO RELAX.
YOU DORKS ARE THE REASON
WHY I AM WASHING WINDOWS
AND NOT AT THE MOVIES
WITH MY BOYFRIEND.
WE'VE GOT THE FULL DETENTION
PERIOD.
SO TAKE YOUR TIME.
UM, MR. SIMPSON,
MS. SAUVE CAN'T SEE ME
DOING THIS.
IF SHE KNOWS THAT YOU
GOT ME IN TROUBLE?
I LOSE MY FREEDOM.
DARCY, YOU GOT YOURSELF
INTO TROUBLE.
COME ON.
IF SHE COMES OVER HERE,
JUST TELL HER I VOLUNTEER.
PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE.
SAUVE:
I SEE MR. SIMPSON
HAS PUT YOU TO WORK.
(CHUCKLES)
ON A STRICTLY
VOLUNTEER BASIS.
THE WINDOWS ARE JUST
APPALLINGLY DIRTY.
THIS IS DETENTION
PERIOD.
DARCY WAS ACTING OUT
DURING AN EXAM.
OH.
I GUESS WE'LL HAVE SOMETHING
TO TALK ABOUT
IN OUR NEXT SESSION.
THANKS A LOT.
I'M SORRY,
BUT I CAN'T LIE FOR YOU.
(WATER SPLASHES)
(THUD)
SPINNER:
I'VE NEVER HUNG OUT
WITH A GIRL
WHO'S SUCH A POOL SHARK.
JANE:
WELL, I GUESS YOU'VE
BEEN HANGING
WITH THE WRONG GIRLS,
DUDE.
OHHH.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
COULD HAVE USED
A BIT MORE BACKSPIN.
I MEANT MY NOSE RING.
OH.
IT'S NICE.
I LIKE IT.
YOUR SHOT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE IT?
SEE IF YOU CAN GET IT.
OH, NOT MAN ENOUGH.
IT'S OKAY.
I GOTTA GO!
JANE:
NOW? OKAY.
(HEAVY BREATHING)
JIMMY:
HEY...
THERE'S JANE.
OUCH. COLD.
I WAS ABOUT TO ASK
HOW YOUR NIGHT WENT,
BUT I THINK
I JUST FOUND OUT.
SHE'S NOT MY TYPE.
SHE'S NOT YOUR TYPE?
SHE'S YOU WITH BREASTS.
I KNOW.
BUT WHO'D WANT TO BE WITH
A GUY WHOSE STUFF IS -
MALFUNCTIONED!
JIMMY, I DIDN'T MEAN-
SORRY.
(PHONE RINGS)
GREAT!
IT'S THE DOC.
SPIN, YOU GOTTA DEAL
WITH THIS.
I CAN'T.
DON'T YOU GET IT?
I CAN'T HAVE
THAT DISEASE, MAN.
WHEN MY DAD GOT IT?
HE DIDN'T HAVE A CHANCE.
THAT WAS LUNG CANCER.
SO?!
NOTHING THE DOCTORS DID
WORKED, MAN.
IT WAS A DEATH SENTENCE.
MS. SAUVE SAID
I HAVE TO APOLOGIZE
FOR TOSSING THE WATER,
SO - SORRY.
WELL, HOW ABOUT YOU
SAY IT AGAIN
AND ACTUALLY MEAN IT
THIS TIME?
I DON'T MEAN IT,
MR. SIMPSON!
YOU COULD'VE HELPED ME
AND YOU DIDN'T!
NOW I'M BACK IN STUPID
COUNSELLING
THREE TIMES A WEEK!
DARCY, IF YOU'RE
ON SUICIDE WATCH?
THEN MAYBE THAT'S
NOT SUCH A BAD IDEA.
I HATE COUNSELLING!
OKAY?
I HATE IT!
WHY?
BECAUSE SHE'S TRYING
TO GET INSIDE MY MIND.
SHE WANTS TO KNOW THINGS!
LOOK, WHATEVER IT IS
YOU'RE COPING WITH,
LASHING OUT ISN'T THE WAY
TO DEAL WITH IT.
AND UNLESS YOU CONTROL
YOURSELF AND STOP ACTING OUT-
I WAS RAPED!
SPINNER:
MOM...
WHATEVER HAPPENS,
WE'LL GET THROUGH IT.
IT'LL BE OKAY.
WELL, I'LL START
WITH THE GOOD NEWS.
IT LOOKS LIKE WE'VE CAUGHT
THIS VERY EARLY.
CAUGHT...
WHAT EXACTLY, DOC?
GAVIN, I'M SORRY.
YOU HAVE TESTICULAR
CANCER.
NOW I KNOW
IT'S QUITE A SHOCK
FOR A MAN AS YOUNG
AS YOURSELF
BUT I WANT TO ASSURE YOU
THAT TESTICULAR CANCER IS ONE
OF THE MOST TREATABLE
FORMS OF CANCER.
WITH FULL REMISSION
IN NEARLY 90% OF THE CASES.
I'M GONNA BOOK YOU
AN APPOINTMENT
AT THE HOSPITALS
ONCOLOGY UNIT,
WHERE YOU'LL DECIDE
ON YOUR COURSE OF TREATMENT
BUT UNTIL THEN
IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS...
I THINK YOU AND I NEED
TO GO SEE MS. SAUVE.
TELL HER
WHAT YOU TOLD ME.
I'M NOT READY
TO TELL ANYONE ELSE.
CAN I SIT?
I FEEL LIKE I MIGHT
HAVE BEEN
A LITTLE TOO HARSH
WITH YOU.
BUT YOU'RE THE FIRST ONE
WHO'S TREATED ME
LIKE A PERSON.
AND NOT SOME CHINA DOLL.
IS THERE ANYONE ELSE
YOU CAN TALK TO?
MANNY KNOWS.
AND PETER.
WELL,
I'M HERE FOR YOU TOO,
WHATEVER YOU NEED.
TOBY:
GUYS, COME ON.
GIVE IT BACK.
COME ON, TOBY,
COME ON.
TOBY:
COME ON, GIVE IT BACK!
YOU HEARD HIM.
GIVE IT BACK.
AND WHAT'RE YOU GONNA DO?
SING KUMBAYA?
NOT THIS TIME.
♪♪♪
WALK AWAY, COWARD!
WALK AWAY!