CRAIG:
WE AT "FREE THE CHILDREN"
REALLY APPRECIATE YOU
GIVING UP YOUR WEEKENDS,
NOT TO MENTION FOOD,
TO CELEBRATE FOR CHANGE!
(APPLAUSE)
CRAIG:
AND NOW, YOUR FREEDOM FAST
CO-ORDINATOR,
ANYA MACPHERSON.
THANKS, CRAIG.
HI. WE HAVE A LOT
OF ACTIVITIES
AND DEMONSTRATIONS PLANNED
TO PASS THE TIME,
AND WE HAVE AN APPEARANCE
FROM OUR VERY OWN MYSTERY BAND,
STUDZ.
DEREK:
NO WAY! YOU GOT STUDZ?
(EXCITED CHUCKLE)
THEY KICK ASS!
STUDENTS:
(APPLAUSE AND WHISTLES)
CRAIG:
SWALLOW THOSE PANCAKES
BECAUSE THE FAST BEGINS IN...
3, 2, AND... GO!
EVERYONE:
(APPLAUDING)
MY STOMACH IS IN KNOTS
AND UM,
IT'S NOT FROM HUNGER.
AT LEAST NOT YET.
OKAY, YOU DON'T SERIOUSLY
EXPECT ME
TO BOIL WATER
FOR EVERYONE?
AFTER YOU HAUL IT
FROM THE WELL.
UH, NEWSFLASH, ANYA.
WE'RE NOT IN AFRICA,
OR WHEREVER!
BOILING CLEAN WATER
IS A WASTE OF TIME.
I'M TRYING TO RAISE AWARENESS
OF CONDITIONS
IN OTHER COUNTRIES.
SPARE ME.
THIS IS AN EGO-TRIP,
PLAIN AND SIMPLE.
AND TRUST ME,
NO ONE LIKES
AN ATTENTION WHORE.
WHY CAN'T YOU BE
SUPPORTIVE?
SAV RAN THE FREEDOM FAST
LAST YEAR
AND HE TAUGHT ME
EVERYTHING HE KNOWS.
(BUCKET CLANKS)
COULDN'T HAVE TAKEN LONG!
HOLLY J JUST BEING
HOLLY J?
I SWEAR, IF SHE GOT TO KNOW
YOU BETTER, SHE...
I GOT IT!
HOW IS MY BIG,
STRONG BOYFRIEND
AT LIFTING BUCKETS?
OH NO. NO WAY.
♪♪♪
SIX HOURS DOWN:
WHO'S DREAMING OF PIZZA?
IF YOU'RE WONDERING
IF IT'S ALL WORTH IT,
THIS SHOULD HELP.
IT'S A THANK YOU LETTER
FROM SIERRA LEONE.
YOU KNOW,
ANYA WORSHIPS YOU.
WHAT HOLLY J SINCLAIR SAYS
IS GOSPEL.
CAN'T ARGUE WITH THAT.
IS THERE ANY CHANCE
WE COULD TRY TO BE FRIENDS?
FOR ANYA'S SAKE?
OKAY.
WELL, THE BASIS OF FRIENDSHIP
IS TRUST, RIGHT?
SO, LET'S TRADE SECRETS.
SECRETS.
LIKE... PERSONAL ONES?
YEAH, TO BUILD TRUST,
DUMMY.
SORRY. HABIT.
YOU FIRST.
OKAY.
I'M IN STUDZ.
OH, COOL.
SO THAT'S HOW ANYA SCORED
SUCH A COUP.
YEAH. I PLAY GUITAR.
SAV BHANDARI,
MAN OF MYSTERY.
HMM...
OKAY,
WHAT'S YOUR SECRET?
I'M ALWAYS IN
MY SISTER'S SHADOW
AND SOMETIMES I FEEL LIKE
I'M A FAILURE.
YOU COULD NEVER BE
IN ANYONE'S SHADOW.
YOU'VE GOT A FIRE INSIDE.
NO WONDER ANYA'S
HEAD-OVER-HEELS FOR YOU;
YOU'RE PERFECT.
UH, HOLLY J?
I NEED SOME ADVICE.
THERE'S SOMETHING
I NEED TO TELL ANYA,
BUT I DON'T KNOW HOW.
HEY, ADVICE?
I'M YOUR GIRL.
SOMEDAY...
MY PARENTS ARE GONNA SET ME UP
WITH A WIFE...
WHO ISN'T ANYA.
YOU'RE HAVING
AN ARRANGED MARRIAGE?!
SHHH!
OKAY, YOU WANT GOSPEL?
DO NOT TELL HER.
(CAR WHIRS PAST)
MANNY:
THERE IT IS.
YEAH.
THAT WAS THE ONLY THING
MY MOM LEFT ME.
I'M SO SORRY, BOO.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO MAKE YOU
FEEL SO SAD.
JAY! STILL?
YOU'VE BEEN GIVING ME
THIS CHILL
FOR TWO WEEKS NOW.
MAYBE IT ISN'T SO EASY
TO GET OVER THE FACT
THAT YOU PAWNED MY RING
FOR TWO USELESS TICKETS
TO MADAGASCAR.
MALTA, OKAY?!
AND I AM REALLY SORRY,
SO CAN YOU LET ME KNOW
WHEN YOU'RE GONNA
STOP PUNISHING ME?
I'M SORRY. I AM.
IT'S JUST...
I FEEL LIKE I FAILED HER.
WELL, LET'S GET IT BACK.
MAYBE IF WE JUST EXPLAIN
TO THE GUY
HOW IMPORTANT IT IS.
PAWN BROKERS AREN'T USUALLY
BLEEDING HEARTS
ABOUT THINGS LIKE THIS.
THERE'S ANOTHER WAY.
QUICK AND EASY.
MANNY:
JAY!
PUT THAT DOWN.
(SIGHS)
'KAY?
THAT'S THE OLD JAY WAY.
RIGHT.
THE OLD JAY WAY.
AUCTIONEER:
AND I'VE GOT $50,
$50 FOR THIS FANTASTIC
ANTIQUE BIRDCAGE.
I'M LOOKING FOR $60,
WHO'S GONNA GIVE ME $60?
AH, I GOT $60.
WHO'S GONNA GO $75?
AND $100. $100. $150...
RICKY HENDERSON
ROOKIE CARD.
GOTTA BE WORTH
SOMETHING.
VERY DORKTACULAR,
DARREN.
EMMA:
IT'S DAMIAN.
WE'LL SEE WHAT JAY SAYS
WHEN I TURN THESE INTO CASH.
SERIOUSLY,
WHAT ARE WE DOING HERE?
WHAT ABOUT EBAY?
WELL, THAT REQUIRES
A CREDIT CARD
OR A BANK ACCOUNT,
MR. CASH ONLY.
THIS IS LAME.
IS IT LAME IF IT SAVES
OUR ENGAGEMENT?
AUCTIONEER:
SOLD, FOR $350!
NEXT UP?
A RATHER UNUSUAL ITEM.
SHHH! WE'RE NEXT!
SHOW ME THE MONEY,
SUCKERS!
TWO AIRLINE TICKETS
TO MALTA.
BIDDING STARTS AT $500.
LET'S GET $500.
I'M LOOKING FOR $500.
IS IT GONNA BE $500?
GOT $500 OVER HERE. THANK YOU.
I'LL JUST GO TO $550.
UH, NO, NO, NO, NO.
(POLITE CHUCKLE)
YEAH, UM...
DO YOU KNOW HOW MUCH
THOSE TICKETS ARE WORTH?
ATTENDEES:
(LOW MURMURS)
TWO GRAND!
COME ON, PEOPLE,
TWO GRAND AND YOU'RE IN LUSH,
TROPICAL MALTA, HUH?
IT'S A STEAL
AT TWICE THE PRICE!
SIR, PLEASE
TAKE YOUR SEAT.
NO, WAIT. OKAY,
GIMME THE TICKETS THEN.
GIMME THE TICKETS.
AUCTIONEER:
A BID HAS BEEN PLACED.
THEY'RE NOT YOURS
ANYMORE.
RULES ARE RULES.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S CONTINUE
THE BIDDING NOW.
WE'RE AT $500.
I'M LOOKING FOR $550.
$550. $550 ONCE? TWICE?
(BANGS GAVEL)
SOLD, FOR $550!
THIS IS ACTUALLY
MY FIRST TIME BACK
TO NORTH AMERICA
IN THREE MONTHS.
I'M FROM CANADA, ORIGINALLY.
I DON'T SPEND TOO MUCH TIME
IN NORTH AMERICA ANYMORE.
I OBVIOUSLY LOVE IT HERE,
BUT MOST OF MY WORK'S
OVERSEAS...
HOW ARE MY WATER-BOILERS?
KEEPING UP WITH DEMAND.
YOUR BOYFRIEND
SURE IS HELPFUL.
SEE? I TOLD YOU YOU'D LIKE SAV
ONCE YOU GOT TO KNOW HIM.
OH, I GOT TO KNOW HIM
ALL RIGHT.
ISN'T HE SWEET?
AND HONEST, AND GOOD?
YEAH,
HE'S A REAL CATCH
AND UH, FULL OF SURPRISES.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
NOTHING. YOU'RE IN LOVE.
LUCKY YOU.
OH, DON'T BE UPSET,
HOLLY J!
MAYBE YOU'RE JUST
A LATE BLOOMER.
I'M SURE YOU'LL FIND SOMEONE,
SOME DAY,
AND YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO BRING HIM
TO MY AND SAV'S WEDDING!
OR MAYBE WE CAN
ALL GO TO HIS.
OKAY, I DIDN'T WANT TO GET
INTO THE MIDDLE OF THIS,
BUT...
MY NEW FRIEND SAV AND I
EXCHANGED SECRETS.
SO IS IT BAD?
I MEAN, YOU KNOW ME,
RIGHT?
SECRETS GO IN THE VAULT,
BUT...
I AM YOUR LOYAL FRIEND
AND I COULD MAKE
AN EXCEPTION.
YEAH, JUST THIS ONCE.
PLEASE?
YOU SURE?
MM-HM.
DAMIEN:
THERE'S MY CLAIM TICKET.
THANK YOU.
AUCTIONEER:
ALL THAT FOR SOME
BASEBALL CARDS?
I KNOW.
NOT BAD, NOT BAD.
STILL THINK THIS WAS
A LAME IDEA, RAY?
(SARCASTICALLY)
HA! HILARIOUS.
MANNY:
UH, THE MALTA TICKETS?
HERE.
HOW COULD I FORGET?
YEAH, NICE JOB,
BUDDY.
WAY TO WORK THE CROWD
OVER ON THAT.
DO YOU NEED A JUICE BOX?
OR A NAP?
STOP ACTING LIKE A BABY.
STOP ACTING LIKE MY MOM!
I HAVEN'T LIVED WITH ONE
MOST OF MY LIFE,
I'M PRETTY SURE
I DON'T NEED ONE NOW.
MAYBE YOU DON'T NEED
A FIANCEE EITHER.
WHERE'S THE GUY
I FELL IN LOVE WITH?
THE CHARMING, CONFIDENT GUY
WHO WOULD FIX THINGS,
NOT MOPE ABOUT THEM?
I DON'T KNOW,
HE MET YOU?
WHAT IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
I'M SAYING,
WHERE'S THE GIRL
I FELL IN LOVE WITH?
THE ONE WHO'S SUPPOSED
TO BE SUPPORTIVE?
SHE'S LEAVING.
(SIGHS)
MANNY, WAIT!
I'M SORRY!
IS IT TRUE?
YOUR LITTLE ARRANGEMENT?
HOLLY J TOLD ME.
THAT WAS A SECRET!
ANYA, WAIT!
IT'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK!
NO, I GET IT, SAV.
YOU HAVE TO MARRY SOMEONE
FROM YOUR OWN CULTURE.
I HAVE TO MEET THE GIRL
MY PARENTS CHOOSE,
LIKE A BLIND DATE,
BUT I STILL HAVE
TO LIKE HER.
AND IT'S YEARS AWAY;
NOTHING IS SET IN STONE.
BUT THAT PERSON
WILL NEVER BE ME.
ANYA,
IF WE'RE TOGETHER,
I'LL FIGHT THAT BATTLE
WHEN THE TIME COMES.
IT'S COMPLICATED,
BUT YOU'RE WORTH IT.
THIS IS ALL HOLLY J.
SHE'S TRYING
TO TEAR US APART.
AND NOW SHE HAS TO PAY.
HOLLY J:
I AM SORRY I HAD TO BE
THE BEARER OF BAD NEWS
ABOUT SAV,
BUT...
NO.
YOU DID ME A FAVOUR.
YOU'RE A TRUE FRIEND,
HOLLY J,
AND I'M SORRY I EVER LET SAV
COME BETWEEN US.
(ELATED SIGH)
JUST HUG IT OUT,
SWEETIE.
IT'S BETTER YOU FIND OUT NOW
THAN LATER.
I... I AM SUCH A MESS.
MUST BE THE HUNGER.
GIRL, I'D EAT ROADKILL
RIGHT NOW.
UM...
EVEN BETTER?
DOUBLE CHOCOLATE CHIP.
(HUNGRY SIGH)
IT'S NOT LIKE THE POOR KIDS
IN TIMBUKTU WILL EVER KNOW.
NO.
(ANXIOUS) OH.
MMM!
♪♪♪
♪ Only one way to say it
I'm a pretty liar, yeah ♪
♪ I'm a pretty liar,
yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I'm a pretty liar, yeah ♪
STUDENT:
WHAT THE...?!
HOLLY J:
THIS IS LIKE CHOCOLATE HEAVEN.
DID YOU WANT SOME?
FINE. YOUR LOSS.
(DISAPPROVING MURMURS
AND BOOING)
(DOG BARKS IN THE DISTANCE)
ANYA:
ONLY TEN MORE HOURS TO GO!
WE CAN DO THIS, PEOPLE!
(SIGHS AND WHINES)
TEN MORE HOURS!
WHY MUST YOU TORTURE US?
ME NEED FOOD!
(SECOND-HAND TICKS)
ANYA:
ALMOST MIDNIGHT!
AND AS PROMISED,
STUDZ IS ON DECK!
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
ANYA:
BUT, BUT...
BEFORE WE GET DOWN
TO BUSINESS,
WE HAVE AN UPDATE
FROM OUR CLEAN WATER TEAM.
JANE:
IT'S THE COOKIE MONSTER!
(STUDENTS BOO)
DEREK:
(SNICKERS)
HOLLY J HUNGRY!
GIRL:
HYPOCRITE!
(STUDENTS BOO)
HEY, HEY! HEY!
STUDENTS:
(DISAPPROVING CHATTER
AND BOOING)
YOU DID THIS?
YOU HAD A CAMERA IN THERE?
SETTLE DOWN!
(HUM OF CHATTER AND LAUGHTER)
STUDENTS:
(EXCITED CHEERS)
(GUITARS PLAY)
PETER:
WE'RE STUDZ!
(WILD CHEERING, WHISTLING
AND APPLAUSE)
(BAND PLAYS)
PETER:
1, 2... 1-2-3-4!
♪ HOLLY J SUCKS!
HOLLY J SUCKS! ♪
♪ CHARITY ROCKS, BABY! ♪
♪ HOLLY J SUCKS!
HOLLY J SUCKS! ♪
(MUSIC PLAYS FROM CAFETERIA)
HOLLY J CHEATING
ON A CHARITY FUNDRAISER.
I GUESS I SHOULDN'T
BE SURPRISED.
HOPE IT WAS WORTH IT.
(SEETHING SIGH)
YOU HAVE ONE CHANCE
TO APOLOGIZE TO ME
IN FRONT OF
THE ENTIRE SCHOOL
FOR YOUR LITTLE STUNT.
I CAN'T.
NICE LOYALTY ON YA,
ANYA.
AFTER EVERYTHING I'VE DONE
FOR YOU?
YOU ALMOST BROKE ME AND SAV UP!
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
ALMOST? THAT'S A SHAME.
ON THE OTHER HAND,
YOU MADE ME LOOK LIKE
I DON'T CARE
ABOUT POOR CHARITY CASES.
YOU... YOU DON'T!
WHATEVER HAPPENS,
YOU HAD IT COMING.
LISTEN VERY CAREFULLY,
ANYA.
YOU DO NOT WANT
HOLLY J SINCLAIR
AS AN ENEMY.
WELL, SHE CERTAINLY
HASN'T BEEN A FRIEND.
BRING IT.
(LOCKER SLAMS SHUT)
(EXHALES)
(CAR WHIRS PAST)
(GLASS SHATTERS,
SECURITY ALARM WAILS)
RISE AND SHINE,
FREEDOM FASTERS.
STUDENTS:
(GROAN)
FOUR MORE HOURS
AND THEN WE EAT.
DANNY:
IF WE CAN'T EAT,
LET US SLEEP.
DEREK:
YEAH. ME HUNGRY.
HOLLY J HAD
THE RIGHT IDEA.
FAILURE IS NOT AN OPTION,
FUZZBALLS.
IT LOOKS BAD,
ESPECIALLY ON ME.
YOUR FACE LOOKS BAD
ON YOU.
ANY MORE ATTITUDE
FROM YOU,
AND I WILL TELL THE GIRLS
ABOUT YOUR UNCONTROLLABLE
MORNING STIFFNESS.
UNDERSTAND?
COME ON.
WE GOT WATER TO BOIL.
WHAT'S WITH THE RAGE?
EXCUSE ME?
I'M HUNGRY,
I'M TIRED,
AND I'M NOT GONNA
LET THOSE LOSERS
TALK TO ME LIKE THAT.
THEY'RE JUST JOKING!
UH, YOU BETTER COME SEE THIS.
♪♪♪
DEREK:
PIZZA?
FOR BREAKFAST?
THANK YOU,
SWEET, SWEET LORD!
ANYA:
NO! WAIT! WAIT!
YOU GUYS CAN'T EAT!
DANNY, DEREK,
YOU GUYS CAN'T DO THIS.
(STAMMERING)
I TAKE BACK WHAT I SAID.
(MUFFLED)
TOO LATE. TOO LATE.
PIZZA! PIZZA!
SAV,
WHAT DO I DO?
I DON'T KNOW.
THIS DIDN'T HAPPEN LAST YEAR.
ALL'S FAIR IN LOVE AND WAR,
ANYA.
SLICE?
CRAIG:
ANYA, WHAT'S GOING ON?
THE FAST STILL HAS
FOUR MORE HOURS.
HUH.
SO MUCH FOR LEADERHSIP.
I GUESS YOU FAIL.
(DOOR CHIMES JINGLE)
JAY: (READING)
YOU'RE MY FIANCEE
AND MY SOULMATE;
LOSING YOU WOULD BE LIKE
AMPUTATING A LEG.
SO, WHATEVER MY ISSUES,
I WILL GET OVER THEM
FOR YOU.
I WILL DO ANYTHING
LOVE, JAY.
WELL, ME.
(NERVOUS CHUCKLE)
YOU HAD TO WRITE
THAT DOWN?
IT COMES WITH THIS.
HOW DID YOU GET THIS?
I JUST GOT IT, OKAY?
AND I WANT YOU
TO KEEP IT -
FOREVER.
JAY, THE WAY YOU ACTED,
IT REALLY FREAKED ME OUT.
IT WAS LIKE THE OLD YOU
WAS BACK.
THE OLD ME IS GONE.
I KNOW YOU STILL ADORE
THE NEW ME.
YOU CAN'T JUST FLICK A SWITCH
AND FALL OUT OF LOVE.
JUST LISTEN TO YOUR HEART.
I NEED YOU, BOO.
I HAVE NOBODY ELSE.
(HUM OF CHATTER
AND TRAFFIC WHIRRING)
(UNINTELLIGIBLE CHATTER
OVER POLICE RADIO)
NO.
DAMMIT!
ANYA, ANYA, ANYA.
YOU STILL RAISED
TONS OF MONEY.
I HEARD CRAIG SAY
YOU DID A GOOD JOB,
AND THE POOR WILL STILL
SING SONGS ABOUT YOU.
THIS ISN'T A JOKE!
ALL I DID WAS TRY,
AND I WANTED TO ACCOMPLISH
SOMETHING
AND TO FEEL GOOD
FOR A CHANGE.
I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU FELT BAD.
WELL, I DO -
ALL THE TIME -
AND IT'S BECAUSE OF YOU!
YOU CAN'T STAND
TO SEE ME HAPPY.
WHY DO YOU HATE ME
SO MUCH?
I DON'T.
YOU'RE MY BEST FRIEND.
THEN WHY DO YOU TREAT ME
LIKE DIRT?
BECAUSE YOU LET ME.
ALL RIGHT.
FOR YOU, ONE HALF-FAT
VANILLA HAZELNUT LATTE
TO GET YOU THROUGH
THE SCHOOL DAY,
AND FOR ME,
A SECOND CHANCE.
PRESTO!
I GOTTA SAY, THAT RING LOOKS
MUCH BETTER ON YOUR FINGER
THAN IN SOME SLEAZY
PAWN SHOP WINDOW.
THAT'S NOT MY RING.
THIS IS YOUR STOLEN RING.
A BROKEN WINDOW
DOESN'T LIE,
UNLIKE YOU -
AGAIN, AGAIN,
AND AGAIN.
YOU CAN'T STEAL
WHAT'S YOURS.
JAY, BREAKING
AND ENTERING
IS A WHOLE NEW LEVEL
OF CRIMINAL.
I AM THE SAME CRIMINAL
THAT YOU FELL IN LOVE WITH.
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
YOU'RE HOPELESS.
YOU'RE... A BITCH!
GOODBYE, JAY.
DON'T EXPECT ME
TO VISIT YOU IN JAIL.
WELL...
IT WAS FUN WHILE IT LASTED,
DIMPLES.
(DOOR OPENS
AND DOOR CHIMES JINGLES)
(SIGHS) NEW DAY,
NEW WEEK, NEW HOLLY J.
LEAVE ME ALONE.
OKAY, WE'VE HAD FIGHTS
BEFORE,
BUT WE ALWAYS MAKE UP.
WELL LOOK, I'LL EVEN HELP
YOU CLEAN UP THE MESS.
STOP HELPING, HOLLY!
IT'S HOLLY J.
YOU ONLY MAKE MESSES
OF LIVES,
AND YESTERDAY
IS THE LAST TIME
I'LL EVER LET YOU
MAKE A MESS OF MINE.
(SCOFFS) OKAY,
ARE YOU OFF YOUR MEDS?
YOU'RE HYSTERICAL.
COMMENTS LIKE THAT
IS WHY WE'RE NOT FRIENDS
ANYMORE.
ANYA, COME ON.
DON'T DO THIS.
'KAY, WITHOUT YOU,
I HAVE NO FRIENDS.
YOU KNOW THAT.
YOU DID THIS TO YOURSELF.
GET OVER YOURSELF.