JAY:
IF YOU WANT TO MAKE IT
IN THIS BUSINESS
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO SELL IT
AND TWO BUTTONS JUST...
THAT ISN'T SELLING IT,
HONEY,
BUT THREE DOES.
EMMA:
STOP TORTURING YOURSELF.
WATCHING THAT AGAIN
ISN'T GOING TO MAKE
YOUR ACTUAL DEMO REEL
MAGICALLY APPEAR.
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
JAY SABOTAGED ME.
WELL, MAYBE
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT?
RIGHT. HE ACCIDENTALLY
SWITCHED OUR ALMOST-SEX-TAPE
WITH MY DEMO,
RIGHT AFTER I BROKE
HIS "WITTLE" HEART.
WITH HIS VINDICTIVE
STREAK?
AFTER JAY RUINED MY AUDITION
WITH SMITHDALE DRAMA,
I'M JUST GONNA GO HOME.
LINDSAY:
OH, AUDITIONING
WITH "THE DAME"?
WAS.
WHY IS THAT BAD?
WELL, PROFESSOR IRIS DUNWOODY
IS AS HARD AS WALNUTS.
LIKE ONE IN EVERY TWENTY
GETS IN.
IF THE HEAD OF DRAMA
SEES ME ACT IN PERSON,
SHE'LL HAVE TO ACCEPT ME,
RIGHT?
EVEN WITHOUT MY DEMO REEL?
YA, WELL, MAYBE IF YOU
START WORKING ON
YOUR "WHY I HAVE NO DEMO REEL"
MONOLOGUE.
(EXHALES)
HELP ME?
(HEAVY SIGH)
♪♪♪
OKAY, WHAT ABOUT THAT JAG
THAT I BROUGHT BACK TO LIFE?
I AM CALLING IN
A FAVOUR.
FAVOUR?
YOU STOLE MY TRUCK, JAY!
JAY:
COME ON, TONY!
IF JENNA DUMPED YOU,
TELL ME,
TELL ME YOU WOULD NOT
JUMP THROUGH HOOPS
TO GET HER BACK.
TONY:
AH, YOU'RE KILLING ME.
I'LL MAKE IT UP.
FREE LABOUR, WHATEVER.
I'LL HAVE HER BACK
IN TWO DAYS.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE LUCKY
YOU'RE MY BEST MECHANIC.
TRUCK'S NOT STOLEN.
(CELL DOOR CLANKS OPEN)
JIMMY:
DUDE, EVEN IF WE
CATCH UP TO MANNY,
DO YOU REALLY THINK
SHE'S GONNA
TAKE YOU BACK NOW?
JAY:
I HAVE GOT TO GET THIS DVD
INTO THE RIGHT HANDS.
I'M NOT GONNA SCREW UP
A GREAT GIRL'S FUTURE.
YOU HAVE A
"MANNY CRUSH",
MANNY-A-HOLIC!
(HALF LAUGHS)
SHUT UP.
COME ON,
LET'S ROCK.
GRAB MY SHOES FOR ME?
(BIRDS CHURP OVER
STREET NOISE)
DARCY:
NOT NOW, OKAY?
PETER:
WHAT'S WRONG?
I THOUGHT AFTER
WE SNUCK OUT TO...
MAKE LOVE,
YOU SAID IT WOULD
MAKE YOU FEEL BETTER.
I THOUGHT IT WOULD.
I THOUGHT MAYBE
I COULD ERASE MY MEMORIES.
I DON'T KNOW,
IT DIDN'T.
LET'S JUST FORGET
IT HAPPENED THEN.
I REALLY DIDN'T WANT
TO MAKE THINGS WORSE.
YOU DIDN'T.
I MAKE THINGS WORSE
FOR MY FRIENDS,
MY TEACHERS,
MY PARENTS.
I DESERVE TO BE
AT THIS STUPID CAMP
'CAUSE I'M HORRIBLE.
DARCY, GETTING RAPED
DIDN'T MAKE YOU
A BAD PERSON,
IT JUST MADE YOU
LIKE SAD AND SCARED.
I'M GONNA HELP YOU
GET THROUGH IT.
OKAY?
DON'T FORGET THAT.
SPIRIT BEAR:
IN THE BACKWOODS,
YOU WILL BE TESTED
BOTH MENTALLY
AND PHYSICALLY,
BUT YOU WILL FIND
YOUR STRENGTHS.
I, I CAN'T DO THIS.
SPIRIT BEAR:
THE BLINDFOLD IS JUST
A MEASURE OF TRUST.
WERE NOT GONNA LEAD YOU
INTO ANY DANGER.
YOU REALLY DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I'M REALLY ON EDGE
RIGHT NOW.
IS THERE SOMETHING YOU'D
LIKE TO SHARE, PHOENIX?
WE ARE ALL HERE
TO LISTEN.
YEAH, WE'RE ALL EARS.
(STUDENTS CHUCKLE)
I GIVE UP.
(IRRITATED BREATH)
(DEEP INHALE)
SPINNER:
I SAW THE WOMEN'S
STUDIES BUILDING.
DO YOU WANT TO GO
STUDY SOME WOMEN?
JAY:
SHUT UP.
IRIS DUNWOODY:
MANUELA SANTOS!
(FAN SWISHES)
(APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS)
YOUR DEMO REEL,
MISS SANTOS?
I FELT IT WOULD BE
A SHAME
TO TAINT THE PURITY
OF THE THEATRE
WITH THE ARTIFICE
OF PRE-RECORDED MATERIAL.
BEEN WORKING VERY HARD
ON THAT ONE, HAVEN'T WE?
NO DEMO REEL,
NO AUDITION.
PLEASE.
PLEASE, MS. DUNWOODY,
TWO MINUTES.
ALL RIGHT.
(FAN HITS DESK)
SURPRISE ME, ENCHANT ME,
ASTONISH ME.
GO.
MANNY:
(CLEARS THROAT)
"I LEFT NO RING WITH HER:
WHAT MEANS THIS MY LADY?"
(FOOTSTEPS THUD OVER SILENCE)
FORTUNE FORBID...
(STILTED)
FORTUNE FORBID
MY OUTSIDE HAS...
IRIS DUNWOODY:
STOP!
THAT VIOLA HAS MR. SHAKESPEARE
SPINNING IN HIS GRAVE.
I HAVE TWO HUNDRED SERIOUS
ACTORS TO AUDITION.
NOW YOU BE GONE.
(HEAVY SIGH)
DUNWOODY:
NEXT.
(FAN SWISHES OPEN
AS MANNY'S FOOTSTEPS TRAIL OFF)
JAY:
MANNY, WAIT.
MANNY, WAIT!
NOT ONLY DID YOU
RUIN MY LIFE,
BUT YOU DROVE
ALL THE WAY HERE
TO WATCH IT HAPPEN?
YOU'RE SICK, JAY!
SICK!!
THE DEMO -
THE REAL ONE.
NOW GO BACK IN THERE
AND MAKE MS. WHATSHERFACE
WATCH IT.
YOU GET ONE AUDITION
AND I BLEW IT!
YOUR SADISTIC MISSION
ACCOMPLISHED.
WHEN I SWITCHED THE DVD,
I WAS MAD.
I DID IT
SPUR OF THE MOMENT.
IT WAS A BAD DECISION!
MY DECISION
TO BREAK UP WITH YOU
WAS THE BEST ONE
I EVER MADE!
SO THE RING
MEANS NOTHING?
THIS FAKE DIAMOND
FOR OUR FAKE ENGAGEMENT?!
YOU KNOW
IT MEANS NOTHING!
I SHOULD'VE KNOWN BETTER.
JAY HOGART BRINGS
NOTHING BUT FAILURE
AND DISAPPOINTMENT
TO LIFE!
(RING THUDS ON GROUND)
THEN I'M GONE.
(CRYING)
JOHNNY:
WHERE THE HELL ARE WE?
SPIRIT BEAR:
WE ARE AT PHOENIX'S SPOT
FOR THE NIGHT.
BLINDFOLD OFF.
DROP YOUR PACK.
YOUR SOLO QUEST IS THE TIME
TO REFLECT ON YOUR FEELINGS.
I WANT YOU TO REMEMBER
WHAT YOU'VE LEARNED
AND GOOD LUCK.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO MAKE
A SHELTER OUT OF THIS?
WEREN'T YOU PAYING
ATTENTION?
CAN'T YOU JUST SHOW ME,
PLEASE?
PHOENIX,
IF I HOLD YOUR HAND,
IT NEGATES
THE SOLO QUEST.
BUT HOW?
HOW AM I GONNA SURVIVE
OUT HERE ON MY OWN?
YOU CAN START
BY LISTENING.
TO YOU?
WELL, I'VE BEEN LISTENING
TO GOD MY WHOLE LIFE
AND LOOK WHERE
THAT GOT ME.
WELL, MAYBE GOD WANTS YOU
TO FIND THE STRENGTH
TO DEAL WITH YOUR PROBLEMS
FROM WITHIN YOURSELF.
(BIRDS CHIRP AS TREES RUSTLE
IN THE WIND)
♪♪♪
EMMA:
HEY, HOW WAS THE AUDITION?
MANNY:
I BOMBED.
SO LONG SMITHDALE,
SO LONG FUTURE,
ALL THANKS TO JAY.
SO HE FOUND YOU?
SPINNER:
WOW! HO!
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET THIS
PARTY STARTED!
HOW'S IT GOING?
SPINNER?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
WELL, WE BUMPED INTO
LIBERTY ON CAMPUS.
SHE TOTALLY VOUCHED FOR US.
DID YOU KNOW SHE'S LIKE
ROYALTY AROUND HERE?
YOU JUST HAPPENED TO BE
AT SMITHDALE?
ACTUALLY, WE UM...
WE GOT SOME TICKETS
TO THE PURPLE DRAGON SHOW.
WE ALSO HITCHED
A RIDE WITH JAY
ON HIS...
"SAVE MANNY MISSION".
SPINNER:
YEAH, YOU KNOW, GUILT-BOY
PULLED SOME REALLY CRAZY STUFF
TO FIND YOU.
I'VE NEVER ACTUALLY SEEN HIM
CARE ABOUT SOMEONE BEFORE?
IT'S KINDA WEIRD.
ARE YOU STILL IN THE MOOD
TO PARTY-PARTY?
BRING IT ON.
JAY'S GONE.
HE CAN'T MAKE ANYTHING
WORSE NOW.
PROFESSOR DUNWOODY?
MANUELA SANTOS'S AGENT.
PLEASURE.
THE GIRL WHO BUTCHERED VIOLA
HAS AN AGENT?
I SUPPOSE YOU DON'T
FEEL SHE NEEDS
SMITHDALE THEATRE TRAINING?
WELL, BETWEEN YOU AND ME,
MAN...MANUELA IS VERY,
VERY PASSIONATE
ABOUT THE THEATRE.
(LAUGHS)
REALLY?
THE THEATRE?
OH, WELL,
I CAN'T HELP YOU.
THE BOARD INSISTS ON
A DEMO REEL.
OH, RIGHT HERE.
SHE WANTS TO LEARN
THE CRAFT.
GIVE HER ANOTHER SHOT.
JUST BECAUSE A FETCHING
YOUNG SWAIN ASKS ME?
WELL...
(HALF LAUGHS)
SURELY, THERE MUST BE
SOMETHING
I CAN DO FOR YOU.
YOU'VE BEEN WATCHING
DEMO REELS ALL DAY;
A COLD COMPRESS
FOR YOUR EYES, PERHAPS?
A FOOT RUB?
DO YOU ENJOY SHIRAZ,
MR...?
HOGART.
JAYSON HOGART.
AND YES,
I DO VERY MUCH.
(CORK CREAKS AND POPS)
(FAN SWISHES OPEN)
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
♪♪♪
(GLASSES CLINK)
OH! (GASPS)
OH, FOR GOODNESS SAKE!
OH NO,
LOOK WHAT I'VE DONE.
OH, DON'T WORRY,
DON'T WORRY.
DON'T WORRY,
BIG GUY.
ALL RIGHT.
THERE YOU ARE.
♪ Do you know where love
first goes ♪
♪ To the sun, to the sun,
She runs her... ♪
♪ Fingers through my hair ♪
♪ San Francisco... ♪
(TANGO MUSIC PLAYS)
(LAUGHS)
(Party music continues)
♪ You should empty all those
bullets from your gun ♪
JAY:
YOU'RE A MODERN WOMAN.
I HADN'T REALIZED
YOU HAD A TATTOO.
IRIS DUNWOODY:
(SIGH OF CONTENTMENT)
JAY:
HOW'S THAT?
VERY GOOD.
OOH...
(SIGHS)
THE FEET.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(CROW CAWS)
(LAUGHS TO HERSELF)
I'M ALIVE.
THANK YOU.
(SLEEPING BAG RUSTLES)
(CROW CAWS)
(STOP WATCH CLICKS)
DID I MAKE IT?
TEN SECONDS TO SPARE.
GOOD.
DARCY:
COME ON,
WE DON'T HAVE ALL DAY!
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
SPINNER:
HELLO!
GOOD MORNING.
WE'RE BACK,
WE'RE FEELING HOLE-Y!
EMMA:
YOU GUYS FOUND A CHURCH?
JIMMY:
SORT OF. IT'S MORE LIKE
A CAMPUS DOUGHNUT SHOP.
(CHUCKLES)
HAVE YOU GUYS
HEARED FROM JAY?
ANY IDEA WHERE
HE STAYED LAST NIGHT?
EMMA:
IT ALMOST SOUNDS
LIKE YOU CARE.
SWANKY PLACE YOU GOT HERE!
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
TELLING YOU ABOUT THE AUDITION
YOU HAVE IN ONE HOUR.
I PULLED SOME STRINGS.
DUNWOODY WATCHED YOUR DEMO.
BUT...
WHAT DID YOU DO?
NEVER YOU MIND, DIMPLES.
JUST ROCK THE AUDITION,
AND I PROMISE I WON'T BOTHER YOU
ANY MORE.
MANNY:
"ALAS,
IT IS OUR FRAILTY
THAT IS THE CAUSE,
NOT WE.
FOR SUCH AS WE ARE MADE
IF SUCH WE BE."
THAT WAS LOVELY.
NICELY DONE.
THANK YOU,
MS. DUNWOODY.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
HOW MUCH I APPRECIATE
THE SECOND CHANCE.
OH, IT WAS YOUR AGENT
THAT CONVINCED ME.
YES,
FOR SUCH A YOUNG MAN,
MR. HOGART CAN BE
VERY PERSUASIVE.
HOW PERSUASIVE,
EXACTLY?
IRIS DUNWOODY:
OH...
HE'S LORD OF THE TANGO,
UH...
FINGERS...
STRONG, YET GENTLE.
I FEEL TWENTY YEARS YOUNGER!
YOU'LL HAVE TO BRING HIM
WITH YOU FOR ORIENTATION.
SO, I'M IN?
IRIS DUNWOODY:
PENDING OTHER FACTORS.
BUT I AM GOING
TO RECOMMEND YOU...
TO BECOME A MEMBER
TO THE SMITHDALE
DRAMA DEPARTMENT.
(FAN SWISHES)
IS THAT ASHLEY?
WHAT IS SHE DOING HERE?
SPINNER:
STALKING YOU?
JIMMY:
HEH. (TIGHT EXHALE)
PROBABLY.
HEH.
THIS IS SWEET.
SPINNER:
YES, YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
MANNY:
HEY, WHAT'D I MISS?
WHO CARES!
ASK ME ABOUT MY AUDITION;
I NAILED IT.
THAT'S AWESOME!
HOW DID JAY
PULL IT OFF?
I THINK HE DID SOME
PRETTY DRASTIC THINGS.
WERE ANY OF THEM
LEGAL?
COMING FROM MS. NAKED
PURPLE DRAGON PROTEST?
BESIDES, I THOUGHT YOU
FORGOT ABOUT THE OLD JAY.
WELL, I'M STILL TRYING
TO GET USED TO THE NEW MANNY.
THE ONE THAT'S
JAY-CRAZY.
WE HAVE FUN.
MY PARENTS
ARE GA-GA OVER HIM.
I JUST NEVER THOUGHT
WE'D GET SERIOUS.
(HALF LAUGHS)
DARCY:
"YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN OUR ANGEL,
SUDDENLY SOMETHING CHANGED.
PLEASE HELP US UNDERSTAND."
I'M SORRY, I DON'T SEE HOW
THIS IS SUPPOSED TO HELP.
THAT LETTER WAS PROBABLY
VERY HARD
FOR YOUR PARENTS TO WRITE.
YOU'RE STILL ANGRY?
NOT AT THEM,
NOT AT MY PARENTS.
SO SOMETHING HAPPENED.
YOU BLAME YOURSELF?
KINDA.
SOMEONE ELSE.
TALK TO THAT PERSON.
IT'S AN EMPTY CHAIR,
SPIRIT BEAR.
IMAGINE THEY'RE THERE.
TELL THE DOUCHEBAG
HOW YOU FEEL.
YOU STOLE EVERYTHING
THAT WAS IMPORTANT TO ME.
YOU RAPED ME.
AND I NEVER EVEN
SAW YOUR FACE.
I FEEL DIRTY.
AND I'VE TRIED
AND TRIED TO ERASE IT,
BUT I CAN'T.
YOU'VE TAKEN A GREAT STEP,
PHOENIX.
(DRUM BEAT PLAYS)
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
MANNY:
HEY.
SO IT LOOKS LIKE
I'M SMITHDALE DRAMA MATERIAL.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU DID,
BUT THANK YOU.
I BLOCKED IT OUT.
ANY CHANCE YOU CAN BLOCK OUT
MY MASSIVE STUPIDITY?
(FUSTRATED GRUNT)
WHY DID YOU DO THAT,
DUMMY?
I HAVE NOT-BEING-
A-COMPLETE-TOOL ISSUES,
BUT I'LL WORK ON THEM.
AND I'LL HAVE TO LEARN
TO TRUST YOU.
NO RISK,
NO REWARD, RIGHT?
NATASHA:
AND HERE TO ROCK YOU
SENSELESS
IS OUR OFF THE WAGON
WITH PURPLE DRAGON
MYSTERY GUEST.
ARE YOU READY?
CRAIG MANNING!
AUDIENCE:
(APPLAUDING AND CHEERING)
SPINNER:
CRAIG.
WE DROVE ALL THIS WAY
TO SEE A GUY I CAN CALL?
I WAS HIS DRUMMER.
I WAS HIS DRUMMER!
CRAIG:
SO HOW'S EVERYBODY DOING,
SMITHDALE?
AUDIENCE:
(CHEERING AND CLAPPING)
(HYPED UP)
OW!
I AM SO EXCITED TO BE HERE
WITH FUNKYSAURUS-REX.
WE'RE GONNA PLAY SOME
SONGS FROM THE ALBUM...
SO, YOU KNEW IT WAS HIM,
DIDN'T YOU?
HE EMAILED ME
AFTER WE BROKE UP.
ASKED ME TO GO ON TOUR
IN EUROPE.
YOU'RE GOING ON TOUR
WITH HIM?
THAT'S NICE.
SEND ME A POSTCARD.
CRAIG:
IT'S SO GREAT TO SEE
SO MANY OF MY OLD FRIENDS
HERE TONIGHT,
BUT I COULDN'T HAVE MADE
THIS ALBUM WITHOUT ONE OF THEM.
SHE'S ALWAYS BEEN
MY INSPIRATION.
ASHLEY KERWIN!
AUDIENCE:
(APPLAUDING AND CHEERING)
THIS ONE'S CALLED
"MY WINDOW".
(BAND BEGINS TO PLAY)
SPIRIT BEAR:
TO LET GO OF OUR PAIN,
WE HAVE TO LEARN
TO TRUST OTHERS.
PHOENIX,
DO YOU TRUST YOUR TRIBE?
NOT REALLY.
DO I HAVE TO DO THIS?
WHENEVER YOU'RE READY,
JUST LET GO.
NO. NO-NO-NO-NO-NO.
PLEASE JUST LET ME DOWN,
NOW.
DARCY, JUST DO IT.
WE'RE NOT GONNA
LET YOU FALL.
CRAIG:
♪ AND I SEE IT CARRYING
MY WOES ♪
♪ I SEE IT COMIN' THROUGH
MY WINDOW ♪
♪ 'CAUSE MY WINDOW GOT THE LIGHT
THAT I KNOW ♪
I USED TO BE CRAZY
FOR CRAIG;
HE'S JUST SO YESTERDAY.
YOU'RE MY TODAY
AND MY TOMORROW.
BEN:
HEY, LAST NIGHT,
THANKS FOR THE GOOD TIMES,
TASTY GIRL!
LISTEN,
OUR TONGUES SHOULD CATCH UP
WITH EACH OTHER AGAIN SOON.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
AFTER THE CONCERT,
CALL ME.
WHO ARE WE KIDDING?
THE COLLEGE GUYS WILL BE LUCKY
TO HAVE YOU HERE NEXT YEAR.
CRAIG:
♪ I SEE IT CARRYING MY WOES ♪
ASHLEY:
CRAIG:
♪ I SEE IT COMIN'
THROUGH MY WINDOW ♪
ASHLEY:
♪ SEE IT COMIN' THROUGH ♪
ASHLEY AND CRAIG:
♪ 'CAUSE MY WINDOW GOT THE LIGHT
THAT I KNOW ♪
PETER:
COME ON, DARCE!
OKAY.
TRUST, PHOENIX.
TRUST.
CRAIG:
♪ AND I SEE THE LIGHT COMIN'
THROUGH MY WINDOW ♪
SPIRIT BEAR:
GOOD WORK, PHOENIX.
ASHLEY:
♪ I SEE THE LIGHT COMIN'
THROUGH MY WINDOW ♪
CRAIG:
♪ AND I SEE IT CARRYING
MY WOES ♪
ASHLEY:
♪ I SEE IT CARRYING MY WOES ♪
CRAIG:
♪ I SEE IT COMIN'
THROUGH MY WINDOW ♪
ASHLEY:
♪ I SEE IT COMIN' THROUGH ♪
ASHLEY AND CRAIG:
♪ 'CAUSE MY WINDOW GOT
THE LIGHT THAT I KNOW ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS AND APPLAUDS)
PETER:
ALL RIGHT!
GO, DARCY!
GO, PHOENIX!
GOOD STUFF, DARCE.
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
MANNY,
HOW DID YOU GET THE-
MANNY:
I'VE SEEN YOU DO IT
A HUNDRED TIMES.
AND I KNEW YOU'D COME BACK,
EVENTUALLY.
HMM.
THAT PLAN
SHOULDN'T HAVE WORKED.
BUT IT DID.
KINDA LIKE US.
JAY, ABOUT THAT GUY,
WE JUST-
YA, I'LL...
I'LL GIVE YOU
A "GET OUT OF JAIL FREE"
CARD FOR THAT.
SO WHY IS YOUR CAR
HOOKED UP TO MY RIG?
WHEREVER YOU'RE GOING,
I'M GOING...
OR VICE VERSA.
MANNY,
WE GOT FAKE-ENGAGED
SO THAT YOU COULD HAVE
MORE FREEDOM.
BUT THEN I STARTED
REALIZING
HOW MUCH IT'D SUCK
WHEN YOU LEFT.
I DON'T WANT TO HOLD YOU BACK
FROM YOUR DREAMS, BUT...
JAY, YOU DROVE
FOR TWO DAYS
TO HELP ME
GET INTO SMITHDALE.
THAT'S CALLED MAKING
MY DREAMS COME TRUE, DOOFUS.
OR MAYBE JUST ME
BEING CRAZY.
CRAZY ENOUGH TO BE MY FIANCE
FOR REAL THIS TIME?
SHORTCAKE,
YOU GOT YOURSELF A DEAL.
(STRAINED GRUNT)
♪♪♪
(PLAYS A GUITAR SOLO)
CRAIG:
♪ AND I SEE THE LIGHT
COMIN' THROUGH MY WINDOW ♪
ASHLEY:
♪ I SEE THE LIGHT
COMIN' THROUGH MY WINDOW ♪
CRAIG:
♪ I SEE IT CARRYING MY WOES ♪
ASHLEY:
CRAIG:
♪ I SEE IT COMIN' THROUGH
MY WINDOW ♪
CRAIG AND ASHLEY:
♪ 'CAUSE MY WINDOW GOT
THE LIGHT THAT I KNOW ♪
ASHLEY:
♪ OOH... YEAH ♪