HERE ARE YOUR STUDY
GUIDES.
TWO WEEKS TILL THE EXAM.
GO! BLIND YOURSELF
WITH SCIENCE!
THANKS, MR. BINCE.
UH, DO YOU AND LUCAS WANNA
CRAM WITH SAV AND I?
DOUBLE STUDY DATE?
COUPLES ONLY.
YEAH, COUPLE OF SKIDS.
(BELL RINGS)
(UNINTELLIGIBLE
PA ANNOUNCEMENT)
(WHISTLES)
BUSTED AGAIN?
WHAT DID YOU DO NOW?
(SCOFFS) WOW.
DEFENDED YOU.
DUDE SAID YOU WERE
THE SECOND HOTTEST GIRL
IN SCHOOL.
MMM, TOUGH GUY, HUH?
(LAUGHS)
IN TROUBLE AGAIN?
WHAT A SURPRISE!
JUST TRY TO PRETEND
YOU'RE NOT A JERK TONIGHT.
MMM.
FOR MOM.
ICY.
AND AS HER FORMER BFF,
I'VE SEEN JANE ARCTIC.
WHAT'S TONIGHT?
WELL, MOM'S NEWEST
NET-DORK DATE IS COMING
AND WE'RE SUPPOSED
TO CARE.
WHAT IF YOU HAD BACKUP?
LIKE, SAY ME AND IZZY?
AS A DISTRACTION?
YEAH?
(SMIRKS)
YOU'D DO THAT?
YEAH. OF COURSE!
LUCAS VALIERI.
WE MEET AGAIN.
BELIEVE ME, MS. H.
I'D RATHER BE SPENDING TIME
WITH MY GIRLFRIEND.
GIRLFRIEND?
WELL, IF YOU'RE LUCKY,
MAYBE SHE'LL RUB OFF ON YOU.
HOPE SHE DOES.
(DEEP INHALE)
♪♪♪
SIMPSON:
EXACTLY.
YOU'RE SUCH
A GREAT TEACHER.
AND I KNOW THE STUDENTS
WILL BE HAPPY TO HAVE YOU BACK.
SO I'LL SEE YOU
NEXT WEEK?
YOU KNOW IT.
ALL RIGHT.
SO?
COUNCELLING PROGRESS:
CHECK.
GREEN LIGHT FROM MS. H:
BACK IN MEDIA IMMERSION
ON MONDAY: CHECK!
AMAZING!
SO, YOU'RE GOING BACK MEANS
MOM'S COMING HOME
TOMORROW?
YOU KNOW IT.
THANKS TO MY CONFLICT
RESOLUTION MANTRA -
STAND TALL
AND OPERATE POSITIVELY.
STOP.
SIMPSON:
YEP, S.T.O.P.
HAVE YOU BEEN READING
MY FLASH CARDS?
EMMA:
NO. STOP. LOOK.
IT'S SEAN.
(CAR RUMBLES PAST)
LUCAS, I BET GREG KNOWS
AS MUCH ABOUT BASEBALL
AS YOU DO.
ASK ME ANYTHING.
SHOOT.
SO... GREG,
ARE YOU HAPPY I HAD TO SKIP
THE GAME TONIGHT WITH MY DAD?
YOU KNOW, THE GUY WHO BUSTED
HIS BUTT FOR THIS FAMILY
BEFORE SHE KICKED HIM OUT?
JANE:
YOU MEAN WHEN
HE WAS ACTUALLY AROUND?
(SARCASTIC LAUGH)
GREG:
HEY, WE'VE ALL HAD OUR TROUBLES,
RIGHT?
I MEAN, THE UPS AND DOWNS
OF LIFE.
GREG'S RIGHT.
NOW IS NOT THE TIME.
SO WHY DON'T WE JUST TRY
TO ACT CIVILIZED
AND ENJOY A NICE MEAL,
OKAY?
(CLEARS THROAT)
MIA, YOUR LITTLE GIRL
SURE IS SMART.
(PLEASED)
EVELYN:
AT THIS RATE, SHE'S GONNA BE
READING NOVELS SOON!
MIA:
YEAH, I'VE BEEN USING
MY SPIRIT SQUAD CHEERS
TO UH, TEACH HER HOW TO SPELL.
EVELYN:
AH, SPIRIT SQUAD, GOOD GRADES,
SUPER MOM.
AND I'M ALSO THINKING
OF RUNNING
FOR STUDENT COUNCIL
PRESIDENT.
EVELYN:
YOU ARE A FORCE
TO BE RECKONED WITH, MIA.
(BIRDS CHIRP)
EMMA:
SEAN, I HAVE A BOYFRIEND.
THAT'S GOOD.
GOOD.
I'M HAPPY.
SERIOUSLY.
I'M GLAD WE BOTH
MOVED ON.
I CAME HERE TO SAY BYE
TO ALL YOU GUYS
BEFORE I SHIP OUT.
SHIP OUT, AS IN...
GO TO WAR?
KANDAHAR.
THAT'S WHERE THE ACTION IS.
ACTION?
AS IN ROADSIDE BOMBINGS?
MORTAR FIRE?
I'M SORRY.
IT'S JUST... INTENSE.
SIMPSON:
SPICY SAAG PANEER ANYONE?
NOW THAT'S INTENSE.
I REMEMBER HOW MUCH
YOU ENJOYED IT.
THANKS, MR. S.,
FOR LETTING ME STAY HERE
THIS WEEKEND.
SIMPSON:
FIRST OF ALL,
IT'S ARCHIE -
I'LL EVEN ACCEPT SNAKE -
AND YOU'RE MORE THAN WELCOME
TO STAY HERE
WHENEVER YOU'RE ON LEAVE.
♪ Come on, everybody ♪
♪ Let's get ready ♪
♪ To do the jungle dance ♪
BELLA'S GLUED TO THE GAME.
DADDY'S LITTLE GIRL,
ALL RIGHT.
ARE YOU SURE SHE ISN'T
DEFECTING TO TEAM GREG?
SORRY.
IT'S JUST THAT NOW
I WON'T SEE MY DAD
FOR A MONTH AND...
I KNOW IT SOUNDS LAME,
BUT UH...
HE'S THE ONLY PERSON
I CAN TALK TO.
YOU KNOW,
OTHER THAN YOU.
WHY DIDN'T YOU
TELL ME BEFORE?
YOU'RE ALWAYS
AT SPIRIT SQUAD OR...
BABYSITTING.
YEAH, WELL,
WHEN IT'S YOUR OWN KID,
IT'S CALLED PARENTING.
I GET IT.
I KNOW IT'S HARD
AND I'M TRYING, MIA.
BUT SOMETIMES I WONDER
WHEN THE PARENTING ENDS
AND THE GIRLFRIENDING
BEGINS?
OKAY, I GET IT.
BUT I CAN BE BOTH;
THAT'S HOW AMAZING I AM.
HEY, COME HERE.
I'VE ALWAYS GOT TIME
FOR YOU, OKAY?
(DOORBELL RINGS)
JANE:
MIA'S MOM'S HERE.
LET ME KNOW WHEN YOU CAN
FIT ME IN.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
CHEERLEADER DELIVERY!
DO I KNOW YOU?
UM...
HOW ABOUT YOU COME OVER
TO MY HOUSE
AFTER SCHOOL TODAY?
WE CAN STUDY SOME...
AND THEN SOME.
(WILY CHUCKLE)
WHY DON'T YOU COME OVER
TO MY PLACE?
GREG'S TAKING MY MOM AWAY
FOR THE WEEKEND.
DID YOU KISS YOUR NEW DADDY
GOODBYE?
(BOYS SNICKER)
JANE:
GIRL TALK.
IT CAN'T WAIT.
UM...
LOOK, I KNOW WE'VE
AVOIDED EACH OTHER
SINCE I'VE BEEN
AT DEGRASSI,
BUT UM,
I JUST WANTED TO SAY
HOW AWESOME I THINK
YOU AND BELLA ARE DOING.
RIGHT.
WELL... UM...
OKAY. THANKS.
SO WHY ARE YOU WASTING TIME
WITH SKIDMARK?
YOU SAW HIM
WITH MY MOM.
WELL, HE'S MISERABLE
AT HOME.
HE MISSES HIS DAD.
YOUR DAD.
OH, YOU MEAN THE MAN
WHO DROPS LOTS OF CASH
ON KIDS
HE DOESN'T REALLY WANT
AND THEN DISAPPEARS
FOR MONTHS?
SOUND LIKE ANYONE
YOU KNOW?
YOU DROPPED OUR FRIENDSHIP
THE MINUTE THAT I GOT PREGNANT,
REMEMBER?
SO SAVE THE CONCERN.
LOOK, HE'S GONNA
LET YOU DOWN, MIA.
IT'S WHAT HE DOES.
(LAUGHING)
ARCHIE, I MISSED THIS.
I REALLY MISSED THIS!
WELL, I JUST WANTED TO SHOW YOU
HOW HAPPY I AM THAT YOU'RE HOME.
SPIKE:
(GIGGLES)
WELL, I SEE THAT MISSING ME
HASN'T SPOILED YOUR APPETITE.
(CLEARS THROAT)
YEAH.
YEAH, YOU, YOU KNOW...
SNAKE, YOU LOOK GOOD.
I MEAN, IF WE HAD FOOD
LIKE THIS ON THE BASE,
WE'D PROBABLY ALL BE...
OH, FLATTERY.
YOU SHOULD COME BY MORE OFTEN.
SIMPSON AND SEAN:
(LAUGH)
SIMPSON:
NO, BUT SPIKE IS RIGHT.
I SHOULD PROBABLY TRY
TO GO FOR A RUN OR...
SOUNDS LIKE YOU NEED
A GYM TEACHER.
I COULD MAKE YOU
A TRAINING ROUTINE,
IF YOU'D LIKE.
OH.
YOU MUST HAVE...
FRIENDS YOU WANNA SEE
OR UH...?
SOMEONE AT THE GARAGE?
NO. I DON'T.
SO WHEN ARE WE GONNA
HIT THE GYM?
UM...
I'M FREE TOMORROW.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW
AT 1500 HOURS THEN.
OKAY. (TAKE ABACK)
MR. CAMERON.
GONNA WORKOUT.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
OUR KNIGHT
IN SHINING ARMOUR!
PRESENTING
LADY BELLA!
(WHISPERS)
WE'RE PRINCESSES,
JUST SO YOU KNOW.
UH, I THOUGHT THIS WAS SUPPOSED
TO BE A DATE?
AS IN THE TWO OF US,
MINUS THE KID.
OUR KID.
WHO WILL BE IN BED
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
AND THEN...
I SAID WE'D MEET
WITH THE GUYS.
NOW WE'RE SUPPOSED
TO BAIL?
IT SOUNDS LIKE
YOU'RE BAILING ON US.
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
A FAMILY,
REMEMBER?
SAVE THE SPEECH.
YOU'RE NOT THE PRESIDENT YET.
YOU SURE MAKE IT HARD FOR ME
TO DEFEND YOU SOMETIMES.
I MEAN, JANE-
JANE?
(INCREDULOUS BREATH)
DON'T LET HER
GET INTO YOUR HEAD.
(LUCAS' PHONE RINGS)
IT'S JOHNNY.
SEE?
(PHONE RINGING)
(BEEPS PHONE OFF)
I'LL CANCEL.
UNLESS UH...
AH, FORGET IT.
FORGET WHAT?
NOTHING.
JUST THOUGHT I COULD
MAYBE GO SAY HI
WHILE YOU PUT HER TO BED.
MOMMY, MY TUMMY HURTS.
I'LL UH...
I'LL GET YOU SOME MILK
IN A SECOND,
'KAY, SWEETIE?
SO YOU WANT US TO JUST STAY HERE
WHILE YOU GO?
I'LL BE A HALF HOUR.
HOUR, TOPS.
I LOVE YOU, BEAUTIFUL.
YEAH.
YEAH, I LOVE YOU TOO.
(SIGHS)
ANYA:
BOYFRIEND ALERT.
A LITTLE BIRDIE TOLD ME
YOU LIKE CHARM BRACELETS.
THERE'S AN "M" FOR MIA,
"B" FOR BELLA,
AND A...
AND AN "L" FOR LOSER.
WELL, THANKS, LOSER.
LAST NIGHT...
IT WAS NO FUN WITHOUT YOU,
AND WHEN I CAME HOME
YOU WERE GONE.
MIA:
WELL, WHAT DID YOU EXPECT?
YOUR SISTER TOLD ME
THIS WOULD HAPPEN.
EVEN YOUR MAD FACE
IS CUTE.
OH, SAVE IT.
SO, CAN WE TRY AGAIN?
TONIGHT.
ALL THREE OF US?
ME, YOU, BELLA.
WELL,
SINCE YOU HAVE DETENTION,
I'LL PICK HER UP
AFTER SCHOOL.
(BELL RINGS)
NOW GO. YOU'RE GONNA
GET ME IN TROUBLE.
SEAN:
WOW. MEMORIES.
SIMPSON:
OKEY DOKEY, SARGE,
WHERE DO WE START?
ON THE 5BX PLAN -
SIMPLE CALISTHENICS.
WE'RE GONNA GET
YOUR BODY BACK.
WHY AM I SUDDENLY
VERY AFRAID?
SEAN:
WATCH AND LEARN, SNAKE.
NOW REMEMBER,
IF IT HURTS,
IT WORKS!
(HEAVING GRUNTS)
GOOD.
SIMPSON:
OKAY. OKAY.
(FORCED EXHALE)
ALL THE WAY DOWN.
WELL, I THOUGHT THAT WAS DOWN.
NOPE.
(GRUNT OF EXERTION)
SEAN:
NICE. BREATHE.
BREATHE.
I GOTTA REMEMBER TO BREATHE.
GOTTA BREATHE.
(FORCED EXHALES)
SUPPOSED TO BE SEEING
COLOURS LIKE THIS?
♪ I'm feeling so pumped ♪
♪ And on fire ♪
♪ Driving my body
with total desire... ♪
COME ON, KEEP GOING.
(HEAVY PANTING)
SEAN:
GOOD.
(PANTING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTS AND PANTS)
SEAN:
SIXTEEN,
SEVENTEEN...
OKAY, THAT'S SEVENTEEN.
YOU GOT THREE MORE TO GO.
(WINDED)
TELL YOU WHAT,
WHY DON'T I JUST WATCH YOU
FOR A WHILE, OKAY?
AW, COME ON.
IF I DO IT FOR YOU,
HOW ARE YOU GONNA LEARN?
COME ON, THREE MORE!
LET'S GO! LET'S GO!
ONE... BREATHE!
GO-GO-GO-GO-GO-GO!
(STRAINED GRUNT)
(STREETCAR RUMBLES BY)
(MUSIC PLAYS LOUDLY,
PARTYGOERS CHATTER)
TO MY LADIES!
(WITH A LAUGH)
HEY.
THIS IS ONE CROWDED
FAMILY NIGHT.
WHILE THE 'RENTS ARE AWAY,
THE MICE WILL PARTY
LIKE ROCK STARS.
OKAY, NO.
LOUD MUSIC, BOOZE,
AND A THREE-YEAR-OLD?
NOT A GOOD MIX, LUCAS.
JANE'S OUT;
BELLA CAN USE HER ROOM.
I BOUGHT HER A BEAR...
AND THIS.
SHE LOVES THAT STORY.
AND YOU LOVE
TO THROW DOWN.
AT LEAST, USED TO.
THAT'S I BROUGHT THE PARTY
TO YOU.
YEAH, IT HAS BEEN
A LONG TIME.
YOU DESERVE SOME FUN
FOR ONCE.
RIGHT AFTER SOMEBODY
GOES TO BED.
(GIGGLES)
SEAN:
COME ON, SNAKE!
FEEL THE PAIN!
FEEL IT!
GOOD.
GOOD. KEEP GOING.
(GRUNTS AND PANTS)
AT EASE, SARGE.
(PANTS) OKAY.
THAT WAS GREAT,
BUT I THINK I'M DONE FOR TODAY.
THAT'S JUST THE BEGINNING.
YOU GOTTA BE ABLE TO DO IT
IN YOUR SLEEP.
SIMPSON:
(SARCASTIC CHUCKLE)
IF I CAN SLEEP TONIGHT.
HONESTLY, I THINK THAT'S
AS MUCH STRESS RELIEF
AS ONE TEACHER CAN TAKE,
OKAY?
SEAN:
WHAT ARE YOU, WEAK?
COME ON, YOU GOTTA PUSH
THROUGH THE FEAR.
LET'S GO, TEN MORE!
SEAN, THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU'RE GONNA KILL ME HERE,
OKAY?
YOU CAN'T FAKE THIS!
ALL RIGHT?
YOU GOTTA DO IT!
YOU GOTTA TRAIN!
YOU GOTTA DO IT AGAIN
AND AGAIN AND AGAIN
UNTIL YOU'RE PERFECT!
OR YOU WILL DIE.
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?!
SEAN.
(TO HIMSELF)
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
SEAN. SEAN!
(HEAVY EXHALE)
(MUSIC PLAYS LOUDLY)
BELLA'S FAST ASLEEP.
ALISTAIR THE ANT
WORKS EVERY TIME.
ONLY BOOK I EVER LEARNED
BY HEART.
(LAUGHS)
YOU MAKE THE PARENTING THING
LOOK SO EASY.
IT'S NOT.
I KNOW, AND THAT'S WHY
YOU'RE AWESOME -
AND NEED A BREAK.
TO ONE FUN NIGHT.
WHAT'S A COUPLE OF HOURS
IN THE GRAND SCHEME
OF STUFF,
RIGHT?
(CANS CLINK)
(COUGHS)
THERE'S THE MIA
I USED TO KNOW!
WOW.
SIMPSON:
I WISH YOU'D TOLD ME
YOU WERE SHIPPING OUT
TO AFGHANISTAN.
THAT LITTLE OUTBURST
WOULD'VE...
I JUST...
I GUESS IT JUST HIT ME.
I'M SORRY.
IF YOU NEED TO TALK
ABOUT IT OR...
I'LL BE FINE.
JUST DON'T WORRY.
I'M...
I'M A GOOD SOLDIER.
I HAVE NO DOUBT
THAT YOU ARE.
I BET YOU'RE ONE
OF THE BEST.
I'M SCARED, SNAKE.
TERRIFIED.
YOU'RE WORKING THROUGH
YOUR FEARS
TO DO SOMETHING
THAT YOU FEEL
IS REALLY IMPORTANT.
I'M PROUD OF YOU.
IT'S A GOOD THING
YOU'RE A TEACHER.
YOU ALWAYS...
SAY THE RIGHT THING.
WELL, I HAD A LOT OF PRACTICE
ON A KID I USED TO KNOW.
HATED TEACHERS,
BUT UM...
HE WAS PRETTY GOOD AT GYM,
THOUGH.
YOU THINK HE TURNED OUT
OKAY?
MM-HMM.
(SNIFFS)
SMELLS LIKE A PARTY TO ME!
YEAH, GUESS WHO'S GONNA
HAVE TO CLEAN UP!
JANE:
OKAY, LET'S JUST GO TO MY ROOM.
SPINNER:
WOO.
OH, PRIVATE RENDEZ-VOUS,
HUH?
MAGNIFIQUE.
(MUSIC PLAYS LOUDLY,
PARTYGOERS CHATTER)
WOOO!
WHOA!
THE DRESS IS CUTE,
BUT...
I LIKE YOU
IN THE SPIRIT SQUAD SKIRT.
FUNNY, 'CUZ I LIKE YOU
IN ONE, TOO.
LUCAS:
FIND YOUR OWN HOTTIE, BRUCE.
THIS ONE HAS TASTE.
AND SOME PINT-SIZED BAGGAGE,
LAST TIME I CHECKED.
WHEN'S THE LAST TIME
YOU CHECKED ON THE TATER TOT,
BRITNEY?
BRUCE:
WE'LL GO TAKE A LOOK.
ANY EXCUSE TO TOUR
THE BEDROOMS.
NO, NO, NO.
I, I GOT IT!
LUCAS:
HEY, RELAX.
THEY'RE JOKING.
UH, NO, THEY'RE RIGHT.
UM...
I'LL JUST...
ONE MINUTE.
(MUSIC PLAYS,
PARTYGOERS CHATTER)
(SARCASTIC)
THANKS.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
(MUTED MUSIC AND CHATTER)
BELLA?
ISABEL-
HAS ANYONE SEEN MY DAUGHTER?
SHE'S SCARED.
AND SHE DIDN'T KNOW
WHERE THE BATHROOM WAS.
OR WHERE I WAS.
COME HERE, BABY.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
I'M TRYING TO BE A NORMAL
TEENAGER FOR ONCE
AND KIND OF SUCKING.
WHERE'S DADDY DORKWAD?
HE'S TRYING.
GIVE HIM A BREAK.
WAIT, HE'S DRUNK!
AND YOU SHOULD GET OUT
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT IS LATE.
(MUSIC PLAYS LOUDLY)
LUCAS:
WHAT'S SHE DOING UP?
PUT HER TO BED.
SHE'S GOTTA LEARN.
THAT HER DAD
WOULD RATHER PARTY
THAN TAKE CARE
OF HIS DAUGHTER?
WE'RE GONNA GO,
OKAY?
YOU'RE LETTING HER
RUIN OUR NIGHT?
IZZY COMES FIRST
EVERY TIME.
YOU GOTTA LEARN THAT.
OR NOT.
IT'S TOO HARD.
(DISAPPOINTED SIGH)
JANE:
HEY, UM, DO YOU NEED ANY HELP?
LIKE A RIDE?
I'M FINE.
REALLY? 'CUZ I CAN
CALL YOU A CAB...
I GOT IT, JANE.
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
OKAY?
LET'S GO, SWEETIE.
WE GOT A NOISE COMPLAINT.
AND I'LL BET NONE OF YOU
ARE OLD ENOUGH TO DRINK.
SO THIS PARTY IS OVER
OR WE PRESS CHARGES.
EVERYBODY OUT NOW.
THIS YOUR KID?
NO. IT'S HERS.
(AWKWARD CHUCKLE)
WE WERE JUST LEAVING.
FEMALE COP:
YOU'VE BEEN DRINKING.
WE HAVE TO REPORT THIS
TO CHILDREN'S AID.
NO, NO, NO.
PLEASE, PLEASE DON'T.
I HAVE A CHILDREN'S AID
SITUATION HERE.
YOUNG GIRL,
ABOUT THREE-YEARS-OLD,
FOUND HER IN A POTENTIALLY
DANGEROUS SITUATION;
I'LL HAVE TO FILE A REPORT.
SIMPSON:
HEY, EMMA, YOU GOTTA TAKE CARE
OF JACK TONIGHT.
EMMA:
AH, REALLY?!
SIMPSON:
YEAH. 'CAUSE WE HAVE A DATE.
EMMA:
SURE.
SIMPSON:
(LIQUID POURS, POTS CLANK)
SEAN:
(CLEARS THROAT)
SO, I, I THOUGHT UM...
THAT I'D LEAVE SOME THINGS
BEFORE I SHIP OUT,
'CUZ...
I GUESS IT'S YOU GUYS THAT
I'D WANNA COME BACK TO...
IF I COME BACK.
SIMPSON:
YOU WILL.
AND WE'LL BE WAITING.
I THOUGHT MAYBE WE COULD UH...
GET A NEW PHOTO OF US,
TO SHOW MY PLATOON.
OF COURSE.
SQUEEZE IN CLOSE.
GIVE ME THAT.
ALL RIGHT.
SMILING!
(LAUGHS)
(STREETCAR RUMBLES PAST)
WE'RE NOT INTERESTED
IN TAKING CHILDREN
FROM THEIR MOTHERS.
HOWEVER,
CUSTODY OF YOUR DAUGHTER
IS CONDITIONAL
ON SUPERVISION
BY CHILDREN'S AID.
SHE'S MY NUMBER ONE
PRIORITY.
I'LL DO WHATEVER IT TAKES.
WE'LL MAKE SURE,
TOGETHER.
ISABELLA'S FATHER
MUST SUBMIT
TO THE SAME TERMS,
IF HE'S INVOLVED.
IT'S JUST ME.