♪♪♪
NEW SEMESTER,
NEW HAIR?
I NEEDED A CHANGE.
THE ONLY THING WORSE
THAN GOING BACK TO SCHOOL
IS GOING BACK TO SCHOOL
IN WINTER.
EMMA:
WELL, EVERY STEP WE TAKE,
TAKES US ONE STEP CLOSER
TO GRADUATION.
SPINNER:
OH, FINAL COUNTDOWN DUDES.
EXACTLY 126 DAYS
'TIL GRADUATION -
GIVE OR TAKE.
WHY IS IT SO BUS-Y
AROUND HERE?
WELCOME TO THE NEW WORLD
OF DEGRASSI-LAKEHURST
COHABITATION.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
STUDENT:
UGH, WATCH IT!
HOW CAN THE PEOPLE
FROM THE SCHOOL
THAT KILLED JT
BE COMING HERE?
THEIR SCHOOL BURNS DOWN,
WE GET THEIR ASHES.
GREAT IDEA,
SCHOOL BOARD.
AND WHAT ARE THE CHANCES
THERE'LL BE A SINGLE
CUTE GUY?
WHAT? SORRY!
WELL, MAYBE SOMEONE NEW
WILL STEAL DARCY AWAY
FROM HIS EVIL HIGHNESS.
AND THE GRASSHOPPER SAID,
"WHAT, HAROLD?"
ALL:
(LAUGH)
HIS EVIL HIGHNESS
HAS BEEN DEFEATED
BY THE POWERS OF GOOD.
I.E. ME.
WE'RE IN LOVE
AND HE'S REFORMED.
I HAVE THAT EFFECT.
IF ANYONE COULD,
IT'S THE BLESSED VIRGIN,
DARCY.
PETER:
DARCY, WE'RE IN SCHOOL.
YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENS
IF MY MOM FINDS OUT.
LOOK AROUND, PETER.
YOUR MOM HAS BIGGER
THINGS ON HER MIND.
AND DO YOU REALLY THINK
THE PRINCIPAL
WOULD SEND HER SON
TO BOARDING SCHOOL?
YEAH, WELL,
WHY NOW?
WHAT'S THE RUSH?
YOU'RE HAPPY WE HAVE TO KEEP
OUR RELATIONSHIP A SECRET?
NAH, IT...
(EXHALES)
I'M USED TO IT.
PLUS, SNEAKING AROUND'S
KINDA HOT.
I'M STARTING
TO THINK
THAT YOU DON'T WANT PEOPLE
TO KNOW ABOUT US.
(GASPS)
(EXHALES)
♪♪♪
OKAY EVERYONE,
PLEASE GRAB A SEAT
SO WE CAN BEGIN.
UNTIL THE LAKEHURST
FIRE DAMAGE IS REPAIRED,
YOU'LL BE EXPERIENCING
A LITTLE LESS ELBOW ROOM.
NOW I KNOW,
AND I'M EXPECTING
ALL OF YOU
TO MAKE OUR NEW GUESTS
FEEL RIGHT AT HOME.
NOW DEGRASSI'S
HAD A LONG STANDING HISTORY
OF BEING A WELCOMING
AND NURTURING ENVIRONMENT...
SO...
WHY HAVEN'T WE TALKED?
ABOUT WHAT?
ABOUT WHOLESOME,
CHRISTIAN YOU
DATING DRUG-PLANTING,
STREET-RACING,
BLACKMAILING PETER?
AH, HELLO, MANNY?
RIGHT HERE.
I'M NOT THAT GUY ANYMORE.
THAT WAS THE OLD ME.
EXACTLY.
WHICH IS WHY
THERE'S NO REASON
TO KEEP OUR
RELATIONSHIP SECRET.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
SHOVE MY MOM OUT OF THE WAY
AND MAKE AN ANNOUNCEMENT?
FYI? I SAW YOU.
FLIRTING WITH THOSE GIRLS
FROM LAKEHURST.
AND IF YOU EVER
WALK OFF-
GUYS! SHHH!
DARCE, YOU'RE MY GIRL,
WHAT MORE PROOF
DO YOU NEED?
YOU'RE THE FORMER
CRIMINAL MASTERMIND.
THINK OF SOMETHING.
SIMPSON:
OFF TO CLASS, GUYS.
OFF TO CLASS.
AH, TOBY ISAACS,
READY FOR ONE LAST SEMESTER
AS MY DIGI-GURU?
JOHNNY:
DIGI-WIENER.
DIMARCO, RIGHT?
SOMETHING TO SAY?
NO, SIR.
REALLY?
'CUZ I HEARD SOMETHING.
SOUNDED IMPORTANT,
ACTUALLY.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
OFF TO CLASS, GUYS.
(STUDENTS CHATTER,
CELL PHONE RINGS)
CROWDED MUCH?
I FEEL OUT OF PLACE
IN MY OWN CAF'.
SO, HAS PETER
COME UP WITH A MASTER PLAN
FOR YOU TWO GOING PUBLIC,
YET?
NO. BUT IT WOULD
PROBABLY HELP
IF I COULD EVEN FIND THAT
CHARMING BOYFRIEND OF MINE.
I THINK I FOUND MINE.
(MUTED CHATTER)
HEY,
ARE THESE SEATS TAKEN?
UH, SIT HERE.
MANNY:
THANK YOU.
I'M, SAV,
BY THE WAY.
MANNY.
AND THIS IS, DARCY.
HEY.
JANE. HI.
I WAS JUST TELLIN' JANE
THAT WE SHOULD ROUND UP
SOME PEOPLE
AND GO SNOWBOARDING
THIS WEEKEND.
AND I WAS JUST TELLING SAV
THAT NOBODY'D BE
INTERESTED.
AH, WE MIGHT BE.
RIGHT, DARCY?
UH, SOUNDS LIKE
A BLAST OF COLD.
BESIDES,
I'VE GOT A CHURCH RETREAT.
(SMIRKS)
GOTTA GET YOUR BIBLE ON?
IT'S JUST HER
NEVER-ENDING SEARCH
FOR ETERNAL HAPPINESS.
HAS SHE CHECKED UNDER
HER EXTENSIONS?
DARCY:
UH! NO, BUT THERE IT IS
BEHIND YOUR GIGANTIC RUMP!
(CHUCKLES)
(FOOD AND TRAY CLATTER)
STUDENTS:
(STUNNED GASPS)
HATZILAKOS:
DARCY EDWARDS,
PLEASE REPORT TO THE PRINCIPLES
OFFICE IMMEDIATELY.
WAIT,
THAT'S YOU?
BUT YOU SEEM LIKE
SUCH A GOOD GIRL.
HMPH,
YOU BETTER CLEAN THAT UP.
LOVE OUR NEW GUESTS.
IS THIS BIT OF FILTH
TAKEN?
TRYING TO FEEL ME UP,
TOAD?
THIS IS OUR HALL,
THESE ARE OUR LOCKERS.
THESE ARE OUR...
CRAPPY MOTIVATIONAL POSTERS.
THEY HAVE NO RIGHT
TO TAKE THIS FROM US.
LAKEHURST WAS FORCED
TO COME HERE.
IT WASN'T
THEIR CHOICE.
SO YOU'RE OKAY WITH
JT'S KILLERS BEING HERE?
I FEEL A PODCAST
COMING ON.
I'M SERIOUS.
TOBES, I'M NEVER
GONNA BE OKAY
WITH THE FACT
THAT JT'S GONE,
BUT LAKEHURST
DIDN'T KILL HIM.
ONE PSYCHO DID
AND HE'S IN JAIL.
JOHNNY DIMARCO'S HERE.
HE WAS THERE
WHEN JT GOT STABBED
AND WHAT HAPPENS TO HIM?
NOTHING.
DR. MARTIN LUTHER KING SAID,
"RETURNING VIOLENCE
FOR VIOLENCE
MULTIPLIES VIOLENCE,
ADDING DEEPER DARKNESS
TO A NIGHT ALREADY
DEVOID OF STARS".
LET IT GO, TOBY.
(KNOCKS ON DOOR)
COME IN.
SO, PETER SAYS THERE'S
SOMETHING THAT YOU TWO
WANNA TELL ME?
MOM, UM...
YOU KNOW HOW I LIKE
KETCHUP ON MY BROCCOLI?
SHOULDN'T GO TOGETHER,
RIGHT?
UH, WELL THAT'S A LOT
LIKE ME AND DARCY.
WE'VE BEEN SORTA-
I THINK HE'S TRYING TO SAY
THAT WE'RE TOGETHER.
AND WE DON'T WANT KEEP IT
A SECRET ANY MORE.
HAVE YOUR PARENTS
GIVEN THEIR BLESSING?
OH, SURE,
AS LONG AS WE OBEY
THE RULE OF CHASTITY,
THEY'RE HAPPY.
WE WANT TO BE HONEST,
OR WHATEVER.
WELL, PETER'S, BEHAVIOUR
HAS TURNED AROUND
AND I THINK I KNOW WHY.
SO WHAT CAN I SAY?
HE'S A LUCKY KID.
(JOYFUL GASP)
BUT IF YOU GIVE ME
ANY REASON...
I'LL RECONSIDER.
OH, WE'LL BE ANGELS.
PROMISE.
(PHONE RINGS)
LAKEHURST STUDENT:
YOU WANNA MEET UP AT THE DOT?
THE DEGRASSI PLACE?
WHAT ARE YOU ON?
I'LL SEE YOU
AT THE BREAK ROOM.
LAKEHURST STUDENT:
ALL RIGHT.
SO, LAKEHURST BURNS
TO THE GROUND.
HOW APPROPRIATE.
BELIEVE ME,
I WISH I WERE ANYWHERE
BUT THIS DUMP.
YEAH,
THAT MAKES TWO OF US.
WAIT, YOU'RE THE GUY
WE ROLLED LAST SEMESTER.
AWE, MAN,
I'M OVER THAT, ALL RIGHT.
HOW 'BOUT A PEACE TREATY?
NOT UNLESS YOU SAY
YOU'RE SORRY.
FINE.
I'M SORRY I CALLED YOU
A DIGI-WIENER
AND KICKED YOUR ASS.
YOU STOOD THERE
WHILE YOUR FRIEND
STABBED MY FRIEND
TO DEATH.
(BASKETBALL BOUNCES,
SNEAKERS SQUEAK)
UM, IF WE'RE GOING
TO BE ONE SQUAD?
I NOMINATE MYSELF
AS CO-CAPTAIN.
(SARCASTIC HUFF)
PLEASE, JOB'S TAKEN.
WARM UPS, PEOPLE!
I HAVE AN ANNOUNCEMENT.
ARE YOU A VAMPIRE?
ME AND PETER,
WE'RE OFFICIAL.
AND HIS MOM IS TOTALLY COOL
WITH US BEING US.
THAT'S KIND OF AMAZING.
SO, YOU'RE OKAY
WITH IT, TOO?
AS LONG AS
YOU'RE HAPPY.
SPEAKING OF HAPPY?
I'M IN A SNOWBOARDING MOOD.
A SNOWBOARDING MOOD,
OR A SAV MOOD?
ALREADY WITH
THE BOY CRAZY?
SAV, SHMAV,
IT'LL BE FUN.
UNLESS DITCHING
CHURCH RETREAT
GETS YOU STRUCK
BY LIGHTNING?
EVEN IF I WERE TO RISK
DIVINE ELECTROCUTION?
IT WOULD BE
TO SPEND TIME HERE
WITH MY BOYFRIEND.
MRS. EDWARDS:
(SIGHS)
WHAT'S TAKING SO LONG?
WHERE'S DARCY?
CAN I HELP YOU?
UH, MY DAUGHTER'S
ON SPIRIT SQUAD.
CHAUFFEUR SERVICE,
YOU KNOW.
DARCY:
HI!
SORRY, I'M LATE!
AH, LET'S GO!
OH, I'M DAPHNE HATZILAKOS,
DARCY'S PRINCIPAL.
AND YOU KNOW MY SON,
PETER?
OH, WE KNOW YOUR SON.
HATZILAKOS:
GREAT, WELL,
I WAS HOPING WE'D MEET.
UM, DARCY'S NOT IN TROUBLE,
IS SHE?
OH, NO-NO,
BUT IF MY SON AND YOUR DAUGHTER
ARE GOING TO BE AN ITEM?
IT'S BEST THAT WE HAVE
EACH OTHER ON SPEED-DIAL.
OH, NO-NO-NO-NO-NO.
THERE MUST BE SOME
MISUNDERSTANDING.
DARCY,
IS NOT DATING YOUR SON.
MR. EDWARDS:
DARCY TOLD US HE LEFT HER
TO WALK HOME IN THE RAIN
AFTER BEING CITED FOR DRIVING
WITHOUT A LICENSE?
YES, AND I SEE
SHE SURVIVED.
MR. EDWARDS:
AND WHAT ABOUT
THOSE PHOTOS HE TOOK
AND SENT TO HIS PERVERTED
FRIENDS ON THE INTERNET?
THAT WAS HER IDEA.
HAZILAKOS:
LOOK, I KNOW
PETER IS NO ANGEL,
BUT I AM DOING MY BEST.
MS. HATZILAKOS,
I'M SURE YOUR SON IS A HANDFUL.
I CAN HANDLE MY SON,
MR. EDWARDS.
WELL, MAYBE IF YOU
AND MR. HATZILAKOS
WERE STILL TOGETHER...
MOM!
VERY NICE TO MEET YOU.
DARCY,
DO SOMETHING!
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
MRS. EDWARDS:
DARCY?
ARE YOU READY?
THE BUS IS LEAVING!
(CLEARS THROAT)
OUR MINIVAN
CAN GO WITHOUT ME.
NOBODY'S GOING ON
THE RETREAT WITHOUT YOU.
(COUGHS)
I THINK I'M COMING DOWN
WITH A COLD.
CAN'T I JUST STAY HOME?
MRS. EDWARDS:
BUT YOU ALWAYS HAVE
SO MUCH FUN
ON THE RETREAT.
I DON'T WANT TO
SPREAD MY GERMS
AND I HAVE HOMEWORK,
NEW CHEERS AND-
OH, I DON'T KNOW,
SWEETIE.
STAYING BY YOURSELF?
OVERNIGHT?
MOM, I'M SEVENTEEN!
(EXHALES)
OKAY.
YOU'VE GOT A GOOD HEAD
ON YOUR SHOULDERS.
AND WE TRUST YOU.
THANKS, MOM.
MRS. EDWARDS:
OKAY, REST UP.
WE'LL BE CHECKING IN;
YOU HAVE OUR NUMBERS.
AND WE'LL BE BACK LATER
TOMORROW AFTERNOON.
OKAY.
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
DARCY:
(HURRIED PANTING)
THERE YOU ARE,
ALL JUST IN TIME.
YEAH, I HAD TO WAIT
FOR MY PARENTS TO LEAVE.
I TAKE IT
THE CHURCHERSONS
AREN'T COOL WITH
UNSUPERVISED WINTER FUN?
THAT WOULD BE A "NO",
BUT YOU TAUGHT ME
EVERYTHING THERE IS TO KNOW
ABOUT CALL FORWARDING.
HAVE YOU SEEN PETER?
NO.
UGH, I HAVE VOICEMAIL.
AH, PETER, IT'S ME.
I'M ON MY WAY
TO MOUNT HURON.
THE NEXT BUS LEAVES
IN AN HOUR,
PLEASE COME.
I PROMISE I'LL MAKE IT
WORTH YOUR WHILE.
HURRY UP!
IF LAKEHURST CAST-OFFS
LIKE JOHNNY DIMARCO
THINK THAT I'M GONNA
PERSONALLY
WELCOME THEM TO DEGRASSI?
WAKE UP!
IT AIN'T GONNA HAPPEN!
AND IF ANYONE
HAS A PROBLEM WITH THAT?
REMEMBER:
NOBODY MESSES WITH TOBY ISAACS.
(PROGRESS BAR BEEPS)
♪♪♪
HERE.
WEDGE YOUR FOOT IN.
UGH, I'VE NEVER
DONE THIS BEFORE.
I'M GONNA BREAK
MY NECK.
IT'S NOT AS SCARY
AS IT LOOKS, OKAY.
IF YOU LEARN NOW,
YOU'LL NEVER FORGET.
RIGHT FOOT FIRST?
ARE YOU GOOFY?
NEVER MIND.
(SMIRKS)
HEY, UM,
KILLER PARTY TONIGHT.
GUARANTEED RAGER,
IF YOU'RE STICKING AROUND
'TIL THE LAST BUS.
HUH, FUNNY,
I WAS JUST WONDERING
WHEN THE NEXT BUS LEAVES
TO GO HOME.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
STOP TOUCHING.
(PHONE RINGS)
PETER?
THANK GOSH!
I'M SO SORRY I COULDN'T
STAND UP TO MY PARENTS.
PLEASE JUST TELL ME YOU'RE
NOT CALLING TO BREAK UP.
WELL, YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S
SUPPOSED TO HAVE FAITH.
DARCY:
OH! YOU MADE IT!
YEAH, I PULLED
THE MOM'S HOUSE/DAD'S HOUSE
SHELL GAME.
YOU SAID YOU'D MAKE IT
WORTH MY WHILE.
AND DID YOU HEAR ABOUT
THE PARTY TONIGHT?
PETER:
YEAH. BONUS!
MANNY:
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
I'M NOT HELPING YOU ANYMORE.
♪♪♪
(HOCKEY STICKS CLANK)
LIBERTY:
TOBY!
"LAKEHURST ARE BUNCH OF MOUTH
BREATHING NEANDERTHALS?"
I COULDN'T AGREE MORE.
I HEARD YOUR PODCAST.
HOW IS NAME-CALLING
SUPPOSED TO HELP?
IT'S NOT NAME-CALLING.
IT'S SCIENTIFIC CLASSIFICATION.
I WAS GOING TO ASK YOU
TO HEAD UP
THE INTEGRATION COMMITTEE,
BUT YOUR PERSONAL VENDETTA
ISN'T HELPING.
YEAH WELL, MAYBE SOME PEOPLE
DON'T WANT TO INTEGRATE.
LIBERTY:
(SIGHS)
CAR.
(ENGINE WHIRS)
DANNY:
CHECK IT.
LAKEHURST NINERS.
WANNA GO BUST HEADS?
LATER, OKAY?
IS THIS WHAT YOU WANT?
AN ONGOING WAR.
YOU REMEMBER HOW THAT ENDED
LAST TIME.
(HOCKEY STICKS CLANK)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
(CHATTER)
MANNY:
DITCHING THE CHURCH RETREAT.
LYING TO YOUR PARENTS.
SNEAKING OUT.
YOU KNOW,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO COMMIT
ALL SEVEN DEADLY SINS
IN ONE NIGHT.
HEY, I'M NOT DRINKING,
AM I?
BESIDES, NONE OF THIS
WOULD BE NECESSARY
IF MY PARENTS
HADN'T BANNED ME
FROM SEEING PETER.
WHEN WILL PARENTS
EVER LEARN?
FORBIDDING THINGS
IS AN APHRODISIAC.
(GIGGLES)
TOTALLY.
(PARTY MUSIC CONTINUES)
(DISGUSTED GROAN)
DARCY:
FINALLY I HAVE YOU
ALL TO MYSELF.
PETER:
AND THERE'S NOTHING
OUR PARENTS CAN DO ABOUT IT.
DARCY:
UGH. YOU WERE RIGHT.
THIS WHOLE SNEAKING AROUND
BEHIND THEIR BACKS THING?
IT IS KINDA HOT.
WE'RE GOOD.
(PASSIONATE KISSING)
(HEAVY KISSING)
(UNCOMFORTABLE SMIRK)
WHOA, SLOW DOWN.
YOU KNOW THE "ABOVE-THE-WAIST"
RULE, PETER.
JUST RELAX.
I'M NOT COMFORTABLE
WITH THIS.
WHAT HAPPENED TO "I'LL MAKE IT
WORTH YOUR WHILE"?
I MEANT I'D BUY
YOUR LIFT TICKET, STUPID!
YOU KNOW I TOOK A VOW
OF ABSTINENCE.
YEAH, THE PROBLEM IS,
I DIDN'T.
UGH...
GET OUT.
COME ON, DARCY.
OUT!
ALL RIGHT,
I'M SORRY.
MY PARENTS WERE SO RIGHT
ABOUT YOU!
(EXHALES)
(TRAFFIC WHIRS BY)
(POOL BALLS CLANK)
JOHNNY:
COMING HERE ALONE?
THAT'S BRAVE...
OR STUPID.
MAYBE BOTH.
LOOK, JOHNNY,
I DON'T WANT TO START A WAR.
AND I THINK AS LONG AS
WE'RE UNDER THE SAME ROOF
WE SHOULD TRY TO GET ALONG.
THAT'S NOT WHAT
PODCAST TOBY SAID.
YEAH,
WE'VE ALL HEARD IT.
AND NOW BEFORE SOMEONE
MESSES WITH YOU?
I SUGGEST YOU BUST
OUTTA HERE.
LOOK,
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND!
I WANT TO TAKE YOU UP
ON YOUR PEACE TREATY.
TREATY'S OFF THE TABLE,
WIENER.
I'LL SEE YOU AT SCHOOL.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
(LIVELY CHATTER OF PARTYGOERS)
CHURCH RETREAT,
SMURCH RETREAT.
AREN'T YOU GLAD
WE CAME UP HERE?
NOT REMOTELY.
EASY, TIGER, BUS LEAVES
IN HALF AN HOUR.
YOU WERE RIGHT, YOU KNOW -
ABOUT FORBIDDING THINGS.
JUST NOW,
IN THE BEDROOM;
PETER WAS TRYING
TO MAKE ME DO THINGS.
ISN'T THE RULE OF ABSTINENCE
SUPPOSED TO MAKE LIFE EASIER?
(SIGHS)
IT'S NOT A RULE.
I'M NOT READY.
I WANT TO WAIT
UNTIL I'M MARRIED.
BUT I'M NOT LIKE YOU,
MANNY.
WITH NO VALUES,
NO SELF-RESPECT.
WELL, IF YOU'RE GONNA GET OFF
ON YOUR HIGH-HORSE,
THEN I'M GONE.
YOU AND SATAN JR.
ARE MADE FOR EACH OTHER.
(MUSIC PLAYS)
(LIVELY CHATTER)
(BANGS ON DOOR)
I HAVE TO PEE!
SAV:
HEY, MAN.
GETTIN' YOUR SHINE ON?
WHATEVER, MAN.
SUE ME.
(BOTTLES CLANK)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
I'M A JACKASS.
SORRY. JACK-BUTT.
(LAUGHS)
HOW WASTED
ARE YOU?
(SLURRED SPEECH)
I ONLY HAS ONE DRINK,
JACK-ASS!
OOH, SAUCY!
YOU'RE A BAD
LIAR THOUGH.
EVEN WORSE
WHEN YOU'RE DRUNK.
(EXHALES)
LET'S NOT...
LET'S NOT FIGHT
ANY MORE, OKAY?
DEAL.
PINKIE SWEAR?
WE CAN GO DO IT
IF YOU WANT.
DO WHAT?
WHATEVER.
ANYTHING YOU WANT.
CAN I TELL YOU
A SECRET?
I'M A VIRGIN TOO.
BUT I DON'T CARE,
YOU KNOW.
I'LL...
WAIT 'TIL WHENEVER.
'CUZ... I LOVE YOU.
AND I'M GONNA BARF.
(MUSIC BLARES)
TOBY:
(SNIFFLES)
HEY, JT.
I KNOW YOU'RE BUSY,
BUT UM,
IF I HAD ANYONE ELSE
TO TALK TO, I WOULD.
(SIGHS)
I MISS YOU, JT.
AND I KNOW VIOLENCE
JUST MULTIPLIES VIOLENCE
IN THE DEEP,
DARK SOMETHING,
BUT... (SIGHS)
IT SUCKS THAT THE LAKEHURST
PEOPLE ARE IN OUR HALLS
AND YOU'RE NOT.
IT-IT'S, IT'S NOT FAIR.
BUT MAYBE WITH SO MANY
NEW PEOPLE AT DEGRASSI,
MAYBE THERE'S SOMEONE
LIKE YOU.
AND AS THEY SAY,
"STRANGERS ARE JUST FRIENDS
YOU HAVEN'T MET YET."
(PROGRESS BAR BEEPS)
PARTYGOERS:
(CHATTER)
(WOOZY GROAN)
(DOORKNOB AND LOCK CLICK)
(SLEEPY SIGH)