I COULD GET USED TO THIS
BABYSITTING GIG.
JACK IN BED,
YOUR PARENTS
ON THEIR DATE.
TOO BAD YOU NEED
TO SNEAK OUT
AS SOON AS THEY GET HOME.
YEAH.
SCHOOL BOARD POLICY.
ONLY UNTIL MY DAD'S NAME
IS CLEARED.
SIMPSON:
WELL, WHAT DO YOU EXPECT
WHEN THEY-
OH MY GOD! THEY'RE HOME EARLY,
YOU SHOULD...
YUP.
THAT'S MY CUE.
SPIKE:
POOR YOU.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO BE SO RUDE
TO THAT WAITER.
SIMPSON:
I WASN'T RUDE.
HIS SNOTTY ATTITUDE REMINDS ME
OF WHY I COOK AT HOME.
(SNORTED CHUCKLE)
HIS ATTITUDE?
OR YOUR PARANOIA?
OH, RIGHT,
BECAUSE I IMAGINE EVERYTHING.
LIKE BEING FALSELY ACCUSED
OF SEXUAL ASSAULT, MAYBE, HM?
HAVE FUN ON YOUR DATE?
IT'S NOTHING, EMMA.
WE'RE FINE.
(HOME PHONE RINGING)
THAT'S YOUR RING.
HELLO?
SPEAKING.
RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
THAT WAS MY LAWYER.
SO...
WHAT HAS TWO THUMBS
AND IS OFFICIALLY
NOT A PEDOPHILE?
THIS GUY!
EMMA:
YOU'VE BEEN CLEARED?
THAT'S AMAZING!
(EXCITED SQUEALS
AND CHUCKLES)
SEE? I TOLD YOU
STAY POSITIVE,
BUT DID YOU BELIEVE ME?
ALL:
(EXCITED LAUGHTER)
WOO HOO HOO!
ALL:
(LAUGHING)
♪♪♪
STUDENTS:
(LIVELY OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
(CLEANSING EXHALE)
NEW DAY, FRESH START,
AND THE SWEET SMELL
OF VINDICATION.
IT'S THE PARKING LOT,
NOT THE GREEN MILE.
(AMUSED)
I'M FINE.
LUCAS:
MR. S., THEY LETTING YOU
RUN LOOSE?
NICE TO SEE YOU TOO, LUCAS.
(UNDER HIS BREATH)
A-PERV-SAYS-WHAT?
WHAT?
(LAUGHING)
THEY'RE LOSERS.
JUST IGNORE THEM.
LUCAS:
WHAT A BURN. CLASSIC.
UM, MAYBE IT'S TOO SOON,
EMMA.
WELL, WHAT'LL PEOPLE THINK
IF YOU CHICKEN OUT?
WON'T THAT BE WORSE?
I'M SORRY, EMMA.
I...
I'M NOT CONVINCED
I BELONG AT DEGRASSI ANYMORE.
WELL, WHAT CAN I DO
TO CONVINCE YOU?
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
YOU'D BETTER GET TO CLASS.
UM, I'M GONNA CALL MS. H.
ARMSTRONG:
MOST OF YOU DID VERY WELL,
BUT FOR THOSE
WHO ARE HAVING TROUBLE,
YOU KNOW THE ANSWER -
TUTORING WORKS!
EIGHTY-FIVE?
I SO CRAMMED FOR THIS!
AMAZING!
ANYA:
EIGHT-SIX PERCENT.
HOLLY J,
HOW DID YOU DO?
ANYA, FOR MY SAKE,
COULD YOU AT LEAST TRY TO STOP
BEING BORING?
LET'S FIGURE OUT
WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO TONIGHT.
OH. UM...
DIDN'T I TELL YOU?
SAV AND I ARE GOING OUT.
MIA:
LUCAS IS TAKING ISABELLA
AND ME FOR PIZZA.
WE COULD SO DOUBLE!
HOLLY J:
"WE COULD DOUBLE!"
UGH.
GREASY FOOD
AND GREASY COMPANY?
TRY TO AIM UP, GIRLS.
ALTHOUGH CONSIDERING
THE "BOYS" IN QUESTION,
YOU'RE DOING
THE BEST YOU CAN.
SOMEBODY'S SINGLE
AND BITTER!
SOMEBODY'S BABY DADDY'S
A NEANDERTHAL!
ANYA:
HOLLY J, YOU CAN COME TOO.
JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE SINGLE,
IT WON'T BE WEIRD.
(SCOFFS)
GOT BETTER THINGS TO DO,
THANKS.
MIA:
LIKE WHAT?
A BIG SOLITAIRE TOURNAMENT?
HOLLY J:
OH, MIA.
WHEN DO YOU SHOOT YOUR PILOT
FOR THE NOT FUNNY NETWORK?
(SARCASTIC LAUGHTER)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
(STAMMERING)
I CAN LEAVE,
IF YOU WANT.
ACTUALLY,
I WAS LOOKING FOR YOU.
NOT TO KILL ME,
I HOPE?
NO, DARCY.
I AM SO SORRY
FOR PUTTING YOUR FAMILY
THROUGH ALL THIS.
I KNOW YOU'VE BEEN
THROUGH A LOT.
IT'S NO EXCUSE
FOR FALSELY ACCUSING
YOUR DAD.
I WAS...
I WAS IN A BAD PLACE
AND I PANICKED
AND...
IT'S OKAY.
HE'S BEEN CLEARED,
OFFICIALLY.
THE SCHOOL BOARD CALLED.
THAT'S AMAZING!
WHEN'S HE COMING BACK?
THAT'S THE THING.
I DON'T THINK HE WANTS TO.
WHAT? WHY?
HE'S NOT SURE HE BELONGS
AT DEGRASSI ANYMORE,
THAT EVERYONE WILL
WANT HIM BACK.
HE'S SUCH A GREAT TEACHER,
OF COURSE THEY WILL!
EXACTLY.
THAT IS WHERE YOU COME IN.
ANYTHING.
I'LL DO IT.
EMMA:
SHOW MR. SIMPSON
HOW MUCH YOU MISS HIM!
SHOW ONE OF DEGRASSI'S BEST
HOW MUCH YOU CARE!
WHERE DO I SIGN?
EMMA:
ANYWHERE.
THANKS, MANNY.
AND I'LL SIGN ANOTHER NAME
WITH MY LEFT HAND.
MRS. JAY HOGART.
HAVE FUN EXPLAINING
THAT ONE TO HIM.
GET SIMPSON BACK TO DEGRASSI!
HEY, YOU GUYS,
DO WANT TO SIGN
SIMPSON'S CARD?
SHOW HIM YOUR SUPPORT?
LUCAS:
SO WE CAN HAVE A PEDOPHILE
IN OUR SCHOOL?
NO THANKS.
IF HE GOT ANYWHERE
NEAR MY KID...
YOU HAVE A KID?
OH.
OHHH...
MR. SIMPSON
IS NOT A PEDOPHILE.
YOU'RE HIS STEPDAUGHTER.
YOU HAVE TO DEFEND HIM.
I'M DEFENDING HIM TOO.
OKAY, YOU SAID THAT
HE DID SOMETHING,
THEN YOU SAID HE DIDN'T.
IT'S HARD TO KNOW
WHAT'S THE TRUTH.
SORRY.
WE KNOW THE TRUTH.
(SIGHS)
YEAH.
LIBERTY:
AND REMEMBER, YEARBOOKS
DON'T SELL THEMSELVES!
TO THINK,
IN A FEW WEEKS,
MY ROLE WILL BE ENTRUSTED
TO ONE OF THESE INFANTS.
LITTLE SINCLAIR
COULD BE YOUR HEIR.
LIBERTY:
PERISH THE THOUGHT.
EEEK. I THINK SHE SAW ME.
GOOD LUCK!
(VOICE TRAILING OFF)
WAIT, LIBERTY DON'T
LEAVE ME WITH HER...
TOBY ISAACS, RIGHT?
I NEED TO ASK YOU
SOMETHING.
FANTASTIC.
I NEED... HELP,
IN MATH.
MY SISTER SAID
YOU'RE THE NERDIEST...
I MEAN, THE BEST TUTOR.
HEATHER SINCLAIR
SAID THAT?
AMONG OTHER THINGS.
LOOK, I HAVE CASH.
IN OR OUT?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
FORGET THE MONEY.
HOW 'BOUT
I SCRATCH YOUR BACK,
YOU SCRATCH MINE?
OH, GOD.
SPIKE:
WHAT IS IT GOING TO TAKE,
ARCHIE?
YOU'VE SEEN HOW WORKED UP
EMMA IS.
SIMPSON:
I KNOW, BUT IT'S NOT
ABOUT HER.
SPIKE:
IT'S AFFECTING HER!
CAN'T YOU SEE SHE'S TRYING
TO CONTROL THINGS?
SIMPSON:
DON'T BLAME ME, OKAY?!
SPIKE:
YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENS, ARCHIE.
SHE'S A RECOVERING ANOREXIC!
SIMPSON:
ALL RIGHT.
IF I GO BACK,
HOW AM I GONNA SAVE FACE,
HUH? HOW?
YOU JUST DO IT.
I HAD TO,
IF YOU REMEMBER?
ARE YOU GONNA BRING UP
MY 30 SECONDS OF STUPIDITY
WITH DAPHNE
OVER AND OVER AGAIN?
WELL, IT DEPENDS.
ARE YOU GONNA TELL ME
THE REAL REASON
YOU'RE AFRAID
TO GO BACK?
WHAT?!
I MOLESTED A STUDENT? HMM?
IF I'M SOME KIND
OF SEXUAL PREDATOR?
SPIKE:
NO! BUT MAYBE...
MAYBE YOU WEREN'T
CAREFUL ENOUGH.
I MEAN, ARE YOU SURE
YOU DIDN'T GIVE THE GIRL
THE WRONG IDEA?
SIMPSON:
I DID NOTHING WRONG, SPIKE!
HOW CAN YOU EVEN
ASK ME THAT?!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
GET SOME AIR.
(DOOR SHUTS)
OKAY, SO JUST INSERT
THE Y VALUE,
AND... VOILA!
IF ARMSTRONG HAD
TAUGHT IT LIKE THAT,
MAYBE I'D UNDERSTAND IT.
YEAH, WELL,
ARMSTRONG WOULD HAVE
TO LEARN IT HIMSELF, FIRST.
DON'T YOU HATE BEING
SUCH A MATHLETE?
IT'S ALL RELATIVE.
I MEAN, I'D HATE TO GO UP
AND BOUNCE AROUND
IN FRONT OF THE WHOLE SCHOOL
EVERY WEEK,
BUT YOU LOVE IT.
SPIRIT SQUAD?
IT'S REALLY THE ONLY TIME
YOU'RE NOT SCOWLING.
WELL, TEN YEARS OF JAZZ
AND FIVE YEARS OF TAP
TAUGHT ME
TO SAVE YOUR SMILES
FOR WHEN THEY COUNT.
SO DO I GET ONE
FOR GETTING YOU THROUGH
YOUR NEXT MATH TEST?
WHEN I ACE IT.
(LAUGHS)
SO I BELIEVE
WE HAD A DEAL.
I'M NOT GIVING YOU
MY UNDERWEAR.
GOOD.
(STAMMERS)
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD
OF DANCE DANCE REVOLUTION?
SERIOUSLY?
YEAH.
YOU'RE BACK.
THANK YOU
FOR DOING THIS.
THREE HUNDRED REASONS
TO GO BACK TO DEGRASSI.
SO, WILL I SEE YOU
TOMORROW?
I DON'T THINK SO.
JUST SUCK IT UP, SNAKE!
THEY WANT YOU BACK.
I KNOW THIS HAS BEEN
HARD FOR YOU.
EVERYTHING AT SCHOOL
AND...
EMMA:
NO, IT'S NOT JUST THAT.
IT'S...
YOU'RE SLEEPING ON THE COUCH.
IS IT THAT BAD
BETWEEN YOU AND MOM?
HOW WORRIED SHOULD I BE?
SIMPSON:
LISTEN,
TOMORROW,
I'LL GO BACK TO WORK.
ALL RIGHT?
AND THIS WILL ALL START
TO GET BETTER.
EMMA:
IT BETTER.
GOOD NIGHT.
(EGGERS WHINES)
(CAR RUMBLES PAST,
LOW HUM OF STUDENT CHATTER)
(UNINTELLIGIBLE
PA ANNOUNCEMENT)
MANNY:
HEY! YOU'RE BACK!
CAN'T A GUY TEACH
SOME IMMERSION,
MEDIA-STYLES?
EMMA:
SURPRISE!
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME
HE WAS BACK?
WE MISSED YOU SO MUCH!
OH! OKAY.
NO TOUCHING!
THAT'S THE KIND OF STUFF
THAT GOT ME IN THIS MESS.
RIGHT. SORRY.
SEE? IT'S NOT SO BAD.
I BELIEVE IT'S WHAT
THE KIDS CALL...
"SUCKING IT UP".
SO THE STUDENT
BECOMES THE TEACHER.
NOT FOR LONG.
TAKE A SEAT, MS. NELSON.
VIDEO GAME:
(MUSIC PLAYS)
AWWW, TO BAD!
VIDEO GAME:
TRY HARDER!
FORGET IT!
YOU'RE HOPELESS!
YEAH, WELL,
IF I DON'T NAIL THIS
THEN I FLUNK PHYS ED,
SO...
(HUFFS)
SERIOUSLY!
FORWARD. RIGHT.
LEFT. RIGHT.
BOTH.
FORWARD.
BACKWARDS.
NO, OTHER BACKWARD!
(GAME ENDS)
SOME THINGS SHOULD BE DONE
IN THE PRIVACY OF THE HOME.
YEAH, IT DOES KIND OF GIVE
A WHOLE NEW MEANING
TO "DANCE LIKE NOBODY'S
WATCHING".
TOBY:
(LAUGHS)
WHY IS SOMETHING
THAT'S SO HARD FOR ME
SO EASY FOR EVERYONE ELSE?
HEY,
STORY OF MY LIFE.
WHEN HEATHER WAS HERE,
SHE WAS SMART
AND POPULAR AND CUTE.
YEAH, WELL,
NOW YOU'RE HERE.
YOU'RE FILLING HER SHOES.
ANYA:
HOLLY J?
YOU COMING TO FRENCH?
I TRY TO HELP
AND YOU GROPE ME?
YOU, MR. SIMPSON...
WHAT IS IT WITH YOU DIGI-PERVS?
LOOKS LIKE YOU'LL BE
FAILING P.E., TOAD.
YEAH. I GET IT.
(SIGHS)
SIMPSON:
NOW THE LESSON HERE IS,
NEVER UNDERESTIMATE
THE POWER OF THE STUDENT.
(STIFLED SNORT)
HE SHOULD KNOW.
SIMPSON:
...FACEBOOK, GOOGLE -
ALL CREATED BY STUDENTS.
HAVE YOU EVER SEARCHED
YOUR NAME, MR. S.?
UM... NOT RECENTLY.
LUCAS:
WELL, THERE'S A WEBPAGE.
YOU SHOULD CHECK IT OUT.
CLOSE IT, LUCAS.
SIMPSON:
EMMA.
I CAN HANDLE THIS.
YOU GET YOURSELF DOWN
TO HATZILAKOS.
WHAT? I WAS JUST...
SIMPSON:
I SAID NOW!
LOOKS LIKE
SHE CAME TO ME.
YOU STAY PUT.
I'LL DEAL WITH YOU IN A MINUTE.
EVERYTHING OKAY?
EVERYTHING'S FINE.
FIRST DAY BACK.
MUST BE A LOT OF PRESSURE.
I'M OKAY.
REALLY.
UM, ONE THING THOUGH.
THE UH...
THE CLASS LIST?
LEE CROFTON,
SHE-SHE ISN'T ON IT.
SHE DECIDED TO WITHDRAW.
DO I NEED TO ASK WHY?
HER PARENTS DIDN'T GIVE
A REASON.
BUT THEY DIDN'T HAVE TO.
I GUESS I CAN'T BLAME THEM,
CAN I?
I MEAN, IF I WERE IN
THEIR SHOES, I...
THEY DON'T KNOW YOU,
ARCHIE.
I DO,
AND I KNOW YOU WON'T
LET THIS GET TO YOU.
(WITHDRAWING FOOTSTEPS)
HOLLY J:
HEY! HOW WAS THE TEST?
TOBY:
YOU'RE TALKING TO ME?
JUST AS LONG AS NO ONE'S
AROUND, RIGHT?
OTHERWISE,
SOCIAL SUICIDE.
STOP BEING SO POUTY.
THINK YOU'RE THE FIRST GIRL
TO PULL A STUNT LIKE THIS?
WELL, EXCUSE ME FOR HAVING
A REPUTATION TO PROTECT!
PROTECT?
FROM WHOM?
FOR WHO.
I NEED TO BE HOLLY J. SINCLAIR
FOR MY FRIENDS.
REALLY?
IF THINK IF YOU DROPPED
THE BITCH ACT,
THEY'D ACTUALLY LIKE YOU.
I MIGHT.
OH, AND BY THE WAY,
IT'S "FOR WHOM".
(OBJECTS CLATTER)
EMMA:
I HEARD A CRASH?
I DROPPED SOME ICE.
IT'S 3:00
IN THE MORNING.
I KNOW.
GO BACK TO BED.
DON'T BELIEVE EVERYTHING
YOU SEE ON THE INTERNET.
ISN'T THAT WHAT YOU TEACH US
ON DAY ONE?
SOMETIMES THE HTML
DOESN'T LIE.
WOW. SO THAT'S IT?
IF I'D KNOWN GOING
BACK TO DEGRASSI
WOULD MAKE YOU THIS CRAZY,
I NEVER WOULD HAVE MADE
THAT STUPID CARD.
(SNORTS) I'M NOT TRYING
TO DISAPPOINT YOU.
THEN DON'T.
JUST GO BACK TO WORK
TOMORROW.
THAT'S ALL IT TAKES.
OKAY. I WILL.
GOOD NIGHT.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
PERINO:
MR. SIMPSON CAN'T MAKE IT
TODAY.
I WILL BE COVERING FOR HIM
AGAIN.
EMMA:
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHERE IS HE?
PERINO:
I DON'T ASK QUESTIONS.
SO, I BELIEVE WE HAVE WHAT?
PHOTO ESSAYS,
ACCORDING TO MR. SIMPSON'S
LESSON PLAN NUMBER 117.
(HUM OF STUDENTS CHATTERING)
NEVER FORGET
I'M A GENIUS, ANYA.
WOW!
SURE LOOKS LIKE
THAT TUTORING PAID OFF.
YOU'RE LIKE THE TOBY
OF OUR CLASS.
ANYA, DO YOU REALIZE
HOW DUMB
SOME OF THE THINGS
YOU SAY ARE?
SORRY.
YOU'RE NOTHING LIKE TOBY.
HE'S DISGUSTING.
(SIGHS)
OH, ANYA.
HE'S NOT DISGUSTING.
HE'S...
GEEK CHIC.
HE MIGHT BE RICH ONE DAY,
LIKE BILL GATES.
OKAY, SO WE LIKE HIM...
NOW THEN?
TRY TO KEEP UP,
ANYA.
WE MIGHT LIKE HIM,
YES.
OKAY.
TV ANNOUNCER:
THIS IS (UNCLEAR) SPORTS
WEEKEND SPECTACULAR
DEMOLITION DERBY IN A ROW.
HE'S GOT TWO-THIRDS
OF THE SECOND PLACE...
PERFECT!
DON'T GO TO WORK.
STAY HOME AND GET WASTED!
AND WATCH CARS
SMASH INTO EACH OTHER.
IT'S AWESOME.
YOU'RE A COWARD.
(MUTTERING WITH HIS MOUTH FULL)
THIS MORNING,
I GOT UP AND GRABBED MY LAPTOP
AND I TIRED -
BECAUSE YOU WANTED ME TO -
AND I COULDN'T EVEN GET OUT
THE DOOR.
WHAT IF MOM SEES YOU
LIKE THIS?
WELL, MAYBE SHE NEEDS TO.
HM?
FINE.
WALLOW IN SELF-PITY.
YOU KNOW, WHEN BAD THINGS
HAPPEN TO ME,
YOU TELL ME TO BE STRONG.
BUT YOU'RE NOT STRONG,
YOU'RE A HYPOCRITE.
MAYBE. I'M SORRY.
(DOOR OPENS)
SPIKE:
ARCHIE?
WHAT IS THIS?
IT'S FINE, MOM.
ARE YOU DRUNK?
I'M SORRY,
I FAILED YOU GUYS.
YOU DIDN'T FAIL.
YOU GAVE UP.
TRYING TO RUN AWAY
FROM YOUR PROBLEMS.
THE KIDS SHOULDN'T SEE THIS.
LOOK, I'LL BE FINE,
CHRISTINE, OKAY?
I JUST NEEDED A DAY
TO GET MY HEAD ON STR...
(BOWL CLATTERS)
(EGGERS WHINES)
I THINK THE KIDS AND I
SHOULD GO STAY WITH MY MOM
FOR A WHILE.
MOM, DON'T OVERREACT.
SPIKE:
EMMA, I'M YOUR MOTHER,
AND BEING AROUND THIS...
THIS ENVIRONMENT,
I JUST THINK WE MIGHT NEED
SOME TIME AWAY.
(STUDENTS CHATTER,
BUS RUMBLES PAST)
WELL, MY TEST
WAS A SUCCESS,
ALL THANKS
TO MY SUPER TUTOR.
A LITTLE PRIVACY FROM
YOUR MAN-MADE FIBRES, PLEASE?
MY PLEASURE.
I'LL LET YOU GUYS "TALK".
LISTEN,
WE CAN BE SEEN TOGETHER;
IT'S OUT IN THE OPEN.
SOME PEOPLE THINK
I'M KIND OF A LOSER,
AND UNTIL - WHAT? -
LIKE TEN SECONDS AGO,
WEREN'T YOU ONE OF THEM?
WELL, I CHANGED MY MIND.
LOWERED MY STANDARDS
'CAUSE I LIKE YOU.
(INCREDULOUS LAUGH)
WRONG ANSWER, HOLLY J.
IT WOULD BE SO SWEET
TO HAVE A GIRLFRIEND,
BUT IT JUST CAN'T BE YOU.
NO, YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I MADE EVERYTHING OKAY!
I TOLD MY FRIENDS.
I DON'T CARE WHO YOU TOLD.
THIS ISN'T ABOUT YOU,
IT'S ABOUT ME.
AND YOUR POOR
SELF-ESTEEM?
GET OVER IT, TOBY.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT YOU THINK.
IF PEOPLE SEE YOU WITH ME,
THEY'LL WORSHIP YOU.
NOT THE PEOPLE
I CARE ABOUT.
WHO, LIBERTY?
PLEASE.
LOOK, YOU HAD YOUR SHOT
WITH ME
AND YOU BLEW IT.
TOBY ISAACS
CALLS THE SHOTS.
ANYA, COME OVER TONIGHT.
I DON'T CARE.
DITCH HIM.
WE NEED TO TALK ABOUT THIS
DISTURBING NEW DEPENDENCE
ON BOYS.
DIDN'T EXPECT YOU
TO BE UP.
I'D, UH, WALLOWED IN SELF-PITY
LONG ENOUGH.
SO ARE YOU GONNA
TRY AGAIN?
I DO WANT TO GO BACK,
YOU KNOW.
BUT NOT YET.
I THOUGHT I COULD DO THIS
ON MY OWN, BUT UH...
I CAN'T.
THE UNION HAS COUNSELORS,
SO, UM...
WE'RE GONNA TALK.
WHERE'S YOUR BAG?
COME ON, EM,
PACK YOUR THINGS.
LET'S GO.
I'M NOT GOING.
SIMPSON:
UM...
YOU DON'T HAVE TO STAY,
EMMA.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN,
BUT I CAN'T JUST STAND BY
AND WATCH OUR FAMILY
FALL APART.
EM, YOU NEED TO TAKE CARE
OF YOURSELF.
I KNOW, YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT ME
TRYING TO CONTROL THINGS.
BUT THE ONE THING I CAN DO
IS STAY HERE,
AND SO CAN YOU.
I'M SORRY, EMMA,
BUT I NEED TO TAKE CARE
OF MYSELF TOO.
I'LL CALL YOU TONIGHT.
YOUR MOM AND I,
WE JUST...
WE NEED SOME TIME.
THANKS FOR STAYING
WITH ME.
I BELIEVE IN YOU,
DAD.
DON'T MAKE ME
REGRET IT.