♪ I'd chase the whale
on the run ♪
♪ But I'm... ♪
SPIN.
SPINNER.
WHAT ARE YOU
LISTENING TO?
OH, UM...
MAYBE CRAIG'S ALBUM?
DON'T HIT ME.
OH MY GOD,
IT DROPPED YESTERDAY?
LOOK,
HE'S SO AWKWARD POSING!
TOBY:
YOU KNOW,
IF CRAIG WERE STILL HERE,
WE'D CUT THE AMOUNT OF DORK
IN THE TALENT SHOWCASE
BY LIKE 33%.
LOOK.
"SHE IS THE ASH?"
WHO COULD THAT
POSSIBLY BE ABOUT?
HE WROTE ALL THESE SONGS
IN REHAB?
ASHLEY:
WELL, NOT "MY WINDOW."
IT'S NOT THAT BAD,
ACTUALLY.
UM, IT DOESN'T SOUND
LIKE THE OTHER SONGS, THOUGH.
THAT'S 'CAUSE I WROTE IT.
HEY GUYS...
CRAIG GAVE ME A SHOUT-OUT
IN HIS ALBUM THANK YOU'S.
GLAD ONE OF US
GOT MENTIONED.
HE USED ONE
OF MY SONGS.
AND HE DIDN'T CREDIT YOU?
WELL, WHATEVER,
I CAN ALWAYS MAKE MORE.
TOBY:
GOOD. 'CAUSE LIKE IT OR NOT,
I'M PUTTING YOU DOWN
FOR THE TALENT SHOWCASE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M IN.
MAYBE IT'S TIME
I CAME OUT OF RETIREMENT.
♪♪♪
JIMMY:
86 AVERAGE. NICE!
ASHLEY:
89.
LET'S SEE CRAIG
PLAGIARIZE THAT!
WHAT GRADE DOES IT TAKE
FOR YOU TO CRACK A SMILE?
THIS MEANS NYU
IS GUARANTEED,
AND THEN WE HIT
LAW SCHOOL!
OR WE THINK ABOUT
LAW SCHOOL.
I THOUGHT WE ALREADY
DID THAT.
WHAT'S THE RUSH?
MAYBE THERE'S STILL
SOME TIME TO CHASE DREAMS.
AS LONG AS IT'S A DREAM
YOU'RE CHASING
AND NOT REVENGE
ON A SONGWRITING EX.
IT'S NOT ABOUT THAT.
IT'S NOT ABOUT
GETTING BACK AT CRAIG
FOR WHAT HE DID TO ME.
IT'S ABOUT WHAT CRAIG
DID FOR HIMSELF:
HE FOCUSED ON HIS MUSIC
AND HE MADE IT HAPPEN.
IT'S INSPIRING.
INSPIRED BY ANOTHER DUDE.
OUCH.
JIMMY,
YOU'RE INSPIRING TOO.
YOUR AWESOME ART,
YOUR GUITAR PLAYING,
YOUR MAD FREESTYLE
RHYMING SKILLS.
OKAY. NOW YOU'RE
JUST SUCKING UP.
I'M NOT.
JIMMY,
I THINK YOU'RE GENIUS.
(RHYMING)
WELL, IF YOU'RE THE BEAUTY,
AND I'M THE SMART ONE,
THERE'S NO PROBLEM
WITH THAT
SO I WON'T START ONE,
YOU KNOW?
HOW DO YOU DO THAT
IN A NANOSECOND?
YOU INSPIRE ME,
BABY.
COME ON.
THIS IS HIGH SCHOOL,
NOT A DAYCARE.
OKAY, I DON'T WANT TO SHARE
A LOCKER EITHER,
BUT WE HAVE
TO COMPROMISE.
OKAY,
THIS IS NOT
MEETING HALFWAY.
♪♪♪
SAV:
HEY, HOLLY J!
GREAT LOCKER LOCALE.
SAV! HI!
YOU LOOK HOT
EVEN IN THESE
DISGUSTING HALLWAYS.
UH, WE KNOW EACH OTHER,
RIGHT?
HOLLY J:
YOU PROBABLY REMEMBER HER
WADDLING FROM CLASS
TO CLASS.
I'M MIA... JONES.
I... I WAS AT LAKEHURST.
YEAH, YEAH.
YOU HAD A BABY.
THAT HER?
CUTE.
ALL RIGHT.
SEE YOU GUYS LATER.
THAT'S HORSE!
AND THAT IS WHY
YOU NEVER TRY
AND BEAT THE MASTER
AT HIS OWN GAME.
WELL, I THOUGHT YOU
WERE THE SENSITIVE
ARTISTE-SLASH-CLOTHING
DESIGNER NOW?
WHEN WILL YOU LEARN?
I'M EVERYTHING.
(ASHLEY STARTS SINGING)
INCLUDING DEGRASSI'S
NEXT SUPERSTAR'S BOY-TOY.
(UNENTHUSED)
YEAH.
♪ WHAT'S WRONG WITH BEING
SOMEONE ELSE ♪
♪ NO SHAME... ♪
ASH KEEPS TALKING
ABOUT THIS, UH...
"CHASING OUR DREAMS"
THING.
WHAT I THINK SHE REALLY WANTS
IS A SOLO PROJECT.
SO WHAT'RE YOU GOING TO DO
WHEN SHE GETS ALL FAMOUS ON YOU?
YOU'RE NOT HELPING.
WELL, COME ON,
SHE SOUNDS AMAZING,
HER MUSIC KICKS,
AND...
WELL, DUDE, LOOK AT HER.
(PLAYING LAST FEW NOTES OF SONG)
(HEAVY SIGH)
HEY... ASHLEY?
IS IT TRUE YOU WERE PARTNERS
WITH CRAIG MANNING?
WE PLAYED TOGETHER,
YEAH.
IMAGINE...
YOU USED TO PERFORM
TOGETHER,
ON THIS VERY STAGE.
ALL THE TIME,
ACTUALLY.
ANYA:
WOW.
I HEARD "SHE IS THE ASH"
IS ABOUT YOU.
YOU'RE LIKE OUR OWN LITTLE
PIECE OF HIM, YOU KNOW?
JUST WHAT I ALWAYS HOPED
TO BE KNOWN AS.
AH-HA.
(GIGGLES)
IT'S CRAIG MANNING'S
OLD GIRLFRIEND!
(GIGGLES)
ELLIE:
"RED-HEADED FOR TROUBLE?"
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
GET THIS,
MANNY'S GONNA DIE:
"THONG GIRL,
WRONG GIRL."
OH, SO EVERYONE HE KISSES
IS A SONG TITLE NOW?
MARCO:
HEY, GRIFFIN, HEY.
MEET JIMMY.
WHAT'S UP?
OH, AND ASHLEY,
TWO OF OUR OLDEST FRIENDS.
UH, COOL CHAIR, MAN.
ONE OF THE PERKS
OF BEING SHOT.
GRIFFIN:
OH, I'M SORRY
TO HEAR THAT, DUDE.
UH, MARCO, MAKE SURE
YOU BRING YOUR FRIENDS
TO THE OPEN JAM,
ALL RIGHT?
LATER.
ASHLEY:
OPEN JAM?
THAT SOUNDS COOL.
YEAH,
HE DOES ONE EVERY WEEK.
IT'S LIKE ONE
OF THE THREE THINGS
I KNOW ABOUT THE GUY.
YOU TRYING TO GET
A RECORD DEAL?
YOU SCARED OF ME, UH,
MAKING A NAME
FOR MYSELF?
NO. NOT AT ALL.
AS LONG AS IT DOESN'T
MAKE YOU FORGET
ABOUT YOUR
HIGH SCHOOL SWEETHEART.
PERFORM WITH ME
TOMORROW.
ARE YOU SURE?
THAT'S...
THAT'S YOUR SONG.
YOU CAN FREESTYLE
OVER THE CHORUS.
IF I'M CHASING DREAMS,
YOU'RE COMING WITH ME.
OKAY.
(RECORDING OF ASHLEY SINGING)
♪ NO SHAME IN LIVING LIFE
IN THAT WAY ♪
♪ TELL ME LIES ♪
(RAPPING)
TELL ME ANYTHING
BUT THE TRUTH
'CAUSE I DON'T REALLY KNOW
IF I CAN TAKE IT NOW.
TELL ME ANYTHING
BUT THE TRUTH,
CAN'T FIGURE OUT
HOW I'M SUPPOSED
TO MAKE IT NOW.
TELL ME ANYTHING-
STOP, STOP.
JIMMY, STOP.
WHAT'S WRONG?
IT'S NOT TIGHT ENOUGH?
NO, IT'S, IT'S...
IT'S SOMETHING TONAL.
IT'S COMPETING
WITH THE PIANO.
OKAY, WHY DON'T YOU
JUST TWEAK THE LEVELS?
THEN IT'S NOT ABOUT
THE HARMONY.
I NEED TO FIGURE IT OUT.
ASH, IT-IT SOUNDS
GREAT RIGHT NOW.
WELL,
IT DOESN'T SOUND
THE WAY IT SOUNDS
IN MY HEAD.
I CAN FIX IT,
JUST... I THINK I HAVE
WHAT I NEED.
OKAY.
I'LL GIVE YOU
SOME HEADSPACE.
I CAN'T WAIT
TO HEAR IT.
HATZILAKOS:
IT'S TALENT TIME, DEGRASSI!
BRING YOUR LUNCH
TO THE GYMNASIUM
FOR OUR TALENT SHOWCASE.
WOW.
THAT SAV GUY
SURE IS HOT!
NO, MANNY,
I CALLED HIM!
DON'T WORRY,
I DON'T GO AFTER
TENTH GRADERS.
SO, ARE YOU GONNA
TALK TO HIM?
IT JUST SEEMS SOON,
AFTER MY LAST
BOYFRIEND.
MIA,
THE PAST IS THE PAST.
CARPE DIEM.
SEIZE THE SAV.
MANY HAVE TRIED,
NONE HAVE SUCCEEDED.
ESPECIALLY ONES
WITH BABY WEIGHT.
NOW, WHAT WOULD I DO
WITHOUT HOLLY J. SINCLAIR
LOOKING OUT FOR ME?
HOLD ON.
HOLLY J. SINCLAIR?
AS IN
HEATHER SINCLAIR?
SHE'S MY SISTER.
WAIT,
THE BOYFRIEND-STEALING,
BAD NOSE JOB-HAVING,
PUPPY-DROWNING
QUEEN OF EVIL,
IS YOUR SISTER?
TAUGHT ME EVERYTHING
SHE KNOWS.
THIS MAY BE A PROBLEM,
SWEETIE.
WHAT? WHY?
LISTEN, I HAVE TO DEBATE HER
TOMORROW MORNING,
TELL ME EVERYTHING.
LET'S JUST SAY
IF HOLLY J AND HEATHER
SHARE THE SAME DNA?
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO FIGHT FIRE
WITH HUGE,
ENORMOUS FLAMES.
GOT A LIGHT?
(APPLAUSE)
DANNY:
THANK YOU,
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
DEREK:
HEY-OH!
DANNY:
THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
READY?
YEP.
'KAY,
HERE WE GO.
OP! OP!
HO-OOOH!
OP! WHOOP!
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
HEY, BEAUTIFUL.
DID YOU WORK OUT
THE TONAL ISSUES?
I, UM...
I WENT WITH
AN EARLIER VERSION.
SO IT'S A SOLO
PROJECT?
IT'S NOT THAT
YOUR RAP WAS BAD,
IT JUST DIDN'T
REALLY FIT.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
KNOCK 'EM DEAD.
TOBY:
THANKS... GUYS.
THAT WAS, YEAH...
OKAY, THAT'S... GREAT.
OKAY, UP NEXT,
SHE KEYBOARD-STYLED
WITH CRAIG MANNING...
GIVE IT UP FOR
MY TWISTED STEPSISTER,
ASHLEY KERWIN!
(APPLAUSE)
♪♪♪
♪ YOU SAY IT'S SIMPLE ♪
♪ IT'S WHO YOU WANNA BE ♪
♪ LOOK IN THE MIRROR ♪
♪ YOU ARE NOT WHAT YOU SEE ♪
LAME!
PLAY A CRAIG SONG!
GIRL:
YOU SUCK!
MORE LIKE A NO-TALENT CONTEST!
(LAUGHING)
ASHLEY:
♪ YOU SAY IT'S SIMPLE ♪
♪ BUT AREN'T YOUR WINGS TIED ♪
♪ TELL THE TRUTH ♪
♪ WHY DO YOU HAVE TO HIDE ♪
(RAPPING)
LOOK, ME AND THE MIC,
WE COEXIST,
MY FLOW IS A GLASS BOX
WITH NO EXITS;
YOU CAN OBSERVE
WHILE YOU'RE TRAPPED IN IT.
TOOK MY LADY'S TRACK
AND I SPRINKLED SOME RAP IN IT
AND TELLIN' ME LIES...
ASHLEY:
♪ WHAT'S WRONG WITH BEING
SOMEONE ELSE ♪
♪ NO SHAME IN LIVING LIFE
THAT WAY... ♪
(RAPPING)
THEY'RE LIKE PLEASE,
PLEASE TELL US YOUR REALITY, J.,
WE CAN'T FATHOM HOW IT FEEL
TO BE FOREVER CONFINED.
MY MOTHER ALWAYS TOLD ME
WHAT TO DO WITH MY BEST FOOT,
SO TO THIS DAY, YOU KNOW
THAT IT IS NEVER BEHIND.
AND METAPHORICALLY,
I'M AHEAD OF THE REST
AND I'M PROUD OF THE FACT
THAT I'VE ACCOMPLISHED THAT.
AND EVERY TIME I SAY
THAT I CAN DO IT MYSELF,
IN THE SAME BREATH I WONDER
WHERE MY ACCOMPLICE'S AT
IT'S LIKE...
TELL ME ANYTHING
BUT THE TRUTH
'CAUSE I DON'T REALLY KNOW
IF I CAN TAKE IT NOW.
TELL ME ANYTHING...
THAT WAS AMAZING!
I FORGOT WHAT A RUSH IT WAS
TO BE ON STAGE.
TOBY BURNED OUR SONG.
OUR SONG?
RIGHT,
YOUR SONG.
YOU SCREWED UP
MY SECOND VERSE, JIMMY,
AND MY THIRD.
BUT I HELPED YOU
PICK UP THE CROWD.
I DIDN'T ASK YOU TO,
AND I DIDN'T NEED IT-
JIMMY,
ALL THEY SAW WAS YOU.
DAMN.
THANK YOU.
IT'S WHAT I'M HERE FOR.
(ASH'S SONG PLAYS ON BOOMBOX)
THIS,
THIS IS GREAT!
WISH I COULDA
SEEN IT LIVE.
WHATEVER.
HIGH SCHOOL SUCKS.
I SING, NOBODY CARES;
JIMMY RAMBLES HIS RHYMES
UNREHEARSED,
THEY GO WILD.
EVERYTHING'S EASY
FOR HIM.
YEAH.
EXCEPT... WALKING.
NOT WHAT I MEANT.
BUT...
PEOPLE THOUGHT
I WAS CRAIG'S SIDEKICK.
I DON'T WANNA BE JIMMY'S.
DOES THAT MAKE ME
A BITCH?
FORGET I ASKED.
THIS IS A COOL MELODY.
WHO IS THIS?
YOU'RE LOOKING
AT HER.
THIS IS YOU?
WHO'S THAT
WITH THE FLOW?
JIMMY.
DUDE FROM LAST NIGHT?
WHEELCHAIR?
ARE YOU GUYS COMIN' TO
THE OPEN JAM TOMORROW, RIGHT?
OH, THEY'RE BUSY.
NO, WE'RE NOT.
GRIFFIN:
COOL, MAKE SURE
JIMMY COMES.
BECAUSE THERE'S GONNA BE
SOME A&R GUYS THERE
AND THEY SHOULD REALLY SEE HIM.
ASHLEY:
UM...
ACTUALLY, I'M NOT REALLY SURE
THAT'S HIS THING.
BUT I WROTE
AND PRODUCED THIS.
I COULD BE THERE.
YEAH, SURE.
I MEAN,
IF IT'S COOL WITH JIMMY,
I GUESS YOU CAN PERFORM
WITH HIM.
(SIGHS)
WHEN INTELLIGENT PEOPLE
LOOK AT BOTH SIDES,
A FIGHT BECOMES A DEBATE.
REMEMBER,
PASSION IS PERSUASIVE.
LET'S SEE IT!
SAV:
OUR TOPIC IS FOREIGN
ADOPTION,
WITH HOLLY J
ON AFFIRMATIVE
AND MIA ON NEGATIVE.
HOLLY J:
BE IT RESOLVED
THAT FOREIGN ADOPTION
HAS MANY BENEFITS.
BY ILLUSTRATING
THESE BENEFITS,
I INTEND TO PROVE...
JIMMY:
(BLOWS WHISTLE)
THAT'S IT.
UM... GRIFFIN,
ELL'S ROOMMATE,
WANTS YOU TO PERFORM
AT HIS OPEN JAM TONIGHT.
THAT'S AMAZING!
OKAY, UH...
OKAY, WE GOTTA DOUBLE
THE HARMONY,
I'M GONNA LAYER
THIS NEW RHYME...
UH, NO, NOT WE.
HE JUST WANTS YOU.
OH,
SO I'M GONNA FORGET IT.
JIMMY, YOU SAW
THE AUDIENCE YESTERDAY.
I CAN TAKE THE HINT.
I'M NOT A PERFORMER
LIKE YOU.
JIMMY:
LOOK,
WE ARE A TEAM,
AND THIS IS AN AMAZING
OPPORTUNITY.
OKAY.
I'LL BE THERE.
ORPHANED CHILDREN
IN OTHER COUNTRIES
RECEIVE FAR LESS CARE
THAN ORPHANED CHILDREN HERE.
THAT DOESN'T MEAN
THOSE CHILDREN
DON'T NEED A FAMILY
JUST AS MUCH!
POINT OF PERSONAL PRIVILEGE,
MR. CHAIRMAN.
JUST BECAUSE
I DON'T HAVE A CHILD-
POINT OF INQUIRY,
MR. CHAIRMAN.
DOES THE SPEAKER REALIZE
THAT HER SPRAY TAN IS RUNNING?
SAV?
UH, SPEAKER
IS OUT OF ORDER.
HOLLY J:
MY WORTHY OPPONENT
IS BIASED
DUE TO HER MATRONLY
OBLIGATIONS
AND CANKLES.
MIA:
WELL, THEN MAYBE
WE SHOULD DEBATE
TESTING FOR PSYCHOSIS
IN HERPES-INFECTED TEENS,
SINCE THE SPEAKER'S
HIGHLY QUALIFIED TO-
UH, ORDER IN THE COURT!
KWAN:
MIA...
IF YOU CAN'T BE MATURE
ABOUT THIS,
TAKE A SEAT.
BUT, MS. KWAN,
I WAS-
KWAN:
NEXT GROUP.
♪♪♪
YO, MAN,
HAVE YOU SEEN ASHLEY?
GRIFFIN:
THE GIRLFRIEND?
NO, DUDE.
LOOK,
IF SHE DOESN'T SHOW-
I'M NOT TAKING "NO"
FOR AN ANSWER.
I NEED YOU UP THERE.
SHE'S THE MUSIC,
THOUGH.
IT'S TAKEN CARE OF.
WHAT?
WHERE'D YOU GET THAT?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT,
MAN.
LISTEN,
YOU DO YOU, OKAY?
IF THOSE GOES WELL,
THIS COULD MEAN BIG THINGS
DOWN THE ROAD -
FOR BOTH OF US.
US?
MAN:
GRIFFIN, TWO MINUTES.
YOU'RE UP NEXT.
WAIT.
HEY.
DO YOU HAVE ROOM
FOR ONE MORE?
ACTUALLY, I'VE GOT ROOM
FOR ONE AND A HALF.
(LAUGHS)
(GIGGLES)
HEY, SAV,
ABOUT THE DEBATE,
I WAS STUPID.
HEY, HOLLY J HAS GOT
A KNACK FOR PROVOCATION.
TRUST ME,
I KNOW.
OH.
WHY?
WERE YOU GUYS EVER...
OH NO.
NO WAY.
THE ONLY THING
SHE AND I HAVE IN COMMON
IS LAKEHURST.
SO, YOU'RE NOT, UH...
YOU'RE NOT SEEING ANYONE?
NAH.
FREE AS A BIRD.
(LOUD THUD OF MUSIC)
GRIFFIN:
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY HAVING
A GOOD TIME OUT THERE?
(LOUD APPLAUSE)
YEAH?
OKAY, YOU AIN'T SEEN
NOTHIN' YET.
EVERYBODY, GIVE IT UP
FOR MY NEWEST FIND...
JIMMY BROOKS!
(APPLAUSE)
DO WHAT YOU DO.
THANKS.
(SONG STARTS)
♪♪♪
(TAKES A DEEP BREATH)
(RAPPING)
LOOK, ME AND THE MIC,
WE COEXIST,
MY FLOW IS A GLASS BOX
WITH NO EXITS;
SO YOU CAN OBSERVE
WHILE YOU'RE TRAPPED IN IT.
TOOK MY LADY'S TRACK
AND I SPRINKLED SOME RAP IN IT
AND NOW THEY'RE LIKE PLEASE,
PLEASE TELL US YOUR REALITY, J.,
WE CAN'T FATHOM HOW IT FEEL
TO BE FOREVER CONFINED.
MY MOTHER ALWAYS TOLD ME
WHAT TO DO WITH MY BEST FOOT,
SO TO THIS DAY YOU KNOW
THAT IT IS NEVER BEHIND.
AND METAPHORICALLY,
I'M AHEAD OF THE REST
AND I'M PROUD OF THE FACT
THAT I'VE ACCOMPLISHED THAT. ♪
AND EVERY TIME I SAY IT...
THAT VOCAL TRACK
SOUNDS GREAT.
YOU MUST BE HAPPY.
THIS IS REALLY GOOD
FOR HIM.
YEAH. DEFINITELY BETTER
THAN ME BEING UP THERE
WITH HIM.
(RAPPING)
I CAME INTO THIS WORLD
AS A DIAMOND SO PURE,
BUT CAN'T GUARANTEE TO YOU
THAT I'M GONNA LEAVE THE SAME,
SO TELL ME ANYTHING
BUT THE TRUTH
'CAUSE I DON'T REALLY KNOW
IF I CAN TAKE IT NOW...
TELL ME ANYTHING
BUT THE TRUTH,
CAN'T FIGURE OUT HOW
I'M SUPPOSED TO MAKE IT NOW...
TELL ME ANYTHING
BUT THE TRUTH
'CAUSE I DON'T REALLY KNOW
IF I CAN TAKE IT NOW...
TELL ME ANYTHING
BUT THE TRUTH,
CAN'T FIGURE OUT HOW
I'M SUPPOSED TO MAKE IT NOW...
SO TELL ME LIES,
LIES, LIES, LIES...
I SAID TELL ME LIES
SO, YOU GOT A CD FOR ME,
OR WHAT?
WHERE WERE YOU?
OVER THERE,
WATCHING YOU KICK ASS.
SO WHY DIDN'T YOU
COME UP?
'CAUSE YOU DIDN'T
NEED ME.
GUESS WHAT?
I JUST TALKED TO THE GUY
FROM CO-BASS RECORDS.
HE WANTS TO HEAR MORE!
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YEAH.
JIMMY, HE LOVED YOU.
BUT HE ALSO SAID
THAT ASH'S BACKING TRACK
WAS UM... "SEDUCTIVE."
REALLY?
I WONDER IF IT WAS
THE SECOND VERSE PROGRESSION.
GRIFFIN:
AND GET THIS, OKAY?
WHEN I TOLD HIM
YOU WERE A YOUNG PRODUCER,
HE SAID HE WANTED
TO HEAR A DEMO.
YEAH, YOU GUYS
ARE THE REAL DEAL,
AND I THINK THIS COULD BE
AWESOME, OKAY?
SO YOU SHOULD BE EXCITED.
WHEREVER I GO,
YOU'RE COMING WITH ME.
GOOD MORNING.
MIA!
I HAD A GREAT TIME
LAST NIGHT!
SO MANY COFFEES,
I COULDN'T SLEEP.
LISTEN, TELL ISABELLA
I SAID THANKS, HUH?
TELL HER YOURSELF.
WE GO TO THE PARK
AFTER SCHOOOL.
WANT TO JOIN US?
UH, SORRY,
I GOT SOCCER.
WELL THEN,
MAYBE NEXT TIME.
MIA, YOU'RE GREAT.
BUT I... I DON'T WANT
TO JUMP INTO ANYTHING
UNTIL I'VE GOT MY BEARINGS
AROUND HERE.
OKAY?
OH, YEAH,
OF COURSE.
SEE YOU IN CLASS,
OKAY?
SO...
THE SEARCH FOR A STEPDADDY
CONTINUES, HUH?
THAT'S... SAD.
YOU'RE EVICTED,
HOLLY J.
YOU CAN'T EVICT ME!
OH YEAH?
LOOKS LIKE I JUST DID.
(JIMMY AND ASH'S TRACK PLAYS)
(SONG STOPS)
SO, IT LOOKS LIKE CRAIG
IS GONNA HAVE
SOME COMPETITION.
DID YOU SEND
THE DEMO OFF?
OH, I'M JUST BURNING
A NEW VERSION.
WHAT NEW VERSION?
IT JUST NEEDED
A FEW TWEAKS.
SUCH THE PERFECTIONIST.
BUT YOU ARE THE BRAINS
OF THIS OUTFIT.
AND IF IT DOESN'T
WORK OUT,
THEN AT LEAST WE CAN BOTH
GO TO LAW SCHOOL.
(BELL RINGS)
OKAY.
I HAVE TWO MINUTES.
SO I'M GONNA GO
FIND SPIN
AND I WILL SEE YOU
IN SCIENCE CLASS.
JIMMY: (RAPPING)
TOOK MY LADY'S TRACK
AND I SPRINKLED SOME RAP IN IT.
AND NOW THEY'RE LIKE PLEASE,
PLEASE TELL ME...
ASHLEY: (SINGING)
♪ WHAT'S WRONG WITH BEING
SOMEONE ELSE ♪
♪ NO SHAME IN LIVING LIFE
THAT WAY ♪
♪ TELL ME LIES... ♪