(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS)
(BASKETBALL BOUNCES
IN SLOW MOTION)
(MUTED CHEERS
COME ON!
(BASKETBALL BOUNCES)
(CHEERS AND SHOUTS
SPEED UP INTO REAL-TIME)
STUDENT:
GO! GO! GO! GO!
(SNEAKERS SQUEAK ON FLOOR)
(BALL SWISHES)
(SLOW MOTION CHEERING)
STUDENT:
HEADS UP!
(LAUGHTER)
(HEAVY SIGH)
YOU KNOW WHAT? EVERYBODY JUST...
YOU GUYS GET OUTTA HERE.
I'LL SEE YOU WEDNESDAY,
OKAY?
(SIGHS)
GOOD JOB.
(EXHALES)
(BALL CLUNKS)
MR. BROOKS:
YOU GETTING SOFT, SON?
HEY! WHAT'RE YOU GUYS
DOING HERE?
THIS CAME TODAY.
WE COULDN'T WAIT.
HUDSON.
OPEN IT!
WAIT.
WHAT IF IT'S A "NO"?
MR. BROOKS:
WELL, THEN AT LEAST YOU TRIED.
WHAT DO I ALWAYS SAY?
"YOU MISS 100 PERCENT..."
UH...
"THAT YOU DON'T TAKE."
YEAH,
IT'S A GRETZKY LINE, DAD.
UH-HUH.
WOO!
ALL RIGHT.
"HUDSON UNIVERSITY
IS PLEASED TO OFFER YOU
ACCEPTANCE INTO
OUR PRE-LAW PROGRAM."
JIMMY AND PARENTS:
(EXCITED CHATTER)
MR. BROOKS:
LIKE FATHER, LIKE SON!
THE LAW FIRM
OF BROOKS & BROOKS...
YOU KNOW,
IT'S GOT A NICE RING TO IT.
IT DOES. HA!
IT'S A DREAM COME TRUE,
JIMMY.
OH, YES IT IS.
IT'S A DREAM COME TRUE.
♪♪♪
MR. BROOKS:
TA DA!
JIMMY:
(CHUCKLES)
WHEN DID YOU GET THIS?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
HE ORDERED IT
AS SOON AS YOU APPLIED.
WHAT CAN I SAY?
I HAD FAITH IN MY BOY.
SO,
CELEBRATION DINNER?
OH, HOW 'BOUT THURSDAY?
I'VE GOTTA HEAD BACK
TO THE OFFICE TONIGHT.
MCGRAW CASE.
MRS. BROOKS:
STILL?
YOU SURE YOU WANT
TO BE A LAWYER?
MR. BROOKS:
OF COURSE HE'S SURE!
IF NOT, MAYBE A SUMMER
AT THE OFFICE
MIGHT CONVINCE HIM.
SUMMER AT YOUR OFFICE?
I PULLED SOME STRINGS.
IF YOU WANT IT,
THE LAST INTERNSHIP SPOT
IS YOURS.
AND, YES, WE FINALLY
MADE THE PLACE
WHEELCHAIR ACCESSIBLE.
(LAUGHING)
IT'S ABOUT TIME.
(OVERJOYED) OH!
AH! THANK YOU!
YEAH.
DARCY:
WHEN'S YOUR DAD
PICKING YOU UP?
PETER:
UH, LIKE 5:00.
HE LIKES TO WAIT TILL MY MOM'S
CLEARED THE BUILDING.
WELL, WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
UNTIL HE GETS HERE?
(FRUSTRATED SIGH)
I'M SO SICK
OF SHARED CUSTODY.
OH, WHOA!
MY PARENTS ARE HERE.
EH! EH!
I THOUGHT YOU TOLD THEM
ABOUT US.
I TOLD THEM
ABOUT THE SKI LODGE.
ABOUT THE RAPE.
BUT US?
NOT SO MUCH.
AM I THAT BAD?
WE'RE STILL IN
FAMILY COUNSELLING
AND ALL THIS STUFF'S
COMING UP.
I HAVE TO GO.
I'M SORRY.
GO, HAVE FUN!
CALL YOUR FRIENDS!
YEAH. WHAT FRIENDS?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(WORKOUT EQUIPMENT CLANKS)
JIMMY:
YOU LOOK SO HOT,
I GUESS YOU WON'T EVEN
NEED THIS.
TRINA:
WHAT'S THIS?
JIMMY:
(CHUCKLES)
HUDSON BABY!
PRE-LAW HERE I COME.
YOU GOT IN?
THAT'S AMAZING!
BOTH:
MMM! MMM!
MY SEXY LAWYER.
GUILTY AS CHARGED.
BOTH:
(GIGGLING)
JIMMY:
IS THAT MARCUS?
DUDE, ARE YOU WALKING?
WHAT KIND OF CRAZY
MIRACLE PILL DID YOU TAKE
AND WHERE CAN I GET IT?
STEM CELLS, GUY.
YOU SERIOUS?
THAT WORKED?
DID FOR ME.
GOT MY LEGS BACK.
JIMMY:
ARE YOU SURE IT WASN'T
JUST A COINCIDENCE?
I MEAN, MAYBE YOU HEALED
ON YOUR OWN.
MAYBE. MAYBE NOT.
DID YOU GET IN TOUCH
WITH DR. VOGEL?
JUST SENT MY BLOOD WORK
TO AMSTERDAM.
WH-WHAT? YOU'RE HAVING
STEM CELL SURGERY?
I FINALLY GOT THE MONEY
AND PAPERWORK TOGETHER.
BUT THAT STUFF'S
STILL EXPERIMENTAL.
THEY DON'T HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW IT WORKS.
WELL, YEAH, BECAUSE NO ONE'S
ALLOWED TO RESEARCH IT.
NOT HERE, ANYWAY.
(BREATH OF DISBELIEF)
IF IT WORKS,
THAT WOULD BE AMAZING.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT
WOULD BE MORE AMAZING?
IF YOU CAME WITH ME.
(GENTLY PLUCKING GUITAR)
NICE AXES.
YOU GUYS IN A BAND
OR SOMETHING?
CAN TWO PEOPLE
MAKE A BAND?
ANYTHING TO GET THE CHICKS,
RIGHT?
DANNY:
HEY, WE HAVE CHICKS.
BEST THING ABOUT BEING
IN A BAND
IS GETTING AWAY FROM THEM
FOR A WHILE.
YOU GUYS NEED A FRONTMAN?
CAN YOU SING?
ANYONE CAN SING.
I GOT THE LOOKS.
(CHUCKLES)
AND I GOT THE KEYS
TO THE DRAMA ROOM,
SO WE CAN JAM
ANYTIME WE WANT.
COOL!
WAIT.
WE STILL NEED A DRUMMER.
A BAND WITHOUT A DRUMMER
IS LIKE...
SAV WITHOUT
HIS STICKER BOOK.
SHUT UP, DANNY.
I'M ON IT.
(BELL RINGS)
(WHACK)
SERIOUSLY, MAN.
I AM DONE
WITH THIS WHEELCHAIR.
SPINNER:
YEAH. AND I WANT
MY LEFT NUT BACK,
BUT WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO?
(HEAVY EXHALE)
(COMPUTER KEYS CLACK)
SPINNER:
STEM CELLS?
DON'T THOSE COME FROM
DEAD BABIES
OR SOMETHING?
NO, IDIOT.
THERE'S OTHER WAYS,
LIKE UMBILICAL CORDS.
GROSS.
TWO MONTHS AGO THERE WAS
A GUY IN MY PHYSIO,
HE WAS IN A WHEELCHAIR,
NOW HE CAN WALK.
AWES.
SO WHAT DO THEY DO?
THEY PUT A NEEDLE IN
YOUR SPINE OR SOMETHING?
MMM, SORTA.
IT'S WHEREVER THE SITE
OF THE INJURY IS.
SO, IN YOUR CASE,
IT WOULD BE...
(GUARDED BREATH)
WHOA! OKAY.
UH, NO NEEDLES NEAR MY JUNK,
THANK YOU.
DON'T HAVE THE STOMACH
FOR THAT.
OR THE TEN-G'S.
GET COMFY IN THAT CHAIR,
MAN.
SPIN, I HAVE THAT MONEY.
MAYBE I CAN DO THIS.
JIMMY!
WHERE YOU BEEN?
I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU
AROUND HERE FOR AGES.
I KNOW.
NOT SINCE UH...
IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
YOU TOO.
SO, HOW'S THE NEW RAMP?
AHHH...
GETS THE JOB DONE.
MR. BROOKS:
GREAT.
LET ME FIND THAT INTERNSHIP
APPLICATION FOR YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
ACTUALLY, I'VE BEEN MEANING
TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT THAT.
UH...
I'VE BEEN DOING
SOME RESEARCH AND I...
I WANNA TRY
STEM CELL SURGERY.
THE DAY YOU WERE PARALYZED,
YOUR MOTHER AND I LOOKED
INTO THAT.
BUT IT'S STILL
SO EXPERIMENTAL THAT...
THEY DON'T EVEN KNOW
THE COMPLICATIONS,
WHICH IS WHY
IT'S ILLEGAL HERE.
I KNOW, BUT, I MEAN,
I COULD GO
SOMEWHERE ELSE.
MAYBE WE COULD USE SOME
MONEY FROM MY TRUST FUND.
IT'S, IT'S MY MONEY,
RIGHT?
AND THIS IS EXACTLY WHY
YOU NEED MY SIGNATURE
TO ACCESS IT.
DAD, THIS IS FOR REAL.
THERE'S GUY AT PHYSIO
THAT CAN WALK AGAIN.
MAYBE HE'S LUCKY.
BUT...
EVEN IF THERE'S A CHANCE,
EVEN IF IT'S
ONE IN A MILLION -
AND WE CAN AFFORD
THE TREATMENT -
WHY NOT?
LOOK, JIM,
YOU'RE DESPERATE;
I CAN'T BLAME YOU.
BUT DON'T LET THEM
TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF YOUR DESPERATION.
WHAT HAPPENS IF YOU GO
AND IT DOESN'T WORK?
WHAT THEN?
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE IN A FEW YEARS,
WHO KNOWS?
WE CAN REVISIT.
TRINA'S ALREADY
HOOKED UP WITH A-
TRINA?
JIM, TRUST ME,
NEVER LET A WOMAN
MANIPULATE YOU,
GIVE YOU FALSE HOPES.
SHE'S NOT LIKE THAT.
LET'S JUST FOCUS
ON HUDSON
AND THE SUMMER
INTERNSHIP HERE.
CONSIDER IT.
OKAY?
(PLAYING '50S STYLE BALLAD)
PETER:
♪ NO ONE ♪
♪ CAN STOP
OUR INTER-LOCKER LOVE ♪
♪ NO ONE CAN STOP
♪ OUR INTER-LOCKER LOVE ♪
SO, YOU GONNA BE
OUR DRUMMER?
(LAUGHING)
YEAH, WHAT DO YOU GUYS
CALL YOURSELVES,
"PETER AND THE PRETTY BOYZ"?
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH LOOKING GOOD?
SAPPY LOVE SONGS
AND POLO SHIRTS?
DUDE, WHERE'S THE REBELLION?
WHERE'S THE EDGE?
WHERE'S THE ROCK?
TALK TO ME WHEN YOU HAVE
SOMETHING TO SAY.
(WITH A LAUGH)
'KAY?
(SPINNER SINGS MOCKINGLY)
♪ MY INTER-LOCKER LOVE ♪
(PINBALL MACHINE CLANKS)
HEY.
THAT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
BLOODWORK.
YEAH, I THINK I'M GONNA
STAY HERE.
DO THIS INTERNSHIP
AT MY DAD'S FIRM.
I THINK THIS IS
WHAT'S BEST RIGHT NOW.
OH, TOTALLY.
WAY BETTER THAN WALKING.
LOOK, IT'S NOT ABOUT
THE SHORT TERM, OKAY?
IT'S ABOUT THE LONG TERM.
ME AND MY FAMILY,
WE'VE HAD THIS HUDSON PLAN.
THIS INTERNSHIP JUST
GIVES ME A LEG UP.
PUN INTENDED OR...?
LOOK, I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU HAVE TO CHOOSE?
SEEMS LIKE YOU CAN
AFFORD BOTH.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
COME ON.
GOING TO LIVE
IN NEW YORK?
THAT CAN'T BE
THAT CHEAP.
WELL, WE CAN SPLIT
THE RENT?
OH... SURE.
BUT WALKING THROUGH
CENTRAL PARK
WON'T BE AS MUCH FUN
IF I HAVE TO PUSH YOU
IN YOUR WHEELCHAIR.
I THINK THAT'S CALLED
"CONDITIONAL LOVE".
WHAT?
I HAVE AN APPLICATION
TO HAND IN.
TRINA:
JIMMY, WAIT.
THAT CAME OUT WRONG.
(PASS CARD BEEPS)
(COMPUTER KEYS CLACK)
(UNINTELLIGIBLE MUMBLE)
(GRUNT OF EFFORT)
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
JIMMY:
YEAH, EVERYTHING'S FINE.
YOUR DAD TOLD ME
WHAT HAPPENED.
HE DID?
SWEETIE, I KNOW IT'S NOT
THE ANSWER YOU WANTED,
BUT STEM CELL SURGERY?
COME ON, THAT'S NOT SOMETHING
YOU JUST RUSH INTO.
NOT NOW.
THAT. YEAH,
YOU'RE RIGHT.
OKAY?
OKAY.
(BELL RINGS)
MRS. BROOKS:
BYE, SWEETIE.
BYE, MOM.
(PLAYING '50S-STYLE BALLAD)
♪ NO ONE CAN STOP ♪
♪ OUR INTER-LOCKER LOVE ♪
♪ NO ONE CAN STOP
OUR... ♪
WHAT'S WRONG?
WE HAD IT.
SORRY. DO WE GO FROM THE "A"
TO THE "F" OR...?
I DON'T KNOW CHORDS,
DUDE.
SPINNER'S RIGHT,
WE'RE LAME.
NO, WE'RE NOT LAME.
WE CAN'T BE LAME.
SAV, PLAY A CHORD.
ANY CHORD.
(PLAYS A CHORD)
'KAY, BUT FASTER.
FASTER.
(MIMICS GUITAR CHORD)
(STRUMS CHORD REPEATEDLY)
YEAH! NICE!
COME ON,
I NEED THIS TO WORK.
MY DAD DOESN'T
PICK ME UP 'TIL 5:00.
WE HAVE NOWHERE ELSE
TO GO.
(PLAYS CHORDS FASTER)
DANNY, FOLLOW SAV.
DO IT!
(DANNY PLAYS ALONG
WITH SAV'S RHYTHM)
(TURNS UP VOLUME)
♪ I'M NOT A PRETTY BOY! ♪
AAAAAGH!
(MICROPHONE FEEDBACK SQUEALS)
SAV:
DUDE!
THAT WAS AWESOME!
WHO KNEW YOU WERE
SO PISSED OFF?
THAT FELT GOOD.
WE NEED A NAME.
YOUR DAD HAVING AN AFFAIR?
WOW.
THAT IS SUCH A SHOCK.
ALL THIS TIME
I HAVE TRIED TO LIVE UP
TO THE STANDARDS
OF A MAN
WHO DOESN'T HAVE ANY.
I AM SO SORRY, JIMMY.
I TRIED TO DO EVERYTHING
TO MAKE HIM HAPPY.
I...
LISTEN.
MAYBE IT'S TIME TO DO
WHAT MAKES YOU HAPPY.
GO AFTER WHAT'S YOURS.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
HOW RIGHT YOU ARE.
(HEAVY EXHALE)
(PUNK ROCK PLAYS)
PETER:
♪ ALL WE EVER HAVE TO LOVE ♪
♪ SHARED CUSTODY!
SHARED CUSTODY! ♪
♪ ALTERNATE WEEKENDS
AND HOLIDAYS ♪
♪ TWICE THE GIFTS
TWICE THE GIFTS ♪
♪ BUT ALL WE EVER
HAVE TO LOVE ♪
(MUSIC ENDS ABRUPTLY)
DUDES?
THAT IS HARDCORE.
AWES!
YOU GET ON THE SKINS,
I'LL SET UP THE CAMERA!
WHOA, WHOA!
CAMERA?
TO MAKE A VIDEO.
POST IT ON THE INTERNET.
SHOW EVERYONE
HOW MUCH ASS WE KICK.
PETER, LOOK,
MAYBE YOU AND I CAN
BE SEEN TOGETHER...
LIKE AS FRIENDS?
SURE, FINE.
BUT THOSE GUYS,
THEY'RE LIKE, THEY'RE NINERS.
I'M IN ELEVEN.
SAV'S IN TEN.
YEAH.
WHATEVER.
GUYS, YOU'RE GOOD,
BUT YOUR BAND STILL NEEDS
TO LOOK FOR A DRUMMER, OKAY?
NO! THERE HAS TO BE
ANOTHER WAY.
'KAY?
I HAVE AN IDEA.
(OBJECTS CLATTER)
OKAY.
THINK UH...
THINK KISS,
INSANE CLOWN POSSE,
SLIP KNOT.
AN INCOGNITO BAND?
THAT'S ACTUALLY
A PRETTY WICKED IDEA.
(PUNK MUSIC PLAYS)
PETER:
♪ SHARED CUSTODY!
SHARED CUSTODY! ♪
♪ ALTERNATE WEEKENDS
AND HOLIDAYS ♪
♪ TWICE THE GIFTS!
TWICE THE GIFTS! ♪
♪ ALL WE EVER HAVE TO LOVE ♪
(LOCK CLICKS)
WAIT!
ARE YOU CRAZY?
BREAKING IN?
THIS IS YOUR PLAN?
JUST HURRY UP,
WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME.
THIS ISN'T STEALING
BECAUSE...?
IT'S MY MONEY
FOR MY FUTURE,
AND I'M LOOKING INTO IT
RIGHT NOW.
MMMM.
WHAT CAN I SAY?
YOUR FUTURE
LOOKS VERY BRIGHT.
MM-MM.
PASS ME THE FORM.
OKAY.
AUTHORIZED BY...
JEMAINE BROOKS.
(STAMP CLICKS)
TRINA:
SO YOU TAKE THIS
TO THE BANK?
THEY GIVE US THE CASH
AND WE ARE ON OUR WAY
TO AMSTERDAM.
MMM.
(WHISPERS)
COME ON.
DARCY:
SO, ARE WE STILL ON
FOR TONIGHT?
PETER:
OH, TONIGHT?
I CAN'T.
I'M UH, HANGING OUT
WITH THE GUYS.
GUYS? WHO ARE THEY?
CAN WE HELP YOU?
WE DOIN' OUR SECRET THING
LATER, PETE?
OH, SECRETS.
HOW CUTE!
WHAT'RE YOU GUYS
GONNA DO EXACTLY?
YOU KNOW, GUY STUFF:
EATING AND BELCHING.
MAKING FUN OF SAV'S
STICKER BOOK.
VERY FUNNY.
DARCY:
OKAY, WELL...
HAVE FUN.
PETER:
WE WILL!
UH, HEY!
NO SKETCHY BUSINESS,
OKAY?
DARCY, TRUST ME.
JIMMY:
(TIRED SIGH)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
AFTER SCHOOL?
SPINNER:
UM...
NOTHING.
REALLY. NOTHING.
MR. BROOKS:
JIMMY?
SEE YOU LATER.
MR. BROOKS:
MY BANK MANAGER
CALLED ME THIS MORNING.
SOMEONE ACCESSED
THE TRUST FUND MONEY.
ANY EXPLANATION?
WELL, LIKE YOU SAY, SIR.
"YOU MISS 100% OF THE SHOTS
YOU DON'T TAKE."
AH.
SO WE HAVE THEFT,
FORGERY...
AND LET'S NOT FORGET
ADULTERY.
I SAW YOU LAST NIGHT
WITH MELANIE.
MELANIE AT WORK?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
I WENT TO YOUR OFFICE
TO TELL YOU THAT I WANTED
THE INTERNSHIP.
I SAW YOU TWO
AND THEN LEFT.
WE WERE WORKING LATE.
THAT'S ALL.
LOOK,
I'M NOT AN IDIOT.
SHE WAS ALL OVER YOU
AND YOU DIDN'T SEEM TO MIND.
LOOK, JIMMY,
SOMETIMES MELANIE...
LET ME GUESS,
SHE MANIPULATES POOR,
INNOCENT YOU?
LOOK,
JUST RETURN THE MONEY
AND THIS DOESN'T
HAVE TO GO ANY FURTHER.
THEN HOW DO I GET
TO AMSTERDAM?
SEE YOU AT DINNER.
(STUDZ SONG PLAYS
THROUGH HEADPHONES)
WHAT IS THAT NOISE?
IT'S NOT NOISE.
IT'S AWESOMENESS.
IS THAT STUDZ?
THEY'RE SO RAD!
WAIT, WHY AM I
SO OUT OF THE LOOP?
THEY'RE THIS DEGRASSI BAND.
NOBODY KNOWS WHO THEY ARE.
SPIN IS GONNA LOVE THEM.
PETER:
ONE-TWO-THREE-FOUR!
♪ SHARED CUSTODY!
SHARED CUSTODY! ♪
♪ ALTERNATE WEEKENDS
AND HOLIDAYS ♪
IS THAT BLOOD?
OR RED PAINT?
OH MY GOSH.
IS THAT...?
ARE YOU...?
SHHH. IT'S A SECRET.
IT'S A SIDE PROJECT
FOR ME AND MY FRIENDS.
(CHUCKLES)
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
SORRY I'M LATE.
MMM.
HAVE YOU ORDERED?
NO.
THE MUSSELS LOOK GOOD.
MRS. BROOKS:
WAIT A MINUTE.
SINCE WHEN DO YOU LIKE MUSSELS?
OH, THE THINGS
YOU DON'T KNOW.
MRS. BROOKS:
WHAT'S THAT, SWEETIE?
MOM, DAD AND I HAD
A TALK TODAY.
WE MADE A BREAKTHROUGH.
YOU DID?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WOULD YOU LIKE TO TELL HER,
OR SHOULD I?
JIMMY AND I HAD ANOTHER TALK
ABOUT THE STEM-CELL TREATMENT
AND UH, HE MADE A CASE
THAT WOULD STAND UP
IN ANY COURT OF LAW.
I WAS IMPRESSED.
I'D LIKE TO USE
MY TRUST FUND MONEY
AND GET IT DONE
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
I'M SURPRISED, JEMAINE,
YOU KNOW THE RISKS.
AND WE TALKED ABOUT
GETTING HIS HOPES UP.
JIMMY:
MOM...
TALK TO ME.
'KAY, MAYBE IT WON'T WORK;
I CAN LIVE WITH THAT.
BUT I CAN'T LIVE WITHOUT
NOT EVEN TRYING.
I THINK HE DESERVES
A CHANCE.
YOU'RE SURE ABOUT THIS,
JIMMY?
YEAH.
OKAY.
(ELATED BREATH)
THANK YOU.
OKAY.
ANY OTHER SECRETS YOU GUYS
HAVE TO TELL ME ABOUT?
NOPE. (SIGHS)
THAT'S IT.
MRS. BROOKS:
WELL, IF JIMMY'S GOING
OVERSEAS FOR SURGERY,
WE'VE GOT PLANS TO MAKE.
(LAUGHS)
WE SURE DO.
WHO'S UP FOR DESSERT?
MRS. BROOKS:
DEFINITELY.
(ELATED LAUGH)