(HAIR DRYER WHIRS)
(HAIR DRYER SPUTTERS)
(TAP, TAP, TAP)
(HAIR DRYER WHIRS)
MORNING,
SLEEPING CUTIE.
IF YOU REALLY LOVED ME,
YOU WOULDN'T HURT
MY EARS THIS EARLY.
(DRYER CLICKS OFF)
(SIGHS) GOTTA DROP
THE STORE KEY WITH JIMMY,
HIT THE BANK, GROCERIES,
AND A JOB INTERVIEW.
TRES MULTITASK.
SO WHAT AM I GONNA DO
ALL DAY?
HOW ABOUT RECHARGE
AFTER THE LAST TWO WEEKS?
YOUR FINAL DEGRASSI
SEMESTER
GOT YOU THOSE CRAZY-GREAT
GRADES YOU WERE AFTER.
YET,
NOT EVEN STRAIGHT A'S
COULD GET MY MOM
TO DITCH CHAD
THE FREELOADING CON-MAN.
SO MUCH FOR MOVIN'
BACK HOME.
PAIGE:
HON, I KNOW IT'S HARD,
BUT YOU CAN STAY HERE
UNTIL YOU GET BACK
ON YOUR FEET.
(KISS)
BYE.
PAIGE, HOW LONG
IS ALEX CRASHING?
LIKE IS SHE LOOKING
FOR A JOB, OR-
HER LAST REFERENCE
IS FROM A STRIP BAR.
SHE NEEDS HELP
AND TIME!
YA, WELL, WHO'S GONNA HELP HER
DITCH THE TV REMOTE
AND PICK UP THE WANT ADS?
HON, YOU AND I
ARE LUCKY ENOUGH
NOT TO KNOW
WHAT IT'S LIKE
WHEN YOUR PARENTS
SCREW YOU OVER.
SYMPATHY,
S'IL VOUS PLAIT?
THANK YOU.
SO, CAN I GO TO MY
LIFE-CHANGING INTERVIEW?
WE'LL DISCUSS THIS LATER,
OKAY?
♪♪♪
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
ANDREA?
OKAY, GUESS NOT.
ARE YOU THE NEW GIRL?
PAIGE.
IT IS SO GOOD
TO MEET YOU, ANDREA!
AHN-DRAY-AH.
ANDREA.
OF COURSE.
SO MUCH FOR A GOOD
FIRST IMPRESSION, RIGHT?
LOOK, THIS JOB,
YOU'RE GONNA IRON
MORE CLOTHES
THAN YOU WEAR, OKAY.
WELL,
HOW ABOUT CHIFFONS?
I MEAN,
STEAMING, SURE,
BUT WILL THE MALANDRINOS
REALLY HOLD UP?
"MALANDRINOS"?
WE'VE BEEN PRACTICING
THAT AT HOME, HAVEN'T WE?
MY WHOLE LIFE,
CLOTHES GEEK.
WHOSE PINAFORES
DID YOU LIKE THIS SEASON?
CHANEL'S.
THE REST ARE UNWEARABLE.
LOOK, I NEED SOMEONE
AT MY BECK AND CALL.
TOTALLY COMMITTED.
LOOK,
I WILL GET COFFEES,
I WILL PIN HEMS.
I'LL DO MODEL
SWEAT-DUTY, REALLY.
ARE YOU
A FASHION STUDENT?
GOOD.
WE HAVE OUR SPRING LINE
RUNWAY SHOW FOR CLIENTS
HAPPENING THIS WEEK.
DROP OFFS, DETAILS,
EMERGENCIES - YOU DRIVE?
YES.
ANDREA, I WILL NOT
LET YOU DOWN. SO...
WRITE THIS DOWN...
TODAY AT THREE
MODEL CASTING...
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
OOP.
(DOOR THUDS)
MANNY AND DAMIAN,
A...
MATCH MADE
IN LATENESS.
SOMETHING I SHOULD
KNOW ABOUT?
NOT YET,
MR. SIMPSON.
OKAY, WELL,
WHILE LIBERTY'S AWAY
AT LEADERSHIP CAMP,
ACTING VICE PRESIDENT
TOBY HAS AN ANNOUNCEMENT.
UM, IN RESPONSE TO CONCERNS
RAISED BY THE MERGER,
WE'RE GONNA BE HOLDING
A REFERENDUM.
ON THURSDAY
WE'RE GONNA VOTE
ON WHETHER LAKEHURST
CLUBS AND TEAMS
SHOULD INTEGRATE
INTO DEGRASSI'S
OR STAY SEPARATE.
PFFFT.
(DISAPPOINTED GROAN)
HEY, ALL RIGHT,
COOL YOUR JETS GUYS,
COME ON, LET'S GET THIS
CLASS STARTED, ALL RIGHT.
HEY, LET'S INSTILL
SEGREGATION.
APARTHEID WORKED
SO WELL IN SOUTH AFRICA,
WHY NOT HERE?
WE SHOULD DO SOMETHING,
MANNY.
HELL-O? EARTH TO MANNY.
YEAH, TOTALLY.
TOGETHER GOOD,
SEPARATE BAD.
SPEAKING OF TOGETHER
OR SEPARATE,
WHAT'S WITH YOU
AND DAMIAN?
THINGS KINDA FIZZLED
AFTER THE LAKEHURST FEUD.
KINDA THANKS TO YOU,
ACTUALLY,
BUT AM I BITTER?
♪♪♪
MARCO:
SO, WHY DO YOU THINK
YOU'D BE A GOOD ROOMMATE,
UH, GRIFFIN?
AH, WELL, I'M QUIET,
CLEAN AND STUDIOUS.
HMM, THAT MIGHT
NOT WORK.
WE'RE KIND OF...
LOUD.
AND SORTA MESSY.
YEAH, WE DO HOMEWORK
IN FRONT OF THE TV.
YOU'RE AN ENGINEERING
STUDENT, RIGHT?
YEAH, AND I BOOK
BANDS FOR THE CLUB
AND I SPIN,
SO, LOUD'S OKAY. HEH.
(SMIRKS)
WELL, GRIFFIN,
IT WAS GREAT MEETING YOU.
OKAY, UM...
I'LL LET MYSELF OUT.
YOU GUYS GET RIGHT
TO TALKING ABOUT ME.
ALL:
(CHUCKLE)
THANK YOU,
NO MORE CALLERS!
HEY, I'M NOT SURE.
A HOT ROOMMATE
IS A LOT MORE PRESSURE
THAN... REGULAR ONES.
I NEED FREEDOM
TO WEAR FLANNEL.
GRIFFIN WAS INCREDIBLY
CUTE AND NORMAL.
IT'S TWO TO ONE,
SORRY, ELLIE.
ALEX:
MMM, (KISSES TEETH)
A GUY HERE'D BE WEIRD,
IT'S A TIE.
PAIGE:
UM, (EXHALES) HON,
(TIGHT INHALES)
YOU KNOW WE LOVE YOU,
BUT YOU DON'T REALLY
GET SO MUCH OF A VOTE.
THE RENT'S THE RENT,
YOU KNOW?
RIGHT. OF COURSE.
(PHONE RINGS)
PA ANNOUNCEMENT:
ATTENTION, STUDENTS,
GAMBLING IN THE HALLWAYS...
(SMIRKS) DAMIAN.
THE GUY WHO LET A TINY
CHEERLEADING PROTEST
WRECK OUR RELATIONSHIP
LAST SEMESTER.
YA, WELL,
A GYM FULL OF PEOPLE
SHOUTING
"GO HOME LAKEHURST"
DOESN'T LEAVE
THE MEMORY EASILY.
WELL, NOW YOU HAVE
A REASON TO FORGET.
ALSO KNOWN AS ME,
OR WAS THAT NOT FLIRTING
THAT I SAW IN CLASS TODAY?
(EXHALES)
WHAT ARE YOU SUGGESTING,
MS. SANTOS?
THAT WE GIVE
IT ANOTHER TRY.
THAT WE LIVE
IN THE PRESENT.
HMM, I LIKE PRESENTS.
ANYA:
UM...
SMILE FOR THE GRAPEVINE?
(CAMERA CLICKS)
PAIGE:
ALEX, PLEASE STOP POUTING,
YOU KNOW, IT'S ONLY BE-
NO, NO,
NO, OH, COME ON!
I'M SO STUPID!
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
MY LICENSE EXPIRED
AND I THOUGHT I COULD
RENEW IT ONLINE, BUT...
(INHALES AND EXHALES)
ALEX, HALF THIS JOB
IS DRIVING!
ALEX:
72-HOUR WAIT.
OH, I HAVE TO BE
THERE IN AN HOUR!
YOU HAVE A CAR.
I HAVE A LICENSE.
YOU WOULD DO THAT?
WELL, IT MIGHT EAT
INTO MY COUCH TIME,
BUT IT'LL BE FUN
TO HANG OUT FOR A CHANGE.
(GASPS)
THANK YOU,
THANK YOU.
THE ENTIRE FASHION INDUSTRY
OWES YOU HUGE.
(KEYS JINGLE)
READY TO HIT THE ROAD?
♪♪♪
(DOOR OPENS)
BONJOUR COUTURE!
AND... ALEX,
ITS NEWEST FAN?
UH, NOT QUITE.
PAIGE:
HAD A LITTLE
LICENSE ISSUE,
BUT THIS ADORABLE
SUPERHUMAN
IS CHAUFFEURING
SO I DON'T LOSE MY JOB.
THE THINGS I DO
TO SPEND TIME WITH YOU.
I STILL DON'T GET
WHY WE HAD TO
BRING ALL THIS
STUFF HERE.
UM, HON, WE CAN'T LEAVE
THEM AT THE VENUE ALONE,
THEY ARE PRICELESS.
MARCO,
FLOWN FROM MILAN,
TODAY.
NO.
OH, NE TOUCHE PAS.
I SAW A PAIR OF $1200
SHORTS TONIGHT.
WHO BUYS $1200 SHORTS?
I WISH I COULD.
BEING NEAR THEM
ON THE RUNWAY'LL HAVE TO DO.
THAT'S JUST... SAD.
SO, AH, THIS SHOW,
IT'S FOR THE WORLD'S
FIVE OTHER SHORTS
LOVING FREAKS?
MARCO:
THIS SHOW IS LIKE
A HUGE DEAL.
IT SAID IN THE PAPER TODAY
WHO'S SITTING FRONT-ROW.
HON, I WILL BE DONE
AT THE OFFICE AT FOUR TOMORROW,
BUT IF I'M NOT OUTSIDE,
YOU CAN JUST WAIT
FOR ME, OKAY.
SURE,
GETTING USED TO THAT.
MARCO:
THIS IS UNREAL.
PAIGE:
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT TO DO. (LAUGHS)
TRY IT ON.
THAT'S WHAT YOU DO.
LIKE, ARE YOU KIDDING?
♪♪♪
YOU'RE ON THE INTERNET.
AGAIN?
MANNY:
I SWEAR I'VE DONE
NOTHING NET-WORTHY.
DEGRASSI GRAPEVINE
DISAGREES.
MANNY:
GOOD NEWS TRAVELS FAST,
I GUESS.
DAMIAN, LOOK,
WE'RE THE INTERRACIAL
POSTER CHILDREN
FOR DEGRASSI-LAKEHURST
UNITY.
DAMIAN:
HMM.
WHAT, TOO MUCH PRESS
TOO SOON?
NO, IT'S JUST...
A LITTLE IRONIC.
THE WHOLE SEPARATION THING
WAS KINDA MY IDEA.
PA ANNOUNCEMENT:
LAKEHUST STUDENT LOOKING
TO BOOK A GUIDANCE APPOINTMENT,
SHOULD DO SO...
MANNY:
HOLD ON.
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
BECAUSE
I BELIEVE IN IT.
LAKEHURST NEEDS
IT'S OWN IDENTITY.
ESPECIALLY NOW.
DAMIAN, THE RIVALRY
IS ONLY GONNA GET WORSE.
WHAT ABOUT?
DAMIAN:
NO PROBLEM,
WE CAN BE TOGETHER
EVEN IF OUR SCHOOLS
ARE APART.
WOULDN'T IT BE BETTER
IF WE WERE DOUBLE-TOGETHER?
(EXHALES)
MANNY,
YOU JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND
POLITICS.
THE ONLY THING
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
IS WHY I EVER THOUGHT
THIS COULD WORK,
CONDESCENDING ASS.
HOLD ON,
THAT CAME OUT WRONG.
(CARS HONK)
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
SAY YOU'RE AT THE CORNER,
I'VE BEEN WAITING HERE
FOR 40 MINUTES.
ALEX:
I WILL BE SOON, PAIGEY,
I JUST HAD TO, UM...
JUST READ THE STYLE
SECTION, OKAY?
I'LL GET THERE
AS SOON AS I CAN.
(SIGHS)
HOW ABOUT DON'T BOTHER?
I CAN TAKE CARE OF MYSELF,
OKAY.
TAXI!
(DIAL TONE)
(PHONE BEEPS OFF)
(SMIRKS)
I HAVE TO GO GET HER.
JAY:
FIRST MEL LEAVES ME,
NOW YOU?
MY HEART IS...
CRACKED OPEN,
AND LEAKING LOVE JUICE
ALL OVER THE PLACE.
UGH,
WELL, YOUR HEART WILL HEAL.
(WITH A LAUGH)
AND I CAN'T DRIVE,
I'M TOO STONED.
(LAUGHS)
NO, WHAT AM I GONNA
TELL PAIGE?
THAT I'M A MESS,
THAT...
THAT-THAT YOU'RE BEING
A GOOD FRIEND,
SHE'LL GET IT.
NO, SHE'LL HAVE A FIT,
ACTUALLY.
THESE ARE THE ONLY THINGS
SHE CARES ABOUT.
(ZIPPER ZIPS)
(PLASTIC RUSTLES)
WHOA, MEL WOULD
LOOK SO HOT IN THAT.
GOD, I MISS HER.
AND THAT'S WHY
I KEEP YOU AROUND,
FOR YOUR BRILLIANT IDEAS.
PAIGE:
(DOOR CLOSES) ALEX?
ALEX!
CAN YOU AT LEAST
DO ME THE COURTESY
OF BEING HERE
WHEN I YELL AT YOU?
YOU DITCHED ME!
I KNOW, I'M SORRY,
BUT MEL DUMPED JAY
AND HE REALLY NEEDED-
LET ME GUESS, SAY,
A SHOULDER TO GET HIGH ON?
(SMACKS LIPS)
I'M SORRY,
I WAS A JERK,
BUT...
CAN I MAKE IT
UP TO YOU?
(GASPS)
OH MY GOD!
TAKE OFF THE DRESS,
NOW!
BUT I WAS TRYING
TO SURPRISE YOU.
WELL, CONGRATULATIONS.
(HEAVY BREATH)
TAKE OFF THE DRESS
AND...
AND THEN
GET OUT OF MY ROOM.
♪♪♪
COFFEE?
I FOUND MORE.
PAIGE, I'M SORRY.
(STAMMERS) I THOUGHT
MY WONDER-GIRL PAIGE
COULD MANAGE
ON HER OWN.
ON MY OWN?
I'M FINE.
SOMEONE ELSE
CAUSED THE PROBLEM.
I MADE A MISTAKE.
I DIDN'T UNDERSTAND
HOW SERIOUSLY
YOU WERE TAKIN' THIS
WHOLE GIG.
HOW COULD YOU NOT?
THIS IS THE FIRST THING
I'VE BEEN EXCITED ABOUT
SINCE I BOMBED
OUT OF BANTING.
I'M NOT LIKE YOU,
WITH PLANS AND STUFF.
I ALWAYS FEEL
LIKE I'M BEHIND.
MAYBE THAT'S WHY
I NEED YOU.
WELL, WHAT ABOUT
WHEN I NEED YOU?
I'LL BE THERE.
HOW CAN I PROVE IT?
CHOCOLATE REMINDERS
FOR TONIGHT'S SHOW.
THEY HAVE TO BE WRAPPED
AND COURIERED
TO ALL THE VIP'S
BY NOON.
SHOULD'VE BEEN DONE
LAST NIGHT, BUT UM...
I WAS BUSY.
(SIGHS)
I'LL GET IT DONE, PAIGE.
I KNOW YOU WILL,
BECAUSE SCREWING UP
IS NOT AN OPTION.
DAMIAN:
MANNY! MANNY?
MANNY, STOP.
SORRY, NOT ONLY DO I
NOT UNDERSTAND POLITICS?
I HAVE TROUBLE
WITH SIMPLE COMMANDS.
I'M SORRY
ABOUT YESTERDAY.
LISTEN,
I DIDN'T MEAN TO IMPLY
YOU WERE ANYTHING LESS
THAN BRILLIANT.
BUT WE'RE BOTH SMART
ENOUGH TO REALIZE
THE TRUTH, RIGHT?
ABOUT US?
UH OH.
DAMIEN,
IT'S NOT GONNA WORK.
I THINK THE PERSONAL
IS POLITICAL.
AND IF I CAN'T SUPPORT
YOUR CAMPAIGN,
THEN I CAN'T SUPPORT YOU.
I RESPECT THAT,
BUT IT DOESN'T SOUND GOOD
FOR THE FACES OF DEGRASSI
LAKEHURST UNITY.
WELL, AT LEAST
WE CAN AGREE ON THAT.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
THINK WE JUST
SET THE RECORD
FOR THE WORLD'S
SHORTEST RELATIONSHIP.
(LAUGHS)
I GUESS IT WASN'T
MEANT TO BE.
WE'RE JUST TOO DIFFERENT.
IT'S 'CAUSE I'M BLACK,
ISN'T IT?
WELL, NOW THAT YOU
MENTION IT.
SO WHAT,
YOU JUST WANTED THE CRED?
WHY DO YOU PEOPLE
ALWAYS PLAY THE RACE CARD?
THAT'S HIGHLY OFFENSIVE.
(HUFFS)
ANDREA:
WHAT'S MRS. HAGGERTY
GOING TO WEAR?
PAIGE:
COURIERED THE PURPLE
JERSEY.
AND THE MODELS?
ARE IN MAKEUP
AS WE SPEAK.
AND WHAT ABOUT
THE NEW MUSIC MIX?
OH, UH, TRACKS 1 TO 6
HAVE IT ON A LOOP.
NOW,
WHY HAVEN'T
ANY OF MY VIP'S CALLED
TO GUSH OVER THEIR
EDIBLE GOLD REMINDERS?
THEY HAVEN'T?
BUT I HAD THEM SENT OUT.
YOU HAD THEM SENT?
ANDREA, I-I SWEAR
THEY WERE AT
THE COURIER BY NOON.
IT'S YOUR FIRST WEEK
AND YOU'RE SUBCONTRACTING,
ALREADY?
(SIGHS) ALEX...
PAIGE, FOCUS,
WE'RE IN THE WEEDS HERE.
NOW, IF YOU CAN'T
HANDLE THIS...
NO, I CAN.
I CAN.
I'M SURE IT WAS NOTHING
MORE THAN A LITTLE SNAG.
I CAN FIX IT
TRUST ME.
YEAH,
YOU CERTAINLY WILL;
IT WON'T BE A PROBLEM
AT SHOWTIME, RIGHT?
OF COURSE NOT.
EVERYTHING
IS UNDER CONTROL.
(PAPERS RUSTLE)
UM...
YOU LOOKING
FOR SOMETHING?
I, YEAH... HUH.
I JUST CAN'T SEEM TO FIND
THE CONTACT SHEET.
(PAPERS FLICK)
THANK YOU.
JUST DO YOUR JOB.
AND DON'T WEAR THAT.
HOLLY J:
SO, MANNY,
CHANTAY AND I WERE JUST TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT WHO'S HOTTER:
BRAD OR KANYE?
YOU'RE SERIOUS?
RYAN GOSLING
HANDS DOWN.
FIGURES.
WHAT'S THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
AS LONG AS HE'S
NOT BLACK, RIGHT?
EXCUSE ME?
RUMOUR HAS IT
YOU'RE A RACIST.
HUH, RUMOUR HAS IT
YOU HAVE WEBBED TOES.
SORRY, MANNY,
BUT MOST OF US UNDERSTAND
THAT RACISM IS A VERY
SERIOUS ISSUE.
STUDENT:
UH-HUH.
GUYS,
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
SO THE RUMOUR'S TRUE,
THEN?
NO! WHERE ARE YOU
GETTING THIS CRAP FROM?
(DISGUSTED SIGH)
(EXHALES) PEOPLE,
WHO OVERHEARD YOU
TALKING TO DAMIAN TODAY.
DUDE, WE WERE JOKING!
THIS IS INSANE!
COME ON, I'LL PROVE IT.
(STUDENT CHATTER)
MANNY:
SO, YOU HEARD?
RACIST, AWESOME, HUH?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
SOME PEOPLE DIDN'T THINK
OUR JOKE WAS VERY FUNNY,
BUT SEEMS WORKING OUT
WELL FOR YOU THOUGH,
LOTS OF SUPPORT, HUH?
YOU THINK PEOPLE
ARE SUPPORTING ME
BECAUSE OF THAT?
WELL, I DON'T THINK
IT'S HURTING.
SO YOU NEED TO DO
SOMETHING FOR ME.
HEY, LISTEN UP!
UNSCHEDULED ANNOUNCEMENT
FROM DAMIAN HAYNES!
(STUDENT CHATTER SUBSIDES)
I HEARD SOME
VICIOUS RUMOURS.
I WANT YOU ALL
TO KNOW
THAT MANNY SANTOS
IS NOT A RACIST.
THEN WHY DID SHE
DUMP YOU?
(SMIRKS)
TRUST ME,
THE REASONS ARE FAR MORE
THAN SKIN DEEP.
UNLIKE DAMIAN,
I HAPPEN TO BE A FIRM
BELIEVER IN UNITY.
HE WANTS TO KEEP
THE SCHOOLS DIVIDED,
BUT WHAT DAMIAN DOESN'T
GET ABOUT POLITICS?
IS THAT WHEN THERE'S
SOLIDARITY,
THERE'S STRENGTH.
I HOPE YOU
ALL REMEMBER THIS
AS YOU MAKE YOUR WAY
TO THE POLLS.
DEREK:
YEAH. (CLAPS HANDS)
DANNY:
(CLAPS HANDS) BRAVO!
ONE SCHOOL,
ONE LOVE.
(PHONE RINGS)
PAIGE HERE.
MS. LEAVOY.
YOU WILL, GREAT!
WE'LL SEE YOU SOON.
PAIGE, HOW ARE MY-
THIS CHAIR IS CROOKED.
HOW ARE MY VIP'S?
THE LAST ONE
JUST CONFIRMED.
ALL SEATS FILLED
WITH APPROPRIATE SEATS.
IMPRESSIVE, BUT
WE'RE STILL REALLY BEHIND.
NOW I NEED YOU TO...
(HURRIED STEPS PATTER
AGAINST THE RUNWAY)
(GASPS)
ALEX:
PAIGE.
I, UM...
OKAY.
I COULDN'T GET THE-STUFF
TO EVERYONE.
PAIGE?
WE CAN'T HAVE THIS -
HER.
(PAIGE'S HEELS TAP)
(ALEX'S SNEAKERS SQUEAK)
ALEX, WHAT IS WRONG
WITH YOU?
YOU DIDN'T DELIVER
THE REMINDERS, DID YOU?
NO, 'CAUSE
I SAW THE INVOICE.
$3000 FOR CHOCOLATE?
THAT'S THREE MONTHS RENT
TO WHERE I COME FROM.
AND IF I HADN'T SPENT
THE LAST HOUR
FRANTICALLY CALLING PEOPLE
ABOUT THE SHOW,
I'D HAVE LOST MY JOB.
ALEX:
THIS ISN'T HAPPINESS,
PAIGE,
THIS IS A LAME TEMP GIG
THAT HAS YOU ACTING
LIKE A DIVA.
WHO ASKED YOU
TO JUDGE WHAT IS OKAY
FOR THIS COMPANY
OR ME?
I AM TRYING
TO START A CAREER
I ACTUALLY CARE ABOUT.
YOU ACTUALLY CARE ABOUT
THIS ARTIFICIAL CRAP?
PAIGE, YOU WRAP PRESENTS
AND IRON DRESSES
LIKE A MAID.
SORRY,
IF I HAVE PRINCIPLES.
(ANGERED EXHALE)
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU WERE BETTER OFF
AS A STRIPPER.
IT IS ALL GREAT
TO CLIMB UP
ON YOUR HIGH HORSE?
BUT AT LEAST THAT GIRL
WAS WORKING FOR SOMETHING.
(EXHALES)
ALEX, I'M DONE.
YESTERDAY, YOU WENT
TO THE POLLS TO DECIDE
WEATHER THE DEGRASSI
AND LAKEHURST TEAMS AND CLUBS
SHOULD BE SEPARATE
OR TOGETHER.
AND THE RESULTS ARE IN
WITH A RESOUNDING VOTE
IN FAVOUR OF UNIFYING
THE CLUBS AND TEAMS.
STUDENTS:
(ELATED CHEERS)
THANK YOU.
THING OF BEAUTY,
DEMOCRACY.
AND SPEAKING OF DEMOCRATIC
FREEDOM,
FEEL FREE TO TAKE
YOUR SEATS.
HEY,
IF IT'S ANY CONSOLATION,
YOU ARE AREN'T
TOTALLY WRONG.
SOME THINGS ARE BETTER
APART, LIKE US.
NO HARD FEELINGS?
ARE YOU KIDDING?
YOU TOTALLY BLIND-SIDED ME
IN FRONT OF THE WHOLE SCHOOL.
(EXHALES)
IT'S NOT MY FAULT
YOU SMART BOYS
ARE SO EASILY MANIPULATED.
OH, IS THAT
WHAT YOU THINK?
EVERYONE!
MANNY'S SEXIST-
JOKING.
VERY FUNNY.
SO YOU'RE SURE YOU
DON'T WANT TO GO OUT
ON ONE MORE DATE?
POSITIVE.
HOW ABOUT EMMA?
IS SHE SINGLE?
(SMIRKS)
PAIGE:
THEN I HAD TO RETURN
EVERYTHING
AFTER THE SHOW,
SO I BLEW EVERY CENT
I MADE ON TAXIS.
YEAH, BUT YOU STILL HAVE
YOUR JOB THOUGH, RIGHT?
ANDREA GAVE ME
A GIFT BAG,
SO UNLESS THAT'S CODE
FOR "MOVE ON, SISTER"?
IT'S CODE FOR
HOTTEST SHADES EVER.
(PATTER OF APPROACHING
FOOTSTEPS)
I THINK EVERYTHING'S
IN THERE.
(KEYS JINGLE)
WHERE YOU GONNA GO?
(SIGHS)
MY MOM HAS A COUSIN
IN AJAX.
I'LL FIND A JOB.
I GOT OPTIONS.
LOOK...
I'M SORRY.
I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE
GOOD FOR YOU HERE.
YEAH,
BUT I WAS STILL ALONE.
I LOST YOU
TO A FANTASY WORLD.
THIS IS THE RIGHT
THING TO DO.
BUT IT STILL HURTS.
YOU MAKE IT SOUND
LIKE COUGH SYRUP.
(SMIRKS)
(EXHALES)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)