TOBY:
HEY.
THOUGHT YOU'D BE AT THE DOT
CRAMMING FOR HISTORY.
PROM PLANS,
SCHOLARSHIP ESSAYS,
MY SPEECH...
MY BRAIN'S CHOCKABLOCK.
SO ARE YOU UP FOR A POST GRAD
REDEDICATION
OF THE JT YORKE
MEMORIAL ZEN GARDEN?
REALLY?
HATZILAKOS APPROVED IT?
YUP.
YOU, ME, EMMA AND MANNY
CAN HAVE A MOMENT
FOR OUR FALLEN HOMEY
RIGHT AFTER GRAD.
GOOD. I ALWAYS HAVE TIME
FOR JT'S MEMORY.
(FOOTSTEPS THUD ON STAIRS)
OOH! BETTER GET
A COUPLE TICKETS
FOR ME AND THE MISSUS.
OH, WHERE IS EMMA?
SHE AND MANNY ARE TALKING
PROM DRESSES... AGAIN.
YOU ALL SET FOR THE EXAM?
WELL,
MY ONLY QUESTION IS,
HOW WILL I CHEAT OFF
DEGRASSI'S SMARTEST GUY?
THE REAL QUESTION IS,
WILL DEGRASSI'S SEXY GENIUS
GET AN "A"
OR AN "A-PLUS"?
SEXY GENIUS?
THAT'S A NEW ONE.
(LIBERTY CHUCKLES,
CELL PHONE RINGS)
LIBERTY VAN ZANDT.
I SUBMITTED THAT ESSAY
WEEKS AGO.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?!
OF-OF COURSE!
UM, CNTO PLAYS TODAY'S
BEST HITS!
THANKS!
WHAT?
CNTO PLAYS TODAY'S BEST...
WHAT, WHAT-WHAT-WHAT?
I...
WE JUST WON A CONTEST,
AND NATASHA-FREAKING-BEDINGFIELD
IS PLAYING AT OUR PROM!
HOLY COW! THAT'S...
THAT'S CRAZY.
THAT'S AMAZING!
THAT'S HUGE!
(UNDER HER BREATH)
UM... YEAH.
♪♪♪
DARCY:
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE'VE ALMOST
MADE IT THROUGH THE WHOLE YEAR.
AH, PIECE OF CAKE,
DARCE.
NEXT YEAR, WE'RE GONNA BE
DEGRASSI'S HOTTEST COUPLE.
BORING LOSERS
WATCH OUT.
AND I HAVE AMAZING NEWS.
MY PARENTS WANT TO HAVE
YOU OVER FOR DINNER.
THEY WANT TO GET
TO KNOW YOU.
REALLY? SWEET.
DO YOU REALIZE
WHAT THIS MEANS?
NOW NOTHING'S
IN OUR WAY.
(CLOCK TICKS)
(BUZZER RINGS)
NAMES ON YOUR SHEETS,
DROP THEM UP FRONT,
AND HAVE A NICE LIFE.
DAMIAN:
SO... HOW'D YOU DO?
LIBERTY:
ENH, PRETTY GOOD.
DAMIAN:
(UNCLEAR COMMENT)
LIBERTY:
AS USUAL.
EMMA:
SOMETHING I SHOULD KNOW,
YOU TWO?
EVERY TIME I LOOK,
IT SEEMS LIKE YOU'RE IN ON
SOME KIND OF SECRET.
SHOULD I TELL HER?
UNH-HUNH.
ANNOUNCEMENT EVERYONE!
IF YOU HAVEN'T ALREADY PURCHASED
YOUR TICKETS,
DON'T MISS YOUR CHANCE
TO SEE NATASHA BEDINGFIELD
LIVE AT OUR PROM.
STUDENTS:
(APPLAUDING AND CHEERING)
FOR REAL? I MEAN "UNWRITTEN"
IS MY FAVOURITE SONG.
MANNY:
LIBERTY, YOU TOTALLY
RAISED THE PROM BAR!
WE'RE SO LUCKY.
I THINK WE'RE ALL GONNA
GET LUCKY TONIGHT.
NO, I MEAN,
(STAMMERS) CONCERT.
SHE'S SINGING,
IT'S FUN.
NICE... TOBES.
TOBY:
LIBERTY, UM...
I WAS... WONDERING
STRAPLESS CHIFFON
OR VAMPY SATIN?
UH...
I, I MEAN...
I WAS JUST WONDERING
WHAT DRESS
YOU WANTED TO WEAR
AS... MY DATE?
REALLY?
I'D LOVE TO, TOBES.
GREAT! GREAT, UH...
I'LL CATCH YA LATER,
DANCE PARTNER.
ABSOLUTELY, PROM DATE.
(LAUGHS)
COOL.
DAMIAN:
TOBY, HUH?
WHAT DID YOU EXPECT?
OPTION "A" WAS UNAVAILABLE.
(FOUNTAIN SPRINKLES,
PIANO MELODY PLAYS)
SPINNER:
HEY, JIMMY.
HEY, DON'T YOU ALL
LOOK SUPAFLY.
SWANKY DIGS
AND AN INTERNATIONAL
RECORDING ARTIST?
YOU GOTTA BRING IT.
DAMIAN:
WHOA.
OH...
MANNY:
HEY, CALL THE FIRE DEPARTMENT!
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
TOO ANYTHING?
EMMA:
GORGEOUS.
YOU HAVE COME A LONG WAY
SINCE GRADE SEVEN.
DID YOU GUYS EVER IMAGINE
WE'D BE DOING THIS?
IT'S SAD TO THINK
THAT WE'RE ALL GONNA BE
GOING IN DIFFERENT
DIRECTIONS SOON.
BUT EVERYTHING
THAT WE'VE BEEN THROUGH
HAS ONLY MADE
OUR FRIENDSHIPS STRONGER.
(HEARTFELT)
OH! BEST GIRLFRIENDS FOREVER.
AND... TOBY.
AW!
MANNY, LIBERTY AND EMMA:
(GIGGLE)
(URBAN BEAT PLAYS,
EXCITED CHATTER)
(STUDENT CHATTER)
OH.
HEY, AFTER I GET
NATASHA'S AUTOGRAPH,
WILL YOU SIGN MY YEARBOOK,
FOR MEMORY'S SAKE?
YEAH, WELL,
ONCE I'M AT BANTING
I'LL BE A VERY DISTANT ONE.
BANTING?
YEAH, I'VE BEEN ACCEPTED,
AND IF THE SCHOLARSHIP'S
WARRANT-
I'M GOING TO BANTING TOO!
YOU ARE?
YEAH.
MAYBE WE'LL BE SEEING
A LOT OF EACH OTHER.
I COULD GET INTO THAT.
NATASHA:
CHEERS DEGRASSI!
THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME
AT YOUR LOVELY PROM.
AND NOW LET'S TOAST
TO YOUR LUCKY CONTEST WINNER,
LIBERTY VAN ZANDT!
STUDENTS:
(APPLAUDING AND CHEERING)
THIS IS "POCKETFUL
OF SUNSHINE".
(BAND STARTS TO PLAY)
NATASHA:
(SINGS VARIOUS NOTES)
♪ I GOT A POCKET,
GOT A POCKETFUL OF SUNSHINE ♪
♪ I GOT A LOVE AND I KNOW
THAT IT'S ALL MY OWN ♪
♪ WHOA ♪
♪ DO WHAT YOU WANT ♪
♪ BUT YOU'RE NEVER
GONNA BREAK ME ♪
♪ STICKS AND STONES
ARE NEVER GONNA SHAKE ME ♪
♪ OH... ♪
♪ WHOA-OA... ♪
♪ TAKE ME AWAY
(TAKE ME AWAY) ♪
♪ A SECRET PLACE
(A SECRET PLACE) ♪
♪ A SWEET ESCAPE
(A SWEET ESCAPE) ♪
♪ TAKE ME AWAY
(TAKE ME AWAY) ♪
♪ TO BRIGHTER DAYS
(TO BRIGHTER DAYS) ♪
♪ TAKE ME AWAY
(TAKE ME AWAY) ♪
♪ OH HOW TO PLAY
(OH HOW TO PLAY) ♪
(SONG CONTINUES
AND FADES AWAY)
BYE, MOM.
I'M GOING OUT.
HOLD ON A SEC,
WE NEED TO TALK.
TALK? SCHOOL'S OVER.
YOU'RE NOT MY PRINCIPAL
ANYMORE.
WELL, I MAY NOT BE
ANYONE'S PRINCIPAL ANY MORE.
(PATS COUCH)
LOOK, YOU KNOW THAT
YOUR GIGIA'S HEALTH
HASN'T BEEN GOOD.
SO I'VE ASKED FOR
A LEAVE OF ABSENCE.
WE'RE GONNA BE MOVING
CLOSER TO HER
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
WHAT? MOM, GRANDMA LIVES
IN REGINA!
WHAT ABOUT MY FRIENDS?
WHAT ABOUT DARCY?
I KNOW YOU'RE GONNA MISS DARCY.
LOOK, I AM SORRY.
THE LAST THING I WANT TO DO
IS UPROOT YOUR LIFE AGAIN.
WELL, THEN DON'T.
YOU GO,
I'LL JUST STAY HERE.
I'VE BEEN GOOD.
PETER,
WE'VE TALKED ABOUT THIS.
YOU'VE COME A LONG WAY,
BUT YOU'VE HAD YOUR SHARE
OF TROUBLE.
I CANNOT LEAVE YOU
ON YOUR OWN.
DID YOU EVEN TALK TO DAD
ABOUT THIS?
CAN'T I JUST STAY WITH HIM
AND THE NEW LADY?
I'M SURE YOU CAN GUESS
WHAT HE HAD TO SAY.
I'M SORRY, I TRIED.
YEAH, WELL...
MAYBE YOU DIDN'T TRY
HARD ENOUGH.
PETER.
PETER:
I'M GOING OUT!
PETER!
(FRONT DOOR OPENS
AND SLAMS SHUT)
("UNWRITTEN" BY
NATASHA BEDINGFIELD PLAYS)
♪ I AM UNWRITTEN ♪
♪ CAN'T READ MY MIND ♪
♪ I'M UNDEFINED ♪
♪ I'M JUST BEGINNING ♪
♪ THE PENS IN MY HAND ♪
♪ ENDING UNPLANNED ♪
♪ STARING AT THE BLANK... ♪
I HAVE TO ASK YOU SOMETHING,
AS A FRIEND.
I HAVE SOMETHING
TO ASK YOU TOO,
BUT NOT JUST AS A FRIEND.
IT'S DAMIAN.
THERE'S AN UNDENIABLE
ATTRACTION BETWEEN US.
MY HEART SAYS ONE THING,
BUT...
I JUST KEEP THINKING
OF EMMA.
I THOUGHT I WAS YOUR DATE?
YEAH, YOU ARE,
AS A FRIEND...
LIKE ALWAYS.
WHY,
IS SOMETHING DIFFERENT?
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
IT'S JUST...
AS FOR DAMIAN?
I RECENTLY DISCOVERED THAT
FOLLOWING YOUR HEART SUCKS.
NATASHA:
(SINGS VARIOUS NOTES)
♪ OOH, OOH, OOH, YEAH! ♪
(STUDENTS JOIN IN)
♪ STARING AT THE BLANK PAGE
BEFORE YOU ♪
♪ OPEN UP THE DIRTY WINDOW ♪
♪ LET THE SUN ILLUMINATE
THE WORDS ♪
♪ THAT YOU COULD NOT FIND ♪
♪ REACHING FOR SOMETHING
IN THE DISTANCE ♪
♪ SO CLOSE YOU CAN
ALMOST TASTE IT ♪
NATASHA:
♪ RELEASE YOUR INHIBITIONS ♪
♪ FEEL THE RAIN ON YOUR SKIN ♪
♪ NO ONE ELSE
CAN FEEL IT FOR YOU ♪
♪ ONLY YOU CAN LET IT IN... ♪
GUYS?
GUYS,
I JUST HIT THE JACKPOT,
NEAR THE URINAL
IN THE MENSROOM.
NO SNAPPY COMEBACK?
I'M NOT GOING NEAR
THAT ONE.
OKAY.
THIS KEY GETS US
INTO THE POOL.
I JUST TRIED IT.
IT WORKS!
SO DID YOU GIRLS
PACK YOUR G-STRINGS
LIKE I TOLD YOU?
MANNY.
MANNY!
OH...
UH, (LAUGHS)
NICE TRY, SPIN,
BUT WE BROUGHT SWIMSUITS.
IN HERE.
WE WON'T BE SEEN.
SOUNDS NAUGHTY,
I LIKE IT.
YOU ARE
A NOTORIOUS FLIRT,
BUT I THINK THERE'S
SOMETHING HERE.
SOMETHING WE'RE BOTH
FEELING?
(PASSIONATE KISS)
WOW.
OH MY GOD,
I'M THE OTHER WOMAN.
CANNONBALL!!
(WATER SPLASHES)
(WATER SPLASHES OVER
PLAYFUL YELPS)
HELLO, FELLOW GRADUATES,
ARE WE ALL ENJOYING
OURSELVES?
HEY, WHERE WERE YOU GUYS?
JUST THANKING
NATASHA BEDINGFIELD.
JUST SETTLING UP
THE HOTEL BILL.
SO WHICH IS IT?
WELL, YOU'RE MISSING OUT
ON ALL THE FUN.
ARE YOU AFRAID
OF A LITTLE WATER?
DAMIAN:
NO, I'M NOT...
EMMA:
(LAUGHING)
DAMIAN:
HERE WE GO.
(WATER SPLASHES,
STUDENTS LAUGH)
MY DRESS.
MANNY:
RELAX, MY DAD CAN DRY CLEAN IT.
HEY.
STUDENTS:
(PLAYFUL CHATTER)
WHAT ABOUT
YOUR CONSCIENCE?
I SAW YOU AND DAMIAN
SNEAKING OUT TOGETHER.
AH, SIMPLE EXPLANATION...
SAVE IT.
IT'S OBVIOUS.
IT WAS A MOMENTARY LAPSE
OF REASON.
THE MORE WE TRIED TO RESIST,
THE MORE EXCITING IT BECAME.
SO YOU GUYS HOOKED UP?
ARE YOU TRYING TO RUIN
THE BEST NIGHT OF EMMA'S LIFE?
I'M SORRY, MANNY.
GUESS I SHOULD JUST
FACE THE MUSIC,
TELL EMMA?
AFTER GRADUATION.
BUT TONIGHT JUST...
KEEP YOUR MOUTH SHUT
AND STAY FAR AWAY
FROM DAIMAN.
SPINNER:
HEY, VALEVICTORIAN,
END THE YEAR WITH A SPLASH!
COME ON, JUMP!
STUDENTS:
(EXCITED HOLLERING)
JUMP! JUMP!
JUMP.
STUDENTS:
(WORDS OF ENCOURAGEMENT)
OKAY.
STUDENTS:
(EXCITED HOLLERING)
(WATER SPLASHES,
BUBBLES GURGLE)
(BUBBLES GURGLE OVER
MUTED CHEERS)
THANK YOU.
I'M SORRY WE'RE LATE,
SON.
TRAFFIC.
IT'S AFTER MIDNIGHT.
I KINDA WANTED TO TALK TO YOU
IN PRIVATE.
ANYTHING YOU HAVE TO SAY,
YOU CAN SAY IT
IN FRONT OF MY FIANCEE.
MUST BE PRETTY IMPORTANT,
DRAGGING US AWAY
FROM THE CASINO.
I WAS ON A RUN.
MOM SAYS WE'RE MOVING.
I KNOW.
YOU KNOW, YOUR GRANDMA'S
GONNA BE BE HAPPY
TO HAVE YOU AND YOUR MOM
CLOSE BY.
YEAH, BUT...
I HAVE A LIFE HERE,
CAN'T I JUST STAY
WITH YOU?
YOUR MOM BROUGHT THAT UP,
PETE.
I MEAN, SHE DOESN'T WANT
TO TAKE YOU AWAY.
COOL,
SO I'LL MOVE IN?
(UNCOMFORTABLE BREATHS)
MISSY AND I HAVE
A LIFE TOO.
AND WITH THE BABY,
WE...
WE JUST...
WE WON'T HAVE ROOM.
I'M YOUR SON,
YOU CAN MAKE ROOM.
MR. STONE:
LOOK, YOU'RE JUST BEST OFF
WITH YOUR MOM.
REGINA'S NOT SO BAD.
MAYBE YOU AND I CAN
CATCH AN ARGOS GAME
BEFORE YOU GO.
(EXHALES)
(WATER SPLASHING,
EXCITED YELPS)
OH.
STUDENTS:
(LAUGHING)
DON'T YOU WISH JT
WERE HERE?
YOUR RECENTLY DECEASED
EX-BOYFRIEND?
YOU KNOW,
YOU REMEMBER THAT TIME...
TOBY.
JT'S VIRTUALLY THE LAST THING
ON MY MIND RIGHT NOW.
HOW CAN YOU EVEN SAY THAT?
I HAVE MORE PRESSING
CONCERNS.
I FOLLOWED MY HEART
AND IT DID NOT SUCK,
DESPITE WHAT YOU SAY.
(SHIVERS)
HEY,
HOW'S THE DATE GOING?
IT'S... OKAY.
TOBY KNOWS ABOUT US
AND HE CAN KEEP A SECRET.
RIGHT, PROM DATE?
SO SHE TOLD YOU WE HAD OURSELVES
A LITTLE FUN, HUH?
FUN? AS IN SEX?
OH, NO. I HAD TO KEEP
THE BRAKES ON THAT.
GIRL IS WILD!
(RAGGED SIGH)
HEY, THANKS FOR KEEPING IT
ON THE DOWN-LOW, HUH?
LIBERTY SAID YOU'D DO
ANYTHING FOR HER.
TOBY:
(LOUDLY)
OH, DON'T WORRY,
I WON'T TELL ANYONE
THAT LIBERTY AND DAMIAN
FOOLED AROUND
AND NOW HE'S BRAGGING
ABOUT IT!
(UNDER HER BREATH)
SNAP.
TOBY, YOU'RE KIDDING,
RIGHT?
HE'S NOT, EM.
EMMA:
OH MY GOD, AM I THE ONLY ONE
THAT DIDN'T KNOW ABOUT THIS?
I WAS GOING
TO TELL YOU.
EMMA:
YEAH, BECAUSE THAT MAKES IT
SO MUCH BETTER.
THANKS FOR RUINING
MY PROM NIGHT, PIG!
EVERYBODY OUT.
NOW!
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
MY VALEDICTORIAN SPEECH
EMPHASIZES THE IMPORTANCE
OF FRIENDSHIP.
IRONIC.
NICE TIMING.
(INHALES AND EXHALES)
YOU'RE MOVING TO REGINA?!
WELL, MY MOM IS
SO, SO AM I.
YOU CAN'T.
NOT, NOT NOW.
EVERYTHING'S JUST STARTING
TO COME TOGETHER FOR US.
PLEASE, DON'T GO.
WHAT CAN WE DO?
ELOPE?
ELOPE AND GO WHERE?
MY STUPID DIVORCED PARENTS.
DARCY:
I WISH YOU COULD GET
DIVORCED FROM THEM.
WAIT.
DARCY,
THERE'S TOTALLY A WAY.
MR. VAN ZANDT'S A LAWYER.
HE'S HERE FOR GRAD.
OKAY, AND...?
I'M GONNA MAKE IT
SO NO ONE CAN TELL ME
WHAT TO DO.
TRUST ME.
(EXCITED CHATTER)
EMMA JUST DUMPED ME.
ANY CHANCE YOU NEED
A PRACTICE AUDIENCE?
WHY BOTHER?
JUST LIKE YOU AND MANNY
AND YOU AND EMMA,
YOU AND I WILL UNDOUBTEDLY
AMOUNT TO NOTHING.
YOU REALLY WANT IT
TO GO DOWN LIKE THIS?
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO STAND
IN FRONT OF MY FRIENDS -
OH, MY FORMER FRIENDS -
AND TRY TO SUMMARIZE
WHAT SIX YEARS OF FRIENDSHIP
HAS MEANT TO ME?
IF THEY'RE REAL FRIENDS,
THEY'LL UNDERSTAND.
LIBERTY:
ACQUIRING AN EDUCATION
IS ABOUT MORE THAN EARNING
A DIPLOMA.
IT'S ALSO ABOUT YOUR FRIENDS
WHO HAVE SEEN YOU
IN YOUR WORST MOMENTS
AND LOVE YOU JUST THE SAME.
UNFORTUNATELY, ONE FRIEND
DID NOT FINISH THE JOURNEY.
HIS NAME IS
JAMES TIBERIUS YORKE.
IF JT'S DEATH
HAS TAUGHT ME ANYTHING,
IT'S THAT THE WORST MISTAKES
ARE THE ONES YOU NEVER
LEARN FROM.
AND ALSO,
TO NEVER EVER
TAKE YOUR FRIENDS FOR GRANTED.
(WELLING UP)
I'M SORRY.
(CONFUSED CHATTER)
(AUDITORIUM DOOR OPENS)
(CONFUSED CHATTER,
AUDITORIUM DOOR SHUTS)
THIS IS OBVIOUSLY
AN EMOTIONAL TIME
FOR OUR GRADUATES.
ARE YOU OKAY?
I ONLY RUINED THE HAPPIEST
DAY OF OUR LIVES
WITH MY ASININE SELFISHNESS.
I UNDERSTAND IF YOU'RE FURIOUS
WITH ME RIGHT NOW.
I AM... WITH DAMIAN.
I AM NOT READY TO THROW AWAY
SIX YEARS OF OUR FRIENDSHIP.
IT'S LIKE YOU SAID,
IT'S ONLY A MISTAKE
IF YOU NEVER LEARN FROM IT.
TOBY:
YOU'VE DONE SO MUCH FOR US
AND FOR THE WHOLE SCHOOL,
I THINK YOU DESERVE
TO BE CUT SOME SLACK.
LOTS OF IT.
I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER BEEN
CUT SLACK BEFORE.
DUDE,
I COULD BUNGEE JUMP
WITH ALL THE SLACK
I'VE BEEN CUT.
WANNA HEAD BACK IN THERE?
COME ON,
WE'VE GOT SOME SERIOUS
GRADUATING TO DO.
("UNWRITTEN" BY
NATASHA BEDINGFIELD PLAYS)
HATZILAKOS:
TOBY ISAACS.
♪ I am unwritten ♪
♪ Can't read my mind ♪
♪ I'm undefined ♪
GAVIN MASON.
AUDIENCE:
(EMPHATIC CHEERING
AND APPLAUDING)
♪ I'm just beginning... ♪
EMMA NELSON.
♪ The pen's in my hand ♪
♪ Ending unplanned ♪
♪ Staring at the blank page
before me ♪
MANNY SANTOS.
♪ Open up the dirty window ♪
♪ Let the sun illuminate
the words ♪
♪ That you could not find ♪
♪ Reaching for something
in the distance ♪
AND LIBERTY VAN ZANDT.
♪ So close you can almost
taste it ♪
♪ Release your inhibitions ♪
♪ Feel the rain on your skin ♪
CONGRATULATIONS
TO THE DEGRASSI CLASS OF 2007!
STUDENTS:
(CHEERING)
♪ No one else
No one else ♪
♪ Can speak the words
on your lips ♪
♪ Drench yourself
in words unspoken ♪
♪ Live your life
with arms wide open ♪
♪ Today is where
your book begins ♪
♪ The rest is still unwritten ♪
PETER:
DANNY?
CAN I TALK TO YOUR DAD
ABOUT SOME LEGAL STUFF?
DANNY:
SURE. WE JAMMING TOMORROW?
YOU KNOW IT!
STUDZ RULES.
YOU NEED SOME, UH,
LEGAL ADVICE?
HOW DOES A GUY
GET EMANCIPATED?
(HALF LAUGHS)
EMANCIPATED.
YOU SURE YOU KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS?
YEAH, I SAW IT
ON THE SIMPSONS.
BART GETS EMANCIPATED
FROM HIS PARENTS
THEN HE MOVES IN
NEXT TO TONY HAWK?
(UNDER BREATH)
OH BOY.
WE CAN TALK ABOUT THIS
IN MY OFFICE,
BUT GENERALLY,
THERE'S THREE WAYS...
♪ ...in words unspoken ♪
♪ Live your life
with arms wide open ♪
♪ Today is where
your book begins ♪
♪♪♪