GET HIM!
STUDENTS:
(SHOUTING ENCOURAGEMENT)
GET HIM!
(KNUCKLES CRACK)
(DEEP EXHALE)
(THWACK)
UGH!
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
SPINNER:
VICTORY FOR TEAM THUNDERHEART!
JIMMY:
THIS IS EXACTLY
WHAT WE NEEDED.
ARE YOU SURE
IT WAS ALL YOUR IDEA?
SPINNER:
WELL, I AM A BRIDGE-BUILDING,
PEACE-MAKING,
LOVE-SPREADING MANIAC.
YEAH? THAT'S WHY YOU
PUNCHED JOHNNY
IN THE CHOPS
YESTERDAY?
YOU KNOW,
THE OLIVE BRANCH
IS MIGHTIER THAN
THE SWORD, MY MAN.
DUDE,
A SWORD CAN EASILY...
WHAT'S GOING DOWN
IN JUNK TOWN?
YOU EVER TAKE THAT CALL
FROM THE DOC?
(EXHALES)
YEAH,
IT'S THE BIG C, DUDE.
CANCER.
WOW. MAN, THAT'S...
THEY'RE SURE?
YEAH, I'M GOING
TO THE ONCOLOGIST TODAY
TO FIND OUT WHAT I GOTTA DO.
WELL, I MEAN,
THERE'S A GOOD-
THERE'S A GOOD CHANCE
YOU COULD BEAT IT, RIGHT?
(SCOFFS)
SURE, DUDE.
NO PROBLEM.
(INHALES)
HEY, THANKS FOR AIMING
AT MY CROTCH, HUH?
♪♪♪
STUDENTS:
(CLAPPING AND CHEERING)
HATZILAKOS:
ALL RIGHT, WE'D LIKE
TO THANK YOU ALL
FOR MAKING THE FIRST ANNUAL
UNITY GAMES A HUGE SUCCESS!
ALL:
(CLAPPING AND HOLLERING)
AND A SPECIAL THANKS
TO THE BRAINS
BEHIND TODAY'S EVENTS,
GAVIN MASON!
STUDENTS:
(CHEERING AND CLAPPING)
HATZILAKOS:
SO EVERYONE CAN PROCEED
TO THEIR CLASSES AFTER LUNCH...
DEREK:
DUDE, DUDE, DUDE, DUDE!
YOU'RE OUR HERO.
CHECK IT.
WE UPLOADED IT
THIS MORNING.
WHAT'D YOU...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHY DID YOU DO THAT?
SO EVERYONE COULD SEE YOU
LAY A SMACKDOWN
ON STUPID JOHNNY'S
STUPID LAKEHURST FACE.
NO, NO-NO-NO.
NO ONE CAN SEE THAT,
OKAY?
EAT IT, BURN IT,
I DON'T CARE.
DANNY:
WHOA, WHOA,
IT'S TOO LATE.
IT'S ALREADY ALL OVER
MYROOMPAGEVIDEO.
WHOA, DON'T KILL ME, SIR.
JUST...
ANNOUNCEMENT:
NEWSFLASH, THIS JUST IN:
ANY STUDENT INTERESTED IN
WRITING FOR A GREATER CAUSE,
COME TO THE RESOURCE CENTER
AFTER SCHOOL TODAY.
(MOUSE CLICKS,
COMPUTER BEEPS)
SO YOU DITCH
OUR GAME OF POOL
AND THEN AVOID ME?
YOU WANNA TELL ME
WHAT THE HELL IS UP?
I CAN'T TALK RIGHT NOW,
JANE.
TOO BAD,
THAT'S WHAT SEPARATES US
FROM THE CAVE PEOPLE.
THOUGH YOU HAVE BEEN ACTING
PRETTY CRO-MAGNON.
THEN LET'S JUST NIP THIS
IN THE BUD, OKAY?
QUIT SEEING EACH OTHER.
UM, DO I GET AN EXPLANATION
AT ALL?
IT'S JUST SOME DUDE ISSUES,
OKAY?
IT'S NOTHING.
SO...
THAT HOW YOU WORK OUT
YOUR DUDE ISSUES?
I'M NOT THE GUY
YOU THINK I AM.
LOOK, I'VE KNOWN JOHNNY
FOR A LONG TIME.
HE GOT WHAT HE DESERVED.
BUT YOU'VE GOT
YOUR ISSUES,
SO... SEE YA.
(THUMPS DESK)
(DOOR OPENS AND SHUTS)
READY FOR
THE CHUCK KLOSTERMAN TALK?
I CAN'T THINK OF A BETTER WAY
TO PROCRASTINATE.
OH, WELL,
THAT SOUNDS COOL.
YOU GUYS GOT
AN EXTRA TICKET?
ACTUALLY, IT'S FREE,
BUT UM...
MARCO:
UH, IT'S OKAY.
YOU GUYS CAN GO AHEAD,
I WANNA FINISH THIS.
(TAKES A DEEP BREATH)
WHAT'S A THREE LETTER
WORD FOR 7, 8, 9?
OKAY,
GOING TO A SOUND CLASH
TONIGHT.
GONNA BE AN ABUNDANCE
OF LADIES THERE.
WHICH SHIRT?
WRONG ROOMMATE.
PAIGE IS THE ONE
WITH THE FASHION CONNECTIONS.
YEAH, BUT YOU GOT
ALL THE STYLE.
WELL... THAT ONE.
THAT ONE LOOKS LIKE
YOU'RE TRYING TOO HARD.
BUT I AM TRYING HARD.
(CHUCKLES)
YEAH, BUT THAT ONE SAYS
YOU'RE CONFIDENT,
YET VULNERABLE, SEE.
OOH! YOU'RE GOOD.
IF THIS WORKS,
I OWE YOU A SOLID.
I'LL HOLD YOU TO THAT.
HEY, UH, WHAT'RE YOU
DOING TONIGHT?
NOT MUCH.
WORKING ON MY SHODOKI.
(SURPRISED GASP)
NEVER REALLY FIGURED YOU
FOR THE MARTIAL ARTS TYPE.
UM, YOU SHOULD COME.
I COULD ALWAYS USE
A WING MAN.
REALLY?
NAH, I WOULDN'T WANT
TO CRAMP YOUR STYLE.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
GAY DUDES ARE CHICK BAIT.
AND IF THE FISH
AREN'T BITING,
WE COULD ALWAYS
JUST HANG OUT, RIGHT?
(REGGAE MUSIC PLAYS)
OH, MAN,
YOU ARE RIPE.
I HOPE YOU'RE GONNA SHOWER
BEFORE CLASS.
SO... I LOOKED UP
TESTICULAR CANCER.
IT'S NOT A DEATH SENTENCE,
SPIN.
OH, DOCTOR JIMMY
TO THE RESCUE.
JIMMY:
THEY CAN TREAT THIS.
IT'S LIKE 80 OR 90 PERCENT
CURABLE.
I GUESS YOU JUST
WANNA LOOK RIPPED
NEXT TIME YOU FIGHT
DIMARCO?
JOHNNY DESERVED IT,
MAN.
ACTION EQUALS RESULTS.
THAT VIDEO IS POSTED
AS DEGRASSI VS. LAKEHURST.
DO YOU REALLY THINK
THAT HELPS UNIFY THE SCHOOLS?
(WEIGHTS BANG)
WHY IS IT UP TO ME
TO MAKE SURE EVERYONE
GETS ALONG?
(CHUCKLES)
I DON'T KNOW MR. PEACE
AND UNITY COMMITTEE.
YOU'RE FANNING THE FLAMES
JUST LIKE WE DID
BACK THEN.
OR DID YOU FORGET
HOW I ENDED UP IN THIS CHAIR?
YOU KNOW IT'S EASY FOR SOMEONE
WHO CAN'T FIGHT
TO CHOOSE NOT TO.
(OFFENDED HUFF)
AND HAVING CANCER
DOESN'T GIVE YOU THE RIGHT
TO BE A JACKASS.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
ANNOUNCEMENT:
CALLING ALL FASHION STUDENTS.
STUDENTS INTERESTED
IN PERFORMING
IN THIS YEARS
(UNCLEAR) PAGEANT,
SHOULD STAMP ON DOWN
TO THE GYMNASIUM
AFTER SCHOOL TODAY.
JOHNNY,
I WANT TO APOLOGIZE
ABOUT THE FIGHT, OKAY?
I LOST MY COOL.
YOU KNOW, I'M LOVING
THE PEACE AND LOVE ACT, GAVIN.
LOOK, WE GOTTA STOP THIS
LAKEHURST-DEGRASSI CRAP,
OKAY?
ALL RIGHT, WHO CARES
ABOUT THAT, ALL RIGHT?
WE'RE FAMOUS.
DUDE, ARE YOU INSANE?
THE VIDEO IS OUT THERE
AND EVERYONE CAN SEE IT.
JOHNNY:
EXACTLY.
LOOK, THIS IS ABOUT
PUTTING ON A SHOW.
WHEN GUYS SQUARE OFF,
PEOPLE WANT TO WATCH.
GREAT, I HAVE BETTER THINGS
TO WORRY ABOUT.
JOHNNY:
WELL, IF YOU EVER DECIDE
TO MAN-UP?
MY BUDDY BRUCE HERE'S
A BIT RUSTY,
HE'D LOVE A SHOT AT YOU.
RUFF, RUFF, RUFF!
JOHNNY AND CREW:
(SNICKER)
BEING TOLD
YOU HAVE CANCER
IS ONE OF THE SCARIEST THINGS
IMAGINABLE.
BUT WE'LL STAY POSITIVE
AND BEGIN AGGRESSIVE TREATMENT.
FIRST, I HIGHLY RECOMMEND
AN ORCHIECTOMY.
AWESOME,
SIGN ME UP.
THAT MEANS WE REMOVE
THE TESTICLE.
OH.
UM, SO THEN YOU, UM,
YOU ZAP IT,
AND YOU PUT IT BACK IN
AND YOU SEW ME UP, RIGHT?
IT DOESN'T WORK
QUITE LIKE THAT.
ONCE IT'S GONE,
IT'S GONE.
MRS. MASON:
BUT WILL HE STILL BE ABLE TO,
YOU KNOW,
GIVE ME GRANDCHILDREN?
(NERVOUS BREATH)
MOM!
ONCOLOGIST:
ABSOLUTELY.
BUT YOU'LL STILL NEED CHEMO
OR RADIATION THERAPY.
OKAY, WAIT.
WHAT IF I, UM,
WHAT IF I CHANGE MY MIND?
NO OPERATION, NO CHEMO,
THEN WHAT?
THE CANCER WILL SPREAD.
YOU COULD DIE IN MONTHS,
MAYBE WEEKS.
I'LL BOOK THE PROCEDURE
FOR TOMORROW.
HOW DOES AFTER SCHOOL SOUND?
(CLIPPERS BUZZ)
("To A Friend" by Alexisonfire)
♪ You shouldn't have
to fight alone ♪
♪ It's nobody's battle
but your own ♪
(CLIPPERS BUZZ)
(Screaming)
♪ I think it's time to get out ♪
♪ My pictures are fading fast ♪
♪ My bruises just a little bit
easier ♪
♪ Dark times
these shadows cast ♪
(Singing)
♪ What are you suffering for ♪
♪ You're proud of some kind
of personal war ♪
♪ I'll stay in time
and watch you pass by... ♪
(GRUNT OF EFFORT)
(CRASHES INTO GARAGE)
ARGH!
YOU WANT A SHOW?
YOU GOT ONE.
COME ON, JOHNNY,
CAMERA'S ARE ROLLING, MAN.
WAIT, MAN,
CHILL, ALL RIGHT?
SORRY, JOHNNY-BOY,
"MAN-UP!"
(HARD KICK, SCUFFLING)
(HARD PUNCHES,
PAINED GRUNTS)
GET HIM OFF!
(STRUGGLING GRUNTS)
(Screaming)
♪ Oh, there's no relief! ♪
♪ Oh, this won't get off of me ♪
(GRITTED TEETH)
YEAH!
(GROANS IN PAIN)
(Singing)
♪ I'll stay in time
and watch you pass by ♪
(APPROACHING CAR HONKS)
♪ I'll draw this line
and hope you'll take my side ♪
♪ You shouldn't have
to fight alone ♪
(LAUGHING)
♪ It's nobody's fight
but your own ♪
DANNY:
YOU'RE TOP TEN
ON MYROOMPAGEVIDEO, SIR.
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE MISSED
THE JOHNNY LOSERFACE SMACKDOWN
LAST NIGHT!
YEAH, WELL, GOOD THING
THERE'S VIDEO EVIDENCE.
AND NOW THERE'S
A RUMOUR
ABOUT YOU
AND BRUCE THE MOOSE.
SO YOU GUYS GONNA
STEP INTO THE RING,
OR WHAT?
IF IT HAPPENS,
WE'LL BE THERE.
WITH A CAMERA
AND A BODY-BAG.
SIMPSON:
MR. MASON.
(IRRITATED SIGH)
WE DON'T APPRECIATE PEOPLE
POSTING FIGHTS ONLINE
UNDER THE SCHOOL'S NAME.
IF YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT
THE REPUTATION OF THE SCHOOL,
HOW ABOUT YOU GO AFTER
THE PEOPLE
WHO POSTED THE VIDEOS?
I AM.
BUT IF YOU KEEP
THIS UP,
THE POLICE ARE GONNA
GET INVOLVED.
(SIGHS)
(LOCK RATTLES,
LOCKER CLINKS OPEN)
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
JANE?
I WON'T BITE.
JANE:
REALLY?
I CAUGHT YOUR LATEST
PERFORMANCE ONLINE.
NOT COOL,
DESPITE THE NEW 'DO.
WHAT HAPPENED TO
"JOHNNY HAD IT COMING"?
THIS IS DIFFERENT.
WAY DIFFERENT.
IT'S LIKE YOU BECAME
SOME KIND OF MONSTER.
EVERYONE'S SCARED OF YOU,
SO AM I.
LOOK, WHATEVER
YOUR ISSUES ARE,
YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN,
OKAY?
(LOCKER BANGS)
I HAVE
TESTICULAR CANCER.
THEY'RE GONNA RIP IT OUT
AFTER SCHOOL.
HOW'S THAT FOR ISSUES?
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY.
DON'T BOTHER.
I HAVE TO SHOW EVERYONE
I'M STILL A MAN.
SPINNER, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO PROVE THAT
BY BASHING SOME GUY.
YOU'RE A GIRL,
YOU DON'T GET IT.
LIKE YOU SAID,
I'M ON MY OWN.
(DOOR OPENS)
GRIFFIN:
I'M LATE.
AH, MARCO,
HOW DO I LOOK?
PERF! BANG ON.
GRIFFIN:
BEAUTY.
(TURNS TAP ON)
(DOOR SHUTS)
OH, LAST NIGHT,
ACTUALLY WE HAD THE MOST
KILLER TIME.
HIM AND I, WE-
UH HUH.
I LIKE HIM -
AS A FRIEND.
AND DOES YOUR FRIEND KNOW
THAT YOU'RE "IN LIKE"
WITH HIM?
WHAT?
FIRST, YOU HANG OUT
WITH ERIC
EVEN THOUGH YOU TWO
ARE GOING NOWHERE.
AND NOW
NOT-EVEN-GAY GRIFFIN?
MAN, YOU REALLY CAN'T
BE ALONE, CAN YOU?
(CHUCKLES)
THAT IS NOT TRUE.
IT'S JUST THAT SOMETIMES,
MARCO,
YOU CAN GET
A LITTLE INTENSE.
I CAN'T HELP IT.
I'M A PEOPLE PERSON.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
GET A PET.
OH, WELL,
THAT'S FUNNY, ELL.
HILARE.
SORRY,
I'LL BACK OFF.
THERE IS NOTHING WRONG
WITH YOU AND GRIFFIN
BEING FRIENDS.
FROM ONE STYLIST
TO ANOTHER,
MAYBE YOU GUYS
SHOULD CHECK THIS OUT.
IT CAME INTO WORK.
IT'S A HUGE SALE.
(PAPER RUSTLES)
(STUDENT CHATTER)
JOHNNY:
YOU WIN, MR. UNITY GAMES.
PEACE, LOVE, HARMONY,
ALL OF THAT.
SO THAT'S HOW YOU "MAN-UP"?
WHATEVER.
SIMPSON'S TALKING
ABOUT CALLING THE COPS,
SO FORGET IT.
YOU'RE SAFE,
JOHNNY-BOY.
I WANT HIM.
AFTER SCHOOL.
BRING THE CAMERAS.
(SNORTS)
YOU'RE DEAD.
PLAYERS:
OH. ALL RIGHT!
(JIMMY BLOWS WHISTLE)
ALL RIGHT,
GREAT PRACTICE!
THE TWO TEAMS ARE REALLY
COMING TOGETHER.
YOU GUYS ARE FREE TO GO.
UM, DO YOUR STRETCHES,
HIT THE SHOWERS, WHATEVER,
I WILL SEE YOU TOMORROW MORNING,
ALL RIGHT?
PLAYERS:
THANKS. GOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
HEY, COACH,
GOT A SEC FOR SOMEONE
YOU BARELY KNOW?
JANE, RIGHT?
YEAH, UM...
THIS MIGHT SOUND STRANGE,
BUT...
HAVE YOU NOTICED
ANY SPINNER WEIRDNESS?
(HALF LAUGHS)
UM...
THE DAY I MET HIM.
EVERY DAY SINCE.
SO YOU KNOW ABOUT
HIS CONDITION...
DOWN THERE?
YEAH,
IT'S TOUGH I GUESS.
SO THEN YOU MUST
ALSO KNOW
HE'S ON HIS WAY TO FIGHT
BRUCE THE MOOSE.
EVERYONE'S TALKING
ABOUT IT.
LOOK, JANE, UM...
THERE'S NO GETTING THROUGH
THAT THICK SKULL OF HIS.
OKAY, SO MAYBE IF THE GUY GETS
THE CRAP KICKED OUT OF HIM-
THAT'S NOT THE POINT.
HE'S GONNA MISS
HIS OPERATION.
GUY'S A GROWN-UP.
HE'S GOTTA TAKE CARE
OF HIMSELF.
HE'S REALLY SICK,
JIMMY.
HE NEEDS A FRIEND,
OR HE COULD DIE.
(DISBELIEVING EXHALE)
WE GOT A PROBLEM CAUSE-
THANK YOU.
ALL OUR (UNCLEAR)
IS IN SECTION C-
MARCO:
GRIFFIN! BUDDY!
HEY, RECOVERED
FROM LAST NIGHT?
'CAUSE LIKE I'M RUNNING
ON FUMES RIGHT NOW.
HEY, MARCO,
WHAT'S UP?
AH, JUST A SOLUTION
TO YOUR CLOTHING DILEMMA.
HIGH-END GEAR
AT BARGAIN BASEMENT
PRICES, HERE.
(CHUCKLES)
COOL, UM...
BUT LISTEN, MARCO,
WE'RE KIND OF IN
THE MIDDLE OF TALKING
ABOUT, YOU KNOW,
ENGINEERING STUFF, SO...
OH. YEAH, OF COURSE.
AH, YOU GUYS GET BACK
TO BRIDGE-BUILDING.
I'LL-I'LL JUST...
BUT HEY!
WE COULD HIT THE SALE TONIGHT.
SEE YOU AT THE HOMESTEAD?
IT'S A DATE!
UH...
A PLAN. IT'S A PLAN.
COOL.
LATER.
SORRY.
LAST TIME BRUCE
THE MOOSE FOUGHT?
SENT THE GUY
TO THE HOSPITAL
THEN ATE HIS
SKATEBOARD.
YEAH, THE ODDS
ARE AGAINST YOU,
BUT, UH, IF YOU WIN,
I'M LOOKING AT 10 BUCKS.
WHAT, PEOPLE THINK
I'LL LOSE THE FIGHT?
WELL, SOME TEETH,
MAYBE YOUR LIFE.
SIR.
JOHNNY'S CREW:
(CHATTING)
I'M NOT TOO LATE
FOR THE SHOW, AM I?
DUDE, I KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE GONNA SAY.
YOU GOT YOUR MIND
MADE UP,
I CAN'T CHANGE IT.
YEAH, THEN WHAT ARE
YOU DOING HERE?
I KNOW HOW IT FEELS
TO HAVE YOUR BODY
LET YOU DOWN.
BATTLING CANCER
IS GONNA BE SCARY.
YOU'RE GONNA FEEL SICK,
REALLY SICK.
ALL I KNOW,
IS IF YOU WANT TO LIVE?
YOU CAN'T BEAT CANCER
WITH YOUR FISTS.
BRUCE:
ARE YOU COMING OR WHAT?
IF YOU'RE GONNA DO THIS,
BE SMART.
PROTECT YOUR FACE,
FISTS UP.
YOU DON'T WANT TO RUIN
THAT MODELLING CAREER.
(CHUCKLES)
THANKS, DUDE.
(IMPATIENT CHATTER)
GRIFFIN:
HOW WAS THE SALE?
I DIDN'T GO.
BECAUSE OF ME?
SORRY, DUDE.
THIS GIRL CALLED,
YOU KNOW HOW IT IS.
WELL, HOW IS IT,
EXACTLY?
(CHUCKLES)
THIS GIRL CALLED.
COME ON,
YOU DON'T GET IT?
MUST BE THE GAY THING.
OH, REALLY.
IS THE "GAY THING"
GONNA BE A PROBLEM?
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
NO, WELL, I'M JUST SAYING,
MAYBE WE NEED TO RETHINK
THE LIVING SITUATION
AROUND HERE.
LOOK, I'M SORRY I BAILED,
BUT I DID LEAVE A NOTE.
(SNORTED LAUGH)
WHAT'S THIS ALL ABOUT?
IT'S ABOUT BUILDING
A RELATIONSHIP.
(CHUCKLES)
IT'S NOT A RELATIONSHIP,
MARCO.
YOU'RE JUST MY ROOMMATE.
(SIGHS)
RISE AND SHINE.
WHAT TIME IS IT?
MRS. MASON:
AROUND MIDNIGHT.
YOU'VE BEEN SLEEPING FOR HOURS.
HOW'RE YOU FEELING?
LIKE A SELF-DEFENSE
PRACTICE TARGET.
I'M PROUD OF YOU,
GAVIN.
YOUR DAD WOULD BE TOO.
DID THEY KEEP IT?
GAVE YOU A DOGGIE BAG.
(TAKES A DEEP BREATH)
HEY, BUDDY...
PAIGE:
MARCO, THAT YOU?
AH...
PAIGE:
WHERE'S ELLIE?
STILL CHEATING ON YOU
WITH HER BOYFRIEND?
YEAH, (CHUCKLES)
TWO NIGHTS AND COUNTING.
PAIGE:
AND UH,
WHAT ABOUT GRIFFIN?
AH, HE MET A NEW GIRL.
PAIGE:
GOD, POOR YOU.
BETWEEN MY JOB
AND EVERYONE ELSE'S LOVE LIVES-
MARCO:
IT'S COOL.
I MEAN, YOU'VE ADJUSTED,
YOU KNOW, TO LIFE POST ALEX.
AND...
PAIGE:
THE LAST THING I NEED RIGHT NOW
IS A RELATIONSHIP.
AND, HON,
BEING SINGLE DOESN'T MEAN
YOU HAVE TO BE ALONE.
I'M STARTING
TO FIGURE THAT OUT.
HAVE FUN AT WORK.
(RELIEVED EXHALE)
(DOOR SHUTS)
COME HERE.
HEY...
GET READY,
HIP-HOP,
CAUSE YOU AND I
ARE GONNA BE SPENDING
A LOT OF TIME TOGETHER.
HOW'S IT GOIN',
PRECIOUS?
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
ANNOUNCEMENT:
FOR ALL ENRICHMENT STUDENTS,
THE BUS TO THE GREATER
TORONTO...
WILL LEAVE THE MAIN PARKING LOT
AT 3:30 SHARP.
(STUDENT CHATTER)
SPINNER:
JANE. JANE! WAIT UP.
JANE.
SO, I'M PRETTY BUSTED.
I CAN SEE THAT,
AND LIMPY.
YEAH, JOHNNY AND I GOT FINES
AND DETENTION UP THE YIN YANG.
THEY MIGHT CHARGE
THE OTHER GUYS FOR FILMING.
UH-HUH.
AND WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
I'M NOT STILL MAD AT YOU?
LOOK, FROM NOW ON,
THERE'S ONLY ONE THING
I'M GONNA BE FIGHTING.
CANCER...?
I JUST WANTED TO SEE
IF YOU COULD SAY IT.
SO YOU MADE IT
TO YOUR OPERATION?
YUP,
WITH 10 MINUTES TO SPARE.
AND YOU'RE BACK
SO SOON? WOW.
WELL, MOST OF ME IS.
JANE:
GOD FORBID YOU MISS ANY SCHOOL
AFTER A MAJOR JUNK-ECTOMY.
YEAH, WELL, I DO HAVE
CHEMO COMING UP.
SO I FIGURE THAT WILL COUNT
AS A SICK DAY OR TWO.
JEEZ, MILK IT,
WHY DON'T YA?
DON'T MAKE ME LAUGH,
I'M TENDER.
I ALWAYS KNEW YOU WERE,
DUDE.
SEE YA.