ANNOUNCEMENT:
HEY, DEGRASSI BOOKWORMS,
THE DEGRASSI READATHON
STARTS NOW.
MAN, DETENTION SUCKS.
BRUCE:
WHAT'S A GUY GOTTA DO
TO GET SENT TO HER OFFICE?
JOHNNY:
OH, I WOULD LOVE
TO SPEND SOME ALONE TIME
WITH PRINCIPAL
HOT SAUCE.
WOO!
SO YOU GUYS
AREN'T INTO GIRLS
YOUR OWN AGE?
MUST BE WHY I'VE NEVER
SEEN YOU WITH GIRLFRIENDS.
YOU WANNA APPLY
FOR THE JOB?
DEPENDS.
WHAT ARE THE PERKS?
BRUCE:
LOOK, DON'T WASTE
YOUR TIME, MAN,
SHE'S STILL WEARING
HER ABSTINENCE RING.
JOHNNY:
OH, RIGHT.
GOD SAYS, "SKI TRIPS
WITH PRETTY BOY PETER
DON'T COUNT."
SIMPSON:
JOHNNY! BRUCE!
YOU KNOW THERE'S
NO TALKING IN DETENTION
AND YOU'LL HAVE PLENTY OF TIME
TO PROVE YOU KNOW IT,
BECAUSE YOU'VE JUST EARNED
YOURSELVES ANOTHER WEEK.
AND THE LITTLE TEASE
GETS OFF SCOTT-FREE?
OW!
DO YOU SEE WHAT
I HAVE TO PUT UP WITH?
AS SOON AS YOU
TURN YOUR BACK,
THESE TWO GANG UP
ON ME.
THIS IS YOUR LAST DAY,
WHY DON'T YOU GO HOME EARLY?
REALLY?
MM-HMM
JOHNNY:
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
SHE STARTED IT.
GUYS, I WARNED YOU.
THANK YOU!
THANK YOU! THANK YOU!
YOU ARE MY SAVIOUR.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT,
OFF YOU GO.
♪♪♪
(CAR DOOR SLAMS)
SO, SHOULD I PICK YOU UP
AFTER SCHOOL
OR DO YOU HAVE ANOTHER
DETENTION?
I CAN WALK HOME
BY MYSELF,
LIKE I HAVE
SINCE I WAS A KID.
WELL, WHEN YOU WERE A KID,
DARCY,
I DIDN'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT WHAT TROUBLE
YOU WERE GETTING INTO
EVERYTIME YOU LEFT
MY SIGHT.
WELL, SORRY FOR CHANGING.
IT'S GOOD THING
YOU'VE STILL STAYED THE SAME.
(UNDER BREATH)
YOU'RE STILL A BITCH.
HEY, EXCUSE ME,
YOUNG LADY?!
I HEARD THA-
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
DEGRASSI NEEDS A NEW LOGO?
I LIKE THE PANTHER
WE'VE GOT.
(TRUNK THUDS CLOSED)
JIMMY, USE THE SLIDER,
IT'S SAFER.
I GOT IT.
(GRUNT OF EFFORT)
(EXHAUSTED BREATH)
DEGRASSI'S HAD
THAT LOGO FOR AGES.
IT'S LAME.
LOOKS MORE LIKE A JAGUAR
THAN A PANTHER TO ME.
BUT....
WITH THE PURPLE DRAGON CASH,
THAT MEANS NEW UNIFORMS
FOR ALL OUR TEAMS,
AND IF I WIN...
MY LOGO'S GONNA BE EVERYWHERE.
THAT'S PRETTY COOL,
I GUESS.
YEAH.
SO YOU HAVE PHYSIO
AFTER CLASS, RIGHT?
I'LL MEET YOU BACK
AT THE CAR?
I UM...
I'M GONNA START
TAKING TRANSIT.
SO, DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT.
JIMMY, WE'RE A TEAM.
IT'S WHAT I'M HERE FOR.
I JUST NEED TO START DOING
MORE THINGS ON MY OWN,
THAT'S ALL.
FINE.
JUST TRYING TO HELP.
♪ Get low ♪
♪ And bring it like that
to the floor ♪
♪ You'll break your back ♪
♪ You know we drop it hot... ♪
MANNY:
5, 6, 7, 8.
1, 2, 3, 4,
5, 6, 7, 8,
COME ON, GIRLS,
MORE ENERGY.
DARCY, SMILE.
A SMILE'S WORTH
A THOUSAND CHEERS.
(CHEERLEADERS CLAP)
HEY!
WATCH IT,
PRINCESS SUNSHINE!
I COULD'VE HURT MYSELF.
OH, POOR BABY,
YOU'LL BE FINE.
MANNY:
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S DO THAT AGAIN.
DARCY, WHY DON'T YOU LOOK
AT THE CHOREOGRAPHY WITH ME?
I KNOW YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH
A LOT LATELY, BUT-
FORGIVE ME
IF I'VE LOST MY SPIRIT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I QUIT.
HON?
YOU DON'T MEAN THAT.
OKAY, YOU CAN'T JUST
DROP OUT OF LIFE.
DARCY:
WATCH ME.
OH, THE KEYS
I HAVE TO STEAL
TO GET A MOMENT
OF PRIVACY.
THIS CAN BE
OUR SPECIAL PLACE;
OUR NEW HIDING SPOT.
(CARS RUMBLE BY
IN THE DISTANCE)
DARCE, DON'T STAND
TO CLOSE TO THE EDGE.
(EXHALES)
YOU KNOW, I USED TO BE AFRAID
OF HEIGHTS?
I WONDER HOW FAR DOWN
THAT IS?
DARCE,
BE CAREFUL.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HAVE YOU GONE MENTAL?
THAT RING BELONGED
TO VIRGIN DARCY,
BUT I AM NOT A VIRGIN
AND MY ONLY SEXUAL
EXPERIENCE
WAS WITH
A TOTAL STRANGER.
DARCY, WHAT HAPPENED
WASN'T SEX.
WHATEVER.
THIS TIME
IT'S MY CHOICE.
WHOA!
YOU WANT TO HAVE SEX
ON THE ROOF?
BETTER THAN ON ROOFIES!
COME ON,
NOBODY WILL SEE US.
NO.
(SIGHS) DARCE,
I'VE REALLY TRIED
TO HELP,
BUT I DON'T EVEN
KNOW YOU ANYMORE.
YOU'RE LIKE...
YOU'RE LIKE HOPELESS.
I'M SORRY.
♪♪♪
(SCANNER CLANKS SHUT
AND WHIRS)
PETER AND I BROKE UP.
UM...
THIS SOUNDS LIKE
THE TYPE OF THING
YOU SHOULD TELL
A COUNSELOR.
HAVE YOU TALKED TO MS. SAUVE,
LATELY?
NO.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO UNDERSTANDS
WHAT I'M GOING THROUGH.
COME IN.
I'M JUST SCANNING LOGO
CONTEST ENTRIES.
(PAPERS SHUFFLE AND FLAP)
ARE YOU GONNA
DESIGN ONE?
IT SEEMS LIKE
IT MIGHT BE SOMETHING
THAT'S RIGHT UP
YOUR ALLEY.
I'M KINDA SICK OF THE WHOLE
SCHOOL SPIRIT THING.
I THINK THIS'LL EVEN BE
MY LAST WEEK
ON SPIRIT SQUAD.
YOU'RE REALLY MAKING
SOME CHANGES IN YOUR LIFE.
CHANGE IS AN IMPORTANT
PART OF HEALING.
EXACTLY.
THAT'S WHAT I TRIED
TO TELL MANNY TODAY,
THEN PETER, BUT...
THEY JUST DIDN'T GET IT.
NOT LIKE YOU.
UM...
WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF THIS ONE?
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
DARCY:
MEH,
IT'S NOT VERY SEXY,
I THINK I CAN DO BETTER.
SEE YA.
♪♪♪
MAN:
GOOD WORK.
(WEIGHTS CLANK,
GRUNTS OF EFFORT)
HEY, YOU'RE STILL
AT IT?
THAT'S GREAT!
YEAH, STILL UH...
FLAILING AROUND
LIKE A BABY DEER.
(TIGHT INHALE)
OOH!
TELL ME THIS
GETS EASIER.
WELL,
WHAT'S YOUR GOAL HERE?
JIMMY:
UH...
WORK HARD,
WALK OUT OF HERE,
LIVE A NORMAL LIFE.
WELL, THEN IT DOESN'T
GET EASIER.
AND IF YOU'RE DOING IT
SO YOU CAN WORK IN
A "NORMAL" OFFICE BUILDING
AND LIVE IN
THE "NORMAL" SUBURBS,
YOU'LL NEVER MAKE IT.
OH YEAH?
SO WHAT'S YOUR GOAL?
HIKE THE GRAND CANYON,
DO AN IDITEROD OR TWO,
WATCH THE SUN RISE
FROM THE TOP
OF MOUNT HALEAKALA.
WOW. THAT'S AMBITIOUS.
TRINA:
WELL,
I BET YOU DIDN'T USED TO BE
THE TYPE OF GUY
WHO'D SETTLE FOR "NORMAL."
HMM?
HMM...
THANKS.
I SHOULD GET GOING,
THOUGH.
SPEAKING OF LIMITATIONS,
I HAVE TO CATCH
THE BUS TO SCHOOL.
HEY, WANNA DRIVE?
UH, YEAH, SURE,
THAT'D BE GREAT.
NO.
(KEYS JINGLE)
DO YOU WANT TO DRIVE?
(CHUCKLE OF DISBELIEF)
WHAT?
TRINA:
SO EVERYTHING'S DONE
WITH YOUR HANDS.
OKAY, SO BRAKE IS HERE...
JIMMY:
OKAY.
TRINA:
AND THEN GAS IS FORWARD.
ALL RIGHT.
(CHUCKLES)
(CAR DOOR SHUTS)
NO LAUGHING.
OKAY.
NO LAUGHING,
ALL RIGHT?
(RADIO PLAYS)
(CAR SCREECHES FORWARD)
(LAUGHING)
IT'S OKAY,
IT'S OKAY.
(LAUGHING)
NOT BAD, GRANDMA.
NOT BAD.
CUT ME SOME SLACK,
OKAY?
I KNOW, I KNOW, I KNOW.
OKAY, OKAY,
SHUTTING MY MOUTH.
(CHUCKLES)
(ENGINE WHIRS)
TRINA:
YEAH, BABY.
(CHUCKLES)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
♪♪♪
YO, WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
TEACHER'S PET?
NONE OF YOUR BEESWAX,
SHREK.
DO YOU THINK YOU CAN
FLIRT YOUR WAY
OUT OF NEXT PERIOD?
MAYBE WE CAN GO
SOMEWHERE
AND PRACTICE SOME
"DARCY STYLE" ABSTINENCE.
(HUFFS)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
SIMPSON:
ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE,
YOUR CORPORATE
REBRANDING PROJECTS
ARE DUE NEXT WEEK.
PLEASE CONFIRM YOUR PROPOSALS
WITH ME FIRST.
I MADE A NEW LOGO.
YOU'LL LIKE IT,
SNAKE.
I REALLY HAVE TO GET GOING.
DARCY:
WAIT.
(PAPER FLAPS)
LOOK, I THINK YOU'RE
A LITTLE CONFUSED.
I KNOW, IT WAS SUPPOSED
TO BE A PANTHER,
BUT I LIKE SNAKES BETTER.
I'M NOT TALKING
ABOUT THE LOGO, DARCY.
I'M GLAD YOU FEEL COMFORTABLE
TALKING TO ME,
BUT I THINK...
YOU NEED TO OPEN UP
TO SOMEONE ELSE -
(STAMMERS)
YOUR PARENTS, UM...
SAUVE, ANYONE.
(PAPER CRUNCHES)
CAN'T...
CAN'T, CAN'T I JUST EAT
LUNCH WITH YOU?
LET'S JUST TALK.
WE'LL JUST TALK, OKAY?
JUST FOR A FEW MINUTES.
PLEASE?
(PANICKED BREATHS)
DARCY,
GIVE ME THE SCISSORS.
(HEAVY BREATHS)
(SCISSOR SNIPS)
(SCISSORS WHACK ONTO SURFACE)
(FOOTSTEPS CLONK WITH HASTE)
(INHALES AND EXHALES)
DARCY?!
DARCY,
HANG ON A MINUTE.
MR. SIMPSON,
I'M SO SORRY ABOUT ACTING
LIKE A PSYCHO EARLIER.
IT MUST'VE BEEN PMS
OR SOMETHING.
I'M FINE NOW, REALLY.
SIMPSON:
GOOD.
CAN I SEE YOU
IN MEDIA IMMERSION
AFTER SCHOOL?
OF COURSE,
I WILL DEFINITELY BE THERE.
THANKS,
MR. SIMPSON.
NO PROBLEM.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
(MACHINE BEEPS)
(DOOR OPENS)
JIMMY:
THANK YOU.
SPINNER:
HEY MAN.
WHERE'S JANE?
I GAVE HER
THE DAY OFF.
DUDE, I LOVE YOU,
UM,
BRINGING MY HOMEWORK
IS ONLY HALF
OF JANE'S JOB.
JIMMY:
FUNNY.
BUT LOOK,
I HAVE A SERIOUS
PROBLEM.
YOU KNOW TRINA
FROM PHYSIO?
I THINK I LIKE HER,
A LOT.
SO, GO FOR IT.
JIMMY:
YEAH...
BUT WHAT ABOUT ASH?
SO DON'T GO FOR IT.
THANK YOU, SO HELPFUL.
LOOK,
ME AND TRINA,
WE WENT DRIVING YESTERDAY.
JUST THE TWO OF YOU?
ISN'T THAT DANGEROUS?
SHE HAS A HAND-CONTROLLED CAR,
YOU IDIOT.
AND IT WAS AMAZING.
SPINNER:
SO, ALL I'M HEARING
IS ASHLEY: BAD;
TRINA: GOOD.
YOU DON'T NEED ME TO HELP
MAKE UP YOUR MIND FOR YOU,
DUDE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
(EXHALES)
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
(KNOCKING)
(KNOB CRANKS
AS DOOR OPENS)
MOM, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
DARCY, I ASKED EVERYONE
HERE BECAUSE...
I'M WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
(DISBELIEVING GASP)
WHAT IS THIS?
AN INTERVENTION?
SIMPSON:
YOUR BEHAVIOURS
BEEN TROUBLING LATELY
AND UM,
TODAY THERE
WAS AN INCIDENT
INVOLVING SCISSORS.
WHAT?!
I TRUSTED YOU.
DARCY, I'VE BEEN
YOUR CONFIDANT,
BUT I'M NOT
A COUNSELOR.
SO I THINK IT'S TIME
THAT YOU TELL EVERYONE
WHAT YOU'VE BEEN HIDING.
FINE.
I'LL TELL THEM.
I WILL TELL THEM
ALL ABOUT
HOW YOU TREAT ME
LIKE SOME KIND
OF TEACHER'S PET
AND HOW SOMETIMES...
YOU HUG ME...
AND TOUCH MY LEGS,
AND I FIND IT UNCOMFORTABLE.
DARCY, (NERVOUS CHUCKLE)
YOU KNOW THAT'S NOT TRUE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
HE TOUCHES YOUR LEGS?
HE BRUSHES UP AGAINST THEM...
(GASP OF DISBELIEF)
AND RUBS THEM SOMETIMES.
WHEN? IN CLASS?!
SIMPSON:
HOLD ON A MINUTE, OKAY?
I THINK DARCY'S
A LITTLE CONFUSED HERE.
IN FACT, SOMETIMES
WHEN WE'RE ALONE,
SHE'S THE ONE-
YOU'RE SPENDING TIME ALONE?
(INCREDULOUS WHISPER)
JUST THE TWO OF YOU?
MRS. EDWARDS:
MY DAUGHTER'S A CHILD!
WHAT DID YOU DO
TO HER?!
SIMPSON:
WAIT.
I KNOW HOW THIS ALL LOOKS,
BUT UM...
WAIT FOR ME
IN MY OFFICE.
(EXHALES)
DAPHNE,
I ASSURE YOU THAT-
HATZILAKOS:
ARCHIE?
YOU KNOW THE POLICY.
AUTOMATIC SUSPENSION.
(DOOR CLOSES SHUT)
I ASSURE YOU,
WE'LL INVESTIGATE THIS MATTER
FULLY.
(STUDENTS CHATTER,
SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
ANYA:
SIMPSON ALWAYS SEEMED SO NICE.
HOLLY J:
WELL, THAT'S HOW HE LURED GIRLS
INTO HIS NERD DEN.
MY SISTER SAID HE MADE OUT
WITH ONE OF HER FRIENDS.
JOHNNY:
HEY, WHEN YOU SEE
YOUR DADDY,
TELL HIM I SAID,
"WHAT'S UP?"
BRUCE:
(LAUGHS)
BUT DON'T GET TOO CLOSE,
HE MIGHT GET GRABBY.
JOHNNY'S CREW:
(CHUCKLES)
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
SURE I DO.
JUST ASK TEACHER'S PET
ALL ABOUT HER
"EXTRA CREDIT."
IT WAS YOU, WASN'T IT!
EMMA, I AM,
I'M SO SORRY.
ALL I SAID WAS THAT
HE MADE ME UNCOMFORTABLE.
ALL YOU SAID?
YOU'VE RUINED
HIS REPUTATION,
HIS JOB, HIS LIFE!
EMMA,
I DIDN'T MEAN TO.
DOESN'T MATTER.
BECAUSE PRETTY SOON
EVERYBODY IS GONNA FIND OUT
WHAT A PATHETIC LIAR
YOU ARE.
(PANICKED BREATHS)
HEY, WANNA EARN SOME
EXTRA CREDIT?
JOHNNY'S CREW:
(LAUGHING)
(WHISTLES AND HOLLERS)
THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR THE LIFT.
UM...
IT'S REALLY COOL
HANGING OUT WITH YOU
AFTER PHYSIO.
THEN WHY DON'T
WE MAKE PLANS
TO DO SOMETHING OUTSIDE
OF PHYSIO?
THE DRIVE-IN
JUST OPENED UP AGAIN.
YEAH.
AH, SEE,
HERE'S THE THING...
(LAUGHS)
YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET'S DO IT.
YEAH?
JIMMY:
HOW DOES NEXT WEEKEND SOUND?
IT SOUNDS AWESOME.
SEE YOU.
BYE.
DRIVE SAFE.
THANKS.
(VEHICLE RUMBLES AWAY)
NEW FRIEND, JIMMY?
REAL NICE.
(ROOF DOOR CLOSES)
JOHNNY:
WHOA.
HOW'D YOU FIND
THIS PLACE?
KEYS TO THE SCHOOL,
COURTESY OF PRETTY BOY
PETER.
DO YOU LIKE THE VIEW?
(KISSING)
HATZILAKOS:
AND NOW, TO ANNOUNCE
THE NEW DEGRASSI PANTHER,
IS YOUR STUDENT COUNCIL
PRESIDENT,
LIBERTY VAN ZANDT.
(STUDENTS APPLAUD)
FIRST, I'D JUST LIKE TO SAY
A BIG THANK YOU TO MR. SIMPSON
FOR ORGANIZING THIS CONTEST.
AND I'D JUST LIKE TO SAY
THAT PEOPLE ARE INNOCENT
UNTIL PROVEN GUILTY.
AH, WE HAD A HUGE NUMBER
OF ENTRIES...
IF DARCY DOESN'T SHOW,
I'M MAKING MYSELF
CO-CAPTAIN.
SHE'LL BE HERE,
DON'T WORRY.
HAVE YOU SEEN DARCY?
AFTER WHAT SHE DID,
I HOPE SHE NEVER SHOWS
HER FACE HERE AGAIN.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT?
SHE'S THE ONE
WHO ACCUSED SNAKE,
SHE TOLD ME.
BAD IDEA
ON HER PART.
EM, SHE'S BEEN THROUGH
A LOT LATELY.
YOU'RE SIDING WITH HER?
WHERE'S DARCY?
I DON'T KNOW.
SOMEWHERE SHE CAN BE
CRAZY IN PEACE?
OH, SHE STILL HAS MY KEYS
TO THE ROOF.
THE ROOF?
(HEAVY KISSING AND BREATHING)
(ROOFTOP DOOR CLANGS OPEN)
DARCY!
GOOD LUCK, MANNY.
(STEPS CRUNCH
AGAINST GRAVEL SURFACE)
CAN I HELP YOU?
LEAVE, DIRTBALL. NOW!
YOU DEGRASSI CHICKS
ARE CRAZY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHY ARE YOU ON THE ROOF
MAKING OUT WITH THAT LOSER?
AND FALSELY ACCUSING
MR. SIMPSON?
I'M CRAZY, MANNY.
HAVEN'T YOU HEARD?
I'M A CRAZY SLUT.
AND ONCE EVERYONE
FINDS OUT
THAT I LIED ABOUT SIMPSON,
THE WHOLE SCHOOL
WILL THINK IT TOO.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THEY'RE RIGHT.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES,
CAR RUMBLES AWAY)
I JUST FEEL LIKE DIRT,
MANNY.
I'M DIRT!
MANNY:
NO YOU'RE NOT,
YOU'RE THE SAME PERSON
YOU ALWAYS WERE
AND YOU CAN FIX THIS.
DARCY, GET BACK!
DARCY!
(CRYING)
HOW WILL I FACE PEOPLE?
HOW AM I GONNA TELL
MY PARENTS THE TRUTH?
IF YOU DON'T,
I'M GONNA DO IT FOR YOU.
I'VE BEEN KEEPING
YOUR SECRETS
FOR TOO LONG.
HEY, MAN.
JIMMY:
HEY, ASH,
WAIT UP.
WHY HAVE YOU NOT RETURNED
ANY OF MY TEXTS OR CALLS?
WHAT, SO YOU CAN BEG
FOR MY FORGIVENESS, JIMMY?
I DON'T WANT
TO HEAR IT.
YOU WON'T HAVE TO.
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED
TO MEAN?
LOOK, YESTERDAY,
ME AND TRINA,
YOU WEREN'T SUPPOSED
TO SEE THAT, BUT-
JIMMY, I'VE SUPPORTED YOU
FOR MORE THAN A YEAR.
YEAH, EXACTLY.
YOU "SUPPORTED" ME.
OKAY, THIS RELATIONSHIP
HAS BECOME A CRUTCH
FOR BOTH OF US.
SO WHAT, YOU JUST WANT ME
TO WALK AWAY?
I'D DO IT MYSELF
IF I COULD.
♪♪♪
(BIRDS CHIRP AS DOG BARKS
IN THE DISTANCE)
(KNOCKING)
(DOOR OPENS)
ARE YOU HERE
TO MAKE THINGS WORSE?
SIMPSON:
I CAN HANDLE THIS, EMMA.
I TOLD EVERYONE
I LIED -
MY PARENTS,
MS. H.
I SIGNED A STATEMENT.
I KNOW.
MS. HATZILAKOS CALLED ME.
DID YOU TELL ANYONE WHY?
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOU?
BUT IT'S ALL BETTER NOW,
RIGHT?
YOU'LL BE BACK
AT SCHOOL?
DARCY, SOMETIMES
GIRLS SAY THINGS
AND THEN THEY
TAKE THEM BACK
BECAUSE THEY'RE SCARED.
SO, EVEN THOUGH
WE BOTH KNOW YOU LIED,
I'LL STILL BE UNDER
INVESTIGATION.
I'M SO SORRY.
YOU MUST HATE ME.
YOU CAUSED
A LOT OF DAMAGE.
(DOORKNOB RATTLES)
BUT I DON'T HATE YOU.
♪♪♪