AND FINALLY,
THE DANCE COMMITTEE IS REMINDED THAT THEY FIRST PERIOD OFF,
TO TRANSFORM OUR GYM INTO A HAWAIIAN SURF PARADISE.
ALOHA.
GUYS, GUYS - YOUR ATTENTION PLEASE?
SOME OF YOU HAVE ALREADY HEARD,
BUT - I HAVE SOME UNFORTUNATE NEWS.
CRAIG MANNING'S FATHER DIED OVER THE WEEKEND,
IN A CAR ACCIDENT.
UH, CRAIG'S OKAY, RIGHT?
I MEAN HE WASN'T IN THE-?
NO, HE'S FINE.
BUT HE WON'T BE BACK FOR THE REST OF TERM.
UM, MR. SIMPSON?
I THOUGHT THAT WE SHOULD SEND FLOWERS.
SO I'M TAKING UP A COLLECTION, IF THAT'S OKAY?
THAT'D BE GREAT ASHLEY. THANK YOU.
GIVE WHAT YOU CAN, GUYS -
I'LL MAKE SURE CRAIG GETS THEM TODAY.
SORRY I'M LATE, SIR.
IS SOMETHING WRONG...?
UH... NO, NO. WE JUST UH...
WE WEREN'T EXPECTING YOU.
UM, NOT SUMMER HOLIDAYS YET!
NOT YET.
SO, UH - TAKE YOUR SEAT.
OKAY UH, LET'S SEE WHO ELSE IS HERE.
ADEN, BAZOIAN,...
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I know I can make it through
♪ If I hold out
♪ Be the best
♪ The best that I can be
♪ Hear what I say to you
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I can see it
♪ I know I can make it
♪ I know I can make it through
(Someone is doing a sound check)
ASH, MY DONATION FOR THE FLOWER FUND.
THANKS, PAIGE.
I TOLD YOU -
NO PRESSURE ON YOU HAVING TO COME INTO TEN CLASSES.
YEAH.
HAPPY WAY TO END SUCH A HAPPY YEAR.
I KNOW. POOR CRAIG.
I JUST WISH I COULD DO SOMETHING FOR HIM,
YOU KNOW?
YOU CAN'T. NOT REALLY.
I KNOW FIRSTHAND. MY MOM, REMEMBER?
LISTEN, IF THERE IS ANYTHING ELSE I CAN DO FOR YOU,
DON'T HESITATE TO ASK.
THANKS.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
I KNOW. BUT I'M GOING TO TRY.
HEY CRAIG. HOW'RE YOU DOING?
I'M FINE.
I MEAN, I WAS GOING CRAZY AT JOEY'S,
NEEDED TO GET OUT SO...
I'M HERE.
WOW, THE GYM LOOKS AMAZING. I CAN'T WAIT FOR THE DANCE.
YOU STILL WANT TO GO?
YEAH, WHY WOULDN'T I?
WELL I'M MAKING SURE MY YEAR ENDS ON A POSITIVE NOTE.
NOTICE ANYTHING?
I THINK YOU'RE GETTING A PIMPLE ON YOUR NOSE...
I WENT TO THE TANNING SALON YESTERDAY.
IF I'M GONNA WIN THE PART, I GOTTA LOOK IT, RIGHT?
IF YOU'RE GONNA WIN WHAT PART?
SPIN AND ME - LUAU KING AND QUEEN.
UM - THIS DANCE IS OPEN
TO KIDS ALL THE WAY UP TO GRADE ELEVEN.
SO?
SO ONE OF THEM WILL GET THE CROWN.
NOT IF I GET ALL THE SEVENS, EIGHTS AND NINES
TO VOTE FOR ME.
YOU KNOW I WAS REALLY SURPRISED BY THE RESULTS OF YOUR TEST.
YOU MUST HAVE STUDIED VERY HARD.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW WELL HE'S TAKING IT.
I WOULDN'T BE THAT COOL.
GOOD JOB!
I'M PROUD OF YOU.
HEY! THAT'S MY MAN.
WOW! THAT'S AMAZING BUDDY.
YEAH, MY DAD ACTUALLY DID SOMETHING WORTH-WHILE FOR ME.
HE'S A GOOD STUDY PARTNER.
LOOK WE'RE REALLY SORRY TO HEAR ABOUT YOUR DAD, MAN.
YEAH...
SO YOU OKAY?
GUYS, I'M FINE.
HEY, I'M THE LUCKY ONE.
MY DAD DIED. I WALKED AWAY WITH A SCRATCH.
BUT I THOUGHT YOU WEREN'T IN THE CAR.
FRIDAY NIGHT.
WE'RE LIKE, SPEEDING DOWN THE HIGHWAY.
MY DAD'S MAD - HE WON'T SLOW DOWN.
AHEAD THERE'S A RIG.
I SEE IT, MY DAD DOESN'T.
AND WE HIT. HARD.
(Laughing)
GUYS! I WAS AT JOEY'S WHEN IT HAPPENED.
I HAD YOU GOING, THOUGH.
IT WAS LIKE HE WAS JOKING ABOUT IT.
IT'S NOT LIKE HE WAS - HE WAS.
YO, CAFETERIA BOY!
YOU BETTER HURRY. YOU'RE GONNA BE LATE FOR WORK.
YEAH GLAD TO SEE YOU STILL HAVE YOUR SENSE OF HUMOUR.
YEAH, WELL YOU DIDN'T GET AROUND TO STEALING THAT.
ENOUGH ALREADY, OKAY?
GAVIN? COULD YOU TELL ME ABOUT SOME OF TODAY'S LUNCH SPECIALS?
GO AHEAD, LAUGH IT UP.
BUT YOU WON'T BE LAUGHING WHEN I'M VOTED LUAU KING.
OKAY.
GUYS, CAN WE JUST DO THIS LATER?
YEAH, WE'LL DO THIS LATER.
COUNT ON IT.
(IMITATING) OH, WE'LL DO THIS LATER, OOOH...
OKAY JIMMY! GIVE IT UP.
HE AND PAIGE WOULD MAKE AN AMAZING LUAU KING AND QUEEN.
ALL STUDENTS WHO ARE INTERESTED
IN RUNNING FOR DEGRASSI'S LUAU KING AND QUEEN
AND HAVE NOT REGISTERED,
SHOULD SEE TOBY ISSACS IN THE MEDIA IMMERSION LAB
BEFORE THE END OF THE DAY.
JUST THE GIRL I WAS LOOKING FOR.
OH HI.
THE DANCE, ARE YOU STILL GOING SOLO?
CAUSE YOU'RE NOT ANYMORE.
UM... OKAY...?
AND WHO KNOWS,
I MEAN, MAYBE WE'LL EVEN WALK AWAY WITH THE LUAU CROWN.
PAIGE WANTS THAT CROWN.
SO? IT'S A FREE COUNTRY.
YEAH, BUT - SHE'S MY BEST FRIEND.
AND YOU'VE BEEN IN HER SHADOW FOR HOW LONG?
ISN'T IT TIME FOR HAZEL ADEN TO STEP INTO THE SPOTLIGHT?
THINK ABOUT IT.
ATTENTION STUDENTS!
TEXTBOOK DROP-OFF HOURS
HAVE BEEN EXTENDED UNTIL 6 P.M. TODAY.
AND THERE YOU GO.
YOU'RE ON THE LIST.
SO, THE RUMOUR'S TRUE?
OH, IT'S NOTHING PERSONAL, PAIGE.
THERE'S TWENTY COUPLES ON THIS LIST.
YEAH AND ONLY ONE FROM NINTH GRADE.
YOU'RE SPLITTING OUR VOTE.
PEOPLE CAN VOTE FOR WHO THEY WANT.
WHAT DOES IT MATTER, ANYWAY?
WHO WANTS TO BE SOME STUPID LUAU THING?
AND THAT'S WHY I LOVE YOU.
NO, NO. NOT, NOT LOVE YOU - JUST LIKE YOU. A LOT.
YOU OKAY?
I'M GOING UPSTAIRS.
YOU KNOW, YOU LEAVING WAS A HUGE WAKE-UP CALL FOR ME.
I GOT MYSELF INTO ANGER MANAGEMENT
AND I'VE GOTTEN BETTER.
I'VE GOTTEN A LOT BETTER.
GOODNESS AND MERCY ALL MY LIFE SHALL SURELY FOLLOW ME.
AND IN GODS HOUSE FOREVER MORE MY DWELLING PLACE SHALL BE.
AMEN.
THE GRACE OF OUR LORD AND THE LOVE OF GOD,
BE WITH US EVERMORE.
AMEN.
AT THIS TIME, I CALL ON DOCTOR STEPHEN WATLEY,
ONE OF ALBERT'S CO-WORKERS, TO SAY A FEW WORDS.
STEPHEN?
I KNEW ALBERT MANNING FOR ALMOST TWENTY YEARS.
I KNEW HIM AS A GOOD FRIEND,
A TOP-NOTCH SURGEON,
AN ABSOLUTELY DEVASTATING SQUASH PLAYER,
AND A DEDICATED FATHER.
BUT IF YOU WERE TO ASK HIM?
THIS LAST ROLE WAS THE MOST IMPORTANT.
PLEASE...
ALBERT TOLD ME TIME AND TIME AGAIN
HOW HIS SON CRAIG
WAS THE GREATEST GIFT HE EVER RECEIVED.
A GIFT HE CHERISHED.
A GIFT HE NEVER WANTED TO RELINQUISH.
(Laughing)
MAYBE CRAIG NEEDS SOME AIR.
CRAIG, COME ON. LET'S GO OUTSIDE.
SORRY.
... THIS IS WHY HE WAS A GREAT DOCTOR AND A GREAT SURGEON.
WE'RE GONNA MISS HIM.
(Laughing)
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT IDIOT?
"ALBERT MANNING WAS A DEDICATED FATHER..."
CRAIG, YOU AND YOUR FATHER HAD A COMPLICATED RELATIONSHIP-
YEAH, HE BEAT ME.
NOT GONNA DO THAT AGAIN NOW, IS HE?
COME ON.
I'M HAPPY, JOEY.
I'M REALLY HAPPY... 'CAUSE HE'S DEAD.
'CAUSE HE'S GONE FOR GOOD.
IT WAS DISTURBING.
THE COFFIN'S RIGHT THERE, AND CRAIG'S LAUGHING.
FUNERALS ARE STRESSFUL.
WEIRD THINGS HAPPEN.
LADIES...
HEY CRAIG.
HEY.
YOU READY FOR THE HAWAIIAN SURF PARADISE?
UM SURE. CAN'T WAIT.
HEY, SAVE THE FILM FOR TONIGHT...
WHEN ASH AND I WIN THE LUAU CROWN.
YOU PUT US IN THE CONTEST?
YEAH. THIS IS OUR NIGHT. EVERYONE'S GONNA KNOW IT.
OKAY...
GREAT.
UH, I GOTTA GO CLEAN OUT MY LOCKER.
BUT I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
SO YOU GET IN,
PULL THE LID DOWN,
PRESS THE START BUTTON.
UM, WAIT.
DO I REALLY HAVE TO PULL THE LID DOWN?
CAUSE I'M KINDA CLAUSTROPHOBIC.
IF YOU REALLY WANT TO TAN, YEAH.
I CAN DO THIS. OKAY, OKAY...
WHAT... WHAT DID HE-OH, OH NO, OH NO!
(Screams)
WHAT WAS THAT?
OKAY PAIGE. I CAN'T DO IT! I CAN'T!
I TOLD YOU I WAS CLAUSTROPHOBIC!
SPINNER... CAN I AT LEAST HAVE MY TURN NOW?
NO!
I'M SCARED. I WANNA GO HOME.
I'LL TAN MY WAY, YOU TAN YOURS.
OKAY?
FOLLOW ME.
CRAIG.
OH, YOU GOT THE BIG DANCE TONIGHT?
YEAH.
OH, I HOPE YOU DON'T MIND,
BUT I BORROWED ONE OF YOUR OLD SHIRTS.
KNOCK YOURSELF OUT.
HEY LISTEN BEFORE YOU GO TO ARUBA, I WANTED TO-
HAWAII.
RIGHT.
UM, LOOK, I HATE TO BRING THIS UP
BUT WE HAVE TO GO OVER WHAT YOU GONNA SAY TOMORROW
AT CHILDREN'S AID.
NOW?
YEAH, IF THAT'S OKAY.
UM, IT'S JUST I'M A BIT DISTRACTED.
YOU KNOW - ASHLEY, THE DANCE.
YOU DON'T THINK I SHOULD GO, DO YOU?
NO. I DO.
I THINK IT'S GREAT YOU'RE TRYING TO HAVE FUN, CRAIG
BUT...
BUT WHAT? I'M FINE.
NO ONE IS "FINE" AFTER LOSING SOMEONE.
I WASN'T, WITH YOUR MOM.
I JUST THINK THE PAIN IS GONNA CATCH UP TO YOU.
I'VE GOT A DANCE TO GO TO.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN!
STEP RIGHT UP - CAST YOUR VOTE
FOR DEGRASSI'S LUAU KING AND QUEEN!
THANKS FOR YOUR VOTE.
STEP RIGHT UP AND VOTE FOR LUAU KING AND QUEEN.
ALOHA. WELCOME TO DEGRASSI ISLAND.
DON'T FORGET TO VOTE FOR YOUR LUAU KING AND QUEEN:
JIMMY AND HAZEL.
ALOHA. DON'T FORGET TO VOTE FOR YOUR LUAU KING AND QUEEN:
ALOHA AND- (Laughs)
WELCOME TO DEGRASSI ISLAND.
WHAT ARE YOU LAUGHING AT?
YOUR LAME ATTEMPT AT STEALING OUR VOTES?
RED, I DON'T HAVE TO STEAL ANYTHING TONIGHT.
BUT HEY, MAYBE SPIN COULD TRY.
DUDE, LIKE - ANCIENT HISTORY.
(Dance Music)
SPIN!
SPIN, IF YOU WANT TO WIN, STOP DOING THAT ROBOT THING!
(Dance Music)
GOTH LUAU - COOL.
I THOUGHT IT'D SET US APART.
AND YOU KNOW, KEEP YOUR DIGNITY INTACT.
UNTIL WE START TO LIMBO, OF COURSE...
GUYS!
(Taps staff on floor)
THE TIME HAS COME.
VOTES ARE IN FOR LUAU KING AND QUEEN.
OH AND UH, THANKS TO TOBY ISAACS AND KENDRA MASON
FOR ALL THEIR HARD WORK ON THIS.
AND THE WINNER IS...
FROM GRADE NINE -
ASHLEY KERWIN AND CRAIG MANNING!
(Cheering)
DAD.
DAD?
DAD, DAD LOOK!
LOOK - LOOK, I'VE WON!
SORRY.
I'M SORRY MR. BOYD. I THOUGHT YOU WERE...
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN? THEY'RE WAITING FOR OUR DANCE.
CRAIG, ARE YOU OKAY?
LOOK, I'M FINE. I'M JUST REALLY TIRED.
I KNEW COMING HERE WAS A MISTAKE.
WHAT?
IT'S TOO SOON. YOU SHOULD BE HOME.
COULD YOU, LIKE, REVEL IN THIS ANY MORE -
MS. GOTH!
MS. DOOM AND GLOOM!
THAT'S NOT FAIR. I'M JUST CONCERNED ABOUT YOU.
WELL I'M SICK OF YOU, AND EVERYONE,
JUST BEING CONCERNED.
CRAIG-
LET HIM COOL DOWN.
EVERYONE BACK INTO THE DANCE.
I'LL CHECK IN ON CRAIG IN A MINUTE.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH ME?
NOTHING.
YOU'RE ANGRY, AND YOU'RE SAD.
THIS WAS SUPPOSED TO BE MY NIGHT.
I'M WITH ASH!
WE'RE THE STUPID LUAU KING AND QUEEN!
WHEN MY MOM DIED,
I WAS AT MY FRIEND'S BIRTHDAY PARTY.
I WAS HAVING A GREAT TIME - AND THEN MY DAD CAME TO TELL ME.
AT THE PARTY?
YEAH. I WAS SO MAD-
'CAUSE SHE DIED?
NO - 'CAUSE I COULDN'T PLAY PIN THE TAIL ON THE DONKEY.
THAT'S A FUN GAME WHEN YOU'RE A LITTLE KID.
EXACTLY.
IT WASN'T TILL LATER THAT IT HIT - THAT, THAT SHE WAS DEAD.
BEFORE MY DAD DIED -
I WANTED HIM GONE.
SO WHY AM I CRYING, NOW THAT HE IS?
'CAUSE YOU LOVE HIM.
(Crying)
I'M WORRIED ABOUT COMING IN EIGHTH PLACE
IN SOME STUPID LUAU CONTEST
AND POOR CRAIG IS HAVING A BREAKDOWN.
CAN WE SAY SHALLOW?
SHALLOW.
WELL, PAIGE ISN'T THE ONLY FREAK.
DUDE, WHAT PLAGUE DO YOU HAVE?
YOU KNOW, I THINK IT'S THESE FLOWERS.
I'M ALLERGIC TO THEM.
AT LEAST YOU DON'T HAVE RADIOACTIVE SKIN.
OR A PUMPKIN FOR A DATE.
A PUMPKIN IN A DRESS.
OH, LOSERS -
I'D SAY YEARBOOK, FRONT COVER.
GOING SOMEWHERE?
ARE YOU?
SOON. I WANNA GO HOME.
I THINK WE OWE EVERYONE A DANCE.
YOU CAN ASK.
ASK WHAT?
HOW I'M DOING.
I WON'T GO PSYCHO.
HOW'RE YOU DOING, CRAIG?
BETTER.