THE PHYSICS OF ATTRACTION AND REPULSION -
IS WHAT WE'RE GOING TO EXPLORE TODAY USING STATIC ELECTRICITY.
SO I WANT ALL OF YOU TO PAY CAREFUL ATTENTION
TO YOUR EXPERIMENTS
AND PLEASE MAKE SURE THAT YOU TAKE DETAILED NOTES.
WILL YOU BE MY FRIEND, TOBY ISAACS?
WILL YOU SHUT UP AND DO YOUR WORK?
HELLO!
JT!
UGH!
I'M A MASTODON. I DIED 10,000 YEARS AGO.
YOU RUINED THIS.
WILL YOU BE MY FRIEND?
NO!
YOU HAVE THE CUTEST BONES...
I BET YOU SAY THAT TO ALL THE SKELETAL MASTODONS...
NO... JUST YOU... I'M GONNA KISSY- KISS YOU ALL OVER...
JT YORKE.
SORRY, MS. HATZILAKOS.
I'M SORRY TOO. OH DON'T LISTEN TO HIM, HE'S LYING.
ONE WEEK, GUINEA PIG DUTY -
EVERY DAY BEFORE AND AFTER SCHOOL, RIGHT HERE, WITH ME.
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I know I can make through
♪ If I hold out
♪ If I do
♪ I know I can make through
♪ Be the best
♪ The best that I can be
♪ Hear what I say to you
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I can see it
♪ I know I can make it
♪ I know I can make it through
THANKS.
COME ON IN.
GOOD MORNING MS. HATZILAKOS.
OH, GOOD MORNING JT.
OKAY LET'S GET STARTED. RIGHT THIS WAY.
SO WE MAINLY FEED THE GUINEA PIGS DRIED TIMOTHY GRASS.
SUPPLEMENTED WITH PELLETS, FRESH VEGETABLES.
OF COURSE, THEY ALWAYS NEED A FRESH SUPPLY OF WATER.
DO YOU MIND?
OH SORRY.
OH, IS THAT YOUR PEN ON THE GROUND?
NOPE. MUST BE YOURS.
OKAY, LET ME INTRODUCE YOU TO THE BROOD.
RIGHT HERE WE HAVE JASPER, BISMARCK,
AND THIS CUTIE IS ISABELLA.
SHE'S LIKE A BIG BALL OF FLUFF.
A REALLY FAT BALL OF FLUFF.
YEAH, SHE IS MUCH BIGGER THEN USUAL.
WELL LOOK AT YOU.
YOU'VE HAVE THE MAGIC TOUCH.
DID YOU EVER THINK OF BECOMING A VETERINARIAN?
I TRIED ONCE, BUT THERE AREN'T ENOUGH RECIPES.
PLUS I LOVE MEAT.
I SAID VETERINARIAN, NOT VEGETARIAN.
I KNOW. I WAS JOKING.
"THE MEDIUM IS THE MESSAGE." DOES ANYONE KNOW WHO SAID THAT?
MARSHALL MCLUHAN -
THE GODFATHER OF MODERN MEDIA AND COMMUNICATIONS.
AND DID YOU KNOW MCLUHAN WAS CANADIAN?
HEY - HOW WAS YOUR 'QUALITY TIME'
WITH MS. HOT SAUCE?
HOT AND SAUCY.
FULL REPORT. NOW.
FIRST? I DID ONE OF THESE - OOPS!
THEN SHE BENT DOWN TO PICK IT UP - OH!
JT? IS THIS YOURS?
YEAH.
YOU WANNA PAY ATTENTION? OKAY.
ANYWAYS...
YOU GUYS CAN'T IMAGINE THE THINGS I SAW...
NOT BAD, GAVIN. BUT WHAT EXACTLY IS A "SEXAGRAM"?
THAT THINGY WITH SIX POINTS?
AH NO, THAT'S A "HEXAGRAM".
OH. OOPS.
COME TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
YOU REALLY NEED TO TAKE ANOTHER LOOK AT YOUR ANSWER
FOR PROBLEM NUMBER TEN.
OH THAT HAS TO BE A TRICK QUESTION.
AH NO, JUST UH, SIMPLE BATH - UH, MATH.
JULIAN CAN I SEE YOUR ASSIGNMENT PLEASE?
IS THAT SPINNER THAT SMELLS? SHOULD WE TELL HIM?
HONESTY NEVER HURTS.
RULE NUMBER ONE OF PUBERTY? SHOWER EVERY DAY.
DUDE, DUDE.
THE TRUTH - DO I STINK?
UM, YEAH, ACTUALLY.
YOU'VE SMELLED REALLY BAD ALL WEEK.
WELL, WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
I DIDN'T WANT TO HURT YOUR FEELINGS.
WELL, BETTER I HEAR IT FROM YOU, THEN ELLIE, DUDE.
THE TRUTH FROM NOW ON, OKAY?
"YOU CAN'T HANDLE THE TRUTH."
JACK NICHOLSON.
UM OKAY. BUT THIS - IT'S SERIOUS,
IT'S IMPORTANT. COME ON, LET'S MAKE A PACT.
SURE, MAN. WHATEVER.
JIM-!
OKAY IF IT TAKES FRED 45 SECONDS
TO FILL HIS TEN LITRE FISH TANK,
HOW LONG WILL IT TAKE HIM TO FILL HIS OTHER TANKS:
NOW, FIVE OF THEM ARE FIVE LITRE TANKS
AND TEN OF THEM ARE TWO LITRE TANKS?
YEAH, I THINK FRED NEEDS TO GET A LIFE.
THANK YOU, MR. YORKE...
JT HAS A LIFE. HE'S GOT A NEW GIRLFRIEND.
REALLY? YOU MEAN LIBERTY?
FINALLY!
NO.
MS. HOTS-O-LA-KOS...
THAT IS SO TYPICAL.
NO, SO JT. IMMATURE AND DUMB.
WHY?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH A YOUNGER GUY DATING AN OLDER WOMAN, ANYWAY?
THERE'S A RULE.
THE YOUNGEST YOU CAN DATE IS HALF YOUR AGE PLUS SEVEN.
SO FOR MS. H - WHO'S, WHAT, THIRTY?
THAT'S - FIFTEEN PLUS SEVEN...
WHICH IS TWENTY-TWO.
AND YOU'RE SHORT BY A COUPLE OF YEARS.
AND MORE THEN A COUPLE OF FEET.
MELANDA STARED INTO THE SOUL OF THE ECLIPSE.
AND SAW THE WORLD FOR WHAT IT WAS -
A SHADOW OF BLACK, EMPTY, DESPAIRING NOTHINGNESS.
WOW. HAPPY.
THOUGHTS ANYONE?
JIMMY BROOKS?
OH UH, WELL I, YOU KNOW - THOUGHT IT WAS POETIC.
YO, YOU MADE A PROMISE, DUDE.
SPIN - SHUT UP.
GENTLEMEN, IF YOU HAVE ANY COMMENTS,
PLEASE SHARE THEM WITH THE CLASS.
I DON'T.
OH, HE DOES, MS. KWAN. JIMMY?
OKAY. I THOUGHT YOU WERE TRYING WAY TO HARD TO BE PROFOUND
AND YOU JUST LOST THE STORY.
HONESTLY? IT SOUNDED LIKE A SUICIDE NOTE.
WELL, I WOULDN'T EXPECT A CONFORMIST TO UNDERSTAND.
ASHLEY - THIS EXERCISE IS ABOUT CONSTRUCTIVE CRITICISM.
OKAY WE'VE GOT ABOUT FIFTEEN MINUTES LEFT.
ENOUGH TIME FOR TWO MORE VOLUNTEERS.
ANYONE? STEVEN, ARE YOU READY TO READ?
HEY, WHAT'S UP?
JT! I WANT TO SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
I'LL BET SHE DOES...
WELL, I THOUGHT ABOUT WHAT YOU SAID -
ABOUT ISABELLA'S WEIGHT PROBLEM.
WELL IT'S NOT THAT - SHE'S PREGNANT!
WOW. A HUNDRED LITTLE GUINEA PIGS JUST WAITING TO BE BORN.
WELL, MORE LIKE THREE OR FOUR.
YOU CAN FEEL THEM, INSIDE HER. THAT'S HOW I REALIZED.
HERE.
RIGHT THERE.
CAN YOU FEEL THEM?
WOW.
I CAN'T BELIEVE ISABELLA IS GONNA BE A MOM.
THAT IS SO COOL.
DOES SHE NEED ANYTHING?
LIKE - A SPECIAL DIET OR SOMETHING?
HOW ABOUT I DO SOME RESEARCH?
THAT'D BE GREAT. THAT WOULD BE A GREAT HELP, THANKS JT.
IT'S OKAY.
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
AND ON YOUR LUNCH HOUR?
JUST TRYING TO DO SOME RESEARCH FOR MS. HATZILAKOS.
YOUR SPELLING...
AH, THERE IS SUCH A THING AS PRIVACY, YOU KNOW.
YEAH, I KNOW, BUT --
OH... THANKS.
NO PROBLEM.
NOW - WHEN MANNY RUBS THE BALLOONS ON HER HAIR,
THEY BECOME NEGATIVELY-CHARGED.
AND THEY BECOME ATTRACTED TO HER POSITIVELY-CHARGED HAIR.
NOW THE MOMENT MANNY STEPS AWAY ...
THE BALLOONS REPEL
BECAUSE THEY'RE BOTH NEGATIVELY-CHARGED.
MS. HATZILAKOS - CAN I SEE YOU FOR A SECOND?
AH, SURE.
WHY DON'T YOU CONTINUE BLOWING UP YOUR BALLOONS.
AND I'LL JUST BE A MINUTE.
LOOKS LIKE YOUR GIRLFRIEND HAS A BOYFRIEND.
MR. ARMSTRONG IS MARRIED.
SO? MS. HATZILAKOS ISN'T.
SHE'S NOT LIKE THAT.
IT WAS A JOKE.
YEAH REMEMBER?
YOU USED TO TELL THEM?
HELLO I'M A MASTODON.
TOBY SHUT UP? I'M TRYING TO CONCENTRATE.
SORRY, LIBERTY.
SO TEACHER'S PET,
WHEN IS MS. H GETTING YOU YOUR OWN CAGE?
I'M NOT HER PET.
OH REALLY. LET'S SEE HERE.
WE'VE GOT JASPER, BISMARCK, ISABELLA - JT.
WHAT'S THE MATTER SEAN? HUH?
YOU JEALOUS?
DO YOU WANT TO BE MY OTHER GUINEA PIG BOY?
OH AND WHAT ABOUT YOU, TOBY?
MY, MY, MY YOU'RE A FURRY LITTLE ONE.
YEAH, I'M SURE YOU DO-
ASH AND I WERE THIS CLOSE TO RECONNECTING -
AND YOU HAD TO RUIN IT WITH YOUR STUPID HONESTY PACT.
DUDE, YOU DID HER A FAVOUR. SHE SHOULD HAVE THANKED YOU.
YEAH WELL TELL HER THAT.
SPIN, SOMETIMES PEOPLE DON'T WANT THE WHOLE TRUTH.
WELL, THEN THEY'RE STUPID.
IF IT WAS ME? I'D WANT THE WHOLE TRUTH ENCHILADA.
JIMMY.
ASH. UHM, LOOK,
I'M REALLY SORRY ABOUT YESTERDAY.
ACTUALLY? YOU SAVED MY STORY.
WHAT?
YOU WERE RIGHT.
I WENT THROUGH IT LAST NIGHT AND MADE SOME CHANGES
AND IT IS WAY BETTER.
I LIKE THIS NEW JIMMY.
I GUESS YOU WERE RIGHT, MAN.
ALL HONESTY - ALL THE TIME FROM NOW ON.
GOOD. CAN I BE HONEST WITH YOU?
GO AHEAD. WE'RE TIGHT.
OKAY. YOU AND ASH GETTING BACK TOGETHER?
THE STUPIDEST IDEA I EVER HEARD.
WHAT?
WELL, YOU BECOME THIS WEAK,
PATHETIC PUPPET WHEN SHE'S AROUND.
AND SHE'S THE EVIL PUPPETMASTER.
HERE THIS IS YOU -
ASHLEY I DON'T WHAT TO GO...
(WHIPPING SOUND) OKAY, OKAY I'M GOING.
OW, THAT HURTS. OW.
OKAY, OKAY I GET IT.
THANKS FOR THE HONESTY.
DUDE? MY PLEASURE.
LOOK I'M SORRY, OKAY?
I APOLOGIZE.
THANK YOU.
THAT'S' IT?
PARDON ME.
I APOLOGIZED. WHAT MORE DO YOU WANT?
JT DO YOU KNOW WHY I'M ANGRY?
BECAUSE OF THE THING I DID.
YES. BUT DO YOU KNOW WHY I'M REALLY ANGRY?
NO.
LOOK, YOU'RE FUNNY, OKAY?
BUT YOU'RE ALSO VERY INTELLIGENT,
AND YOU'RE JUST WASTING IT BY ALWAYS BEING THE CLASS CLOWN.
JUST WASTING IT.
WELL THEN I'LL JUST STOP WASTING YOUR TIME.
I'LL TRANSFER OUT OF YOUR CLASS.
WELL YOU DO WHAT EVER IT IS YOU NEED TO DO.
WHAT'RE YOU DOING? SCHOOL'S OUT.
IT'S AN HONESTY LIST ABOUT SPINNER.
ARE YOU CRAZY?
NO, IT'S CONSTRUCTIVE CRITICISM.
"YOU'RE CHEAP." VERY CONSTRUCTIVE.
OKAY, DON'T MAKE ME START A TERRI LIST.
TOP ITEM? NOSEY - DOESN'T MIND OWN BUSINESS.
OH GREAT. HELLO?
OH NO!
MS. H!
MS. HATZILAKOS.
I'M ON MY WAY OUT.
YEAH I KNOW. BUT I NEED YOUR HELP.
WELL MY OFFICE IS OPEN EARLY TOMORROW.
NO, IT'S ISABELLA. SHE GOT OUT OF HER CAGE.
WHAT? OH NO!
I WAS JUST ON MY WAY TO CLEAN THE ROOM
AND THE DOOR WAS LOCKED.
I WAS JUST WALKING BY
AND I SAW THAT SHE WAS UNDERNEATH THE DESK.
THE CAGE...
WAIT. THERE SHE IS. OKAY.
SHHH, LET'S BE VERY QUIET.
OKAY.
CLOSE THE DOOR BEHIND YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
TRY NOT TO SCARE HER.
COME ON ISABELLA.
I'LL TRY TO PUSH HER TOWARDS YOU.
THAT'S A GOOD GIRL. COME ON.
OH! SH--.
GO! GO! YOU GO THAT WAY.
GO THAT WAY.
OH, THERE SHE IS.
QUIET.
I GOT HER, I GOT HER, I GOT HER, I GOT HER.
OW!
OH MY ELBOW!
THERE SHE IS.
WHERE DID SHE GO?
RIGHT THERE, RIGHT THERE.
LOOKS LIKE SHE JUST FOUND A DARK, SAFE SPOT
TO HAVE HER BABIES.
THAT'S WHAT THEY LIKE TO DO.
I DID SOME GUINEA PIG RESEARCH ON THE COMPUTER.
SHE'S NOT SAFE, JT.
THE JANITOR'S SPREAD RAT POISON ALL AROUND THE SCHOOL.
BECAUSE OF RODENT PROBLEMS...
WHAT?!
ISABELLA! COME ON!
16. DANCES LIKE A STUPID ROBOT. 17. BAD TASTE IN MOVIES.
AND 18. SHOOTS BASKETS LIKE A GIRL.
OKAY, DUDE ARE YOU DONE?
UM. ONE MORE THING. YOU SAY 'DUDE' LIKE EVERY THIRD WORD.
OH YEAH? WELL YOU HAVE A SHINY FOREHEAD, DUDE.
WHAT?
AND... CAN YOU STOP COPYING ME?
YOU'RE THE ONE THAT COPIES ME.
OKAY, POPPY-SEED BAGELS!
THE SEEDS STICK TO YOUR TEETH
AND YOU WALK AROUND ALL DAY LIKE SOME POPPY-TOOTHED FREAK.
SHRIMP CHIPS!
THEY MAKE YOU STINK UP THE CHANGEROOM.
SHRIMP AND B.O.
YOU'RE A BUM AND YOU HANG OUT AT MY HOUSE TOO MUCH.
THAT'S BECAUSE YOU PEE ON THE TOILET SEAT!
MY MOM DOESN'T WANT YOU OVER!
WHAT!
COME ON ISABELLA, COME ON.
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT -
I THINK I LEFT HER CAGE OPEN WHEN I FED HER.
NO, NO, IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
COME ON!
I CAN'T QUITE REACH HER.
WELL IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE SHE'S COMING OUT ANY TIME SOON.
LOOK JT I CAN STAY,
YOU CAN GO.
NO.
LOOK, CAN YOU CALL MY PARENTS?
TELL THEM I'M STAYING HERE UNTIL ISABELLA COMES OUT.
OKAY, BUT THIS COULD TAKE AWHILE.
THAT'S OKAY,
COME ON.
MAYBE WE HAVE TO LURE HER OUT.
MAKE IT SEEM MORE COMFORTABLE OUT HERE.
IT'S HOPELESS.
IF I WASN'T SO TIRED.
I SAW ON THE NET THAT THEY LIKE SOFT MUSIC AND LOW LIGHTS.
HEY, YOU EVER WONDER WHY THEY CALL THEM GUINEA PIGS?
I MEAN, THEY'RE NOT FROM GUINEA AND THEY'RE NOT PIGS.
THEY'RE RODENTS.
EXACTLY. IT'S LIKE QUICKSAND.
THEY CALL IT QUICK-SAND,
BUT IT ACTUALLY WORKS REALLY REALLY SLOWLY.
AND A BOXING RING IS SQUARE.
STAND-UP COMIC, HUH?
ALL RIGHT, I CAN SEE IT.
SO SHOULD I GIVE UP MY DREAMS OF VET-HOOD?
NO, YOU SHOULD DO EXACTLY WHAT IT IS THAT YOU WANT DO.
BUT MAKE SURE YOU GRADUATE FROM SCHOOL FIRST.
WERE YOU ALWAYS A SCIENCE TEACHER?
I MEAN, NEVER A - A MODEL?
NO. TEACHING IS MY LIFE, JT.
AND THAT'S WHY WHAT YOU DID - REALLY HURT ME.
I'M SORRY OKAY.
I REALLY AM.
UH JT, YOUR PLAN WORKED.
LOOK.
HEY.
CLOSE THE DOOR.
ALL RIGHT, GOOD JOB.
ANYMORE HONESTY YOU WANNA SHARE?
UM YEAH - YOUR IDEA SUCKED.
YEAH. THE TRUTH DOES HURT.
OKAY, LET'S TAKE OUT YOUR COPIES OF "THE CHRYSALIDS".
GENTLEMEN? IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG?
UM... NO NOTHING AT ALL - HONEST.
YEAH WE WERE JUST TALKING ABOUT
HOW STUNNING YOU LOOK TODAY, MS. KWAN.
OKAY, LET'S START WITH THE THEME.
YOU KNOW I WASN'T REALLY GOING TO TRANSFER OUT OF YOUR CLASS?
REALLY? MAYBE YOU SHOULD HAVE.
THE TOUGH PART OF THE TERM STARTS TODAY.
I'VE GOT A KILLER POP QUIZ.
GOTCHA.
OKAY HOW DID EVERY ONE DO WITH THEIR HOMEWORK ASSIGNMENT?
HEY.
I HEARD YOU HAD A LITTLE "QUALITY TIME" LAST NIGHT
WITH MS. HOT SAUCE.
YEAH SO THROW US A BONE HERE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
LAST NIGHT? WELL THE LIGHTS WERE DIMMED.
SOFT MUSIC PLAYED ON THE RADIO.
WE JUST LOOKED INTO EACH OTHER'S EYES.
I MEAN, WE WERE THIS CLOSE.
AND...
IT WAS BEAUTIFUL.
ISABELLA CRAWLED IN HER CAGE
AND HAD HER BABIES FIFTEEN MINUTES LATER.
THAT'S IT?
THAT'S ALL?
HEY GUINEA PIG CHILDBIRTH IS A VERY EXCITING PROCESS, GUYS.