GOOD MORNING, DEGRASSI. I'M LIBERTY VAN ZANDT.
CONGRATS THIS MORNING TO TOBY ISAACS
AND HIS COMPUTER PROGRAMMING TEAM.
THANKS TO THEM, DEGRASSI PLACED THIRD IN THE REGIONALS!
NICE WORK, TOBY.
THE CHESS CLUB IS ALSO ON A WINNING STREAK.
THEY PLACED SECOND IN THE ALL CITY FINALS
WHICH WERE SIMULTANEOUSLY BROADCAST ON THE INTERNET...
THAT'S IT?
NASCAR IS EXCITING.
BRITNEY IN A HOT TUB? THAT'S EXCITING.
THIRD PLACE IN SOME GEEK CONTEST - NOT.
IN SPORTS, FOR ALL BOYS INTERESTED
IN THE WRESTLING TEAM,
THERE'S A MEETING AFTER SCHOOL IN THE GYM.
SPEAKING OF WRESTLING, LAST YEAR'S CHAMPION, SEAN CAMERON,
HAS BEEN NAMED THIS MONTH'S OVERALL SPORTS MVP
BY THE STUDENTS' ATHLETIC ASSOCIATION.
THAT'S FANTASTIC, SEAN!
NICE TO BE HIM.
FORGET IT. JUST FORGET IT.
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I know I can make it through
♪ If I hold out
♪ If I do...
♪ I know I can make it through
♪ Be the best
♪ The best that I can be
♪ Hear what I say to you
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I can see it
♪ I know I can make it
♪ I know I can make it through.
THIS IS DEOXYRIBONUCLEIC ACID OR DNA.
AND DNA MAKES UP YOUR GENES.
TAKE ONE AND PASS IT BACK.
YOU DONE SULKING?
I'M NOT.
I JUST EXPECTED -
I DON'T KNOW, SOMETHING.
SOME KIND OF REACTION.
LIKE WHAT?
'OH TOBY, I JUST LOVE A MAN WHO CAN WRITE BINARY CODE.'
BOYS?
CARE TO SHARE WITH THE CLASS?
I WAS JUST WONDERING IF EVERYTHING ABOUT US
IS DECIDED BY DNA?
SOME THINGS. LIKE YOUR EYE COLOUR.
BUT THERE ARE OTHER THINGS ABOUT US
THAT WE HAVE THE POWER TO CHANGE.
OKAY GUYS, REMEMBER TO BRING BACK THESE DIAGRAMS
FOR TOMORROW'S CLASS.
BUT NO ONE NOTICES ME.
SURE THEY DO.
YOU'RE THE LOVEABLE-IF SLIGHTLY-INVISIBLE
COMPUTER EXPERT.
THAT'S IT?
WELL. YEAH.
NO BIG DEAL. YOU COULD CHANGE YOUR IMAGE.
YOU COULD MOON THE CAF.
I COULD DYE MY HAIR GREEN.
YOU COULD TAKE UP SNOWBOARDING.
I COULD TRY OUT FOR WRESTLING.
YEAH, NOW THAT'S FUNNY.
NO. BAD TOBY.
NO ONE IGNORES JOCKS, JT.
I THINK IT'S A GREAT IDEA.
WIRELESS WEB ACCESS, EMAIL
AND GPS? TER, YOUR PHONE RULES.
THE SALESMAN SAID IT WAS THE BEST.
TER!
OKAY, HON. WE GROW TIRED OF YOUR GAMES.
YOU GOT TO SPILL.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
A NEW COAT TWO DAYS AGO A NEW COAT.
YESTERDAY, A NEW BAG.
TODAY, A NEW CELL PHONE.
WE WON'T STAND FOR IT ANY LONGER.
MY DAD MADE SOME EXTRA MONEY.
WHAT? DID HE ROB A BANK?
PAIGE, GET OFF HER BACK.
I WILL. WHEN SHE TELLS ME WHERE THE MONEY'S COMING FROM.
I FORGOT MY LUNCH IN MY LOCKER.
CAN YOU BELIEVE HER?
OKAY, CALL ME CRAZY BUT -
DO YOU THINK TERRI'S GOT A BAD CASE OF STICKY FINGERS?
MORE LIKE, SHOPLIFTING?
TOBY, YOU REALIZE YOU'LL GET KILLED.
CREAMED. SQUASHED. MURDERIZED.
QUIT IT, JT.
I'M JUST BEING REALISTIC.
REMEMBER WHAT HAPPENED IN GYM YESTERDAY?
THAT'S BECAUSE ALL I EVER DO IS SIT IN FRONT OF A COMPUTER.
UH-HUH?
SO IF I GO OUT FOR WRESTLING
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO GET FIT.
AND NO ONE WILL EVER LAUGH AT ME AGAIN.
TOBY...
DO YOU HAVE YOUR KEYS? I WON'T BE HOME AFTER SCHOOL.
FOR YOUR INFORMATION, VAMPIRE,
I HAVE WRESTLING PRACTICE AFTER SCHOOL.
YOU? WRESTLING? RIGHT.
DON'T SAY A WORD.
I CAN MAKE THE TEAM, JT.
SECRET ADMIRER?
NO. JUST A FRIEND.
JUST HER PAROLE OFFICER.
OKAY, TER. WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL US?
TELL YOU WHAT?
YOU DON'T KNOW?
OKAY, COME WITH ME. I'VE GOTTA SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
NOT THAT AGAIN.
I MEANT OUTSIDE. C'MON.
TERRI MCGREGOR. UNDERCOVER SUPER-MODEL.
TER, YOU LOOK FABULOUS.
HON, WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL US?
WHY? BECAUSE I'M FAT.
TER. THERE'S NOTHING TO BE ASHAMED OF.
AT ALL.
YOU'RE A MODEL.
YEAH, IN A HUGE AD CAMPAIGN.
YO BELUGA!
YO, SHUT UP, MORON.
HEY, THE PHOTOGRAPHER USE THE WIDE-ANGLE LENS OR WHAT?
YES, LOSER.
JUST LIKE YOU NEED A MICROSCOPE TO FIND YOUR--
I WAS GOING TO SAY "BRAIN"!
OH, MAN.
TOBY!
YOU LOST?
NO. NO, I'M HERE FOR WRESTLING.
OKAY, GUYS, LISTEN UP.
NOW THE TRY OUTS ARE NEXT WEEK.
AND AS YOU KNOW, WE ONLY HAVE ROOM FOR ONE WRESTLER
IN EACH WEIGHT CLASS.
SO, LET'S GET STARTED. ANDREWS?
51 KILOS - GOOD.
ISAACS?
55.
SHOULD TOBY AND I START?
NO. YOU GUYS ARE IN DIFFERENT WEIGHT CLASSES.
ACTUALLY, ISAACS YOU'RE IN THE 54 TO 57-AND-A-HALF KILO CLASS.
UP AGAINST - SEAN.
TEN MINUTES LEFT. SO, USE THIS TIME FOR INTERNET RESEARCH.
HEY, I FOUND THE BEST WRESTLING SITE.
MAYBE IN A FEW YEARS I COULD BE LIKE THIS GUY.
UH, EARTH TO TOBY.
LET'S JUST CONCENTRATE ON GETTING YOU ON THE TEAM FIRST.
POINT TAKEN.
HEY, CONGRATULATIONS ON PLACING THIRD IN THE FINALS.
I'M PROUD OF YOU, TOBY.
THAT'S INTERESTING RESEARCH TOPIC, GUYS.
YOU KNOW 'MAKING WEIGHT' IS A PRETTY SERIOUS PROBLEM.
A LOT OF KIDS END UP IN THE HOSPITAL.
WELL, ON THE COMPUTING TEAM WE DON'T 'MAKE WEIGHT' -
WE MAKE PROGRAMS.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, TOBY?
THAT'S RIGHT, COACH.
I HAVE TO MAKE THE WRESTLING TEAM.
THIS IS MURDER.
THREE DAYS AND I'VE ONLY LOST ONE POUND.
DING! LOSING ATTITUDE!
YOUR PENALTY? THIRTY CRUNCHES.
AH! UNCLE!
FINE, WE'LL GET A DRINK FIRST.
TAKE IT FROM SOMEONE WHO LEARNED THE HARD WAY -
THOSE AREN'T REALLY CHOCOLATE.
ONLY YOU'D MAKE THAT MISTAKE.
I'M JUST HERE FOR A GOOD ENERGY BAR.
UH, LAXATIVES - SO TASTY GOING IN, SO NASTY GOING OUT.
MATCH TO FEIN!
WELCOME TO THE TEAM, REGGIE. GOOD JOB.
ISAACS, SCALE.
53 KILOS?
THAT'S QUITE A LOSS.
I'M TRAINING HARD, COACH.
YOU KNOW ANY PLAYER CAUGHT 'MAKING WEIGHT' WILL BE CUT.
WOULDN'T DO ANYTHING SO STUPID.
ANDREWS?
LOOKS LIKE YOU GOT COMPETITION. LET'S GO.
SHAKE HANDS.
GOOD LUCK.
YOU TOO.
MATCH TO ISAACS. WELCOME TO THE TEAM!
YEAH!
SOMEONE'S IN A GOOD MOOD.
TODAY MARKS A NEW CHAPTER IN THE BOOK OF TOBY ISAACS.
MAKING THE WRESTLING TEAM IS THAT IMPORTANT TO YOU?
YES. BECAUSE NOW, I AM A JOCK.
NERD TOBY IS NO MORE.
WELL, JOCKSTRAP - THERE ARE TWO OF THOSE GIANT
CHOCOLATE MUFFINS YOU LOVE IN THE BREAD CUPBOARD.
NOT HUNGRY.
THAT'S WHAT YOU SAID YESTERDAY. AND THE DAY BEFORE THAT.
THANK YOU, MOM.
SO YOU'RE NOT HAVING BREAKFAST.
NO. NOW, GO BACK TO SIPPING YOUR BLOOD AND LEAVE ME ALONE.
YOU MAKE THE TEAM - YOU GET A WINDBREAKER.
CONGRATULATIONS, BUDDY.
HEY NADIA - TAKE A PICTURE!
FOR THE YEARBOOK?
YEAH, SURE.
IT'S A MOMENTOUS OCCASION.
OKAY, NOW, KENDRA -
NOW, STAND HERE, ACT LIKE YOU'RE IN AWE OF ME.
GRAB MY ARM IF YOU WANT.
UM, I THINK I'LL PASS.
SO - BIG MEET TODAY.
WE'LL BE THERE TO CHEER YOU ON.
MY OWN PERSONAL FAN CLUB. COOL. CATCH YA, LAY-TAH.
SO YOU GOT YOUR NEW WINDBREAKER, HUH?
COOL, HUH?
GET A NEW PERSONALITY TO GO WITH IT?
CATCH YA, LAY-TAH?
THAT'S HOW WRESTLERS TALK.
COOL - NOT.
WHAT? JEALOUS BECAUSE I'M ON A TEAM,
WHILE YOU'RE JUST A MASCOT?
GREAT.
THIS MINI-SKIRT PHOTO IS WOW!
I'D TOTALLY WEAR IT,
IF I WAS A "PLUS".
SO, WHEN'S THE NEXT SHOOT?
TODAY. BUT MY AGENT CALLED AND CANCELLED.
HOW NICE, ANOTHER LIE FROM MS. MCGREGOR.
IT'S NOT A LIE.
I DON'T WANT TO GO, OKAY?
NOT OKAY. YOU'RE IN A NATIONAL AD CAMPAIGN.
IT WASN'T NATIONAL WHEN I AGREED TO DO IT.
SO THAT'S IT?
THAT -
AND WHAT MOHAMMED SAID.
MORNING, GANG. FIVE SECONDS TO HOME ROOM LIFT-OFF.
TER, WHO CARES WHAT MOHAMMED SAID?
THIS DISCUSSION IS NOT OVER.
OH, YES IT IS, PAIGE.
OR, IT WILL BE, IN 3-2-1.
(Bell)
BIG MEET TODAY.
DOING ANYTHING SPECIAL TO GET READY?
MAYBE NOT DOING SOMETHING?
LIKE - NOT EATING?
NOT THIS AGAIN.
TOBY, YOU'RE NORMALLY A GARBARATOR.
I'M JUST NOT HUNGRY THESE DAYS.
FINE. I'LL JUST HAVE TO TAKE IT UP WITH MOM AND JEFF.
BACON CHILI BURGER SUPREME WITH CHUNKY FRIES.
EXTRA SHEILA SAUCE.
HEY, EASY BIG GUY, I GOT TO FEED A WHOLE SCHOOL.
THERE YOU GO, LUMBERJACK!
SEE?
EATING.
HAPPY?
(Vomiting)
TOBY? IS THAT YOU?
SHEILA'S SPECIAL SAUCE AIN'T SO SPECIAL.
COULD YOU LEAVE ME ALONE?
WELL, DO YOU WANT THE NURSE OR SOMETHING?
NO, JUST SOME PRIVACY.
NOW!
(Vomiting)
JT?
OH, HEY ASHLEY.
I WONDERED WHEN YOU'D TUNE INTO MY LOVE VIBE.
LET'S SKIP YOUR LITTLE FANTASY.
OKAY. LET'S TALK ABOUT YOURS.
JT -
I'M WORRIED ABOUT TOBY.
I KNOW. HE'S BEEN ALL WEIRD AND CRABBY LATELY.
BUT, HE IS IN TRAINING.
TRAINING FOR AN EATING DISORDER.
WHAT? YOU'RE SERIOUS.
YEAH, I AM.
I'M PRETTY SURE TOBY'S A GUY.
I MEAN, THAT'S GIRL STUFF.
NO, IT ISN'T. GUYS CAN HAVE IT TOO.
SO IF YOU NOTICE ANYTHING -
I WANT TO KNOW ABOUT IT.
OKAY - POP QUIZ.
CLICK ON THE 'POP QUIZ' LINK.
YOU HAVE 15 MINUTES.
AND WHEN YOUR TIME IS UP,
THE TEST WILL AUTOMATICALLY END.
ARE YOU OKAY?
DO YOU WANT TO SEE NURSE HENDERSON?
NO. NO, I'M FINE, MR. SIMPSON.
GOOD AFTERNOON STUDENTS,
GO SUPPORT YOUR DEGRASSI WRESTLERS,
AS THEY TAKE ON THE BARDELL TEAM THIS AFTERNOON.
ANNE MARIE, PLEASE?
I NEED TO CANCEL A SHOOT.
YEAH, SHE CAN CALL ME BACK.
TER?
MORE GRRRL CAN FIND A NEW MODEL.
WHY?
OKAY, IT'S NONE OF MY BUSINESS.
I JUST THINK IT'S TOO BAD YOU'RE GIVING UP.
SPINNER, I DREAMT OF BEING A MODEL FOR YEARS.
BUT NOT "PLUS-SIZE". NOT -
OKAY, SO YOU'RE NOT SOME TWIG.
YOU THINK GUYS REALLY LIKE THAT?
DON'T YOU?
SOMETIMES.
BUT LOTS OF TIMES GUYS LIKE GIRLS LIKE YOU.
WITH A FIGURE.
GIRLS LIKE ME?
YOU MEAN FAT?
TER, YOU'RE PRETTY.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO LIE.
I'M NOT LYING.
TER, YOU'RE REALLY PRETTY.
AND ANYONE WHO TELLS YOU DIFFERENT IS BLIND.
OR JEALOUS.
SO YOU JUST TELL THEM TO SHUT UP.
HEY.
TOBY, YOU LOOK AWFUL.
I CAUGHT YOU YAKKING.
THAT WAS SHEILA'S SAUCE.
THAT WAS YOU.
ASH AND I ARE WORRIED.
YOU'VE BEEN TALKING TO HER? BEHIND MY BACK?
TOBY, DON'T WRESTLE.
WHAT?
DON'T WRESTLE.
THERE'S A GYM FULL OF PEOPLE OUT THERE WAITING FOR ME.
ME - AND I'M GONNA GO IN THERE AND I'M GONNA WIN.
AND NOT THIRD PRIZE IN SOME 'GEEK CONTEST'.
ISAACS? WEIGH-IN! LET'S GO!
54 TO 57 KILO CHAMP - REDGATE, BARDELL HIGH!
NEXT UP. REPRESENTING BARDELL, BRAD THERRIAULT.
FOR DEGRASSI, TOBY ISAACS.
SHAKE HANDS.
TOBY?
BUDDY, WAKE UP!
IT WAS SO AWESOME.
HERE, LOOK AT THE TEST SHOTS.
SO NICE.
YEAH.
HEY, LOOK WHO IT IS.
IT'S THE MORE-OF-EVERYTHING GIRL.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK YOU SHOULD JOIN OUR SUMO TEAM. SERIOUSLY.
HEY! MOST GIRLS ON THE PLANET LOOK LIKE THIS,
SO GET USED TO IT!
NO KIDDING.
I MADE 500 BUCKS TODAY AS A PLUS-SIZE MODEL -
YEAH, PLUS-SIZE.
WHAT DO YOU MAKE ICE CREAM BOY?
NICE, TERRI.
HEY, YOU OKAY?
ASH IS ON THE PHONE WITH MY DAD.
HE'S ON HIS WAY.
YOU'RE OFF THE TEAM, RIGHT?
ARMSTRONG CHEWED ME OUT.
HE SAID I WAS PLAYING WITH MY LIFE.
LISTEN, TOBES, YOU CAN CRY IF YOU WANT.
BUT I'M NOT GIVING YOU A HUG.
LEAST I GAVE EVERYONE A GOOD LAUGH.
HARDLY.
NEWS GOT OUT, PEOPLE FREAKED.
EVEN SEAN ASKED IF YOU WERE OKAY.
THE WHOLE SCHOOL'S WORRIED.
I HAD A NICE LITTLE CHAT WITH KENDRA.
SHE'S LIKE, 'OH, I HOPE HE'S OKAY. I'M SO WORRIED!'
SO, YOU STILL THINK YOU'RE INVISIBLE, TOBES?