HOW COULD YOU EVEN THINK OF HAVING AN ABORTION?
IT'S A WOMAN'S CHOICE.
WHAT ABOUT THE BABY'S CHOICE?
I'M NOT GONNA DEBATE THIS WITH YOU. IT'S MY DECISION, EM.
WHAT ABOUT SNAKE?
OF COURSE, HE'D BE A PART OF IT.
YEAH, LIKE HE'S A PART OF IT RIGHT NOW.
EMMA, YOU'RE WAY OUT OF LINE.
WHAT DO YOU EXPECT ME TO SAY?
MAYBE SOMETHING SUPPORTIVE.
IF YOU HAD AN ABORTION THE FIRST TIME,
I WOULDN'T BE HERE.
WELL IF YOU WERE IN MY SHOES,
AND MADE THIS MISTAKE A SECOND TIME?
EM... NO, I DIDN'T MEAN IT THAT WAY.
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I know I can make it though
♪ If I hold out
♪ If I do
♪ I know I can make it through
♪ Be the best
♪ The best that I can be
♪ Hear what I say to you
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I can see it
♪ I know I can make it through
OKAY, FANCY PROBABLY WON'T BE ON FOR AWHILE.
BUT WE'LL HAVE TO STAY AWAKE, OKAY?
YEAH, YEAH, OKAY.
I'LL TAKE FIRST SHIFT, YOU TAKE SECOND.
DEAL.
WHAT IF WE GET CAUGHT?
WE WON'T.
AND EVEN IF WE DO, WHAT'RE WE DOING WRONG?
I DON'T KNOW. INVASION OF PRIVACY?
TOBY, SHE'S A STRIPPER.
PRIVACY ISN'T IN HER VOCABULARY.
YEAH, I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT. SHE IS TAKING OFF HER CLOTHES.
AND SHE'S GETTING PAID.
I JUST WISH WE WERE INSIDE.
I KNOW.
BUT WE'LL STILL BE CLOSER THAN EITHER OF US HAVE COME
TO SEEING A REAL LIVE NAKED WOMAN.
EXCEPT FOR THAT TIME
WHEN YOU WALKED IN ON YOUR GRANDMA IN THE SHOWER.
WE BOTH AGREED - THAT NEVER HAPPENED.
RIGHT.
COME ON.
GO, GO, GO, GO.
TIME TO TEST OUT THE FANCY CAM.
RADITCH!
AHHHHH!
TURN IT OFF! TURN IT OFF!
SORRY.
WHY IS HE THERE?
IT'S GETTING LATE.
I THOUGHT WE WERE HEADING TO THE BOWLING ALLEY.
OH, YOU WERE SERIOUS ABOUT THE BOWLING ALLEY?
WHAT? BOWLING'S FUN.
ARCHIE, MY MAN.
THIS IS YOUR STAG AND I WANT YOU TO GET INTO IT.
RIGHT, MR. RADITCH.
AND I MEAN - RIGHT NOW.
AND IT'S DAN TONIGHT.
OOH! CHEESE BALLS.
I'M SURE SHE DIDN'T MEAN IT.
SHE SAID, "SAME MISTAKE TWICE."
YEAH, BUT SHE DIDN'T HAVE AN ABORTION.
SO?
SO, YOU WERE WANTED.
OKAY, FINE, WHATEVER!
BUT THIS ISN'T ABOUT ME.
IT'S ABOUT MY FUTURE HALF-BROTHER... OR SISTER.
AND WHAT ABOUT SNAKE?
EMMA -
I MEAN, HERE WE ARE DEBATING ABORTION
AND HE DOESN'T EVEN KNOW SHE'S PREGNANT.
WHAT IF SHE DOESN'T TELL HIM?
DO NOT EVEN THINK OF INTERFERING.
DON'T WORRY. I'M NOT THAT STUPID.
GOOD. SO LET'S GET SOME SLEEP.
BECAUSE TOMORROW'S GOING TO BE A LONG AND WONDERFUL DAY.
WOW!
YEAH! YEAH.
(DOOR BELL)
HOLD ON.
GUYS, THE PARTY'S STARTED.
HI.
HEY.
ARE YOU SNAKE?
WHY, YES, I AM.
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
COME ON!
GO UPSTAIRS, GO UPSTAIRS NOW.
HI, COME ON IN.
(Clapping)
UH, THAT'S SNAKE RIGHT OVER THERE.
JEREMIAH...
IT'S YOUR PARTY MAN, HAVE FUN.
OW! WHOO HOO HOO!
SO, SNAKE.
EMMA DOESN'T HATE YOU.
IF YOU COULDA SEEN THE LOOK IN HER EYES.
WHAT WAS I THINKING?
YEAH, BUT YOU'VE JUST BEEN THROWN FOR A MAJOR LOOP.
YOU GOT TO CUT YOURSELF SOME SLACK.
I NEED TO TALK TO ARCHIE.
UH, NOT TONIGHT THOUGH, RIGHT?
BACHELOR PARTY - NOT IN A STATE TO HEAR THIS.
HE NEEDS TO KNOW.
AND YOU NEED TO GET YOURSELF TOGETHER. RIGHT?
CALL IN THE MORNING. IT CAN WAIT.
IT'S GOING TO BE OKAY.
AHHHHH!
AHHHH!
WHAT ARE YOU TWO DOING HERE?
SEEING A STRIPPER. AND YOU?
OH, SURPRISE, SURPRISE.
COME HERE, COME HERE - BOTH OF YOU.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
GET IN THE HOUSE!
BOTH OF YOU! DO YOU KNOW WHAT TIME IT IS?
MR. SIMPSON, WE NEED TO TALK.
YOUR PARENTS MUST BE WORRIED SICK.
MY PARENTS? WHAT ABOUT US?
WE MISSED FANCY, HOW DO YOU THINK WE FEEL?
DO YOU THINK I CARE? BUT I'M SURE YOUR PARENTS WILL.
I WANT YOU TO BOTH STAY THERE, DON'T GET INTO ANY TROUBLE.
I'M TAKING YOU BOTH HOME.
EMMA, IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW HOW TO SAY THIS.
TRY. BECAUSE YOU'RE GIVING ME A HEART ATTACK.
OKAY. MOM IS PREGNANT.
AND SHE'S THINKING OF HAVING AN ABORTION.
YEAH, I'M WORRIED ABOUT A STRIPPER, AND SHE'S PREGNANT.
SNAKE, PLEASE, JUST LISTEN.
EMMA, WHY ARE YOU HERE?
WHY ARE YOU HERE TELLING ME THIS?
BECAUSE YOU NEED TO KNOW.
WHY YOU? WHY NOT YOUR MOM?
WHY NOT YOUR MOM?!?
I'M SORRY.
BUT REALLY, WHAT KIND OF FAMILY IS THIS?
YOU WAIT HERE AND JOEY WILL DRIVE YOU HOME.
THIS IS JUST GREAT.
IT'S MY WEDDING DAY AND THE GROOM HAS DISAPPEARED.
HE'S NOT AT HIS APARTMENT OR AT JOEY'S.
HE'S NOT ANSWERING HIS CELL.
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO REACH YOU!
BUT NOT YESTERDAY?
NOT LAST NIGHT?
NO, RIGHT. BECAUSE IT WAS EMMA WHO WAS LOOKING FOR ME.
WHAT?
HOW DOES INFORMATION TRAVEL IN THIS FAMILY?
OH, RIGHT - EVERY WHICH WAY EXCEPT FROM YOU TO ME.
EMMA.
NO, NOT EMMA! THIS IS ABOUT YOU AND ME!
HOW COULD YOU NOT TELL ME THAT YOU'RE PREGNANT?!
WE NEED TO TALK. BUT WE ARE NOT DOING IT HERE.
WE ARE GOING TO TALK ABOUT THIS RIGHT NOW.
NOT HERE!
♪ EVERYBODY WANTS SOMETHING, THEY'LL NEVER GIVE UP.
♪ EVERYBODY WANTS SOMETHING.
HEY, EM.
THAT'S A DUMB SONG.
IT'S SAVE THE HAIR TIME.
IF WE'RE GONNA DO THIS, COME ON INSIDE.
I'LL GIVE YOU THE SHIRT OFF MY BACK.
HEY COME ON, I KNOW THINGS LOOK BAD.
BUT WE GOT TO KEEP GOING AS IF THE WEDDING IS HAPPENING. HERE.
AS IF IT'S HAPPENING?
WHICH MEANS, IT'S NOT?
HEY COME ON, YOU DON'T KNOW THAT.
JUST FORGET IT! I'VE RUINED EVERYTHING!
EMMA, STOP BEING A BABY.
JUST GET READY FOR THE WEDDING.
MANNY, MIND YOUR OWN BUSINESS.
OH, THAT'S FUNNY.
DIDN'T I TELL YOU THE SAME THING, LAST NIGHT.
I DID WHAT I FELT WAS RIGHT.
YESTERDAY YOU FREAKED BECAUSE I TALKED TO SEAN.
WHAT YOU DID, WAS SO MUCH WORSE.
WELL, GEE, MANNY.
THANKS FOR THE SUPPORT. WHAT A BEST FRIEND YOU ARE.
GUYS...
HEY, HEY, LADIES, LADIES, TAKE IT EASY.
EVERYTHING'S GOING TO BE FINE. I KNOW IT.
HEY!
DON'T HIT THE CAR.
I JUST FOUND OUT YESTERDAY.
THEN YOU SHOULD'VE COME TO ME.
I KNOW -
TO HEAR IT FROM EMMA... AND AN ABORTION!?
DO YOU REALLY THINK I'D SEND EMMA,
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT, TO BREAK THE NEWS TO YOU?
YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES IT'S LIKE YOU AND EMMA ARE THE COUPLE,
NOT YOU AND ME.
SHE'S MY DAUGHTER.
YOU CAN'T EXPECT THAT I'LL JUST CHANGE OUR RELATIONSHIP.
OF COURSE NOT.
BUT IF THIS IS GONNA WORK, THEN SOME THINGS HAVE TO BE PRIVATE.
I DON'T LIKE SECRETS, SNAKE.
AND NEITHER DO I. TRUST ME.
YOU SURE YOU'RE NOT HAVING DOUBTS?
ARCHIE...
THIS ALL HAPPENED PRETTY FAST.
WE'VE KNOWN EACH OTHER SINCE JUNIOR HIGH.
YEAH. AS FRIENDS.
MAYBE WE'RE SUPPOSED TO KEEP IT THAT WAY.
MAN, THESE WRESTLER'S TODAY.
OH SEAN, YOU GOT TO CHECK THIS OUT, MAN.
HI EMMA.
EMMA? GREAT.
SEAN, I'VE RUINED EVERYTHING.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I INTERFERED AND I RUINED EVERYTHING.
AND I DON'T EVEN THINK THE WEDDING'S GONNA HAPPEN.
AND EVERYONE'S GOING TO HATE ME.
EMMA - YOU INTERFERING?
IT'S NOTHING NEW.
DO PEOPLE EVER HATE YOU FOR IT?
MAYBE? BEHIND MY BACK.
NO. NEVER.
SO, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT. IT'LL ALL WORK OUT.
I REALLY, REALLY HOPE SO.
SEAN.
WHAT ABOUT WHAT I DID TO YOU? IT WAS -
IT SUCKED, ALL RIGHT?
MANNY SHOULD HAVE NEVER INVITED ME.
I KNOW. I SHOULD HAVE.
SEAN, IF THE WEDDING DOES HAPPEN?
THE PARTY STARTS AT THREE.
THANKS.
EMMA?!
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR HAIR?
YOU'RE - YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
SO UM, I TAKE IT THAT WE HAVE A CHANGE OF PLANS TODAY?
WHERE IS THE BRIDE?
YEAH, NO BRIDE, NO GROOM.
NO BRIDE'S MAID EITHER.
HOW BAD DID YOUR PARENTS BUST YOU?
ON A SCALE OF 1 TO 10?
136.
YEAH, I'M GROUNDED TILL DOOMSDAY.
ME TOO.
IF I WASN'T AN USHER,
KATE WOULDN'T HAVE LET ME OUT OF THE HOUSE.
HEY.
OH, LOOK WHO IT IS.
YOU HERE TO STEAL ANOTHER ONE OF OUR BRILLIANT IDEAS, CRAIG?
NO, I'M HERE TO TELL YOU
THAT SOMEONE VERY, FANCY JUST PULLED UP.
FANCY?
YEAH. FANCY.
MADAME.
YOU'RE HERE FOR THE GROOM?
NO, THE BRIDE.
CHRISTINE DOES MY HAIR.
OH, VERY GOOD.
RIGHT THIS WAY.
OH, THANK YOU.
HE GETS LOST EASILY.
ALLOW ME.
OH, THANK YOU.
NO, ME.
NO REALLY, ME!
OKAY.
REALLY, OKAY, THAT'S ENOUGH.
I GOT IT.
SPIKE'S JUST LATE, AS USUAL.
YEAH, NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
OKAY.
RIGHT?
OH, I JUST HOPE I CAN GET MY MONEY BACK FOR THE SUIT.
HUH!
JOEY!
HEY! ARE THEY HERE YET?
NOT YET.
BUT I'M GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
SORRY ABOUT EARLIER.
SORRY ABOUT THE HAIR.
LUCY, IF IT'S HUMANLY POSSIBLE,
COULD YOU PLEASE TRY AND DO SOMETHING ABOUT THIS HAIR?
SURE, COME ON EMMA.
I JUST CAN'T UNDERSTAND HOW IT HAPPENED.
YOU WERE THERE.
I MEAN, YOU'RE ON THE PILL.
YEAH, WHICH IS 98 PERCENT EFFECTIVE.
SO WE'RE JUST IN THE UNLUCKY TWO PERCENT.
GREAT.
SOME COUPLES WOULD THINK OF THIS AS A BLESSING.
TOO BAD YOU'RE AGAINST KIDS.
HEY, I NEVER SAID THAT.
HOW ABOUT YESTERDAY?
YOU SAID YOU HAVE TOO MUCH ON YOUR PLATE.
WELL YEAH, I DO. I'VE GOT A LOT GOING ON RIGHT NOW.
I'M MOVING IN, I'M GONNA BE A HUSBAND AND A STEP-DAD
AND I'VE GOT A LOT -
A LOT OF ADJUSTING, I KNOW.
BUT LIFE DOESN'T WAIT FOR YOU TO 'GET ADJUSTED', SNAKE.
IT JUST HAPPENS.
I MEAN, LOOK AT EMMA.
SHE COULDN'T HAVE COME AT A WORSE TIME.
BUT WAS IT A MISTAKE TO HAVE HER?
NO.
I WOULDN'T TRADE HER FOR ANYTHING.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE THERE'S A LITTLE ONE GROWING IN THERE.
THERE IS. SHE - OR HE IS GONNA BE BEAUTIFUL.
SO, WHICH ONE OF US DOESN'T WANT THIS BABY ANYWAYS?
IT IS A BIT LATE.
THEY'LL BE HERE ANY SECOND.
WE HAVE ANOTHER WEDDING COMING IN HERE IN AN HOUR.
I'M AFRAID IF THEY'RE NOT HERE SOON,
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO RESCHEDULE.
NO, THEY'LL BE HERE. NOT TO WORRY.
EMMA, THEY'LL BE FINE, THEY'LL MAKE IT.
AHHH!
EMMA!
HEY!
HEY MOM, SNAKE.
WE'VE GOT A WEDDING TO GO TO. COME ON.
COME ON, WE'RE GETTING MARRIED!
HELLO! HEY... SORRY WE'RE LATE, EVERYBODY.
DO YOU, CHRISTINE NELSON, TAKE ARCHIBALD RUPERT SIMPSON
TO BE YOUR LAWFULLY WEDDED HUSBAND?
I DO.
AND DO YOU, ARCHIBALD RUPERT SIMPSON,
TAKE CHRISTINE NELSON TO BE YOUR LAWFULLY WEDDED WIFE?
I DO.
THEN WITH THE POWER VESTED IN ME,
I NOW PRONOUNCE YOU HUSBAND AND WIFE.
YOU MAY NOW KISS THE BRIDE.
(Clapping)
WOO HOO HOO!
YEAH!
WOO HOO!
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR COMING, EVERYBODY.
THANK YOU.
CONNIE! YOU MADE IT.
OH, OF COURSE I MADE IT.
I WOULDN'T MISS IT FOR THE WORLD.
THIS IS MY HUSBAND, ARCHIE.
ARCHIE, HUH?
HONEY? YOU DON'T LOOK LIKE AN ARCHIE TO ME.
CONGRATS.
HONEY, IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
UH, NO.
WHAT IS IT?
I UM... HOW DO I SAY THIS?
JOEY SORT OF ARRANGED FOR A STRIPPER TO COME THE STAG.
AS A MATTER OF FACT - IT WAS FANCY. CONNIE.
(Laughing)
YOU'RE NOT MAD?
FANCY CAN DO WHAT SHE WANTS WITH HER BODY.
IT'S HER BUSINESS.
WHAT A RELIEF.
WAIT A SECOND. I'M COOL WITH HOW FANCY MAKES HER LIVING...
I SENSE A 'BUT' COMING.
BUT I'M NOT COOL WITH MY HUSBAND
BEING ONE OF THOSE PATHETIC LOSERS WHO GOES TO STRIPPERS.
ESPECIALLY WHEN I KNOW THE STRIPPER.
GROSS.
POINT TAKEN. NEVER AGAIN.
WAIT A MINUTE. WHAT IF PEOPLE FIND OUT?
WELL, THEY WON'T. IT'LL BE OUR LITTLE SECRET.
THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK...
GIRLS?
NO, NO, NO, DON'T - DON'T YOU -
IT'S TIME TO TOSS THE BOUQUET!
COME ON. WHO WILL BE THE LUCKY GIRL?
LOOKS LIKE I'M THE LUCKY GIRL.
WICKED CATCH.
SORRY.
WHAT?
IT ACTUALLY HAS TO BE CAUGHT BY A GIRL.
BUT I HAD SO MANY PLANS.
EXCUSE ME, WOULD YOU MIND PUTTING THAT DOWN FOR ME.
THANK YOU.
DO TELL.
I WILL. BUT YOU HAVE TO DANCE WITH ME FIRST.
WELL, ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
SO DEMANDING.
NO, NO.
♪ IT WAS AN AVERAGE DAY, DULL IN EVERY WAY
♪ UNTIL - UNTIL THE SUN BROKE THROUGH
♪ IT WASN'T IN THE SKY, NO. THE LIGHT CAME FROM HER EYES
♪ SHE TURNED - TURNED THE GREY SKY BLUE
♪ ON A CLEAR SEPTEMBER MORNING, I SAW HER IN THE RAIN
♪ TO ME SHE WAS A MOVIE STAR TO THE WORLD
♪ FIRST SHE SEEMED CONFUSED
♪ I SAW SHE WASN'T SURE MY SMILE WAS MEANT FOR HER
♪ I SAID I CAN'T HELP NOTICE YOU
♪ AND WHEN YOU FIND THAT SOMEONE SPECIAL
♪ DON'T LET THEM SLIP AWAY
♪ SO TELL ME WHAT YOUR NAME IS
♪ SHE ANSWERED BY SAYING, JUST JANE...
HEY.
UH, IT'S A SLOW SONG, AND YOU'RE NOT DANCING?
NO ONE REALLY CAUGHT MY INTEREST.
OH. HOW 'BOUT NOW?
I'D LOVE TO.
♪ SHE'LL ALWAYS BE JUST JANE.
♪ BUT BECAUSE OF HER MY WORLD HAS CHANGED
♪ OH... CHANGED... OH...