IT'S ALL ABOUT THE TIGHT SATIN SHORTS IF YOU ASK ME.
OOH! TIGHT SATIN SHORTS? WE'RE THERE!
THEN PENCIL IT IN, BOYS. RETRO ROLLER-SKATING PARTY!
ROLLER-SKATING PARTY? THAT SOUNDS COOL.
FUNNY HOW SOMETHING IS COOL ONE YEAR
AND SO TOTALLY UNCOOL THE NEXT. KIND OF LIKE PEOPLE.
I GET IT, PAIGE. YOU DON'T HAVE TO INVITE ME TO YOUR DUMB PARTY.
AW. BUT I WAS KIND OF HOPING YOU COULD TAKE DRUGS
AND ACT LIKE A TOTAL FREAK AND DESTROY EVERYTHING.
OH WAIT - YOU DID THAT LAST YEAR.
I DON'T GET IT - IT WAS JUST ONE MISTAKE.
ALRIGHT, ONE BIG MISTAKE.
IT'LL ALL BLOW OVER.
OR, IT WON'T. I WANT MY FRIENDS BACK, TER.
AND JUST STANDING BY IS NOT GONNA MAKE THAT HAPPEN.
♪ WHAT EVER IT TAKES
♪ I KNOW I CAN MAKE IT THROUGH
♪ IF I HOLD OUT
♪ BE THE BEST
♪ THE BEST THAT I CAN BE
♪ HEAR WHAT I SAY TO YOU
♪ WHAT EVER IT TAKES
♪ I KNOW I CAN MAKE IT
♪ I KNOW I CAN MAKE IT THROUGH
SO WHICH DO YOU LIKE BETTER - LEFT PROFILE? OR RIGHT?
IT'S NOT A FASHION SHOOT...
UH, IT'S OUR PHOTO DAY, AND I WANT IT TO BE JUST - PERFECT!
ELLIE, RIGHT?
UH-HUH...
HERE'S THE DEAL.
HAZEL AND I - BEST FRIENDS.
BUT HAZEL'S STUCK ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE ROOM.
YOU, HOWEVER, ARE RIGHT HERE.
AND YOU WANT ME TO SWITCH.
I KNEW YOU'D UNDERSTAND.
HON. MAYBE YOU DIDN'T HEAR ME -
I DID. LOUD AND CLEAR. THANKS.
HEY, PAIGE-
OKAY THIS IS SO NOT THE TIME TO TALK TO ME.
JUST FOR A SEC? PLEASE.
WHAT?
YOU AND I HAVE BEEN FRIENDS SINCE GRADE TWO.
THAT'S ALMOST TEN YEARS. HALF OF OUR LIVES --
IS THIS AN APOLOGY OR A MATH LESSON?
AN APOLOGY. WHAT I CALLED YOU -
I BELIEVE THE WORD WAS "HAG"?
IT WAS WRONG.
I WAS THE REAL HAG. AND I'M SORRY.
MORNING FOLKS. PHOTO DAY'S COMING.
AND I'VE GOT THE FORMS TO PROVE IT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW MANY SITES THERE ARE DEVOTED TO ANIME.
NOT THIS AGAIN.
JT, ANIME IS THE BIGGEST DEVELOPMENT IN ANIMATION IN YEARS.
AN-I-REALLY-DON'T-CARE. AN-I-THINK-IT'S-FOR-GEEKS.
ANIME IS ACTUALLY VERY CURRENT.
SEE! SHE KNOWS ABOUT ANIME!
WHO'S YOUR FAVOURITE CHARACTER? ASHUHARA?
I SAID I KNOW ABOUT IT. I DIDN'T SAY I LIKE IT.
YOU SEE?
TOBY, GIRLS AREN'T INTO THAT STUFF.
HEY, CRAIG!
YOU SEE TOBY, THAT'S WHAT GIRLS ARE INTO.
AND IT'S SURE NOT ME.
I MAY BE THE FIRST JEWISH MONK.
ALRIGHT SO WHAT MOLECULE DO YOU GET
WHEN YOU HAVE TWO ATOMS OF HYDROGEN
AND TWO ATOMS OF OXYGEN?
GAVIN? GAVIN?
SORRY, MS. HATZILAKOS. I DON'T KNOW.
HYDROGEN PEROXIDE.
OR VERY BLONDE HAIR, IF YOU'RE NOT CAREFUL...
ALRIGHT REMEMBER - THE FIRST 20 ELEMENTS
ON THE PERIODIC TABLE FOR NEXT CLASS.
JIMMY.
STOP AND LISTEN. PLEASE?
I'M REALLY SORRY FOR HUMILIATING YOU.
FOR BEING CRUEL. FOR WHAT HAPPENED, WITH SEAN.
IT WAS THE DRUGS. IT WASN'T ME.
YOU MAKE IT SOUND LIKE NO BIG THING.
IT WAS. AND I'VE BEEN PAYING FOR IT, JIMMY.
I SPENT THE SUMMER IN COUNSELLING.
YOU OKAY?
YEAH. I JUST MISSED YOU, ASH.
I MISSED YOU A LOT.
I MISSED YOU TOO.
IT HASN'T FELT THE SAME.
EVEN MY MOM MISSES YOU.
REALLY?
TOBY, TOO -
HIS BASKETBALL GAME'S TOTALLY HURTING WITHOUT YOUR HELP.
WELL MAYBE I COULD COME OVER SOME TIME?
I MEAN, IF TOBY'D WANT ME TO...
KNOW WHAT? I THINK HE WOULD.
OKAY.
HEY MR. SIMPSON -- IS THAT DRAWING ANIME CD-ROM IN YET?
AH SORRY, TOBES. I FORGOT YOU WANTED IT
AND LET IT OUT TO SOMEONE ELSE.
OH ALRIGHT. WHO'S GOT IT?
ME.
TOBY ISAACS, MEET KENDRA MASON. MY TWO BIGGEST ANIME FANATICS.
MEET ME AT LUNCH TOMORROW. I'LL HAND THIS OFF.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
GREAT, SEE YOU AT LUNCH THEN.
UH... OKAY.
GUYS, THIS IS CLASSIC ASHLEY.
SHE'S SWEET-TALKING HER WAY THROUGH ALL OF US.
PAIGE, C'MON -
C'MON WHAT?
IF I CAN FORGIVE ASH, THEN SO CAN YOU.
YOU STILL LIKE HER, DON'T YOU?
WE HAD A GOOD TALK, LIKE OLD TIMES.
YEAH. TOTALLY OLD TIMES.
ASH'S BEEN "MISSING JIMMY" TOO.
OKAY, AM I, LIKE, THE ONLY SANE ONE HERE?
OR THE ONLY THREATENED ONE...
WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?
I SAID, MAYBE YOU SHOULD LET IT GO.
ASH MADE A MISTAKE, SHE APOLOGIZED.
YOU GUYS MIGHT BE RIGHT.
BUT IF YOU'RE NOT? ASH BETTER WATCH OUT.
LISTEN QUEEN-BEE, THIS ISN'T A SOUP KITCHEN I'M RUNNING HERE.
I KNOW. I'LL BRING THE EXTRA DOLLAR TOMORROW, I PROMISE.
HEY I GOT THAT.
SAVED BY THE KNIGHT IN SHINING DENIM. NEXT!
THANKS FOR THAT.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
SO, HOW LONG ARE WE GOING TO PRETEND LIKE NOTHING HAPPENED?
HAVEN'T WE PAID FOR IT BY NOW?
IF YOU SAY SO.
I DO. FRIENDS, OKAY?
YEAH.
ARE YOU EVER GONNA TELL ME WHAT HAPPENED WITH YOU TWO?
A PARTY LAST YEAR, WE HOOKED UP.
AND SHE'S IGNORED YOU EVER SINCE.
WELL SHE'S NOT IGNORING YOU NOW...
OKAY, TWELFTH NIGHT, ACT FIVE.
EVERYTHING ALL WRAPPED UP IN A SHAKESPEAREAN HOLLYWOOD ENDING.
THE ONE THING I DISLIKE MORE THAN LATENESS,
ASHLEY KERWIN, IS PEOPLE TRYING TO GET AWAY WITH IT.
SEE ME AFTER CLASS.
SORRY, MS. KWAN.
LET'S HANG A BELL AROUND KWAN'S NECK.
'CAUSE SHE'S A TOTAL COW.
OKAY, WHAT ABOUT THIS?
WHAT ABOUT THIS MASSIVE ZIT ON MY FACE -
THE DAY BEFORE PHOTO DAY!
YOU CAN PHOTOSHOP THAT OUT.
SOMEONE'S IN A GOOD MOOD.
SOMEONE'S HAD THE BEST DAY IN A LONG TIME!
I SHOULD'VE APOLOGIZED MONTHS AGO.
IT'S ALL ABOUT KNOWING WHAT YOU WANT, AND THEN GOING FOR IT.
(PHONE RINGS)
HELLO?
HEY, IT'S ME.
HEY YOU.
HEY AH, LISTEN WHAT ARE YOU DOING THIS WEEKEND?
THIS WEEKEND? I DON'T KNOW. WHY?
I DON'T KNOW I WAS THINKIN' MAYBE IF YOU WANTED
WE COULD CATCH A MOVIE ON FRIDAY?
UH - YEAH, SURE SOUNDS GREAT.
REALLY? OKAY.
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW AT SCHOOL.
OKAY, SEAN CAMERON JUST ASKED ME OUT.
REMIND ME, DID LAST YEAR EVEN HAPPEN? THIS IS INCREDIBLE!
I GUESS...
NO, IT'S PERFECT. IT COULDN'T BE BETTER IF I WANTED IT TO BE.
BUT WHAT ABOUT JIMMY?
WHAT'LL HE DO WHEN HE HEARS YOU'RE DATING SEAN?
I'M NOT DATING ANYONE.
AND I'M NOT JIMMY'S GIRLFRIEND.
I KNOW, BUT MAYBE YOU SHOULD JUST KEEP A LOW PROFILE FOR A BIT -
TER, ONE DAY, WHEN A GUY LIKES YOU, YOU'LL UNDERSTAND HOW THIS WORKS.
I DIDN'T MEAN IT LIKE THAT -
ISAACS.
HEY, SPINNER...
KENDRA MASON. DO YOU NOW HER?
SHE'S SHORT, DARK HAIR, CARTOON FREAK.
UH - YEAH. WHY?
SHE SEEMS TO KNOW YOU.
SHE WOULDN'T STOP TALKING ABOUT YOU JUST NOW.
REALLY? COOL.
NOT COOL.
SEE, HER LAST NAME IS MASON. MY LAST NAME IS MASON.
GEE, WHAT'S THE CONNECTION?
YOU'RE BROTHER AND SISTER?
BUT SHE'S -
-ADOPTED, MORON.
AND ONLY IN GRADE SEVEN.
SO, GO NEAR HER, I TURN YOUR GLASSES INTO CONTACTS.
TODAY IS PHOTO DAY.
CLASSES WILL BE CALLED DOWN INDIVIDUALLY.
HEY, SEX-KITTEN. HOT OUTFIT.
NOT LOOKING BAD EITHER, MICHALCHUK.
UH, WHAT WAS THAT?
WHAT WAS WHAT?
THAT LITTLE ROLLING TRICK YOU DID WITH YOUR EYES.
THAT'S MY MOVE.
IT WAS NOTHING.
WE WERE TALKING ABOUT ASH'S DATE WITH SEAN ON FRIDAY,
AND ASH SAID SOMETHING MEAN TO ME.
YOU'RE KIDDING.
A DATE? ASHLEY AND SEAN.
SO? THEY'RE JUST GOING TO A MOVIE -
SO JIMMY'S STILL TOTALLY IN LOVE WITH HER.
AND SHE MADE HIM THINK THERE'S SOME HOPE.
I KNEW THIS WOULD HAPPEN -
PAIGE, C'MON.
SHE DOESN'T CARE WHAT SHE DID. SHE'S PLAYING ALL OF US.
SHE'S NOT.
YOU'RE RIGHT SHE'S NOT.
NOT ANY MORE. I'M GONNA MAKE SURE OF THAT.
ALRIGHT SO NOW WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO IS WE TAKE SOME DRY ICE
AND WE GONNA PLACE IT IN WATER.
OKAY. THIS EXPERIMENT WILL ILLUSTRATE THE SUBLIMATION PROCESS.
WE HAVE FROZEN CARBON DIOXIDE,
OR DRY ICE, AND BASICALLY IT GETS DESTROYED BY THE WATER.
GEE THAT KIND OF REMINDS ME OF TWO OTHER ELEMENTS.
THIS IS ASHLEY KERWIN.
AND THIS IS JIMMY BROOKS.
AND THAT'S REALLY FUNNY, PAIGE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I HEARD.
FRIDAY NIGHT.
ASHLEY. A DATE. NOT YOU. GEE, GUESS WHO?
PAIGE, JIMMY - THE EXPERIMENT, PLEASE?
OBSERVE AND TAKE NOTES. OKAY?
I FINALLY MEET THE GIRL OF MY DREAMS. SO CUTE.
SO INTO THE SAME THINGS I AM.
AND SO RELATED TO SASQUATCH.
JUST FORGET ABOUT HER.
LOOK THERE SHE IS. COME ON.
TOBY LET'S GO.
FINE, WIPE THE DROOL OFF YOUR CHIN.
HI TOBY, WATCH ASHUHARA LAST NIGHT?
YEAH. I LOVE ASHUHARA.
ME TOO. SO - LUNCH TODAY?
YEAH, LUNCH.
SORRY TO BREAK THIS UP.
BIG FOOT, IS HEADING THIS WAY.
LET'S GO.
COME ON.
SEAN CAMERON.
JIMMY BROOKS.
THOUGHT ME AND YOU WERE COOL, MAN.
THERE IS NO ME AND YOU.
FINE BY ME.
ONE WARNING THOUGH. YOU STAY AWAY FROM MY GIRL.
WHAT'RE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
ASH AND I ARE A THING AGAIN.
REALLY?
YEAH REALLY.
I GUESS I HAVE TO ASK HER THAT. WHEN I TAKE HER OUT ON FRIDAY.
HEY, HEY TAKE IT EASY.
YOU ALRIGHT?
YEAH I'M FINE.
IF JIMMY KNOWS WHAT'S GOOD FOR HIM.
HEY JIMMY.
DON'T TALK TO ME YOU SLUT.
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
THAT'S THE WORD FOR GIRLS WHO CHEAT ON THEIR BOYFRIENDS.
YOU'RE NOT MY BOYFRIEND.
WELL I WAS LAST YEAR WHEN YOU MESSED AROUND WITH SEAN
NOW YOU WANNA DO IT ALL OVER AGAIN.
ATTENTION, WOULD MRS. CHIDLOW'S GRADE SEVEN HOME ROOM,
AND MS. KWAN'S GRADE EIGHTS, PLEASE HEAD TO THE GYM.
PERFECT, THANKS. WHO'S NEXT?
SO YOU THINK THIS LOOK WORKS? I WENT FOR SHARP. YET CASUAL.
YOU LOOK GREAT, LIBERTY.
(CHICKEN SOUNDS)
SHUT UP.
I'M TRYING TO HELP YOU, TOBY.
YOU LIKE HER. SHE LIKES YOU.
HER BROTHER LIKES TO MAIM AND KILL.
WITH HIS TEETH.
SPINNER ALMOST CAUGHT ME TALKING TO KENDRA EARLIER.
AND?
AND I DON'T WANT TO DIE.
IF YOU WORRY ABOUT BLINKING, HAZEL, YOU'LL BLINK.
JUST TRUST THE CAMERA.
GUYS I'M SO GLAD I FOUND YOU.
I THINK MAYBE I MADE A BIG MISTAKE, ABOUT SEAN, AND -
THERE'S NO ROOM AT THIS TABLE.
OH. UM, I THOUGHT -
YOU THOUGHT WRONG.
THE KEY IS TO THINK ABOUT SOMEONE REALLT HOT. LIKE BRAD PITT.
YOU'LL KEEP YOUR EYES OPEN
AND HAVE A GENUINE SMILE ON YOUR FACE.
WHAT WAS THAT ALL ABOUT?
NOTHING.
ARE YOU SURE? ASH LOOKED UPSET.
HON. IT'S SIMPLE, REALLY.
FOUR YEARS OF HIGH SCHOOL.
WILL YOU SPEND THEM COOL, WITH ALL OF US?
OR AS A BIG OUTCAST LOSER, WITH ONE OF HER.
YOU DECIDE.
TAKE THIS. I'M DONE WITH IT.
WHERE WERE YOU AT LUNCH?
LUNCH? I HAD SOME WORK TO DO.
REALLY. AND WHAT ABOUT THE GYM EARLIER?
YOU IGNORED ME THEN, TOO.
I DON'T GET IT. WHAT DID I DO WRONG?
IT'S JUST, YOU'RE IN GRADE SEVEN, I'M IN GRADE EIGHT.
AND WE CAN'T BE FRIENDS? WHY NOT?
YOU'RE AFRAID OF MY BROTHER.
NO -
LOOK ME IN THE EYE, AND TELL ME THAT'S NOT IT.
YOU COWARD.
HEY.
FRIDAY NIGHT. WE CAN SEE WHATEVER YOU WANT.
YOU KNOW, IT'S UP TO YOU.
OKAY GREAT.
BUT, I WAS WONDERING - WOULD YOU HATE ME IF I POSTPONED?
YOU DON'T WANNA GO OUT WITH ME, DO YOU?
I DO BUT-
BUT YOU'RE SEEING JIMMY AGAIN. RIGHT?
THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH JIMMY.
DOES IT HAVE TO DO WITH PAIGE AND - YEAH WHATEVER...
THAT WENT WELL.
SPINNER.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
I WANT TO TALK TO YOUR SISTER.
ISAACS. MOVE ON. NOW.
NO.
NO?
YOU ARE AWARE I COULD RIP OUT YOUR BOWEL
AND EAT IT FOR BREAKFAST?
YEAH. I'M WILLING TO TAKE THAT RISK.
AS LONG AS YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENS IF YOU BREAK HER HEART?
WE'RE COOL.
MESS ME AROUND AGAIN AND I'LL RIP YOUR BOWEL OUT MYSELF, ISAACS.
WANNA GO FOR ICE CREAM?
NICE SWEATSHIRT.
TER, OVER HERE.
MISS.
WHAT A LONG FACE.
A GIRL AS PRETTY AS YOU SHOULD NEVER FROWN.
JUST TAKE THE PICTURE.
NOT UNTIL YOU SMILE.
TAKE THE PICTURE PLEASE.