I'M GONNA GET YOU! I'M GONNA GET YOU!
TRY IT AGAIN...
YOU CAN DO IT. COME ON...
YOU GOT IT.
OH, THAT'S LOTS...
MORE, MORE, COME ON...
COME ON. MORE BUBBLES, MORE BUBBLES. LET'S GO.
CRAIGOR...
HEY DAD.
WHAT HAPPENED TO SIX O'CLOCK?
I KNOW, AH I'M SORRY.
IT'S JUST - THE LIGHT OUTSIDE...
LATE SUMMER... INCREDIBLE.
AND I JUST AH...
-GOT DISTRACTED AND MISSED DINNER.
YEAH, AH... DAD, I'M SORRY.
WHEN I SAY SIX O'CLOCK,
I DON'T CARE HOW GREAT THE LIGHT IS. YOU'RE HOME!
DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
JUST CLEAN IT UP.
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I know I can make it through
♪ If I hold out
♪ Be the best
♪ The best that I can be
♪ Hear what I say to you
♪ What ever it takes
♪ I know I can make it
♪ I know I can make it through
MAN, GRADE EIGHT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE OURS.
THIS IS SO UNFAIR.
I HAVE NO PROBLEM WITH AN EXPANDED DEGRASSI.
WAY MORE FISH IN THE SEA.
WHAT - YOU'RE FISHING FOR A NEW BABYSITTER?
DUDE. OLDER WOMEN.
HOT, SEXY, OLDER WOMEN.
JUST WAITING TO MAKE ME INTO A MAN, OKAY?
THIS YEAR, TOBY. JUST TRUST ME. I KNOW IT.
THANKS FOR THE LIFT.
OKAY. DO YOU NEED A LIFT TONIGHT?
NO, NO, I CAN AH - MAKE IT HOME.
I'LL BE ON TIME TONIGHT, OKAY?
GOOD.
GOOD LUCK TODAY, SPORT.
IS THAT THE SOUND OF YOUR HEART POUNDING?
NO WAIT - IT'S MINE.
PROOF THAT SUMMER IS SO OVERRATED.
BACK AT THIS DUMP FOR FOUR MORE YEARS.
FOUR LONG YEARS.
LOOK AT THIS PLACE. IT'S A ZOO IN HERE.
OH, LOOK, THERE'S ONE OF THE MONKEYS NOW.
GOOD MORNING, STUDENTS AND WELCOME TO DEGRASSI.
IF YOU'RE A NEW STUDENT
AND HAVEN'T RECEIVED YOUR NEW HOME ROOM NUMBER YET,
PLEASE SEE MRS. SMITH IN THE MAIN OFFICE IMMEDIATELY.
IS DEGRASSI A HIGH SCHOOL AND A BLIND SCHOOL THIS YEAR?
SORRY, MAN. I'M LOST.
BUY A MAP.
ALREADY GOT ONE.
NOT BLIND - JUST AH -
HEY BOYS. WHO'S THE NEW GUY?
-DIRECTIONALLY CHALLENGED.
HEY CUTEY...
M.I. LAB?
HERE. I'LL - I'LL SHOW YOU.
CLOSING DOWN THE HIGH SCHOOL
WAS A LAST-MINUTE BOARD DECISION.
MEANING WE ARE NOT FULLY PREPARED
FOR THE INFLUX OF STUDENTS.
WILL THERE BE A SEPARATE STUDENT COUNCIL?
SEPARATE VIDEO ANNOUNCEMENTS?
WHAT ABOUT THE GRAPEVINE?
OKAY, ONE QUESTION AT A TIME.
IN THE SHORT-TERM,
DEGRASSI'S GOING TO BE A VERY CROWDED PLACE.
SMALL PRICE TO PAY.
OLDER WOMEN, YOUNGER MEN, VERY HOT.
OLDER WOMAN, JT YORKE - VERY NOT.
TAKE A SEAT...
YOU MAY EVEN HAVE TO SHARE LOCKERS.
SEE ME AFTER CLASS.
WE'RE GOING TO BE COVERING
"PONTY POOL CHANGES EVERYTHING" BY TONY BURGESS...
ADDING GRADES 9 TO 12 IS A GREAT OPPORTUNITY FOR DEGRASSI.
AND FOR YOU GUYS.
I TAUGHT YOU M.I. FOR THE PAST TWO YEARS,
YOU GET ME FOR ANOTHER FOUR.
LATE NIGHT LAST NIGHT, HUH CRAIG?
UH - VERY AH - VERY LATE NIGHT, SIR.
KEPT - KEPT WAKING UP, IN ANTICIPATION OF -
WELL, OF THIS EXACT MOMENT - SIR.
YEAH, WELL SAVE THE ZZZ'S FOR HOME, OKAY?
DON'T FORGET TO PICK UP YOUR TEXTBOOKS IN THE GYM.
AND EVEN THOUGH TODAY'S A HALF DAY - TOMORROW IS NOT.
OKAY, AND EVERY SECOND WEEK, WE'LL TAKE OUT LUNCHES,
OLD SCHOOL STUFF -
WHATEVER YOU SAY, ROOMIE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU GUYS VOLUNTEERED TO SHARE.
AW, IT'S JUST OUR WAY OF GIVING SOMETHING BACK TO DEGRASSI, THAT'S ALL.
YEAH OR OF DESTROYING YOUR FRIENDSHIP.
SLOW DOWN.
HOW SOON TILL WE TELL THEM WE TOLD THEM SO...?
NOW I GET THE TOP SHELF, ALL RIGHT?
WHY? WE SAID I GOT IT.
NO, I GET THE TOP SHELF BECAUSE I'M TALLER.
YEAH, BY LIKE A MILLIMETER.
NO, CHECK THIS OUT. READY? LOOK. SEE? WAY TALLER.
PAIGE, YOUR HAIR IS FINE.
FINE? I HAVE A MULLET.
WHAT'S A MULLET?
THAT.
HAIRSTYLE OF THE TRAILER DWELLERS AND FASHION-IMPAIRED.
SO GET IT FIXED.
YEAH, BUT THAT'LL TAKE ABOUT EIGHTY BUCKS.
I HAVE FIFTY PUT AWAY BUT MY EVIL PARENTS
ARE INSISTING I CLEAN OUT THE GARAGE FOR THE REST.
HELLO? CHILD LABOUR?
YOU KNOW, THERE ARE LAWS AGAINST CHILD LABOUR.
OKAY THANKS, MR. NEWS AT 5.
CUTE.
VERY.
TRY DERANGED.
GUYS, HEY! I TRIED TO CALL YOU WHEN I GOT BACK.
HOW WAS YOUR SUMMER?
ANYWAY, ABOUT MY HAIR.
GIVE THEM TIME.
I'M SURE THEY'LL, YOU KNOW...
WHAT? FORGIVE AND FORGET? RIGHT.
CRAIG!
YOU'VE BEEN GONE FOREVER!
I KNOW. BUT - SUMMER'S OVER, I'M BACK FROM CAMP
AND NOW YOU WON'T EVER GET AWAY FROM ME!
OKAY: SAY...
BAD DONKEY BREATH.
LET ME TAKE YOURS!
WHO ME? I'LL BREAK THE CAMERA.
REMEMBER HOW TO USE IT?
YEP.
ONE HAND THERE.
DADDY AND ME ARE GONNA VISIT MOMMY.
WANNA COME?
JUST AH - TELL HER I MISS HER, OKAY?
HEY, YOU CAN'T TELL YOUR DAD ABOUT US MEETING, ALL RIGHT?
I PROMISE. ALWAYS, ALWAYS.
ANGELA?
LOVE YOU, KID.
ANGELA, HONEY. WHO WAS THAT?
MY BROTHER.
OKAY. I GIVE YOU THE ISAACS SYSTEM.
THE WHAT?
OKAY. YOU WANT AN OLDER WOMAN?
THE SYSTEM WILL DETERMINE YOUR BEST MATCH.
MEET... TERRI MACGREGOR.
GUYS, YOUR DEDICATION TO GRADE EIGHT IS IMPRESSIVE
BUT AH - GO HOME ALREADY.
CAN WE JUST FINISH THIS FIRST?
FIVE MINUTES.
TERRI'S - NOT REALLY MY TYPE.
SHE'S OLDER, PRETTY AND BREATHING.
EXACTLY YOUR TYPE.
NO. I NEED MORE OF A CHALLENGE.
SOMEONE LIKE...
OH, LORDY.
BUT YOU ONLY HAVE A 0.03% CHANCE OF SCORING WITH-
PAIGE MICHALCHUK. COME TO PAPA.
THAT'S A LOT OF YELLOW, ANGE.
BUT THAT WAS MOMMY'S FAVOURITE COLOUR. REMEMBER?
YES, I DO.
DO YOU THINK SHE MISSES US?
OH, I KNOW SHE DOES.
JUST AS MUCH AS WE MISS HER.
BUT DO YOU THINK SHE LIKES IT UP IN HEAVEN?
CRAIG SAID THAT -
CRAIG SAID WHAT?
HONEY, DID YOU SEE CRAIG?
NO. I DIDN'T. I PROMISE.
COME ON, SWEETIE. TELL ME THE TRUTH...
STAY RIGHT HERE, OKAY?
CRAIG?
CRAIG!
HEY SPORT, ARE YOU READY TO EAT?
AH YEAH.
AH - I'M JUST COMING!
WOW, ROAST BEEF, MASHED POTATOES, YORKSHIRE PUDDING.
YOUR FAVOURITE!
YEAH, TOTALLY. I LOVE ROAST BEEF.
REMEMBER - REMEMBER HOW MOM USED TO MAKE -
SO, HOW WAS THE FIRST DAY? MAKE ANY FRIENDS?
YEAH. ONE GUY - SEAN. HE'S COOL.
THAT'S GREAT.
LISTEN, THERE WAS A MESSAGE ON THE MACHINE TODAY.
FOR ME?
NO. FOR ME.
FROM JOEY JEREMIAH... ANY THOUGHTS?
ANY IDEA WHY HE MIGHT BE CALLING?
YOU DIDN'T CALL HIM?
DAD, COME ON. WHY WOULD I CALL JOEY?
WHY WOULD YOUR MOTHER LEAVE A SURGEON
FOR A USED CAR SALESMAN, CRAIG?
I MEAN THE MYSTERIES OF THE UNIVERSE ARE INFINITE TO ME.
WELL, I DIDN'T - I DIDN'T CALL. PROMISE.
I'M NOT AH - I'M NOT LIKE MOM, OKAY?
SO AH...
ARE YOU GONNA CALL HIM BACK?
NOW, WHY WOULD I DO THAT?
OKAY, MY DESTINY IS APPROACHING.
PROJECT PAIGE HAS OFFICIALLY BEGUN.
YEAH. IT'LL BE OVER IN ABOUT TWO MINUTES.
OH LOOK IT'S GROSS AND GROSS-ER.
LOOKS LIKE GROSS-ER WANTS A WORD WITH YOU.
AH PAIGE, MAY I SAY, YOU'RE LOOKING RATHER RADIANT TODAY?
MAY I CARRY YOUR BAG FOR YOU?
AH, YOU WANT TO CARRY MY BAG.
YEAH. I'LL CARRY IT HOME, I'LL CARRY IT TO SCHOOL.
YOUR WISH IS MY COMMAND.
OH, WELL, IN THAT CASE
I WISH THAT - YOU'D GO BACK TO YOUR GIRLFRIEND OVER THERE,
AND LEAVE ME ALONE. NOW.
WOW! YOU - YOU'RE AN INSPIRATION.
THE BATTLE HAS JUST BEGUN.
PAIGE MICHALCHUK WILL BE MINE!
OKAY.
AND I GUESS I BELIEVE THAT WITH A POSITIVE ATTITUDE
AND A DRIVE TO SUCCEED WE CAN PRETTY WELL ACHIEVE ANYTHING.
AT LEAST THAT IS WHAT I TELL MY SELF I FACE A CHALLENGE.
SO THAT'S ME.
VERY ILLUMINATING, ASHLEY.
OKAY, WHO'S NEXT?
CRAIG MANNING?
I AM CRAIG MANNING. THANK YOU.
CRAIG, WE KNOW YOUR NAME.
NOW, WE WANT TO KNOW ABOUT YOU.
RIGHT.
ME. IN AN INFINITE UNIVERSE.
AN INSIGNIFICANT PLANET.
WHAT ARE WE?
ONE OF SIX BILLION INHABITANTS. BIG DEAL.
AND HONESTLY?
IF I WERE TO, SAY, IF I WERE TO DISAPPEAR?
WHO'D CARE?
WHAT WOULD IT MATTER?
A SUB-ATOMIC BLIP IN THE TEMPORAL FABRIC OF CREATION.
SO THERE YOU HAVE IT. CRAIG MANNING.
VERY EXISTENTIAL, CRAIG.
OKAY, HEATHER SINCLAIR. COME ON DOWN.
SO HE'S IN GRADE NINE?
YEAH I SAW HIM COMING OUT OF SIMPSON'S HOMEROOM THIS MORNING
WHY DO THE NINERS GET ALL THE HOTTIES?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN? WE HAVE JT AND TOBY.
UGH... SHHH- THERE HE IS.
WHERE?
EMMA NELSON, RIGHT?
YOU AH, YOU BABYSIT ANGELA JEREMIAH.
I DO?
I MEAN, I DO, BUT -
YOU DON'T RECOGNIZE ME. FIVE YEARS AGO?
OUR MOTHERS MADE US DANCE.
THE WEDDING!
CRAIG IS JOEY'S STEPSON!
ANGELA'S HALF-BROTHER!
OH... OH, HI.
HEY. ANYWAY AH, NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
CRAIG, WAIT.
I'M BABYSITTING ANGELA LATER.
MY MOM'S HAVING THIS BIG PARTY
AND I WAS WONDERING IF MAYBE YOU WANT TO COME ALONG?
I WOULDN'T WANT TO CRASH.
NO. YOU'D BE MY GUEST.
IF YOU DO WANNA COME, MEET ME OUT FRONT AFTER SCHOOL.
I'LL BE THERE. THANKS.
HE'S COMING TONIGHT.
IF THIS CAR IS A LEMON - WHICH IT IS NOT -
I'LL GIVE YOU A REAL LEMON, AND LET YOU SQUEEZE IT IN MY EYES.
SOUND FAIR?
OH, LISTEN TO THE MAN. HE KNOWS CARS.
AH, WOULD YOU EXCUSE ME FOR JUST A MINUTE?
WHY DON'T YOU OPEN 'ER UP AND SEE HOW SHE FEELS.
OKAY, I'LL BE WITH YOU RIGHT AWAY.
HELLO ALBERT. YOU GOT MY MESSAGE?
SURE DID.
GOOD. WELL, IT'S ABOUT CRAIG.
I KNOW THIS IS NOT REALLY MY BUSINESS BUT -
YOU'RE GOING TO BUTT IN ANYWAY?
I'M JUST WANT TO KNOW HOW IS HE DOING.
WHAT'S YOUR INTEREST IN MY SON?
I JUST -
HE IS MY SON, RIGHT?
YES. BUT HE'S ALSO ANGELA'S BROTHER.
HALF-BROTHER. WHAT'S YOUR POINT?
ANGELA MISSES HIM, OKAY.
AND I KNOW HE MISSES HER.
YOU AND I NEED TO DO SOMETHING.
OKAY. YOU AND I NEED TO DO NOTHING.
EXCEPT STAY AWAY FROM EACH OTHER.
YOU'RE NOT GETTING IT HERE, OKAY.
CRAIG WANTS TO SEE ANGELA
AND I KNOW HE HAS BEEN SEEING HER.
I JUST FOUND OUT MYSELF.
HE'S BEEN DOIN' IT ON HIS OWN TIME.
YOU AND I MAY HATE EACH OTHER, BUT DO OUR KIDS HAVE TO?
EVEN IF IT'S JUST ONCE A MONTH -
OKAY, ACCORDING TO THE ISAACS SYSTEM,
YOU AND PAIGE ARE NEVER GONNA HAPPEN!
WOULD THAT BE THE SAME "SYSTEM"
THAT STOPPED YOU FROM DOING ANYTHING ABOUT EMMA LAST YEAR?
NEWS FLASH, TOBY.
IT DOESN'T WORK.
AH, PAIGE! HOLD UP.
OKAY, I NEED A RESTRAINING ORDER.
WHAT!?
AH... WILL YOU GO OUT WITH ME?
ALL I'M ASKING FOR IS ONE DATE.
IF WE CLICK, THEN WE'LL TALK COMMITMENT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
MAN, THAT IS CLASSIC! WHAT A KNOB!
IN TIME...
OKAY. HAS MY REP FALLEN
TO THE POINT WHERE A LOSER LIKE JT THINKS HE CAN ASK ME OUT
AND GET AWAY WITH IT?!
IT'S HILARIOUS.
YOU SHOULD TOTALLY DO IT.
YEAH. PAIGE AND JT ON A DATE?!
OH YEAH.
NEVER GOING TO HAPPEN. EVER.
EVERYONE HAS THEIR PRICE.
LIKE, SAY, THIRTY BUCKS?
ENOUGH TO GET YOUR HAIR DONE?
YOU HONESTLY THINK I'D GO OUT IN PUBLIC WITH IT
FOR THIRTY BUCKS?
A LIGHT EVENING WITH FRODO?
OR AN ENTIRE DAY GAGGING THROUGH COBWEBS
IN YOUR PARENTS' GARAGE.
YEAH, YOU KNOW, IT'S ABOUT THE EARWIGS.
SHARP PINCHERS, JUST WAITING-
THIRTY DOLLARS? IN CASH?
FINE. BUT THERE WILL BE CONDITIONS.
BIG CONDITIONS.
IS THAT A FROG?
ARE YOU KIDDING?
THIS IS A BIG, RAZOR-TOOTHED DINOSAUR!
WITH A TASTE FOR LITTLE GIRLS NAMED - ANGELA!
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING TO HER?
OH, JUST FEEDING HER TO THE DINOSAURS.
OKAY, GUYS. DINNER'S SERVED.
COME ON.
DADDY!
YEAH!
HEY! WE DIDN'T EXPECT YOU.
I MEAN, IT'S ONLY MY BIRTHDAY.
MUCH LESS IMPORTANT THAN A BLIND DATE...
OKAY, OKAY. MY BAD...
SO. JEREMIAH. HOW WAS MISS NOVEMBER?
IF SHE WAS MISS NOVEMBER, IT WAS IN 1973.
IT WAS LIKE GOING OUT WITH MY MOTHER.
AH, WELL, YOU KNOW, WOMEN OF A CERTAIN AGE
DO HAVE A SPECIAL APPEAL -
YOU CAN LEAVE NOW.
WHAT AND MISS WATCHING YOU TURN GREY?
DON'T WORRY, HE'S COMING HOME WITH ME.
AFTER WE EAT.
CRAIG.
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I INVITED HIM.
THAT'S OKAY, ISN'T IT?
YEAH, YEAH. NO AH -
CAN I TALK TO YOU FOR A SECOND?
LISTEN, IT'S GREAT SEEING YOU AND I MEAN THAT.
BUT YOUR DAD DOESN'T WANT YOU -
OH, HE'S, HE'S FINE WITH THIS.
HE KNOWS YOU'RE HERE?
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW WHY,
BUT HE DOESN'T WANT YOU HANGING OUT WITH ME OR WITH ANGE.
HE'S MADE THAT RADICALLY CLEAR.
WHAT, YOU TALKED TO HIM?
HE CAME BY THE DEALERSHIP THIS AFTERNOON.
CRAIG, COME ON. YOUR DAD WON'T ALLOW IT.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
NO PROBLEM. I GET IT.
HEY AH, MS. NELSON, THANKS FOR THE HOT DOG.
I'M GONNA GO DOWN TO MY DARK ROOM...
ARE YOU LOOKING FOR SOMETHING?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING -
WHAT ARE YOU DOING? WHAT ARE YOU--
ARE YOU LOOKING FOR SOMETHING?
I WORK MY ASS OFF FOR YOU!
WHAT DO I GET?!
WHAT DO I GET IN RETURN?
I GET RUDENESS!
I GET LIES!
I GET THIS.