HEY, SPIRIT.
DEAN, WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN THE GIRL'S WASHROOM?
I THOUGHT I'D SAY HI.
OKAY.
RELAX, WE HAD A GOOD TIME AT THAT PARTY TOGETHER, DIDN'T WE?
DEAN, YOU -
I WHAT?
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING. JUST HAD A GOOD TIME.
YOU RAPED ME!
YOU WANTED IT, AND DON'T YOU DARE TELL ANYONE ANY DIFFERENT
NO, NO! GET OFF ME.
STOP, NO!
GET OFF ME, STOP IT!
(Alarm Clock)
HUH!
♪ WHATEVER IT TAKES
♪ I KNOW I CAN MAKE IT THROUGH
♪ IF I HOLD OUT
♪ BE THE BEST
♪ THE BEST I CAN BE
♪ HEAR WHAT I SAY TO YOU
♪ WHATEVER IT TAKES
♪ I KNOW I CAN MAKE IT
♪ I KNOW I CAN MAKE IT THROUGH
PAIGE, WAIT. READ IT.
PRO-VOICE SONG WRITING CONTEST.
CELEBRATING WHAT WOMEN HAVE TO SAY.
DOES YOUR BAND HAVE WHAT IT TAKES TO MAKE A SPLASH
ON THE MUSIC SCENE?
NOW'S YOUR CHANCE.
TER, WE DON'T HAVE A BAND. PMS BROKE UP, REMEMBER?
BUT IT'S TOO PERFECT.
WINNING BAND GETS A DEMO CD AND A TRIP TO L.A.?
I TOLD YOU.
TO PERFORM LIVE FOR RECORD EXECUTIVES.
THAT'S A SERIOUS PRIZE.
THAT'S NOT LIKE WINNING SOME BEACH TOWEL OR MOVIE PASSES.
TERRI, WE COULD MOVE TO L.A.!
PMS COULD TOTALLY WIN THIS.
WITH ASH WE'D HAVE A BETTER CHANCE.
NOT IN THIS BAND.
ENJOY THE DAY, GANG.
BUT WE NEED A REAL SINGER.
FINE!
MEET - HAZEL SPICE.
THIRD MEMBER OF THE NEW AND IMPROVED PMS REUNION TOUR.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
♪ AMAZING GRACE,
♪ HOW SWEET THE SOUND
♪ THAT SAVED A WRETCH LIKE ME...
OKAY, HAZEL, CAN WE PLEASE KEEP IT TO A DULL ROAR.
I'VE BEEN TAKING VOICE FOR THREE YEARS NOW.
YOU WON'T REGRET THIS.
AND WE CAN USE MY ENGLISH POEM FOR LYRICS.
I - I PRAY AT NIGHT, YOU'LL SEE THE LIGHT.
YOU'LL COME AND HOLD ME, TILL EVERYTHING'S ALRIGHT.
I WISH I KNEW JUST WHAT TO DO
TO MAKE THIS SECRET WISH COME TRUE.
BECAUSE MY POEM SMELLS LIKE POO.
GUYS...
THANKS, TERRI.
WHAT DID YOU THINK?
UM, IT WAS SWEET.
IN A RHYMING DICTIONARY SORT OF WAY.
ASHLEY, YOU OKAY TO GO NEXT?
IT HAPPENS TO OTHER PEOPLE.
YOU SAY HOW SAD, YOU SAY POOR THING.
BUT WHEN IT'S YOU, IT'S SOMETHING ELSE.
IT'S EVERYTHING.
IT STARTED WITH SOMETHING MINOR,
WENT FROM THERE TO SOMETHING WORSE.
THE FRIENDS YOU LOVED, AND THOUGHT YOU KNEW,
JUST DISAPPEARED.
FELT SO WEIRD, HALF BLESSING, HALF CURSED.
IT HAPPENS TO OTHER PEOPLE,
YOU SAY HOW SAD,
YOU SAY POOR THING.
WHEN GOTTLIEB DAIMLER DIED IN 1900,
HE HAD NO IDEA HOW FAR OR HOW FAST
THE BONE SHAKER MOTORCYCLE HE INVENTED WOULD TAKE US.
THANKS.
GOOD ADDITION TO OUR BIOGRAPHY FILE.
UH, WE HAVE TIME FOR ONE MORE. LIBERTY.
I HAVE SOMETHING DONE ON TIME FOR ONCE,
AND WE RUN OUT OF TIME. TYPICAL.
TYPICAL - IS YOUR PROJECT.
MR. SIMPSON SAID WE COULD DO OUR BIOGRAPHIES
ON ANYBODY THAT WE WANTED.
ANYONE APPROPRIATE.
SOMETHING TELLS ME HUGH HEFFNER DOESN'T COUNT.
AS MY QUEST FOR A WOMAN GOES ON,
NAME ME A BETTER ROLE MODEL.
JUST GO FOR LIBERTY, ALREADY.
UH! BARF.
THAT'S NOT HOW SHE FEELS ABOUT YOU.
IN FACT, SHE FINDS YOU FASCINATING.
JUST WAIT AND SEE.
OKAY, NOW YOU'RE SCARING ME.
FELLOW STUDENTS!
MY HERO ISN'T FROM THE HISTORY BOOKS,
HE'LL BE FAMOUS LATER.
THE NEXT JIM CAREY.
YUCK IT UP, TOBSTER.
I'M JT YORK HERE TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT MY ALL-ROUND FAVORITE SUBJECT - MYSELF.
YOU'LL GOING TO LOVE IT,
BECAUSE IT DON'T GET ANY COOLER
THAN THE YORKMAN - THE EARLY YEARS.
FROM THE VERY BEGINNING I WAS A REAL URBAN COWBOY.
TOBY...
YES.
THEN I WENT ON TO SLAY THE LADIES IN POWDER BLUE RUFFLES.
YOU GAVE HER MY PHOTO ALBUM?
MOI?
THEY CALL ME THE TERMINATOR.
(Laughter)
THE SHOT OF HIM IN THE HEAD GEAR,
I THOUGHT I WAS GOING TO LOSE IT.
YOU BET YOU'RE LOVING HE LADIES.
IT WASN'T THAT FUNNY.
TRUST ME, IT WAS.
IMITATION IS THE LOWEST FORM OF HUMOUR.
IT WASN'T IMITATION. IT WAS A HOMAGE, A TRIBUTE.
YOU WANT TRIBUTE?
YOU TAKE THAT BACK, I DO TOO HAVE FRIENDS, TEN TEXT BOOKS,
A THOUSAND ANIMALS.
OH, AND SOMETIMES EVEN MY PARENTS LIKE ME.
LOSER!
FREAK!
GEES.
LA, LA, LA, LA, LA.
HAZEL!
MUST YOU?
SORRY I'M LATE. I WANTED TO GET INTO THE MOOD.
YOU WORE THAT LAST YEAR,
AND THE CHEESY POP TRICKS ARE OVER.
WHY DO YOU HAVE TO BE SO OUT OF TOUCH?
WHY DO YOU HAVE TO BE SO MEAN?
I'M NOT MEAN, I'M RIGHT.
SO, NEW WARDROBE.
NO.
PARDON?
WHAT DIDN'T YOU GET? I SAID NO.
TER...
PAIGE DOESN'T UNDERSTAND THAT WORD.
NEVER HAS.
YOU BETTER STOP RIGHT THERE.
OKAY, PAIGE, LOOK, WE ALL WANT TO WIN,
SO LET'S JUST CALM DOWN AND REHEARSE. OKAY?
PAIGE? TER?
I WISH I KNEW JUST WHAT TO DO, YEAH,
TO MAKE THIS SECRET WISH COME TRUE -
UH, PAIGE, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
THIS ISN'T WORKING.
(Singing)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE EVEN ASKING.
WE NEED YOU, IT'S EMBARRASSING.
OH, NO, CAN'T LET THAT HAPPEN. POOR PAIGE.
YOUR POEM IS GREAT, OKAY?
IT'S SOMETHING REAL AND IT MADE ME THINK.
IT DOESN'T MATTER, IT'S GOING TO END UP JUST LIKE LAST YEAR.
IT WON'T! I PROMISE
I WANTED TO TAKE IT SERIOUSLY, BUT YOU GUYS WOULDN'T.
WE CHEESED OUT, BUT THIS TIME WE NEED TO SING
ABOUT REAL STUFF.
LIKE WHAT?
LIKE -
HOW IT FEELS WHEN YOU'RE DUMPED, OR LIKE ABUSE.
PAIN. FEELING SAD, WHATEVER YOU WANT.
JUST SO LONG AS IT MEANS SOMETHING.
THIS DOESN'T SOUND LIKE PAIGE.
WITHOUT YOU WE DON'T HAVE A CHANCE?
DO YOU SERIOUSLY THINK WE HAVE A CHANCE?
YOU KNOW WHAT? I DO.
WE HAVE LYRICS?
JUST FINISHED THEM THIS MORNING.
AND I PRINTED OUT NEW COPIES FOR YOU GUYS IN MEDIA IMMERSION.
OH, SNEAKY GIRL.
THE MELODY'S THE SAME BUT THE WORDS ARE WAY MORE POWERFUL NOW.
IT'S KIND OF HEAVY.
WELL, YEAH, I MEAN, IT'S ABOUT RAPE.
PAIGE SAID LAST NIGHT, LET'S MAKE IT REAL.
MY POEM WAS OKAY,
BUT I DID SOME RESEARCH ON-LINE.
DID YOU KNOW THAT BY THE TIME GIRLS REACH UNIVERSITY,
ONE IN FOUR HAS BEEN SEXUALLY ASSAULTED?
YOU TOOK MY BODY AND YOU TORE IT IN HALF?
THIS REALLY ISN'T WORKING FOR ME.
BUT THE STORIES ARE INCREDIBLE. FROM GIRLS OUR AGE.
YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE SOME OF THE THINGS I READ.
LET'S USE THE ORIGINAL LYRICS, OKAY?
BUT THIS IS WAY MORE INTERESTING.
I AGREE.
UM, I DON'T REALLY CARE. I LIKE THE OTHER VERSION BETTER.
YOUR PAINTING IS MASTERFUL.
IT TOOK AGES TO MIX THAT MANY SHADES OF PINK.
WELL WORTH IT.
I'D LIKE TO WORK ON MY ARTSY SIDE.
BUT THAT MIGHT DISTRACT YOU FROM BEING, YOU KNOW,
DWEEBO-SUPREME.
CAN'T YOU JUST LAY OFF?
OH, LIBERTY CAN DISH IT OUT BUT SHE CAN'T TAKE IT, HUH?
I DIDN'T DISH AND I'M NOT A GEEK, JT DORK.
OH, THEM'S FIGHTING WORDS.
YOU WANT FIGHTING WORDS? OKAY, SUCKY-BABY. POOR SPORT...
PRISS-FACE, GOODY-TWO-SHOES.
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW ME.
YOU DON'T KNOW ONE TRUE THING ABOUT ME.
YOU WANT ONE TRUE THING, LIBERTY?
YOU'RE BORING. B-O-R-I-N-G.
I'M STUNNED. JT SPELLED A WORD.
YOU WANT ANOTHER ONE? FUN - F-U-N
SOMETHING YOU WOULDN'T KNOW
IF IT CAME UP AND BIT YOU IN THE BUTT.
FUN ENOUGH FOR YOU?
YOU WANT TO WIN, RIGHT?
NOT WITH THOSE LYRICS. YOU'VE WRITTEN -
I WROTE EXACTLY WHAT WE TALKED ABOUT.
SOMETHING REAL.
BUT YOU'RE ACTING JUST LIKE LAST YEAR.
GIVE IT UP, ASHLEY, OKAY?
TELL ME WHAT'S WRONG WITH THE NEW LYRICS AND I WILL.
SINGING A SONG ABOUT RAPE WILL NOT WIN THE CONTEST.
I THOUGHT WE HAD AN AGREEMENT.
I SAID SOMETHING REAL.
NOT SOMETHING YOU GOT OFF THE NET
AND DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT.
I'M ALLOWED TO IMAGINE.
NO, YOU'RE NOT!
AFTER SCHOOL, IN THE MUSIC ROOM. BRING THE RIGHT LYRICS.
LIBERTY!
HOW COULD YOU DO THAT?
GO AWAY, LITTLE MAN.
YOU JUST WROTE GRAFFITI ON MY LOCKER.
I'M EDGY, JT, I'M ON FIRE.
YOU'RE ON SOMETHING.
NO STRANGER TO DANGER, MY FRIEND.
I LAUGH AT AUTHORITY.
MR. YORK! HOLD IT.
DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING TO SAY?
ABOUT?
ABOUT THAT LITTLE PIECE OF ART PEOPLE SAW YOU CREATING.
IT WASN'T ME. I DIDN'T DO IT.
MR. RADITCH, I WAS- I WAS TRYING TO ERASE IT.
I DIDN'T PUT IT ON THERE...
COME ON IN GIRLS, TAKE A SEAT.
OKAY, BACK TO THE LORD OF THE FLIES.
HEY, HAVE YOU SEEN JT?
I THINK YOUR LITTLE FRIEND IS IN THE OFFICE WITH MR. RADITCH.
THAT'S IT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
SO, THEY'LL CALL HIS MOM. JT'S MOM -
WHAT?
- BATTLE-AX.
THREATEN TO TRANSFER HIM TO A PRIVATE SCHOOL,
IF HE GOT INTO TROUBLE WITH RADITCH AGAIN.
I HOPE YOU SAID GOODBYE.
♪ IT HAPPENS TO OTHER PEOPLE.
♪ YOU SAY HOW SAD, YOU SAY POOR THING.
♪ BUT WHEN IT'S YOU, IT'S SOMETHING ELSE.
♪ IT'S EVERYTHING.
♪ FRIENDS YOU LOVED AND THOUGHT YOU KNEW, JUST DISAPPEAR.
HON, YOU'RE NOT THAT BAD.
PO-LYPSUS?
POLYPS. OVER-PRACTICE.
BUT WE GO ON TOMORROW.
ASH, YOU'RE SINGING THE SOLO.
AWESOME! SORRY, HAZEL.
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR -
♪ YOU TOOK MY BODY AND TORE IT IN HALF, YOU TOOK MY CHILDHOOD,
♪ MY HEART AND MY LAUGH.
HOW MANY TIMES DO I HAVE TO SAY IT?
WE'RE NOT USING THOSE LYRICS.
PAIGE, IF I'M SINGING, THOSE ARE THE LYRICS I'LL PERFORM.
NO, I CAN'T BELIEVE I WANTED YOU BACK IN THIS BAND!
THE SONG IS STRONGER.
ANYONE WITH HALF AN EMOTION WOULD KNOW THAT.
YEAH, WHAT WOULD YOU KNOW ABOUT RAPE?
I RESEARCHED IT, I KNOW A LOT MORE ABOUT IT YOU THAN YOU DO.
PAIGE?
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE, OKAY?
I - I HAD NO IDEA.
I'M SO SORRY.
NOBODY KNOWS. ONLY HAZEL.
I KEEP TRYING TO FORGET, BUT I CAN'T.
HE'S IN MY NIGHTMARES.
HAVE YOU BEEN TO A DOCTOR?
HE WORE A CONDOM.
VERY THOUGHTFUL, HUH?
WHAT ABOUT A COUNSELOR?
I CAN'T! OKAY? I JUST - I CAN'T.
AND I CAN'T PLAY THAT SONG.
I KNOW IT'S A BETTER VERSION, BUT -
SHH... IT'S OKAY. WE'LL PLAY THE OTHER ONE.
IT'S OKAY. IT'S OKAY.
IT'S OKAY. IT'S GOING TO BE OKAY, PAIGE.
THE CUSTODIAL STAFF HAVE REQUESTED
THAT YOU LEAVE A STREAK-FREE SHINE.
I COULDN'T REACH YOUR MOTHER, BUT WHEN THIS IS CLEAN,
WE'LL CALL AGAIN.
I DID IT. I'M A VANDAL.
THIS IS NO TIME TO BE COVERING FOR MR. YORK.
I'M NOT COVERING.
IT WAS A BAD THING TO DO.
IT WASN'T BORING, BUT IT WAS PRETTY STUPID.
AND YOU DID THIS? WHY?
I WAS ACTING ON IMPULSE, SIR.
TOLD YOU I DIDN'T DO IT.
IT WAS TRUANT, REBELLIOUS, MISDIRECTED -
OKAY, MR. YORK, YOU ARE FREE TO GO.
WELCOME TO THE PANTENE PRO-VOICE CONTEST.
YOU LOOK TOTALLY GORGEOUS.
YOU OKAY?
YEAH, I PROMISE.
I'M SO NERVOUS.
TER, DON'T SWEAT IT, WE'LL BE FINE.
UH-UH, WE'LL BE GREAT. ORIGINAL LYRICS, AND ALL.
AND OUR NEXT BAND IS A GROUP FROM DEGRASSI.
GIVE IT UP FOR PMS.
LET'S GO DO IT.
(Applause)
ALRIGHT. WE ARE PMS AND THIS IS 'POOR THING.'
WHAT'S GOING ON?
HE'S HERE.
WHO?
HIM. I CAN'T.
IT -
IT HAPPENS TO OTHER PEOPLE.
YOU SAY HOW SAD, YOU SAY POOR THING.
BUT WHEN IT'S YOU, IT'S SOMETHING ELSE.
IT'S EVERYTHING.
♪ YOU NEVER BELIEVE THE NIGHTMARES,
♪ YOU'LL NEVER KNOW THE PAIN YOU CAUSED.
♪ YOU'LL NEVER FEEL THE SCARS YOU LEFT.
♪ THE THINGS YOU STOLE, EVERYTHING LOST.
♪ YOU TOOK MY HEART AND YOU TORE IT IN HALF.
♪ YOU TOOK MY CHILDHOOD, MY HEART AND LAUGH.
♪ YOU TOOK EVERYTHING I KEPT FOR MYSELF.
♪ AND THEN YOU'RE GONE. I'M NOT YOUR POOR THING.
♪ YOU TOOK MY BODY, TORE IT IN HALF.
♪ YOU TOOK MY CHILDHOOD, MY HEART AND MY LAUGH.
♪ YOU TOOK EVERYTHING I KEPT FOR MYSELF.
♪ AND THEN YOU'RE GONE.
♪ I'M NOT YOUR POOR THING.
PICK IT UP, LITTERBUG.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
A.M. AND P.M. LITTER DUTY. A WHOLE WEEK OF IT.
RADITCH THREW THE BOOK AT YOU, HUH?
TOTALLY. EVEN CALLED MY PARENTS.
BUT JT, THANKS FOR STICKING UP FOR ME.
WHATEVER.
I THINK I MIGHT ALSO OWE YOU AN APOLOGY.
NAH, YOU FESSED UP. THAT WAS COOL.
JT YORK JUST CALLED ME COOL?
DON'T LET IT GO TO YOUR HEAD.
SEE YOU AROUND, RIBBLE.
I GUESS THOSE CALIFORNIA BEACH BOYS WILL HAVE TO WAIT.
YOU KNOW, L.A.'S REALLY NOT THAT GREAT.
IT'S ALL LIKE MINI-MALLS AND FREEWAYS.
YOU WERE ROBBED.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU ONLY GOT AN HONORABLE MENTION.
SERIOUSLY? YOU LIKED IT?
PAIGE, YOU WERE AWESOME, TRULY.
YOU KNOW, SHE WAS RIGHT THOUGH.
A SONG ABOUT RAPE WILL NEVER COME FIRST.
ESPECIALLY NOT WHEN I'M SINGING IT.
SO, YOU OKAY?
I'M READY TO TALK, AT LEAST.
WELL, AS READY AS I'LL EVER BE.