WHAT'S YOUR INTEREST IN MY SON?
HE'S MY SON, RIGHT?
YES, BUT HE'S ALSO ANGELA'S BROTHER.
HALF-BROTHER. WHAT'S YOUR POINT?
ANGELA MISSES HIM AND I KNOW HE MISSES HER.
CRAIG!
YOU'VE BEEN GONE FOR EVER.
I'M BACK FROM CAMP.
AND NOW YOU'LL NEVER GET AWAY FROM ME.
PAIGE MICHALCHUCK -
COME TO PAPA.
ALL I'M ASKING FOR IS ONE DATE.
IF WE CLICK, THEN WE'LL TALK COMMITMENT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
(Laughter)
I DON'T KNOW WHY BUT HE DOESN'T WANT YOU HANGING OUT WITH ME
OR WITH ANG.
HE'S MADE THAT RADICALLY CLEAR.
I WORK MY ASS OFF FOR YOU!
I GET RUDENESS!
I GET LIES! I GET THIS.
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I know I can make it through
♪ If I hold out
♪ Be the best
♪ The best that I can be
♪ Hear what I say to you
♪ What ever it takes
♪ I know I can make it
♪ I know I can make it through
HERE WE ARE. LISTEN, LISTEN...
HOLD ON A SEC OKAY? I HAVE SOMETHING FOR YOU.
MAYBE YOU CAN GET YOURSELF A NEW CAMERA.
ONE OF THOSE DIGITAL ONES.
WOW!
THANKS.
IF YOU NEED ANYTHING ELSE, JUST ASK.
SURE, SURE. THANK YOU.
YOU'RE WELCOME. NO HARD FEELINGS?
NO HARD FEELINGS.
ALL RIGHT THEN.
PAIGE MICHALCHUK AND I WILL GO OUT THIS YEAR.
IT MAY TAKE A LITTLE TIME, BUT -
OH, JT?
UH, HEY PAIGE.
TO WHAT DO WE OWE THIS PLEASURE?
THIS - HONOUR. THIS AH -
I - JUST WANTED TO APOLOGIZE.
- FOR THE OTHER DAY WHEN YOU ASKED ME OUT.
SORRY.
OH. OKAY.
MOVIE AND A BITE. YOUR TREAT.
REALLY? GREAT.
TONIGHT. THE MALL. 5 PM. SHARP.
IF YOU ARE INTERESTED IN HELPING ORGANIZE
THE UPCOMING JUNIOR AND SENIOR DANCES,
THE SOCIAL COMMITTEE WANTS YOU.
JOIN IN THE STUDENT ACTIVITY ROOM IN FIFTEEN MINUTES.
WATCH WHERE YOU'RE GOING!
HEY!
HOW WAS THE REST OF YOUR PARTY?
GOOD. UNTIL ALL THE SUPPOSED ADULTS STARTED SINGING
EIGHTIES HITS.
SORRY I MISSED IT.
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE HAD TO.
DID - DID JOEY TALK TO YOU?
NO.
I WASN'T EAVESDROPPING. IT JUST SORT OF HAPPENED.
I'M JUST ABOUT TO PICK ANGE UP FROM SCHOOL.
HAS YOUR DAD SAID YOU CAN'T HANG OUT WITH ME TOO?
AND HEY, - HOW WAS I TO KNOW YOU WERE GOING TO GO PICK UP
MY SISTER?
HEY, UH, THANKS BY THE WAY -
FOR INVITING ME TO THE BARBEQUE.
NO BIG DEAL.
NO, NO. TO ME IT WAS. IT WAS REALLY -
IT WAS REALLY NICE TO BE THERE.
IT WAS REALLY - COMFORTABLE.
CRAIG!
ARR! UGH!
WHAT'S UP, KID?
CAN WE GO TO THE PARK?
I DON'T KNOW GUYS, I'VE GOT A WHOLE CHAPTER OF MATH HOMEWORK
SO THE TV'S GOING TO HELP BABY SIT.
BUT I WANT TO.
WELL, I - I COULD TAKE HER. RIGHT?
PARK! PARK! PARK!
RIGHT? DROP HER OFF ON MY WAY HOME.
I DON'T KNOW GUYS.
CAN YOU SAY PLEASE?
PLEASE, EMMA? PLEASE...
PARK! PARK! PARK!
JUST FOR A LITTLE BIT, OKAY?
ALL RIGHT.
GET UP.
(Laughter)
OW!
WHAT IS THAT?
WELL, UM, REMEMBER THAT DINOSAUR?
MHM.
MHM!
IT ALSO LIKES BOYS NAMED CRAIG. THAT'S WHERE IT BIT ME.
DOES IT HURT?
YEAH.
YOU KNOW WHAT WOULD BE GREAT?
TO GO SOME PLACE WHERE DINOSAURS
CAN NEVER EVER GET TO US.
LIKE WHERE?
COME ON. COME ON.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
EMMA?
HEY, I CLOSED UP EARLY TODAY. WHERE'S ANGE?
UHM, SHE'S...
IS SHE INSIDE WITH YOUR MOM?
NO, SHE'S -
EMMA, WHERE IS SHE?
SHE'S WITH CRAIG, OKAY?
YOU LET HERE GO OFF HIM?
TO THE PARK.
IT'S ONLY FAIR. SINCE HIS DAD WON'T LET HIM.
EXCUSE ME?
JOEY, HE'S HER BROTHER.
AND YOU ARE JUST HER BABYSITTER.
SO, LEAVE THE PARENTING DECISIONS TO ME!
YOU AH - YOU ARE PAIGE, RIGHT?
I'M LATE.
THOUGHT MAYBE YOU'D STOOD ME UP OR SOMETHING.
HERE, I GOT YOU A LITTLE PRESENT.
CAN WE GO TO THE MOVIE ALREADY?
YEAH.
CRAIG!
ANGIE!
HERE YOU GO
THANKS. DON'T EAT IT TOO FAST.
IS THAT A MILLION DOLLARS?
IT'S A LOT,
BUT NOT THAT MUCH.
YOU REMEMBER BRITISH COLUMBIA?
IT'S BEAUTIFUL. THE WEATHER'S WARM
I DON'T REMEMBER.
YOU WERE JUST A BABY.
YOU KNOW, THIS ISN'T A MILLION BUCKS.
BUT IT IS ENOUGH TO GET US THERE.
TOGETHER?
LET'S GO. THE BUS STATION'S NOT FAR.
COME ON.
ANGE! ANGIE?!
DADDY!
I WAS WORRIED.
I THOUGHT YOU GUYS WERE GOING TO THE PARK.
WE DID, BUT AH - ANGE GOT HUNGRY.
WELL, I'LL TAKE IT FROM HERE OKAY? LET'S GO HOME, HONEY.
CRAIG, CAN DADDY COME TOO?
COME WHERE?
ON THE BUS!
CRAIG'S GOT A MILLION DOLLARS IN HIS POCKET.
IT WAS PRETEND.
WHAT?
WE WERE JUST PLAYING...
NO - SHOW HIM THE MONEY.
NO, NO...
WE'RE MOVING TO BRITISH COLOMBIA!
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?
DO YOU THINK YOU CAN JUST TAKE HER AND GO SOMEWHERE WITH HER?
NO, I DON'T.
IT WAS PRETEND -
YEAH, LIKE THAT MONEY IN YOUR POCKET IS PRETEND, RIGHT?
JUST -
STAY AWAY FROM ANGE, OKAY? LIKE YOUR DAD SAID!
YEAH JOEY, I CAN'T DO THAT.
LOOK, I MEAN IT!
FINE.
HEY, KIDDO.
HOW COME YOU'RE HOME SO EARLY?
EVERYTHING OKAY?
YEAH. I'M FINE. I'M FINE.
I JUST AH - I HAD A LONG DAY.
WELL, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT. WE'VE GOT CHINESE FOOD,
A COUPLE OF VIDEOS. WE'LL TAKE IT EASY TONIGHT.
HOW'S THAT SOUND?
SURE. WHY NOT.
GREAT. LISTEN, DID YOU GET THE CAMERA?
UH - NO.
WHY NOT?
WELL, THE ONE I REALLY WANTED
WAS ABOUT A HUNDRED DOLLARS MORE.
THAT'S NO PROBLEM. I'M AN OUTSTANDING HAGGLER.
(Telephone Ringing)
UH, HOW'S TOMORROW SOUND? DINNER OUT?
HELLO?
JOEY.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
NO, GO AHEAD. I'M STILL HERE...
SEAN? HEY. HEY MAN,
UM, I WAS WONDERING IF YOU AH -
IF YOU WERE DOING ANYTHING TONIGHT?
CRAIG?
OH, WHAT'S THAT?
OPEN THIS DOOR NOW.
YEAH? YEAH.
THIS IS MY HOUSE! WHEN I SAY OPEN THE DOOR,
YOU OPEN THE DOOR!
CRAIG!
OKAY. I'LL BE RIGHT OVER.
OKAY. WANNA HEAR A JOKE?
YOU GOTTA PROMISE NOT TO GET UPSET OR SOMETHING -
AS IF I'D GET UPSET AT A JOKE.
WHAT IS A CHEERLEADER'S FAVORITE DRINK?
ROOT BEER. GET IT?
ROOT BEER? ROOT...
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU WOULD MAKE A CHEERLEADING JOKE
TO LAST YEAR'S HEAD CHEERLEADER.
I'LL FORGIVE YOU - IF YOU ANSWER ME THIS.
WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN A NORTH PARK CHEERLEADER
AND A BAG OF TRASH?
I DON'T KNOW. WHAT?
TRASH GETS TAKEN OUT MORE OFTEN.
(Laughter)
BETTER GET A NAPKIN.
I BETTER GET A NAPKIN.
AHEM...
HAZEL? WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE HAVING FUN.
YOU'VE MORE THAN EARNED THIS.
WET DREAM TIME... IS OVER.
LET'S GO.
YOU GOT PAID TO GO OUT WITH ME?
SUE ME.
SURGEON, HUH? IS HE RICH?
YEAH, CRAZY RICH.
BUT HIS - HIS JOB'S STRESSFUL.
SO UM... SO WE FIGHT.
AND I'VE BEEN THINKING -
I MAY GO SOLO.
I'VE GOT THE MONEY.
I'M THINKIN' B.C.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YEAH, DEADLY SERIOUS. I'M OUTTA HERE. TONIGHT.
YOU'RE GONNA WIND UP ON THE STREETS.
THEY SUCK.
THEN - COME WITH ME!
WE'LL WATCH OUT FOR EACH OTHER!
CRAIG, C'MON. LOOK, I CAN'T LEAVE.
LOOK AH, BEFORE YOU ASKED ME IF MY PARENTS HIT ME, RIGHT?
DID I? SO?
I DON'T KNOW. DOES - DOES YOUR DAD HIT YOU?
COME ON, CRAIG, GET OFF THE TRACKS.
YOU STOP KIDDIN' AROUND, MAN. GET OFF THE TRACKS.
GET OFF ME.
CRAIG! CRAIG, GET OFF THE DAMN TRACKS, MAN.
QUIT PLAYIN' AROUND. GET OFF THE TRACKS!
CRAIG!
CRAIG, QUIT PLAYIN' AROUND MAN, GET OFF THE TRACKS!
CRAIG -
(Laughter)
WHOO!
MAN, WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?!
OKAY, NOW THIS IS AN EASY ONE. TWO PLUS TWO IS?
FOUR.
YEAH.
JOEY? JOEY?
WE NEED TO TALK TO YOU. IT'S ABOUT CRAIG.
YOU SAID HE'S GOING TO B.C.
BUT YOU KNOW HE'S JUST GOING TO END UP ON THE STREETS.
IF HE DOESN'T KILL HIMSELF FIRST.
WHAT?
LAST TIME I SAW CRAIG HE WAS PLAYING CHICKEN WITH A TRAIN.
FOR REAL.
GUYS, WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
I CAN CALL HIS FATHER AGAIN -
JOEY, HIS DAD IS THE PROBLEM.
HE BEATS HIM.
NOW WAIT A MINUTE,
DO YOU KNOW WHAT A SERIOUS ACCUSATION THAT IS?
I CAN'T GO ACCUSING THE GUY OF THAT, ALL RIGHT?
IS SOMETHING WRONG WITH CRAIG?
NOT NOW, HONEY, OKAY? THIS IS SERIOUS.
NO.
I SAW, TODAY -
I KNOW - I KNOW YOU SAW HIM TODAY OKAY?
NO, I SAW. ALL PURPLE.
A DINOSAUR HURTS HIM. HE TOLD ME.
OKAY, SEAN. WHY DON'T YOU AND I START AT THE RAILROAD TRACKS.
EMMA, COULD YOU PLEASE JUST WATCH HER?
OF COURSE.
(Telephone Ringing)
HELLO?
HEY, ANY SIGN OF HIM?
NOTHING.
OKAY. WE'RE GOING TO DO ONE MORE SWEEP OF THE AREA.
IF WE DON'T FIND HIM,
WE'RE GOING TO GO TO THE POLICE, OKAY?
WE MAY BE LATE.
HOLD ON A SEC...
I THINK THERE'S ONE MORE PLACE YOU SHOULD LOOK.
CRAIG?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
HEY, WHOA, WHOA, JUST -
I JUST WANT TO HELP, OKAY?
I'M FINE!
YEAH RIGHT, LOOK AT YOU.
WHAT'S THIS I HEAR ABOUT A TRAIN, HUH?
SEAN TOLD YOU THAT?
WELL HE'S A LIAR.
LIAR!
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA. COME ON.
GET OUTTA HERE!
LET'S GO, OKAY? LET'S GO.
JUST CALM DOWN
AND GET OUT OF HERE OKAY?
WHERE AM I GONNA GO, HUH? WHERE AM I GONNA GO BACK...?
WHAT? BACK HOME SO SO DAD CAN-
WHAT? DO WHAT?
WHAT DOES HE DO TO YOU?
HE HITS YOU DOESN'T HE?
DOESN'T HE?
YEAH.
HE DOES.
JT, PLEASE STOP.
I'M HAVING SOME RESIDUAL GUILT ABOUT FRIDAY NIGHT.
THAT SAID, I REALLY NEEDED THE MONEY.
WOW. YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT MAKES ME FEEL A WHOLE LOT BETTER.
JT, YOU'RE A GOOD DATE.
IF YOU WEREN'T 5-1, AND IN A SUBTERRANEAN SOCIAL STRATA?
I'D MAYBE EVEN CONSIDER GOING OUT AGAIN.
REALLY?
YES. BUT - NO. SORRY, HON.
I ONLY DATE UP. NOTHING PERSONAL.
SURE. OF COURSE.
BUT AH, YOU KNOW, I WOULD FEEL BETTER IF -
IF WHAT? SPIT IT OUT.
CALL ME ROMANTIC, BUT I ALWAYS IMAGINED MY FIRST DATE
ENDING IN A KISS.
NO WAY.
COME ON, PAIGE.
YOU'D BE MAKING MY DREAMS COME TRUE.
WE'RE SO EVEN.
OH HERE. YOU FORGOT YOUR BEAR.
I WANNA DO THIS ALONE.
OKAY.
BUT DO IT JUST LIKE WE TALKED ABOUT.
GO IN. SAY AS LITTLE AS YOU CAN.
GO UPSTAIRS, GET YOUR THINGS AND COME OUT.
HE KNOWS YOU'RE COMING AND HE KNOWS WHAT HAS TO HAPPEN.
I'M JUST GOING TO GET MY STUFF.
CRAIG, JUST LEAVE IT, LEAVE IT.
COME BACK WHEN YOU'VE COOLED DOWN.
WE'LL TALK THIS THING THROUGH.
NO MORE TALKING, OKAY?
OKAY. BUT YOU'RE BREAKING MY HEART, YOU KNOW THAT.
JUST LIKE YOUR MOTHER.
PLEASE, CRAIG.
I KNOW I'VE BEEN IMPATIENT.
BUT, WORK HAS BEEN REALLY STRESSFUL.
YOU CAN'T LEAVE, CRAIG. I LOVE YOU.
THERE'RE THREE OPTIONS, DAD.
I CAN GO TO CHILDREN'S AID RIGHT NOW.
I CAN GO AND STAY WITH JOEY WHILE WE SORT THIS STUFF OUT.
OR I CAN COME BACK HERE.
AND LET YOU BEAT ME.
I DON'T BEAT YOU.