♪ YOU'RE BRAVE BUT YOU CAN'T SEE IT
♪ YOU'RE STRONG BUT YOU CAN'T FEEL IT
♪ YOU'RE GOOD BUT YOU DON'T KNOW IT.
I LOVE IT.
IT SHOWS HOW GLAD I AM WE'RE BACK - REDISCOVERING EACH OTHER.
YEAH. YEAH. ME, TOO.
I MEAN LAST YEAR WE WERE JUST - THIS THING BUT,
NOW WE REALLY CONNECT.
LET ME PLAY YOU THE REST.
♪ I KNOW YOU, THE REAL YOU I KNOW YOU, THE REAL YOU.
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I know I can make it through
♪ If I hold out
♪ Be the best
♪ The best that I can be
♪ Hear what I say to you
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I can see it
♪ I know I can make it
♪ I know I can make it through
ATTENTION STUDENTS, IF YOU'VE LOST A KEYCHAIN
WITH A PINK WHISTLE ON IT,
PLEASE SEE MRS. SMITH IN THE OFFICE
TO IDENTIFY IT AND PICK IT UP.
LOOKING FOR SOMEONE?
YEAH, ACTUALLY. MY BOYFRIEND.
TALL, CUTE. YOU MIGHT'VE SEEN US TOGETHER LAST YEAR?
SPEAKING OF LAST YEAR - GRADE EIGHT YEAR BOOK.
GRADE EIGHT - NOT EXACTLY MY BEST.
SOME OF IT WAS PRETTY GOOD. SO WILL YOU SIGN IT?
WE'RE BACK TOGETHER NOW, RIGHT?
BACK TOGETHER. SOUNDS NICE.
SO SIGN IT?
OKAY, DID MY MOM PICK OUT MY CLOTHES?
YOU LOOK GREAT.
I LOOK AWFUL.
YOU GOT THAT RIGHT, FREAKSHOW.
TRY LOOKING IN THE MIRROR.
FREAKSHOW.
BE CAREFUL, JIMMY.
ALTHOUGH IT IS NICE OF YOU TO DATE THE CREEPY CHICKS,
LEAVE THE HOT ONES FOR US.
SHUT UP. I'M SORRY ASH.
HAPPENS ALL THE TIME.
IF JERKS LIKE HIM KNEW HOW BEAUTIFUL YOU WERE
ON THE INSIDE, THEY'D KEEP THEIR MOUTHS SHUT.
IT'S THE EVENT OF THE YEAR.
DR. SALLY'S SEX-TALK.
AS IF I COULD FORGET ABOUT HER
WITH YOU TALKING ABOUT IT EVERY TWO SECONDS.
FIRST YOU GET THE KNOWLEDGE, THEN YOU GET THE POWER.
THEN YOU GET-
WHAT?
BELIEVE ME, YOU DON'T WANT TO KNOW.
NOW, IN ADDITION TO CONDOMS, WE HAVE THE PILL,
THE DIAPHRAGM AND THE IUD.
GUYS, THERE'S NOTHING TO BE EMBARRASSED ABOUT.
MAYBE WE'D FEEL A LITTLE MORE COMFORTABLE
IF DR. SALLY WAS HERE.
LIKE I TOLD YOU AT THE BEGINNING OF THE CLASS,
DR. SALLY IS IN CHINA.
WELL, SEND HER A PLANE TICKET OR SOMETHING.
BEING SEXUALLY RESPONSIBLE MEANS BEING PREPARED.
BUT THE BEST FORM OF PROTECTION IS ABSTINENCE.
WHAT'S-WHAT'S 'ABSTINENCE'?
NOT HAVING SEX.
NO SEX, YOU DON'T GET PREGNANT OR CONTRACT AN STD.
HOWEVER, IF YOU DECIDE NOT TO ABSTAIN,
MAKE SURE YOU ALWAYS HAVE A CONDOM ON YOU.
UNTIL NEXT TIME WE HOPE YOU ENJOYED
THIS CLASSIC PRESENTATION OF 'TAMING OF THE SHREW.'
SO.
ANY THOUGHTS ON SHAKESPEARE'S COMIC MASTERPIECE?
GAVIN?
UM, MAYBE ADD A JOKE OR TWO?
YOU DIDN'T FIND IT FUNNY?
FUNNY? UH - NO. SORRY.
NO NEED TO APOLOGIZE.
BECAUSE I'M OFFERING YOU ALL A CHALLENGE -
I'VE PAIRED YOU UP,
AND I WANT YOU TO WORK ON ACT TWO, SCENE ONE.
THIS PLAY'S BEEN AROUND FOR OVER FOUR-HUNDRED YEARS,
SO IT MUST BE DOING SOMETHING RIGHT.
WHAT I WANT, GUYS, IS A VERSION THAT RINGS TRUE FOR YOU.
HAVE FUN WITH IT.
ATTENTION STAFF AND STUDENTS-
"GOOD MORROW, KATE; FOR THAT'S YOUR NAME, I HEAR."
HEY I WAS THINKING ABOUT OUR SCENE.
AND YOU WANTED TO SHOOT YOURSELF?
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE HAVE TO DO THIS "COMEDY". IT'S SO -
SEXIST? OUTDATED? UNFUNNY?
ALL THREE. SO I WAS THINKING--
WHY DON'T WE SHOW THAT,
AND PLAY IT FOR WHAT'S REALLY GOING ON.
OR NOT...?
NO. TOTALLY.
I'M JUST - SO GLAD WE'RE ON THE SAME PAGE.
YEAH? KWAN'S GONNA REGRET PAIRING US.
WAS IT JUST ME,
OR WAS HEALTH CLASS MORE THAN A LITTLE CONFUSING?
WHY? BECAUSE DR. SALLY LET US DOWN, BECAUSE DR. SALLY DIDN'T-
WOULD YOU SHUT UP ALREADY?
I MEAN CONDOMS. THEY'RE CONFUSING.
WELL, THEY'RE PRETTY SIMPLE, TOBES.
YOU JUST OPEN THE PACKAGE, SLIP 'EM ON AND--
I MEAN - YOU KNOW, WHEN DO WE BUY THEM?
NO TIME LIKE THE PRESENT.
KNOW THE DRILL, PRACTICE.
I MEAN, WE COULD MEET THE WOMAN OF OUR DREAMS TOMORROW!
I ALREADY MET MINE.
LOOK.
THAT IS EXACTLY WHY YOU WANT TO BE PREPARED.
IT'S WAY TOO EARLY FOR THAT.
WHAT IF PASSION TAKES OVER SOME DAY?
AND YOU, TOBY ISSACS GET A CHANCE TO GET IT.
DON'T YOU WANT TO BE PREPARED?
I GUESS...?
YES, YOU DO.
SO - DRUGSTORE, AFTER SCHOOL. OUR STUDLY FUTURE CALLS.
THE CONCEPT'S HILARIOUS.
"ASSES ARE MADE TO BEAR, AND SO ARE YOU!"
HEY GUYS.
YOUR BOYFRIEND? HYSTERICAL. CIAO.
SOMEONE'S HAVING FUN.
YEAH. OUR SCENE SHOULD BE GOOD.
OF COURSE, NOT AS GOOD AS IF I HAD WORKED
WITH MY FAVOURITE PARTNER.
THAT'S A JOKE, RIGHT?
BURN IT, PLEASE.
AW, BUT YOU LOOK SO CUTE.
SO - DINNER.
JEFF'S MAKING BURGERS AND KRAFT DINNER.
YOU KNOW, MY PARENTS MISSED YOU.
SO DID I.
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE COMING.
J.T., YOU DO NOT NEED EXTRA-LARGE.
WHAT DOES THIS MEAN? RIBBED.
FOR HER PLEASURE? NO IDEA.
HM. BETTER FIND OUT.
DID YOU SEE THE UH - PINA COLADA FLAVOUR?
YEAH.
TOO BAD THEY DON'T HAVE BACON.
SO WHAT'D YOU GET?
OH.
THE FORCE IS STRONG WITHIN YOU.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
NO, COME ON.
OKAY, SO CALL ME LATER? OKAY, BYE.
WE JUST WANT TO BE READY, YOU KNOW.
HE-HE DOES. AND-AND ME. TOGETHER. BUT NOT - TOGETHER.
UH - COULD WE HAVE THOSE IN SEPARATE BAGS, PLEASE?
AND UH - MAYBE YOUR PHONE NUMBER?
SO DID DR. SALLY COME TODAY?
UH - NO. ARMSTRONG FILLED IN.
DID HE GIVE OUT CONDOMS?
WHAT?
NO, NOT THAT THAT'S ANY OF YOUR BUSINESS!
RELAX. I JUST THINK THAT KIDS SHOULD HAVE ACCESS TO CONDOMS.
IT'S AN IMPORTANT ISSUE, EH JIMMY?
SURE IT IS. UH - I'M STARVING.
I DON'T KNOW.
TEACHERS GIVING OUT CONDOMS SUGGESTS
THAT KIDS SHOULD BE HAVING SEX.
WELL, KIDS ARE GONNA HAVE SEX, JEFF -
BUT AT LEAST THEY SHOULD BE PROTECTED.
JIMMY? WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I'M NOT SURE. YOU ALL HAVE REALLY GOOD POINTS.
OKAY, AND WHAT'S YOUR POINT?
I THINK JEFF'S RIGHT.
HANDING OUT CONDOMS SENDS A MESSAGE. SORRY.
DON'T BE. YOU'RE ALLOWED TO HAVE AN OPINION.
I JUST WISH I DIDN'T HAVE TO DRAG IT OUT OF YOU.
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
YOU'RE THE GENIUS WHO TALKED ME INTO BUYING THEM.
THEY'RE YOUR PROBLEM NOW.
"FOR I AM BORN TO TAME YOU, KATE.
AND BRING YOU FROM A WILD KATE, TO A KATE CONFROR- CONFROBAB-"
THAT'S IT, SPINNER - WALK AND TALK.
HA HA HA.
OOH, J.T. THE STUD.
CHECK THIS OUT.
GUYS, THEY'RE NOT MINE.
THEN WHOSE ARE THEY?
THEY MUST BE TOBY'S. THAT'S GROSS.
EW. THAT IS SO CLASSIC.
TOBY? KENDRA? HE'S PLANNING ON-
WITH MY SISTER?
NO, SPINNER - IT'S JUST--
WHEN I FIND ISAACS, HE'S FINISHED.
ATTENTION STAFF AND VISITORS, THERE IS A DARK GREEN MINIVAN-
YOU NEED SOME HELP WITH THAT?
SURE. IT'S FOR JIMMY.
YEAH.
THANKS.
NO PROBLEM. HOPE HE LIKES IT.
JIMMY. FOR YOUR LOCKER.
THANKS.
UM, IT'S SUPPOSED TO REPLACE THAT ONE.
MORE PICTURES OF YOU, THE BETTER.
WHAT?
NOTHING. JUST--
WHICH PICTURE DO YOU LIKE BETTER?
I LIKE THEM BOTH.
YOU DIDN'T ANSWER MY QUESTION.
ASH--
SPEAK YOUR MIND. I MEAN IT. WHICH DO YOU LIKE MORE?
THE OLD ONE, OKAY? THE OLD ONE.
ATTENTION.
IT HAS COME TO MY ATTENTION THAT INCREASING AMOUNTS
OF LITTER ARE BEING LEFT IN THE HALLWAY,
PLEASE BE CONSIDERATE AND PICK UP AFTER YOURSELVES...
(Bell Rings)
WOULD NICOLE HAMILTON PLEASE REPORT TO THE MAIN OFFICE IMMEDIATELY...
AGAIN - NICOLE HAMILTON.
I'LL BE HONEST. I DON'T GET IT.
THIS IS WHO I'VE BEEN SINCE BEFORE WE MET.
ASH! WOW.
WELL, YOU-YOU ACTUALLY LOOK... ALIVE.
THANKS. I THINK.
I WAS JUST GETTING USED TO THE WHOLE GOTH THING.
THIS IS SO--
TAMED?
EVERYONE TAKE YOUR SEATS, PLEASE.
SPINNERS LOCKER PAGE? WHY DO YOU WANT ME TO DIE?
I'M TRYING TO SAVE YOUR LIFE.
LOOK, IF WE CAN FIGURE OUT HIS SCHEDULE,
MAYBE YOU CAN TRY TO AVOID HIM FOR THE REST OF THE YEAR.
AND WHAT ABOUT KENDRA? SHE PROBABLY THINKS I'M SLIME.
YOU'LL EXPLAIN IT TO HER, SHE'LL UNDERSTAND.
EVERYTHING WILL BE FINE.
OR NOT.
DON'T OPEN IT!
TOO LATE.
OH GOOD--
HOW OLD AM I?
UH. TWELVE.
AND WHAT GRADE AM I IN?
SEVEN?
AND YOU THOUGHT I'D HAVE SEX WITH YOU? PERVERT!
I KNOW, I LOVE EXISTENTIAL JEANS.
THE FIT IS LIKE, PERFECT.
YEAH, I LOVE THE COMMERCIAL. WHEN THAT HOT GUY SAYS -
"LIFE IS MEANINGLESS WITHOUT JEANS."
"EXISTENTIAL!" HAHAHA.
I HAVEN'T SEEN THAT ONE.
DON'T WORRY - WE'LL GET YOU BACK IN THE LOOP.
SPEAKING OF LOOP - WHAT'S WITH THE STYLE REWIND, ANYWAY?
YOU DON'T LIKE IT?
SURE, BUT THE GOTH LOOK WAS SORTA WORKING FOR YOU.
WHY THE CHANGE?
I HAVE TO GO, I HAVE TO MEET CRAIG.
FOR I AM BORN TO TAME YOU KATE AND--
HEY.
SORRY I'M LATE.
AND YOU ARE--?
LATE. SORRY. CAN WE START?
YEAH. SURE.
"GOOD MORROW, KATE; FOR THAT'S YOUR NAME I HEAR."
WAIT.
WHAT, NOT STRONG ENOUGH?
NO. IT'S JUST-- THE WAY PETRUCHIO WANTS TO CHANGE KATE.
ISN'T IT OUT OF LOVE?
THAT'S WHAT HE CLAIMS. SO?
SO, WE'RE MAKING HIM INTO A VILLAIN. WHAT IF WE'RE WRONG?
ASH, THE GUY'S A SEXIST PIG. AND ABUSIVE.
I KNOW. I READ THE PLAY, BUT--
BUT - NOTHING. EVEN IF HE WASN'T, HE'D STILL BE A JERK.
WHY?
BECAUSE IF HE REALLY LOVED KATE
HE WOULDN'T WANT TO CHANGE HER. HE'D LOVE HER FOR WHO SHE IS.
IT'S JUDGMENT DAY, ISAACS.
GO AHEAD.
BUT I WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT THE REASON I BOUGHT THAT STUFF
WAS 'CAUSE I REALLY LIKE YOUR SISTER.
I MEAN, I REALLY LIKE HER,
BUT I WASN'T THINKING OF HAVING SEX WITH HER -
WE'VE ONLY KISSED. ONE TIME.
IF YOU WEREN'T THINKING ABOUT IT,
WHY'D YOU BUY ALL THAT STUFF?
BECAUSE - IF I WAS GOING TO HAVE SEX WITH KENDRA,
WHICH I'M NOT - I'D WANT TO TAKE CARE OF HER.
I MEAN, HAVING SEX NEVER EVEN OCCURRED TO ME
UNTIL J.T. STARTED TALKING ABOUT BEING PREPARED--
J.T.? SO THIS WAS J.T.'S IDEA.
NO. NO, NO, NO.
HE JUST SUGGESTED THAT I BUY THAT STUFF,
YOU KNOW, YOU KNOW, JUST IN CASE--
BREAK A LEG.
YOU, TOO.
YOU OKAY?
YEAH. JUST - A LITTLE NERVOUS.
YOU'LL BE GREAT. AND I'LL BE RIGHT THERE, WATCHING.
YOU GUYS ARE SO CUTE!
"KATE; IN SOOTH YOU SCAPE NOT SO."
"I CHAFE YOU IF I TARRY; LET ME GO."
"NAY, FOR I AM BORN TO TAME YOU, KATE,
AND BRING YOU FROM A WILD KATE TO A KATE CONFORMABLE
AS OTHER HOUSEHOLD KATES.
I MUST AND WILL HAVE KATHERINE TO MY WIFE!"
GIMME AN L-O-V-E-! GO LOVE!
SO - THOUGHTS?
IT KEPT MY ATTENTION.
ME, TOO. LOVE THE COSTUMES.
WHY FOOTBALL?
WELL, WE THOUGHT ADDING A MODERN TWIST
WOULD MAKE IT FUNNIER.
PETRUCHIO'S A MANLY-MAN.
MAKING HIM A FOOTBALL PLAYER SEEMED PERFECT.
AND HE MAKES KATE INTO THE PERFECT WIFE FOR HIM -
HIS OWN CHEERLEADER.
GOOD JOB.
OKAY - ASHLEY AND CRAIG?
YOU READY?
YEAH. FOR REAL.
"KATE; IN SOOTH YOU SCAPE NOT SO."
"I CHAFE YOU IF I TARRY; LET ME GO!"
"NAY, THOU MUST BE MARRIED TO NO MAN BUT ME.
FOR I AM BORN TO TAME YOU, KATE,
AND BRING YOU FROM A WILD KATE TO A KATE CONFORMABLE
AS OTHER HOUSEHOLD KATES.
I MUST AND WILL HAVE KATHERINE TO MY WIFE!"
WOW. INTENSE.
UH, YEAH. WE SAW IT A BIT DIFFERENTLY.
ASH?
IT DIDN'T SEEM LIKE A COMEDY TO US. IT FELT - DARKER.
CAN YOU TELL US WHY YOU FELT THAT?
IT'S ABOUT BREAKING A PERSON, THEIR SPIRIT.
TAMING THEM AND MAKING THEM INTO SOMEONE
THAT THEY AREN'T...
MAKING THEM INTO A LESSER VERSION OF THEMSELVES.
ISAACS. JUST THE MAN I WAS LOOKING FOR.
LIKE HIS NEW LOOK?
OKAY, AND NOW FOR YOUR FEET.
NO, SPINNER PLEASE, PLEASE.
I PROMISE I'LL NEVER BUY CONDOMS AGAIN.
IT IS NOT ABOUT BUYING CONDOMS. IT'S ABOUT KENDRA.
THERE'S ENOUGH PRESSURE OUT THERE ABOUT HAVING SEX.
SHE DOESN'T NEED ANY MORE FROM YOU TWO.
NOW LADIES AND GENTLEMEN... ISSACS, HIT THE LIGHTS-
I GIVE YOU, THE HUMAN GLOW-WORM.
(LAUGHTER)
HEY.
I SIGNED IT LIKE YOU ASKED.
"WE CLING TO ONE ANOTHER, THE STORM RAGING AROUND.
MY HEAD SLIPS UNDER THE WATER, YOU CAN'T HEAR ME CRY.
AND SO I LET GO, DRIFT AWAY, LEAVE YOUR COMFORT BEHIND.
AND SAVE US."
"LOVE ALWAYS, ASHLEY."