SHOOT!
YEAH!
WHAT YOU LOOKIN' AT, FAG?
WHAT?
YOU CAN'T TAKE YOUR EYES OFF ME.
YEAH, AS IF BUDDY.
COME ON GUYS. LET'S PLAY.
HEY JIMMY - HOW ABOUT YOUR TEAM BE SKINS NOW?
OH, SO I GET IT. YOU JUST WANNA SEE ME TAKE MY SHIRT OFF.
IS THAT IT?
UH - NO.
THERE. WHO'S THE MAN NOW?
HEY, JUST DO THAT WHILE WE'RE ACTUALLY PLAYING.
ALL RIGHT GIRLS, WE HAVING A GAME OR NOT?
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I know I can make it through
♪ If I hold out
♪ Be the best
♪ The best that I can be
♪ Hear what I say to you
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I know I can make it
♪ I know I can make it through
YOU'RE SURE I LOOK OKAY?
SINCE WHEN DO YOU CARE WHAT PEOPLE THINK ANYWAY?
I DON'T REALLY. JUST... CERTAIN PEOPLE.
WELL I THINK YOU LOOK GREAT. HIPPER THAN HIP.
WHOA! HEY JIM! YEAH, WAIT UP!
I'LL SEE YOU LATER?
WHAT, NO KISS GOODBYE?
I WISH. HE'S A GREAT FRIEND - BUT...
BUT YOU WANT MORE, RIGHT?
OKAY. BIG DAY FOR YOU GUYS. DR. SALLY IS BACK.
WHO'S DR. SALLY.
SEX, HEALTH EDUCATOR. VERY FRANK, VERY INFORMED.
MR. S. -
I'M ALL FOR THIS SEX TALK, OF COURSE.
BUT DIDN'T WE DO THIS LAST YEAR.
YOU DID BUT THERE IS ALWAYS MORE TO LEARN ABOUT.
HEALTHY SEXUAL RELATIONS. SEXUAL IDENTITY,
BEING GAY POSITIVE, YOU NAME IT.
YOU SURE HE DOESN'T MEAN HIV POSITIVE.
GAVIN.
DEROGATORY JOKES ARE NOT ACCEPTABLE EVER.
INTOLERANCE COMES FROM IGNORANCE.
SO IT'S GOOD YOU'RE SEEING DR. SALLY IN HEALTH TODAY.
HEY AH, SHE'S A VALUABLE RESOURCE.
MAKE USE OF HER, OKAY? ASK HER THOSE BURNING QUESTIONS.
NOW, IF YOU DO DECIDE TO HAVE SEX,
THEN IT MUST BE CONDOMS, CONDOMS, CONDOMS.
AND THAT KIND OF RESPECT IS KEY
IN HETEROSEXUAL AND SAME-SEX RELATIONSHIPS.
SAME SEX.
IT MEANS TWO GUYS.
GENTLEMEN, THE FLOOR'S YOURS. DON'T BE SHY.
MOST GUYS - CHICKS TURN THEM ON.
OH YEAH!
OKAY, SO GAY GUYS -
HOW DOES SEEING ANOTHER GUY, UH, DO IT FOR THEM?
THE SAME WAY AS SEEING AN ATTRACTIVE FEMALE
DOES IT FOR STRAIGHT GUYS.
MY OLDER BROTHER'S GAY
AND HE'S KNOWN FOREVER - SAYS HE WAS BORN THAT WAY.
WELL, THAT'S ONE THOUGHT - SOME PEOPLE THINK IT'S GENETIC.
WOULDN'T THAT MEAN THAT GAY PARENTS HAVE GAY CHILDREN?
WELL, IF A CHILD IS BORN WITH THE SO-CALLED "GAY GENE",
THEN YES IT'S POSSIBLE.
SOME PEOPLE SAY IT'S A SIN.
WHICH IS THE GREATER SIN? BEING YOURSELF?
OR PRETENDING TO BE SOMEBODY YOU'RE NOT?
NOW, SOMETIMES REFERRED TO SIMPLY AS THE PROCESSOR
OR CENTRAL PROCESSOR,
THE CPU IS WHERE MOST CALCULATIONS TAKE PLACE.
IN ESSENCE IT'S THE BRAIN OF YOUR COMPUTER,
THE PART YOUR COMPUTER USES TO THINK.
IT PROCESSES DATA AND ANY INSTRUCTION YOU GIVE TO IT.
EITHER DIRECTLY OR THROUGH A PROGRAM.
WHAT IS HE DOING?
I THINK ITS KIND OF CUTE.
AND KIND OF OBSESSED.
THIS RATE IS REFERRED TO AS THE CENTRAL PROCESSING SPEED.
AND IT IS MEASURED IN MEGA-HERTZ.
KENDRA TELL YOUR BOYFRIEND THAT CLASS TIME IS MY TIME, NOT HIS.
SORRY MR. SIMPSON.
IN TERMS OF COMPUTER POWER THE CPU
IS THE MOST IMPORTANT ELEMENT.
THANK YOU, DR. SALLY.
. YOU'RE WELCOME.
EVERYBODY DON'T FORGET TO PICK UP YOUR SAMPLE PACKS
ON THE WAY OUT.
AND TO RECAP FOR MORE INFORMATION
YOU CAN GO TO DR. SALLY'S WEB SITE,
THE ADDRESS IS ON THE BOARD.
AND EVERY WEDNESDAY NIGHT THERE IS
A GAY, LESBIAN, BI, TRANSGENDER YOUTH MEETING
AT THE COMMUNITY CENTER ON CHURCH. CHECK IT OUT.
DR. SALLY, HEY.
GO AHEAD I'VE HEARD EVERYTHING.
IT'S ABOUT A BOY.
I LIKE HIM, HE LIKES ME. AT LEAST, AS A FRIEND.
BUT NOT...
I DON'T KNOW.
I TOLD HIM I LIKED HIM, BUT NOTHING'S HAPPENED.
GUYS GET NERVOUS TOO.
WHY DON'T YOU TALK TO HIM - BE BRAVE.
TALK TO HIM SOME MORE.
THERE YOU GO...
HEY MARCY, DON'T FORGET YOUR FEMCARE!
SHUT UP.
WHAT DISTRACTED BY DR, SALLY'S ADVICE ON BOY-ON-BOY LOVE?
SPINNER SHUT UP, OKAY?
IT WAS A JOKE, DUDE.
LOOK JUST TUNE HIM OUT.
HE'S JUST TRYING TO GET YOU STARTED.
I HATE FAGS OKAY. WHAT THEY DO, MAKES ME SICK.
HEY, MARCO -
SO JUST QUIT IT. I MEAN LIKE YESTERDAY, OKAY?
YOUR EYES ARE SO BEAUTIFUL.
THEY HAVE FLECKS OF GREEN, GOLD, NO... TOPAZ...
REALLY?
YEAH.
UH HI, I'M STILL HERE.
I'M TRYING TO EAT.
SORRY. WE MUST BE PRETTY GROSS.
UH, NOT SO MUCH.
UGH, I'M SO LYING.
SEE YOU GUYS.
TOBY?
MAYBE JT HAS A POINT.
JT? A POINT?
THAT'S A NEW ONE.
SERIOUSLY. MAYBE WE SHOULD,
YOU KNOW, COOL IT OR SOMETHING.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHEN YOU BLEW KISSES AT ME IN SIMPSON'S CLASS?
I GOT IN TROUBLE.
YEAH ME TOO!
KWAN DIDN'T THINK I NEEDED THAT MUCH BATHROOM TIME...
I'VE WAS THINKING ABOUT YOUR ENGLISH TROUBLES.
YOU'RE SWEET, TOBY - BUT I'M FINE.
NO, I WANT TO HELP.
SO I'VE SCHEDULED SOME TUTORING SESSIONS FOR THE TWO OF US.
AND SOME STUDY BREAKS- TO BE TOGETHER.
WEDNESDAY'S MY HOCKEY PRACTICE.
DON'T WE THINK YOUR ENGLISH MARK'S
ARE A LITTLE MORE IMPORTANT THAN THAT?
NO, NO THEY'RE NOT. SO JUST PLEASE STOP.
NOW, IF YOUR GROUP IS WATCHING CAREFULLY,
YOU SHOULD BE ABLE TO NOTE THE FILMMAKER'S TRICKS.
PAY ATTENTION TO THE NARRATIVE AND VOICE-OVER TECHNIQUES.
CONSIDER THE EDITING CHOICES.
HOW IS MUSIC INFLUENCING THE FILMMAKERS POINT OF VIEW, OKAY?
ALL PROJECTS ARE DUE ON FRIDAY. HAVE A GOOD ONE GUYS.
GUYS, I'LL BE BACK IN A FEW MINUTES TO CLOSE UP SHOP, OKAY?
UH YEAH. NO PROBLEM, MR. SIMPSON.
HEY MARCO?
ARE YOU WALKING HOME WITH US, OR NOT?
NO - NO IT'S OKAY,
I'LL JUST SEE YOU GUYS TOMORROW.
OKAY.
BUT I LIKE THE SOUR KEYS.
SURE, THEY'RE GOOD.
BUT THERE'S A WHOLE GUMMY WORLD TO EXPLORE.
HERE.
MARCO?
SORRY, WHAT?
IT'S NOT SO EASY FOR ME TO ASK.
I'M LISTENING. I AM.
OKAY.
WELL, ARE WE JUST FRIENDS?
ELLIE I LIKE YOU. A LOT.
AND I MEAN YOU LIKE ME TOO, RIGHT?
SO LET'S GO OUT. LIKE ON A REAL DATE.
YOU'RE SERIOUS?
YEAH. TOTALLY.
OUR MEDIA IMMERSION GROUP IS MEETING AT MY HOUSE AT SEVEN, OKAY?
SURE. I'LL BRING THE TAPE.
WEIRD HAVING JIMMY OVER AGAIN.
WELL, HE'S IN OUR GROUP...
HEY EL! WAIT UP!
CAN I MEET YOU INSIDE?
EL, HOLD ON.
PLEASE DON'T MAKE THIS INTO SOME CHEESY GIRL-TALK SCENE.
I'M FINE.
OKAY. LET ME GUESS. BAD DATE?
NO. I HAD FUN.
I ALWAYS HAVE FUN WITH MARCO.
BUT - THAT WAS ALL.
OH. NO KISS? NOT EVEN GOODNIGHT?
MAYBE HE DOESN'T LIKE ME THAT WAY.
OR - MAYBE HE DOESN'T LIKE GIRLS.
FROM SPINNER, I'D EXPECT THAT.
BUT FROM YOU?
DISAPPOINTING.
I'M JUST CONCERNED.
BECAUSE...?
WHAT MY FAMILY WENT THROUGH BEFORE MY DAD CAME OUT?
NOT FUN.
AND NOT RELEVANT. MARCO'S STRAIGHT.
SOMEONE'S IN LOVE.
YEAH. BUT I THINK SHE'S MAD AT ME.
AND SO YOU'RE DOING THIS - FOR HER?
BIG MISTAKE.
TRUST ME TOBY, IT'LL MAKE HER FEEL SMOTHERED.
SMOTHERED? NO.
IT'LL SHOW HER I CARE.
TOBY?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
FOR YOU.
THANKS.
TOLD YA.
HEY MARCY, AREN'T YOU IN THE WRONG CHANGEROOM?
SHUT UP, IDIOT.
YOU'RE GOOD FOR ONE JOKE A YEAR.
AND YOU REPEAT IT OVER AND OVER AND OVER...
NO, I DON'T CARE HOW MANY JOKES THIS GUY MAKES.
BECAUSE I'M THE ONE WITH THE GIRLFRIEND.
SERIOUS? WHO?
ELLIE.
ELLIE IS YOUR FRIEND, WHO'S A GIRL,
BUT SHE IS NOT YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
THEY'RE DIFFERENT THINGS.
WELL, NOT AFTER LAST NIGHT.
OKAY, DEL ROSSI. DETAILS.
BURGERS, MOVIE, LONG WALK HOME...
HOW FAR DID YOU GET? THIRD BASE? SECOND BASE?
DID YOU MAKE OUT?
YEAH. THE LAST ONE.
WE LIKE KISSED - FOR, LIKE, FOREVER.
AND YOU'RE A BAD LIAR. LOSER.
I WANT EACH OF YOU TO WRITE A TWO PAGE ESSAY
ABOUT YOUR DREAM CAREER.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT BEING PRACTICAL.
THIS EXERCISE IS ABOUT HOPES NOT FEARS.
MY FEAR IS THAT KENDRA HATES ME.
MY HOPE IS THAT I DIE.
GIMME A BREAK.
I THINK SHE WANTS TO DUMP ME.
WHAT DID I SAY ABOUT TALKING?
SORRY SIR.
CAN I BE EXCUSED?
NO. YOU CAN START THE EXERCISE.
HEY, IT'S MARCO'S GIRLFRIEND.
OR IS IT HIS WIFE? I REALLY CAN'T KEEP UP.
JUST A MINUTE, GUYS.
HEY, ELLIE.
HEY.
I HAD A REALLY GREAT TIME LAST NIGHT.
YEAH, ME TOO.
BUT, I SORTA FORGOT SOMETHING...
MARCO!
THEY'RE WAITING. SEE YOU LATER?
GO MARCO.
THINGS ARE LOOKING UP FOR YOU, BUDDY.
THAT PLAY WAS AMAZING.
I MEAN IT WAS LIKE THE BALL WAS WAITING FOR ME TO KICK IT.
SO COOL.
HEY.
TOBY?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
WHAT DO YOU CARE?
OH COME ON -
NO. YOU DON'T LIKE ME. I'M SMOTHERING YOU.
I NEVER SAID THAT.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO.
WHAT'S THAT?
GO BACK TO SLEEP, SPIN.
SHOT ONE HUNDRED AND TWENTY-SIX OF A RODENT... SAVE ME.
PIZZA'S HERE.
SAVED!
UH GUYS, LADIES FIRST, HUH?
OH WELL THEN, AFTER YOU MARCO.
AW, DID WE OFFEND ELLIE?
GEE, YOU THINK?
DON'T FLATTER YOURSELVES. I'M GOING TO THE BATHROOM.
UH - I'M JUST GONNA GET SOME WATER.
OH, I'LL GET IT.
NO, IT'S OKAY. I CAN GET IT.
I DIDN'T KNOW MY KITCHEN WAS UPSTAIRS.
YOU WANTED TO TALK?
SORRY.
NO, THAT WAS GREAT.
YOU'RE SHAKING. SHOULD WE GO DOWNSTAIRS?
NO. I WANT TO BE HERE.
COULD HAVE FOOLED ME.
ELLIE I LIKE YOU. AND I WANT TO KISS YOU.
THEN KISS ME.
AM I DOING SOMETHING WRONG?
NO, EL, YOU'RE PERFECT.
BUT YOU DON'T THINK I'M ATTRACTIVE.
YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEAN.
DO YOU THINK I'M - HOT?
IT'S A SIMPLE QUESTION.
DO YOU LIKE GIRLS - AT ALL?
ELLIE I WANT TO.
AND I WANT YOU TO SO MUCH.
BUT IF YOU CAN'T...
IT'S NOT FAIR TO LEAVE ME HANGING.
PLEASE. PLEASE WOULD YOU TELL ME?
ELLIE I DON'T KNOW. ELLIE-
I'M JUST - I'M TRYING.
I AM... I'M JUST SO CONFUSED...
I THINK MAYBE YOU'RE OVER-REACTING.
WHAT WAS I THINKING?
ME, TOBY ISAACS, WITH A GIRLFRIEND.
AS IF A GIRL WOULD EVER LIKE ME.
HARD TO BELIEVE I KNOW. BUT KENDRA DOES.
KENDRA DOESN'T.
KENDRA SPEAKS FOR HERSELF, THANKS.
JUST GO AHEAD. GO AHEAD. BREAK UP WITH ME.
OH, IS THAT WHY I'M HERE?
TOBY, I LIKE YOU -
BUT JUST AS FRIENDS.
THAT'S EXACTLY IT, RIGHT THERE.
WHAT?
YOU, ANSWERING FOR ME.
JUST - BEING THERE, CONSTANTLY.
YOU CAN'T STAND BEING AROUND ME.
I LOVE BEING AROUND YOU. JUST - NOT ALL THE TIME, OKAY?
MARCO DEL STUDLY.
NOW OFFICIALLY, MARCO WAS GETTING A "GLASS OF WATER", OF COURSE.
OF COURSE. AND HOW DID THAT GLASS OF WATER TASTE? SWEET?
LIKE SUGAR MAN.
YOU GUYS CAN BE OFFICIALLY JEALOUS OF ME NOW.
JEALOUS OF WHAT?
OF YOU TWO, AND YOUR EXTENDED BATHROOM BREAK FRIDAY NIGHT.
YOU SHOULD BE TOTALLY JEALOUS.
SWEET.
EL -
YOU'RE WELCOME.
BUT I CAN'T PRETEND FOREVER.
YOU CAN'T EITHER.
I KNOW.
I WAS THINKING.
THAT GAY YOUTH GROUP, MR. ARMSTRONG MENTIONED.
IF YOU EVER WANTED TO GO CHECK IT OUT I COULD COME WITH.
ELLIE-
SORRY.
NO. THANK YOU.
REALLY.
IT'S JUST THAT I'M NOT READY FOR THAT YET. OKAY?
WHEN YOU ARE, I'M THERE.