OVER HERE LIBERTY! PASS!
YES!
GREAT STUFF, GIRLS. BRING IT IN.
ALRIGHT, THE FINAL ROSTER WILL BE POSTED TOMORROW.
NOT EVERYONE MADE THE CUT.
BUT TODAY I WAS REALLY IMPRESSED WITH ALL YOUR EFFORT.
GOOD STUFF, EVERYONE.
YOU READY?
YEAH.
UH, LIBERTY? NICE EFFORT OUT THERE.
I WAS PLEASED WITH MY STICK HANDLING.
THOUGH MY SCORING COULD HAVE BEEN BETTER.
YOU DIDN'T SCORE...
WE'LL NEED TO WORK ON THAT,
IF I'M GOING TO LEAD OUR TEAM TO VICTORY.
I KNOW HOW MUCH THIS MEANS TO YOU, BUT I'M SORRY LIBERTY -
YOU DIDN'T MAKE THE CUT.
THERE MUST BE A MISTAKE.
I'VE NEVER LOST ANYTHING IN MY LIFE.
WELL, YOU HAVEN'T LOST,
BECAUSE I DO WANT YOU ON THE TEAM.
TO DO WHAT?
THE ROLE OF TEAM MANAGER.
THIS TEAM REALLY NEEDS YOU.
TEAM NEEDS ME? THEN I'M THERE.
GREAT.
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I know I can make it through
♪ If I hold out
♪ Be the best
♪ The best that I can be
♪ Hear what I say to you
♪ What ever it takes
♪ I know I can make it
♪ I know I can make it through
AWESOME. I MADE IT!
GREAT. NOW FOR THE INITIATION.
INITIATION?
AHH!
CONGRATULATIONS, ONE AND ALL.
THANKS - SORRY YOU DIDN'T MAKE THE TEAM.
BUT YOU'RE MANAGER - THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'S GREAT.
AND BELIEVE ME, I'M GONNA KEEP YOU GIRLS IN LINE.
THE OUTLINE FOR YOUR ESSAY IS STRONG AND THOUGHT-PROVOKING.
NAPOLEON WAS FASCINATING.
I ONLY HOPE MY ESSAY DOES HIM JUSTICE.
I'M SURE IT WILL.
YOU ALWAYS ACCOMPLISH WHAT YOU SET OUT TO DO.
NOT ALWAYS. BUT THANK YOU, SIR.
A STRONG FATE LINE MEANS YOU KNOW WHAT YOU WANT TO DO.
BUT MY LIFE LINE'S SO FAINT.
YOUR QUEST FOR MEANING WILL BE AN ETERNAL ONE.
DIDN'T YOU LEARN ANYTHING LAST YEAR?
ABOUT PLAYING WITH DARK MAGIC?
WOW, DEJA VU. FREAKY OCCULT - AND ASH FREAKING OUT.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE A LITTLE RESPECT.
AND I HAVE TO HAVE A LITTLE FUN. SO, TER - READ THE PALM.
WHAT'S IT SAY, MYSTIC ORACLE?
IT'S GREAT. YOUR PALM'S PERFECT.
UM, HON? I WAS KINDA LOOKING FOR A READING?
MORNING CLASS.
LET'S OPEN OUR TEXTBOOKS TO CHAPTER TWELVE: POLYNOMIALS.
WHAT DO YOU SEE, TERRI?
I SEE PAIGE MICHALCHUK, IN DETENTION, AFTER SCHOOL.
TER.
YOU'VE BEEN AVOIDING ME ALL DAY.
NOT YOU. PAIGE.
WHY?
YOUR FATE LINE WAS REALLY FAINT.
PAIGE'S LIFE LINE DOESN'T EXIST.
HER DAYS ARE NUMBERED?
WHOSE DAYS ARE NUMBERED?
EITHER YOU TELL ME WHAT YOU SAW IN MY PALM,
OR MY NAILS GET UP CLOSE AND PERSONAL WITH YOUR FACE.
OKAY. YOUR PALM.
NO LIFE LINE.
YOU'RE GOING TO DIE.
LIBERTY! LIBERTY! LIBERTY! LIBERTY! LIBERTY! LIBERTY!
SO, LIBERTY. HOW DO YOU LIKE BEING TEAM MANAGER?
GREAT. I LOVE IT.
HOW COME THE GIRLS GET TO WEAR THESE RATTY THINGS
AND THE BOYS GET UNIFORMS?
THAT'S BECAUSE WE DIDN'T BUDGET FOR A GIRLS FLOOR HOCKEY TEAM.
WE DIDN'T THINK THERE'D BE SO MUCH INTEREST.
YOU DO KNOW BOYS TEAMS GET EIGHTY PERCENT
OF THE ATHLETICS BUDGET?
THAT'S BECAUSE THERE'S MORE BOYS TEAMS.
MONEY'S TIGHT FOR ALL TEAMS THESE DAYS.
THERE MUST BE A WAY AROUND IT.
WHAT ABOUT FUND-RAISERS? OR SPONSORSHIPS?
SURE. THAT TAKES A LOT OF WORK.
MR. ARMSTRONG - WORK'S MY FORTE.
AND I KNOW EXACTLY WHERE TO START.
PLUS, YOU CAN WRITE THE SPONSORSHIP OFF
AS A TAX CREDIT.
YES, I KNOW BUT THE BOYS HAVE ALREADY ASKED ME-
TO SPONSOR THEIR BASKETBALL TEAM.
THEY DON'T NEED YOUR HELP, MR. JEREMIAH, WE DO.
BUT THE PANTHERS HAVE DONE AWESOME ALL YEAR.
YES. AND WE CAN TOO - IF WE GET THE SAME FULL SUPPORT.
LOOK, SAY YOUR DAUGHTER WAS ON OUR TEAM.
WOULD YOU WANT HER WEARING THIS? I MEAN, LOOK.
WE NEED THIS, MR. JEREMIAH.
OKAY, LOOK - I CAN'T SPONSOR BOTH TEAMS.
BUT I'LL THINK ABOUT IT OKAY?
OUR NEW JERSEY DESIGN.
WOW. THAT'S AWESOME, LIBERTY.
YEAH.
THAT'S REALLY GOOD.
THANKS. WE DO HAVE TO CONVINCE MR. JEREMIAH TO SPONSOR US
AND NOT BOYS BASKETBALL - BUT, A MINOR DETAIL.
YEAH, LIKE THE BOYS NEED FUNDING.
I KNOW GIRLS, YOU'RE EXCITED ABOUT THIS,
BUT EVEN WITH SPONSORSHIP WE'RE NOT GOING TO WIN ANYTHING
UNLESS WE PRACTICE!
OKAY, SO TAKE YOUR POSITIONS,
WE'RE GOING TO DO PASSING DRILLS.
OH, AND CAN YOU CLEAN THE PINNIES IN THE WASHING?
I JUST WASHED THEM THE OTHER DAY.
I KNOW, THEY'RE DIRTY AGAIN.
OKAY GIRLS, C'MON CAN WE FOCUS PLEASE?
HERE.
"IN PALMISTRY, NO ONE INDICATOR BY ITSELF IS CONCLUSIVE."
OKAY.
WHICH HAND DID SHE READ?
MY LEFT.
AND YOU'RE RIGHT-HANDED.
AND YOUR POINT IS?
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO READ SOMEONE'S DOMINANT HAND.
THE ONE YOU USE.
HEY - I DO HAVE A LIFE-LINE.
HERE, PAIGE.
TO EXPRESS MY GRIEF.
UM - THANKS.
ANYTHING I CAN DO IN YOUR TIME OF NEED -
LET ME KNOW - ANYTHING.
SO, WHEN ARE YOU GOING TO TELL HER?
ABOUT MY MIRACULOUS RECOVERY FROM THE BRINK OF DEATH?
HMMM - I DON'T KNOW.
LIBERTY, WE JUST WANTED TO SAY THAT WE REALLY APPRECIATE
WHAT YOU TRIED TO DO.
THANKS. BUT MS. H PUT ME IN MY RIGHTFUL PLACE.
THE LAUNDRY ROOM.
VAN ZANDT.
WHAT'S UP WITH TRYING TO STEAL OUR SPONSORSHIP?
YEAH, UH - WHO CARES ABOUT GIRLS' SPORTS?
EXCEPT OF COURSE MUD WRESTLING.
LOOK, YOU GIRLS ARE CRAZY.
JEREMIAH'S GONNA BACK US BECAUSE WE'RE A WINNING TEAM.
YOU REALLY THINK YOU'RE BETTER THAN US?
UH, WELCOME TO THE CONVERSATION. YEAH.
THEN PROVE IT. FLOOR HOCKEY. GIRLS VERSUS BOYS.
UH - LIBERTY...
OKAY. SAY, UM - WINNER GETS THE SPONSORSHIP?
AND LOSER DOES THE OTHER TEAM'S LAUNDRY FOR A WEEK.
AWESOME. I SWEAT LIKE A PIG.
YEAH, I GOTTA PAY FOR MY WASHING.
SO, WHOSE IDEA WAS THIS AGAIN?
WELL, I AM NOT COACHING YOU GUYS SO YOU CAN GET INTO
A GRUDGE MATCH WITH THE BOYS OVER BRAGGING RIGHTS.
IT'S NOT ABOUT BRAGGING RIGHTS. IT'S ABOUT A SPONSORSHIP.
WELL, WHY GAMBLE FOR IT? LET MR. JEREMIAH DECIDE.
HE CAN'T - SO WE HAVE TO DO THIS.
LOOK. I KNOW THIS IS VERY IMPORTANT FOR YOU -
BUT BETWEEN SCHOOL,
AND PREPARING YOU GIRLS FOR THE ACTUAL COMPETITION -
I CAN'T HELP YOU WITH THIS. I'M SORRY.
BUT WE NEED A SUPERVISOR.
YES, YES YOU DO.
GREAT. NOW, WHO'S GONNA COACH US?
I WILL. AND I'LL LEAD US TO VICTORY-
LIKE NAPOLEON IN THE BATTLE OF LEIPZIG.
"ONE HUNDRED DAYS TO GLORY"?
OUR STRATEGY.
IT OUTLINES WHAT WE HAVE TO DO TO WIN THE REGIONALS.
YOGA? MEDITATION?
NO JUNK FOOD?
TO ACHIEVE PERFECTION, ONE MUST ENVISION PERFECTION.
ENVISION, ACHIEVE, WIN - A SIMPLE FORMULA.
(COMPLAINING WALLA)
OH MY GOSH I CAN'T- YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING.
NAPOLEON SAID IF YOU WANT AUTHORITY-
YOU MUST DRESS THE PART. I LOOK REGAL. COMMANDING.
STUPID...
(whistle) SILENCE!
(AHEM) LIBERTY? I CAN'T PRACTICE TODAY.
I SORTA, HAVE MY PERIOD.
MANNY.
A TRUE CHAMPION DOESN'T LET A SILLY LITTLE 'MONTHLY VISITOR'
STAND BETWEEN HER AND VICTORY.
NOW. LET'S GET STARTED. (whistle)
FALL IN! POSITIONS!
AND THEN I REALIZED, I'LL NEVER HAVE A DRIVER'S LICENSE
OR A SENIOR PROM. TER, I'M TOO YOUNG TO DIE.(SOB)
DON'T CRY. CAN I GET YOU ANYTHING?
SURE. AND MAYBE YOU COULD EVEN DO MY BOOK REPORT FOR KWAN?
WITH ALL THIS STRESS YOU BROUGHT ME -
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO CONCENTRATE?
YOU'RE RIGHT. I'M THERE.
YOU STAY IN THE LEFT-WING - ALLOWING THE FORECHECKERS
TO GO DEEP IN THE OFFENSIVE ZONE.
WHAT'S THIS PLAY CALLED AGAIN?
THE LEFT-WING LOCK.
IT LIMITS BREAKOUT SPACE AND FORCES THE OPPOSITION'S DEFENSE
TO CARRY THE PUCK OR BANK IT UP IN THE BOARDS.
GIRLS, THIS IS CHILD'S PLAY!
HEY LITTLE MISS HAPPY FACE.
WHAT'S A NEUTRAL ZONE TRAP, HUH?
I DON'T KNOW.
PAGE SIXTEEN. DID YOU READ IT?!
MAYBE YOU DON'T KNOW HOW TO READ?
WHY ARE YOU PICKING ON ME?
BECAUSE YOU'RE THE WEAKEST LINK!
ATTENTION STUDENTS.
A FRIENDLY REQUEST FROM OUR CUSTODIAL STAFF
THAT YOU USE THE GARBAGE CANS PROVIDED IN ALL CORRIDORS--
DON'T TEST ME KENDRA.
WHY NOT? NAPOLEON.
IF WE WANT TO WIN, YOU PLAYERS NEED TO PULL TOGETHER.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO WIN, LIBERTY.
NOT WITH YOU BARKING ORDERS.
THEY'RE NOT ORDERS, THEY'RE PLAYS.
WE DON'T UNDERSTAND THEM.
THEY'RE USELESS. KINDA LIKE YOU, AS COACH.
EW!
FINISHED.
TER? YOUR HEAD!
OH. I GET ZITS WHEN I'M STRESSED.
I JUST EMAILED YOUR REPORT.
I DIDN'T GET MINE DONE, BUT THAT'S OKAY.
I ONLY LOSE TEN PERCENT.
ARE YOU SURE?
UM, THANKS.
WHO SAID DYING WASN'T ANY FUN?
ATTENTION STAFF AND VISITORS, THERE IS A DARK GREEN MINIVAN
PARKED OUTSIDE THE AUTOSHOP.
WOULD THE OWNER PLEASE REMOVE IT IMMEDIATELY.
HEY TERRI - WHAT'S UP?
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHEN I CAN GET SOME SLEEP.
BEING TERRI AND PAIGE IS HARD WORK.
CAN I TALK TO YOU ABOUT THAT?
WHAT?
WELL, LET'S JUST SAY - WHEN I TELL YOU?
YOU'RE GONNA WANNA KILL SOMEONE
WHO'S TECHNICALLY ALREADY DYING.
SOME GIRLS TEAM, EH?
WHAT ARE THEY DOING, PUTTING ON THEIR MAKEUP?
CLOSED SET! EVERYBODY OUT!
UM, IT'S JUST A HOCKEY GAME, LIBERTY.
NO SPINNER. IT'S YOUR FUNERAL.
LAST TIME - OUT!
YOU.
PANTHER. SCOREBOARD.
AY, CAPTAIN.
OKAY GIRLS, REMEMBER WHAT NAPOLEON SAID:
"ONE MUST KNOW WHEN TO LEAVE THE SKIN OF THE LION
TO TAKE THE SKIN OF A FOX."
SO, GET OUT THERE AND GIVE IT TO THEM, RIGHT?
RIGHT!
(whistle)
YOU READY? READY? LET'S GO!
WE SHOULD TOTALLY GO TO THAT MOVIE TONIGHT,
SEEING AS HOW YOUR HOMEWORK'S ALREADY DONE.
MAYBE WE CAN EVEN GET TERRI TO PAY?
ASHLEY? ON A OUIJA BOARD.
TERRI TOLD ME THE SAD NEWS.
I THOUGHT THAT WE SHOULD GET A SECOND OPINION.
HEY TERRI,
WOULDN'T IT WORK BETTER IF PAIGE WAS SITTING HERE?
YES, IT WOULD.
DO I HAVE TO DO ANYTHING?
NO. JUST WATCH AND READ.
MYSTIC ORACLE, IS IT TRUE?
IS WHAT TRUE?
THAT YOU - AND HAZEL - PLAYED ME FOR A FOOL?
WOW, I REALLY BETTER GET GOING.
YOU'RE DEAD, MICHALCHUK!
I'M GONNA GET YOU, GET BACK HERE.
AROUND THE OFFENSE A PERIMETER CREATE!
MANNY - TAKE IT IN. TAKE IT IN!
I CAN'T!
TAKE IT IN! NOW!
WHOA! HOLD ON GUYS. (whistle)
YOU OKAY? HELP ME GET HER UP GUYS. GET HER UP, GET HER UP.
OW.
SLOWLY. WHERE DOES IT HURT?
ARE YOU OKAY?
IT'S MY WRIST. I LANDED ON IT.
SHE'S FINE. YOU'RE FINE, RIGHT?
I DON'T WANT TO TAKE ANY CHANCES.
MANNY GO SEE THE NURSE.
NO, SHE'S GOING BACK OUT ON THE FLOOR, WHERE WE NEED HER.
I'M THE REF AND I'M TELLING HER TO GO SEE THE NURSE.
AFTER THIS PERIOD.
GET SOMEONE ELSE TO PLAY.
THOSE GIRLS? THEY'RE ALTERNATES FOR A REASON, JOEY. NO.
YOU'RE BEING A TYRANT.
I'M DOING MY JOB!
LIBERTY. MAYBE YOU NEED TO RELAX?
AND MAYBE YOU NEED TO SHUT UP, AND DO WHAT I TELL YOU.
ALL OF YOU.
GOOD LUCK TRYING TO WIN SHORT TWO PLAYERS, LIBERTY.
SOMEONE MAKE SURE MANNY GOES TO THE NURSE'S OFFICE, PLEASE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU GIRLS. I THOUGHT YOU WANTED TO WIN.
NOT LIKE THIS.
YEAH. WOO-HOO!
HEY - GAMES NOT OVER, GUYS.
THEY CAN STILL COME OUT AND FINISH IT.
...I CANNOT BELIEVE... IT'S ALL HER FAULT! I KNOW!
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE ALL QUITTING! THIS IS A TEAM!
WE'RE NOT QUITTING THE TEAM, LIBERTY. WE'RE QUITTING YOU.
THAT'S SO UNFAIR.
COACHES ARE SUPPOSED TO INSPIRE PEOPLE. YOU JUST BARK AT US.
AND GIVE US CRAZY TEXTBOOKS.
'A THOUSAND WAYS TO MAKE US MISERABLE.'
AND THE STUPID CAPE?
PLUS THAT WHOLE THING WITH MANNY -
ALRIGHT, I GET THE POINT!
LOOK, YOU'RE A GREAT TEAM.
BE MAD AT ME - BUT DON'T LET THOSE GUYS WIN.
KENDRA? YOUR SLAPSHOT IS DEAD-ON.
EMMA? YOU'RE A GOOD OFFENSIVE CAPTAIN.
FOCUS ON GETTING KENDRA TO THE NET.
LET HER DO THE SCORING. AND IT'S YOUR GAME.
SHE DOES HAVE A POINT.
WE CAN'T LET THOSE JERKS GET THE JERSEYS.
LET'S GET 'EM.
LIBERTY, WE'VE GOT IT COVERED, OKAY?
RIGHT. WELL - GO GET 'EM.
I'M THE WEAKEST LINK.
HEY, LIBERTY.
THE GAME'S STILL GOING ON. WHAT'RE YOU DOING OUT HERE?
I RUINED EVERYTHING, MS. H.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THE GIRLS ALL HATE ME.
DID YOU PUSH THEM TOO HARD?
I REALLY WANTED THEM TO WIN THOSE JERSEYS.
IT'S A WORTHY CAUSE.
YEAH, BUT I THINK I SQUISHED OUT ALL THE FUN OF PLAYING.
YOU KNOW, LIBERTY, IT'S TOUGH FOR ANY COACH -
BALANCING WINNING WITH HAVING SOME FUN.
YEAH, AND IT'S SO NOT WORTH IT.
HAVING FUN?
YEAH, SO MUCH.
SORRY, WE DIDN'T WIN.
YOU ALMOST WON. LOSING BY ONE POINT SUCKS, BUT IMPRESSIVE.
THANKS.
NOT IMPRESSIVE ENOUGH TO GET JOEY'S UNIFORMS, OF COURSE.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT. GIRLS!
MR. JEREMIAH SAID HE HADN'T SEEN SUCH A GREAT BATTLE OF THE SEXES
SINCE BILLIE JEAN KING BEAT BOBBY RIGGS.
WHOEVER THEY ARE.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
JOEY'S SPONSORING BOTH TEAMS.
WE IMPRESSED HIM THAT MUCH.
WOW. YOU GIRLS LOOK INCREDIBLE.
YOU MEAN, WE LOOK INCREDIBLE.
TRY IT ON!
IT'S PERFECT.