MAYBE I SHOULD BRING HAGGIS FOR INTERNATIONAL DAY?
ISN'T THAT MADE FROM STOMACH OR LIVER
OR SOMETHING EVEN GROSSER?
YEAH, BUT IT'S MY SCOTTISH HERITAGE.
TERRI? YOU ARE UNDER ARREST.
FOR WEARING LAST YEAR'S JEANS.
FASHION CRIME!
WELL I KNOW SOMEONE WHO COULD USE A TICKET HERSELF.
ME? A FASHION CRIMINAL?
YEAH - FOR STARTING THE SCHOOL YEAR WITH A MULLET.
BUT YOU GUYS WANT A REAL FASHION CRIME?
DO YOU THINK THEY'RE MAYBE BALD UNDER THERE?
DO YOU THINK MAYBE YOU'RE JUST A BIT IGNORANT?
YOU'RE UNDER ARREST. CRIME?
TERRORIST CHIC.
VERY FUNNY HAZEL.
WELL, OKAY, HAZE?
WHEN I'M OFFENDED YOU KNOW YOU'VE REALLY GONE TOO FAR.
WELL, DRESS LIKE THAT, WHAT DO YOU EXPECT? RIGHT?
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I know I can make it through
♪ If I hold out
♪ Be the best
♪ The best that I can be
♪ Hear what I say to you
♪ What ever it takes
♪ I know I can make it
♪ I know I can make it through
OH, THANK YOU. IT'S NOT EVEN MY BIRTHDAY.
SIR, CAN I HAVE THAT -
LATER.
FIRST UP, A REMINDER THAT TOMORROW
IS GRADE NINE INTERNATIONAL DAY.
SO I EXPECT TO BE DAZZLED BY EACH AND EVERY ONE
OF YOUR DISPLAYS.
WHAT IF YOU DON'T HAVE A CULTURE?
GAVIN, WE'VE BEEN THROUGH THIS.
EVERYONE HAS A CULTURE.
SO BRING FOOD, DRESS UP, DO A PLAY -
AND WHAT IF WE DO NOTHING?
NOTHING? I THOUGHT YOU WOULD HAVE BEEN INTO THIS, HAZEL.
BUT - IF NOT?
CLASS PARTICIPATION IS 10 PERCENT OF YOUR MARK.
OKAY - ATTENDANCE. ADEN?
BAZOIAN? BROOKS? CRUIKSHANK?
HAVEN'T YOU STARTED YET?
OH, WELL, IF YOU HAVEN'T, MAYBE I COULD HELP YOU FINISH IT - TONIGHT.
AS IN ME, COMING OVER TO YOUR PLACE, FINALLY.
SURE. MAYBE.
HON, THE COMPLETE LACK OF INVITES CHEZ VOUS?
PARANOIA-INDUCING.
ARE WE BEST FRIEND OR NOT?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
MICHALCHUK?
I KNOW YOU'RE HERE. TALKING TO HAZEL AS ALWAYS.
I SUCK.
YEAH, YOU MIGHT BE RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
THAT'S YOUR HAND-SEWING PROJECT?
IT'S PERFECT!
YEAH. I GUESS IT'S NOT BAD.
I'D RATHER STICK SEWING NEEDLES IN MY EYES
THAN DO ANOTHER PROJECT.
MORTON'S ASSIGNING MORE TODAY.
YEAH, AND THEY'RE BASED ON HOW WELL WE DID THESE.
I DON'T EVEN CARE. THIS STUFF IS FOR GIRLS.
AND NOT EVEN TRUE, JUST LOOK AT JT -
WHY, LIBERTY?
I'M HORRIBLE!
DOESN'T LOOK LIKE IT, GAY T.
OH, YEAH. NO, NO, THAT'S NOT MINE.
THIS IS MINE.
YOU WIN, MAN. THAT'S THE WORST!
PLEASE HAVE YOUR PROJECTS READY.
MISS SANTOS, IT'S VERY NICE.
HERE, TAKE IT. PRETEND IT'S NOT MINE.
MISS VAN ZANDT?
ABSOLUTELY INCREDIBLE WORK. WONDERFUL.
UH, THANK YOU, SIR.
MR. YORKE?
PERHAPS WE SHOULD SEND YOU BACK TO GEOMETRY
TO FIND OUT WHAT A SQUARE LOOKS LIKE.
HEY, HOW'S IT GOING?
LAST NIGHT I ASKED MY MOM WHAT MY CULTURE WAS.
SHE POINTED TO THE GLOBE.
SAID I'M FROM EARTH.
IT'S GOOD TO KNOW. I HAD MY DOUBTS.
OH, YEAH! SHE...
OKAY, I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU ARE SO AGAINST INTERNATIONAL DAY.
BECAUSE - WE'RE PEOPLE.
WHY DO WE NEED LABELS?
I AM WEARING FULL UKRAINIAN, DOWN TO MY CHOBOTES,
AND AM I COMPLAINING?
OF COURSE, I DID MAKE A LITTLE UPDATE.
YOU'RE AN INSPIRATION. REALLY.
PLEASE. ALL YOU HAVE TO WEAR ARE SOME CUT-OFF SHORTS.
AND BRING IN LIKE ROTI OR JERK CHICKEN.
I EAT JERK CHICKEN ALL THE TIME
BUT WHY WOULD I BRING IT?
WELL, IT'S JAMAICAN ISN'T IT?
JERK CHICKEN? TOTALLY.
AND YOU'RE JAMAICAN. AREN'T YOU?
RIGHT. JAMAICAN, MON.
A REMINDER TO GRADE NINE STUDENTS THAT TOMORROW
IS INTERNATIONAL DAY.
JT! YOU HAVE TO HELP ME!
DID YOU SEE THE PROJECT I JUST GOT ASSIGNED?
YEAH, THE SKIRT THINGY? UH, PIECE OF CAKE.
A WHOLE SKIRT? ON A MACHINE?
YOU CAN DO IT, LIBERTY.
OH RIGHT. YOU SAW WHAT MORTON THOUGHT OF THE PILLOW I DID.
AKA YOUR PROJECT. YOU GOT A D!
WELL, I GOT A D. BUT YOU CLAIMED THE D -
LOOK, LIBERTY, I DON'T CARE, OKAY.
AND YOU'LL BE FINE.
I'LL PROBABLY SEW MY FINGER OFF.
NOT MY PROBLEM.
DON'T MAKE ME TELL THE GUYS YOU'RE THE NEXT MARTHA STEWART.
YOU'RE KIDDING? YOU WOULDN'T.
TRY ME.
FINE, I'LL DO IT.
BUT IF YOU DO TELL ANYONE?
I'LL SEW YOUR FINGER OFF.
THANKS.
NOW, I WAS THINKING A SLIT UP THE SIDE
MIGHT BE CUTE, YOU KNOW,
HAVE BIT OF NICE PLAID FABRIC THERE.
WHAPP'N SWEETNESS?
HEY, WAYNE.
HERE FOR YOUR USUAL CURRIED GOAT?
NO. FOR SCHOOL.
I WANT TO GIVE MY CLASS A TASTE OF THE REAL JAMAICA.
GO FOR THE GOAT. YOU LOVE IT.
I DO. BUT I'M NOT SURE THEY WILL.
AH.
HOW'S ABOUT SOME JERK CHICKEN? THAT'S PRETTY SAFE.
PERFECT. HOW MUCH FOR LIKE, 50 PEOPLE?
JUST TO GIVE THEM A TASTE.
TELL YOU WHAT -
SINCE YOU'RE SUCH A GOOD CUSTOMER,
I'LL GIVE YOU A BREAK.
WOW. THANKS.
WHAT'S THIS FOR?
UM, I'M DOING, A PROJECT ON JAMAICA.
THOUGHT I'D GO FOR EXTRA POINTS.
BUT YOU'RE NOT FROM THE ISLAND.
I KNOW. IT'S FOR GEOGRAPHY.
I'VE ALWAYS LIKED JAMAICA.
HOPE TO VISIT SOME DAY.
FOOD - AND DECORATIONS.
I SEE AN A-PLUS IN YOUR FUTURE.
THIS IS THE GAVIN MASON 'LITTLE SLICE OF PRIDE.'
RUSSIAN SAUSAGE, POLISH SAUSAGE, AND GERMAN SAUSAGE.
WELL, CERTAINLY A CREATIVE LOOK AT YOUR HERITAGE.
WHAT ARE THE WHITE CHUNKS?
OH, THOSE ARE CHINESE WATER CHESTNUTS.
IN HONOUR OF MY SISTER.
HOW LONG DID YOU COOK THIS FOR?
I DON'T KNOW. FIVE MINUTES. WHY?
MISS MICHALCHUK, I HAVE TO COMPLIMENT YOU
ON YOUR UKRAINIAN COSTUME.
I DON'T THINK I'VE SEEN ANYTHING QUITE LIKE IT.
WELL, I HAD TO MAKE SOME MODIFICATIONS.
JUST TO BRING IT UP TO DATE.
WELL, IT'S DEFINITELY UP-TO-DATE.
THANK YOU SIR. PEROGIE?
THIS IS EXCELLENT JERK CHICKEN, HAZEL.
IT'S MY MOTHER'S RECIPE.
YOU KNOW,
I LIVE BY THE CRESCENT MOON CARIBBEAN RESTAURANT.
SHE'D GIVE THOSE GUYS A RUN FOR THEIR MONEY.
THANKS. MY MOM'S FROM JAMAICA,
SO YOU KNOW, THEY ALL KINDA LEARNED IN THE SAME PLACE.
YEAH, MON.
YEAH.
CITIZENS OF THE WORLD - THAT'S LUNCH.
BE BACK HERE IN 45 MINUTES.
WE'LL BEGIN THE PRESENTATIONS THEN.
HAZEL ADEN.
SO, YOU'RE JAMAICAN?
WHAT WAS YOUR FIRST CLUE?
JUST - ADEN. NOT REALLY A COMMON NAME.
MAYBE IN SOMALIA -
REALLY. AND WHAT'S YOUR LAST NAME?
OH, RIGHT - I DON'T CARE.
FUNNY THING IS, YOU SORTA LOOK SOMALIAN TOO.
REALLY?
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU MIND YOUR OWN BUSINESS, FAREEZA.
BEFORE JAMAICA MIGHT DECLARE WAR ON IRAQ.
ANYBODY OUT THERE?
NOT A SOUL.
GOOD.
CAN YOU CUT ME A SIX CENTIMETER STRIP OF THAT STUFF, PLEASE?
NO, NO, NO, NO. STOP. STOP.
LOOK, JUST SNIP -
- AND RIP.
YOU NEVER STOP SURPRISING ME, JT.
YOU'RE NORMALLY SUCH - HOW DO I PUT THIS NICELY? -
A SLOB.
OH, THANKS. FIRST YOU BLACKMAIL ME INTO SEWING,
AND THEN YOU INSULT ME.
I'M NOT INSULTING YOU. I'M IMPRESSED.
YOU MUST LIKE IT.
I DON'T LIKE IT, LIBERTY. MY MOM'S A SEAMSTRESS.
I GUESS I JUST GREW UP DOING IT.
LIKE MOTHER, LIKE SON.
YOU SEE, IT'S THAT KIND OF COMMENT
THAT MAKES ME WANT TO PRETEND I'M NOT GOOD AT IT.
WHY ARE GUYS SO WEIRD ABOUT THIS?
I DON'T KNOW. WE JUST ARE.
LOOK, NO MORE QUESTIONS, OKAY?
I'M TRYING TO CONCENTRATE.
SEAM RIPPER.
SPIN, I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU FINISHED TWO SHEILA SPECIALS.
YEAH, AFTER DEVOURING THE REST OF THE WORLD BEFORE LUNCH.
I WAS JUST DEMONSTRATING MY APPRECIATION
FOR DEGRASSI'S CULINARY CULTURE.
WHOA.
HOW DID THAT HAPPEN?
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
WHO'S PROJECT IS THAT? IS THAT FAREEZA'S?
THAT'S FAREEZA'S.
A HATE CRIME HAS BEEN COMMITTED HERE.
BY WHO, WE DON'T KNOW.
BUT WE'RE GOING TO FIND OUT.
UNTIL THEN, INTERNATIONAL DAY IS ON HOLD.
ALL CLASSES ARE ON HOLD TOO.
BUT NONE OF US DID IT.
ARE YOU SURE?
YEAH.
NONE OF US ARE LIKE THAT.
SO, TER, YOU DIDN'T MAKE FUN OF FAREEZA'S CLOTHING
THE OTHER DAY?
AND WHAT ABOUT YOU, HAZEL?
ASHLEY, I KNOW YOU'RE UPSET.
JUST BECAUSE FAREEZA'S FROM IRAQ
DOESN'T MAKE HER A TERRORIST.
ASH, PEOPLE ARE SCARED.
I MEAN, WHAT DO YOU EXPECT?
SPIN, YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
YOU WANT TO EXPLAIN, JIMMY?
MY NEIGHBOUR HAD HIS BANK ACCOUNT FROZEN THREE TIMES.
JUST BECAUSE HIS NAME IS OSAMA.
IS THAT FAIR?
OF COURSE NOT.
BUT WHAT DOES THAT HAVE TO DO WITH FAREEZA'S DISPLAY
GETTING TRASHED?
IT'S JUST SOME KID TRYING TO GETTING ATTENTION.
COME ON, SEAN - IT'S HATE.
HATE'S AN INTERESTING WORD.
IT'S LIKE HITLER. HE HATED JEWS.
BOTH MY GREAT-GRANDPARENTS DIED IN THE HOLOCAUST.
MY PARENTS - THEY'RE WHITE. I'M CHINESE.
WE'RE STILL A GREAT FAMILY.
I'M LIVING PROOF THAT RACE DOESN'T MATTER.
INTERESTING.
LOOK NO MATTER WHAT WE SAY IN CLASS.
IT DOESN'T CHANGE ANYTHING.
NICE ATTITUDE.
SPINNER OKAY, I DON'T WANNA BE ALL RACIST,
BUT I DON'T EXACTLY WANNA GET BLOWN OUTTA THE SKY
BY SOME TERRORIST EITHER.
I NEED TO SEE HAZEL IN MY OFFICE.
HAZEL, COULD YOU COME HERE?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT, I SPENT THE ENTIRE LUNCH WITH PAIGE AND JIMMY.
AND YOUR THREAT ABOUT JAMAICA DECLARING WAR ON IRAQ?
IT WAS A JOKE!
REALLY?
IT WASN'T FUNNY.
DON'T BLAME BEING HERE ON FAREEZA.
I WANTED TO KNOW EVERYTHING THAT WENT ON.
AND EVERYTHING POINTED TOWARD YOU.
OKAY. I'LL ADMIT - FAREEZA IS NOT MY FAVOURITE PERSON.
BUT I WOULD NEVER DO THAT TO HER DISPLAY.
(Telephone)
YES? YOU DO?
TELL THE POLICE I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
THE POLICE HAVE CAUGHT THE CULPRITS, IT SEEMS.
WHO ARE THEY?
TWO BOYS IN GRADE 10.
SO, CAN I GO NOW?
WHAT HAPPENED TO FAREEZA'S DISPLAY WAS A LARGE EXAMPLE
OF RACISM.
BUT SMALLER THINGS - LIKE WORDS,
THAT'S WHERE THIS STUFF STARTS.
TAKE YOUR FASHION CRIME TICKET.
ACCUSING FAREEZA OF BEING A TERRORIST.
I'D LIKE TO APOLOGIZE TO YOU ON BEHALF OF THE SCHOOL.
AND INVITE YOU TO RECREATE YOUR DISPLAY IN THE FOYER.
THANK YOU.
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE THAT COULD HAPPEN AT DEGRASSI.
I'M JUST SURPRISED FAREEZA DID A DISPLAY ON IRAQ AT ALL.
WHY?
WELL, I MEAN IT'S NOT GONNA BE TOO POPULAR.
SO, WHAT WAS SHE SUPPOSED TO DO?
HIDE WHO SHE REALLY IS?
JT...
LOOK, LIBERTY, I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE GONNA SAY, OKAY?
SO DON'T.
YOU HEARD THEM. IT'S WRONG TO HIDE.
IT'S A NATURAL TALENT, JT.
YOU SHOULD BE PROUD.
THAT SKIRT IS SO CUTE.
YOU HONESTLY MADE THAT, LIBERTY?
OF COURSE.
DID YOU BRING IT?
I FEEL TERRIBLE ABOUT THIS.
I KNOW.
BUT IT'S MY CHOICE.
OKAY. TIME TO LOOK AT YOUR WORK.
LET'S START WITH MR. YORKE.
WHO GAVE US SUCH AN ENTERTAINING PIECE
OF ART LAST TIME.
IT'S IMPROVED.
YOU'LL NEVER BE A TAILOR, BUT YOU WILL PASS THE COURSE.
THANK YOU, SIR.
NOW FOR MISS VAN ZANDT.
I'VE BEEN WAITING ALL DAY. YOUR WORK PLEASE?
LOOK AT THE DRAPERY,
THE PERFECTLY FLAT STITCHING.
IT'S REMARKABLE.
ABSOLUTELY REMARKABLE.
YOU HAVE A REAL GIFT.
A TRUE TALENT.
A SEWING GENIUS.
JT SEWED THIS.
HE'S THE GENIUS.
WHAT?
SH-SHE'S LYING.
HE'S LYING.
I'M ALL THUMBS, SIR.
COMPARE MY BLOOD TO THAT ON THE PILLOW IF NEED BE.
FORENSICS, SIR.
JT, LIBERTY - WE'LL SORT THIS MESS OUT AFTER CLASS,
SHALL WE?
JT'S A SEAMSTRESS!
COULD YOU MAKE ME A MATCHING BLOUSE, MR. FASHION DESIGNER?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO HELP ME.
DON'T YOU THINK I SHOULD?
NO.
AND I'D PREFER IF YOU DIDN'T.
FAREEZA, I KNOW HOW HARD IT IS TO BE MUSLIM.
ESPECIALLY NOW.
HOW? YOU'RE JAMAICAN, REMEMBER?
MY NAME - ADEN.
YOU SAID BEFORE IT SOUNDED SOMALIAN.
MY NAME SOUNDS SOMALIAN BECAUSE -
IT IS.
THAT'S WHAT I AM.
I KNOW.
AT MY LAST SCHOOL,
SOMETHING HAPPENED TO ME.
I GOT - I GOT CORNERED BY THESE GIRLS.
ONE OF THEM HELD ME -
THE OTHER HIT ME -
CALLED ME A TERRORIST.
AND YOU SURE LEARNED FROM THEM.
OH, MR. STITCHERY!
YOU WANT TO MAKE ME A NICE APRON?
GO AHEAD, LAUGH IT UP. REALLY FUNNY.
UM, JT, WE WERE WONDERING IF -
YES, EMMA, GIVE IT YOUR BEST SHOT. COME ON!
WE WERE WONDERING IF YOU WOULD MAKE US SKIRTS LIKE LIBERTY'S?
WE'D BE HAPPY TO PAY YOU.
YOU'RE SERIOUS.
LIBERTY'S SKIRT WAS REALLY GREAT.
I COULDN'T BELIEVE IT.
WHO KNEW OUR OWN JT HAD SO MUCH TALENT?
LADIES, I'LL BE HAPPY TO OBLIGE.
BUT I WILL HAVE TO MEASURE YOU.
ME FIRST.
HOW ABOUT $35 EACH? OR TWO FOR $60?
GUYS? SETTLE.
WE'RE GOING TO START TODAY A LITTLE DIFFERENTLY.
HAZEL HAS SOMETHING SHE WANTS TO SHOW US.
I LIED TO YOU ALL YESTERDAY.
SOME OF YOU I'VE BEEN LYING TO LONGER THAN THAT.
SO LET ME INTRODUCE MYSELF.
MY NAME IS HAZEL ADEN.
AND I WAS BORN IN MOGADISHU, SOMALIA.
NOT JAMAICA.
AND, YES - I'M A MUSLIM.
THESE ARE MY PARENTS.
MY MOM CAME HERE FIRST, WITH ME, TO FLEE A CIVIL WAR.
MY DAD, WHO WAS FIGHTING IN THE WAR, CAME LATER.
FAREEZA WEARS THE HEAD-SCARF THING. HOW COME YOU DON'T?
IT'S A HIJAB.
AND I DO WHEN I GO TO MOSQUE.
BUT TO TAKE IT ON FULL-TIME,
IS A PERSONAL AND IMPORTANT DECISION.
ANYWAY, I'M SORRY I LIED.
UNLIKE YOU GUYS - I WAS ASHAMED OF WHO I AM.
BUT NOT ANYMORE.
(Applause)