SO I TURN IT OVER,
AND I'M SURE I STUDIED THE WRONG STUFF.
I KNOW THE FEELING.
BUT THE EXAM I'M REALLY DREADING? SCIENCE.
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
SCIENCE IS TOTALLY MY WORST SUBJECT.
MAYBE YOU NEED HELP FROM YOUR OLD SCIENCE STUDY PARTNER?
DAD?
WHAT ARE YOU - WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I JUST THOUGHT I'D COME BY AND SEE MY SON.
MEET HIS FRIENDS.
I'M ASHLEY KERWIN.
HI ASHLEY. NICE TO MEET YOU.
AND YOU?
CAN I GIVE YOU A LIFT HOME?
I LIVE WITH JOEY NOW.
TO JOEY'S. WE CAN CATCH UP ON THE WAY.
UM, I CAN'T.
OKAY.
I DON'T KNOW - MAYBE WE COULD HAVE DINNER TOMORROW NIGHT?
YOU COULD COME BY WORK?
DAD -
JUST THINK ABOUT IT, OKAY?
I'VE GOTTA GO.
HE SEEMED NICE.
YEAH, WELL, HE DIDN'T HAVE A BELT IN HIS HAND.
YOU'RE NOT ACTUALLY GOING TO GO, ARE YOU?
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I know I can make it through
♪ If I hold out
♪ Be the best
♪ The best that I can be
♪ Hear what I say to you
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I know I can make it
♪ I know I can make it through
TELL ME AGAIN
WHY I NEED TO KNOW ABOUT GENETICS?
SO YOU CAN CLONE ME, AND I CAN BE IN A MILLION PLACES AT ONCE.
I'VE GOT TO TAKE ANG TO BALLET TONIGHT-
DINNER'S IN THE FREEZER. YOU TWO'LL BE HOME LATE. I KNOW.
IF I'M HOME.
ANG, SWEETIE, FINISH YOUR CEREAL. COME ON.
DON'T WANT TO.
OH, OKAY. WELL HAVE SOME ORANGE JUICE THEN, OKAY? COME ON.
ANG!
ANGELA, CAREFUL! MAN!
OKAY NO, NO, HONEY. IT'S OKAY, DADDY'S NOT MAD. IT'S OKAY.
IS THE BOOK A GONER?
NO, IT'LL BE OKAY.
WHAT A MESS!
YEAH, THIS WHOLE PLACE IS A MESS.
WELL THEN WHY DON'T YOU EARN YOUR ALLOWANCE TODAY,
COME HOME EARLY AND CLEAN UP AROUND HERE?
I'M - I'M STUDYING TONIGHT. AT SEAN'S.
THEN COME HOME EARLY.
SWEETIE, COME ON, IT'S OKAY. IT'S OKAY.
OKAY, DOES ANYONE HAVE ANY QUESTIONS?
YEAH. WHAT I STILL DON'T GET
IS WHAT MAKES AN ELEMENT A NOBLE GAS.
NOBLE GASES ARE STABLE.
BECAUSE THEY HAVE THE MAXIMUM NUMBER OF ELECTRONS
IN THEIR OUTER SHELL,
THEY DON'T FORM COMPOUNDS VERY EASILY. OKAY?
RIGHT, THANKS.
OH, SUMMER WITHOUT HATZILAKOS.
I'M TRYING TO CONCENTRATE, OKAY?
BUT, HOW CAN ANYONE CONCENTRATE WITH -
SO SHUT UP!
OH, SOMEONE'S A BROWNER.
SOMEONE IS JUST IN A BAD MOOD.
SOMEONE JUST WANTS TO PASS HIS SCIENCE EXAM, ALL RIGHT?
ALL RIGHT, DUDE.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
YEAH.
THE STRESS OF THE EXAMS?
YEAH, I WISH THAT WAS IT.
HMPH. YOUR DAD, HUH?
YOU TWO DON'T HAVE THE BEST RELATIONSHIP?
UH, NO.
SORRY.
WE TALK ON THE PHONE ONCE IN AWHILE, BUT YESTERDAY?
IT'S THE FIRST TIME I'VE SEEN HIM IN MONTHS.
PEOPLE CAN CHANGE.
I GUESS.
PSST!
JT?
JT? HELLO?
UH, HI.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO ASK.
SO DO YOU WANT MY TUTORING HELP OR NOT?
UH, YES I DO.
WILL YOU HELP ME, LIBERTY?
PLEASE?
PRETTY PLEASE?
WITH A CHERRY ON TOP?
I WANT ONE TICKET TO PARADISE.
HAWAIIAN SURF PARADISE.
THE DANCE? WHAT?
NO. THAT'S A RIP OFF.
THAT'S THE PRICE YOU'LL PAY.
YOU WANT ME AS A TUTOR.
I WANT YOU AS A DATE. FINAL OFFER.
FINE. MAKE IT SO.
DR. THOMPSON TO RADIOLOGY. DR. THOMPSON TO RADIOLOGY.
MRS. HOLLAND.
HOW ARE YA?
LISTEN TO ME. I'VE DONE THIS OPERATION THOUSANDS OF TIMES.
YOU'RE A VERY HEALTHY WOMAN.
YOU'VE ABSOLUTELY NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
I GUARANTEE SUCCESS. OKAY?
HEY!
HEY.
SO YOU'RE HERE FOR DINNER?
UH, YEAH. IF YOU STILL WANT?
OF COURSE I STILL WANT.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK, DON'T GO. OKAY?
CRAIG?
HEY...
HEY.
SO, HOW'S LIFE UP AT BOARDING SCHOOL?
BOARDING SCHOOL? UM -
YEAH, IT'S, YOU KNOW, GREAT.
YOUR DAD DIDN'T TELL ME YOU WERE BACK IN TOWN.
NO. A SURPRISE VISIT.
WELL, IT'LL DO YOUR FATHER GOOD.
THAT'S THE FIRST SMILE I'VE SEEN ON HIM SINCE YOU LEFT.
CRAIGER - READY?
BYE.
GOOD TO SEE EVERYONE AT THE HOSPITAL AGAIN.
BUT - UM, DAD - BOARDING SCHOOL?
WELL -
I COULDN'T TELL EVERYONE WHERE YOU WENT, WHY.
YEAH. I GUESS NOT.
YOU KNOW, YOU LEAVING WAS A HUGE WAKE-UP CALL FOR ME.
I GOT MYSELF INTO ANGER MANAGEMENT.
AND I'VE GOTTEN BETTER.
I'VE GOTTEN A LOT BETTER.
EVERYTHING WORKING OUT OKAY AT JOEY'S?
RIGHT NOW IT'S A BIT - CRAZY, YOU KNOW.
BECAUSE OF EXAMS. BUT -
BUT YOU CAN CONCENTRATE ON YOUR EXAMS?
I MEAN, YOUR MARKS ARE SO IMPORTANT.
YEAH, NO, IT'S UNDER CONTROL. REALLY.
WELL IF YOU NEED HELP WITH ANYTHING, YOU LET ME KNOW.
I'D HAVE TO ASK JOEY.
ESPECIALLY SCIENCE.
IS THAT STILL YOUR WORST SUBJECT?
YEAH. SOME THINGS NEVER CHANGE.
SOME THINGS DO.
SEE?
YOU DO HAVE A FEVER, BABY.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN, CRAIG?
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE HOME A LONG TIME AGO.
I GOT CAUGHT UP STUDYING.
ANG GOT SICK AT BALLET TONIGHT.
I COME HOME, THIS PLACE IS STILL A DISASTER.
I'M SORRY.
CRAIG, I NEED YOUR HELP AROUND HERE.
AND I NEED TO STUDY FOR EXAMS.
I AM ALLOWED TO STUDY, RIGHT?
YEAH. FINE.
FINE. YOU STILL WANT ME TO CLEAN UP?
THAT WOULD BE HELPFUL. THANK YOU.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY. TIME FOR BED. LET'S GO. COME ON.
CRAIG?
SO.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT THE PERIODIC TABLE?
THE NOBLE GASES: HELIUM, NEON, ARGON, KRYPTON, RADON, XENON.
GOOD.
DEFINING CHARACTERISTIC?
STABILITY.
YES!
NOW, ONLY IF YOU COULD FIGURE OUT WHAT THE COASTER'S FOR -
CRAIG?
I JUST DON'T WANT A RINGS ON THE TABLE. IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
OKAY, MAYBE YOU DON'T GET IT, ALL RIGHT?
I HAVE TO GO TO THIS DANCE WITH LIBERTY.
SHE'S HELPING YOU GET THROUGH EXAMS. SUCK IT UP.
WHAT ABOUT MY DREAM? PAIGE, DANCING WITH ME?
SO CLOSE, SO SLOW.
SO IMPOSSIBLE.
WELL, I COULD STILL ASK HER OUT.
YOU CAN'T USE LIBERTY TO PASS,
THEN DUMP HER AND GO WITH PAIGE, ROMEO.
OH, FLASH CARDS. QUEL SURPRISE.
START. CAPITALS OF EUROPE.
ALBANIA? TIRANA.
AUSTRIA? VIENNA.
BELARUS? MINSK.
MINSK. HELLO?
DO YOU PREFER CHARTREUSE OR FUCHSIA?
I CAN'T DECIDE ON MY GOWN FOR THIS DANCE.
LIBERTY, IT'S A LUAU, OKAY?
YOU DON'T NEED SOME BIG GOWN.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT EVEN A -
I KNOW, IT'S NOT A REAL DATE.
BUT, I JUST WANT SOMETHING YOU'LL LIKE.
OKAY. MOVING ON.
IRELAND - UM, DUBLIN.
I HAVE NO IDEA.
ATTENTION ALL GRADE 11 MATH STUDENTS.
TODAY'S MATH EXAM WILL HELD IN THE RESOURCE CENTRE
AND SUPERVISED BY MRS. ANDREWS.
IN MY DAY WE WERE LUCKY ENOUGH TO GET PENCILS.
YOU GET YOUR GEOGRAPHY EXAM ON-LINE.
SIXTY MINUTES, GUYS!
LOOK WHO'S MOVING ON UP TO GRADE NINE?
I AM THE KING OF DEGRASSI!
AND THERE'S MY QUEEN. PAIGE -
THIS IS TURNING OUT TO BE ONE OF THE BEST DAYS OF MY LIFE.
I'M THRILLED FOR YOU, SWEET POTATO.
UH, YEAH. AND YOU KNOW? YOU CAN MAKE IT EVEN BETTER.
BY ANSWERING ONE LITTLE QUESTION. THE DANCE -
JT!
YOU FINISHED BEFORE ME.
I'M GUESSING YOU DID WELL?
UH, YEAH. CAN WE MAYBE TALK LATER?
ALL RIGHT. UM, LOVE TO STAY AND SOAK UP YOUR COLLECTIVE JOY
BUT - THE MILLION DOLLAR QUESTION, RE: THE DANCE?
YEAH. THE HAWAIIAN SURF PARADISE.
HEATHER SINCLAIR'S TITLE, NOT MINE.
WHATEVER. DO YOU WANT TO -?
YOU KNOW?
DO YOU WANT TO HELP LIBERTY PICK OUT AN OUTFIT?
SHE'S MY DATE.
UM, I'D LOVE TO.
YOU KNOW, FOR A SECOND THERE,
I THOUGHT YOU WERE GOING TO ASK ME.
THANKS.
YEAH, ASK YOU, PAIGE. YES, THAT'S FUNNY.
FREE FROM SCIENCE FOR TWO MONTHS!
AND I'M SURE OUR KNOWLEDGE OF THE PERIODIC TABLE
WILL COME IN HANDY.
SO. YEAR-END DANCE. YOU GOING?
UH, I'M ON THE COMMITTEE, REMEMBER?
NO, I MEANT - WITH ANYONE?
OH. NO.
ME NEITHER.
SHOULD WE GO TOGETHER?
YEAH, WE SHOULD.
DAD, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I JUST WANTED TO SEE HOW YOU DID ON THE EXAM.
UH, IT WAS GREAT.
I SHOULD GO. NICE TO SEE YOU, DR. MANNING.
NICE TO SEE YOU TOO, ALISON.
IT'S ASHLEY.
INTERESTING GIRL.
SHE IS.
SO, DINNER TONIGHT?
CELEBRATE THE EXAM?
I'M SUPPOSED TO BABYSIT UNTIL EIGHT.
I CAN PUSH IT OFF.
I'LL MEET YOU AT THE BISTRO AT EIGHT-THIRTY.
CRAIG?
RIGHT. I'LL BE THERE.
OKAY, SEE YOU TONIGHT.
AGAIN! READ IT AGAIN.
ANG, I'VE READ IT FIVE TIMES ALREADY. I COULD RECITE IT.
CRAIG! PLEASE? I'VE GOT THE CHICKEN POX.
FINE. YOUR WISH IS MY COMMAND.
(Phone Ringing)
HERE, COUNT HOW MANY SPOTS YOU HAVE.
HELLO?
JOEY, YOU'RE LATE.
YEAH, I KNOW IT'S LATE, CRAIG.
BUT I GOT A POTENTIAL SALE HERE, OKAY?
I'M GOING TO BE AT LEAST ANOTHER HOUR.
I HAVE PLANS... WITH FRIENDS.
YOU CAN'T GET HOME SOONER?
IF YOU WANT ME TO LOSE THE SALE, YEAH.
NO, THAT'S FINE. FINE.
OKAY. I'LL SEE YOU IN A BIT.
SEVENTEEN, EIGHTEEN SPOTS.
LUCKY YOU. OKAY, THAT BOOK...
DR. MANNING, MAY I BRING YOU ANYTHING?
FOR THE TENTH TIME, I'M WAITING FOR SOMEONE. OKAY?
DAD, DAD, I'M SORRY. UH, JOEY GOT HELD UP.
JUST SIT, SIT.
I GOT YOU A LITTLE PRESENT.
TICKETS TO LONDON?
WE'LL START THERE, TAKE THE CHUNNEL TO PARIS,
RENT A CAR FOR A COUPLE OF WEEKS.
DAD! THAT'S AWESOME. REALLY?
THIS IS THE PERFECT OPPORTUNITY FOR YOU AND I TO ACCLIMATIZE.
YOU KNOW? BEFORE SCHOOL STARTS.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO COME HOME, CRAIG.
I MEAN, JOEY'S WAS - NECESSARY.
BUT IT'S NOT THE BEST ENVIRONMENT.
UM - BUT I LIKE IT AT JOEY'S.
OF COURSE YOU DO, WITH ANGELA THERE.
BUT LOOK AT YOUR STUDY SITUATION. IT IS NOT STABLE.
BEING AT JOEY'S IS STABILITY.
DAD.
YOU KNOW -
DAD!
DAD! DAD, WAIT UP!
ARE YOU TALKING TO ME OR ARE YOU TALKING TO JOEY?
OH, THAT'S NOT FAIR.
LIFE'S NOT FAIR. AND YOU'RE RIGHT - JOEY IS BETTER FOR YOU.
THIS WAY YOU CAN KISS YOUR POTENTIAL GOOD-BYE,
SETTLE FOR SOME "INTERESTING" LITTLE GOTH GIRL -
DON'T TALK ABOUT ASHLEY LIKE THAT -
YOUR MARKS CAN DROP,
AND ONE DAY YOU CAN TAKE OVER THE CAR LOT.
UGH!
ARR!
CRAIG, I'M SO SORRY. IT'LL -
IT'LL NEVER HAPPEN AGAIN?
HUH?
IS THAT WHAT YOU WERE GONNA SAY?
'CAUSE THAT'S WHAT YOU ALWAYS SAY.
BECAUSE YOU ALWAYS SCREW UP.
NO, DAD - YOU'RE THE ONE WHO SCREWS UP.
IT WON'T CHANGE. EVER!
HEY CRAIG, YOU'RE HOME EARLY.
HEY. YEAH. UH, DON'T WANT TO WEAR OUT THE SUMMER TOO FAST.
SOMETHING WRONG?
I GOT IN A FIGHT.
WITH WHO?
MY DAD.
YOUR DAD? YOU SAW YOUR DAD? WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
WELL, 'CAUSE YOU WOULDN'T HAVE LET ME.
YOU'RE RIGHT I WOULDN'T HAVE LET YOU, CRAIG.
I'M GOING TO CALL THE POLICE.
NO.
TOMORROW? I WANT US TO GO TO CHILDREN'S AID -
AND I WANT TO MAKE SURE I NEVER HAVE TO SEE HIM AGAIN.
OKAY.
I HATE HIM, JOEY.
I HATE HIM SO MUCH.
WE'LL TALK MORE ABOUT THIS IN THE MORNING.
WHY DON'T YOU CLEAN UP?
GOOD MORNING.
HEY. MORNING.
SO YOU GUYS WANT ME TO ADD ANYTHING TO THIS GROCERY LIST?
YEAH, A STEAK FOR MY EYE.
OR MAYBE JUST A PATCH. SORTA LIKE A PIRATE, HUH ANG?
ARRR!
SO, UH, YOU'RE REALLY GOING TO DO THIS?
THE CHILDREN'S AID THING?
YES.
THIS IS WHERE I NEED TO BE FOR GOOD.
(Doorbell & Knocking)
WHAT IF THAT'S HIM?
YOUR DAD? I DOUBT IT.
CRAIG. YESTERDAY I HAD EIGHTEEN SPOTS.
TODAY I HAVE ONE, TWO, THREE,
FOUR, FIVE, SIX, SEVEN,
EIGHT, NINE, TEN,
ELEVEN, TWELVE, THIRTEEN SPOTS.
OH, WAIT! FOURTEEN, FIFTEEN SPOTS!
ANGELA, CAN YOU GO UPSTAIRS AND CLEAN YOUR ROOM, PLEASE?
DO I HAVE TO?
YES, PLEASE.
SO - MY DAD SENT THE POLICE TO COME GET ME. WHAT?
HAVE A SEAT, CRAIG.
OKAY.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO TELL YOU THIS -
WHAT?
YOUR DAD HAD AN ACCIDENT LAST NIGHT.
HE'S IN THE HOSPITAL?
NO, NO, SIT. SIT.
HE DIDN'T MAKE IT.
WHA - WHAT?
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
I'M SORRY, CRAIG.