TODAY WAS SO CRAZY. MELISSA CALL IN SICK AGAIN.
I FORGOT POOR MRS. HIRSCH UNDER THE DRYER. FOR AN HOUR.
IT'S TIME TO FOUND A JUNIOR STYLIST.
I KNOW.
SO. EM.
WHAT'RE YOUR BIG PLANS FOR THE WEEKEND?
GOT ANY 'HOT DATES'?
NO, MR. SIMPSON.
EMMA'S BEEN WORKING REALLY HARD ON HER SCIENCE FAIR PROJECT.
OH GREAT! WHAT'S IT ON, AGAIN?
THE EFFECT OF A HEALTHY BREAKFAST ON SCHOOL PERFORMANCE.
THE BETTER YOU EAT, THE BETTER YOU PERFORM.
OH THAT'S VERY IMPRESSIVE.
THANK YOU MR. SIMPSON.
EMMA, MR. SIMPSON IS FINE FOR SCHOOL
BUT WHEN WE'RE HERE - I'D LIKE IT IF YOU CALLED ME ARCHIE.
WOULD YOU PASS THE KUNG PAO... MR. SIMPSON?
♪ WHAT EVER IT TAKES
♪ I KNOW I CAN MAKE IT THROUGH
♪ IF I HOLD OUT
♪ BE THE BEST
♪ THE BEST THAT I CAN BE
♪ HEAR WHAT I SAY TO YOU
♪ WHAT EVER IT TAKES
♪ I KNOW I CAN MAKE IT
♪ I KNOW I CAN MAKE IT THROUGH
HOW MANY?
FORTY-EIGHT. FOURTEEN MORE THAN YOU DID LAST WEEK,
WHEN YOU WERE EATING JUNK.
EVERY TIME I TURN AROUND, THERE HE IS. AT HOME, AT SCHOOL.
CAN YOU EVER GET TOO MUCH MR. SIMPSON?
UH, YEAH?
HE CAME OVER AGAIN FOR DINNER LAST NIGHT -
AND GUESS WHAT HE ASKED ME.
WHAT?
IF I HAD A 'HOT DATES' THIS WEEK-END.
EW! GROSS!
YOU WANT GROSSER?
HE WANTS ME TO CALL HIM BY HIS FIRST NAME - ARCHIE.
DOES THAT MAKE YOUR MOM BETTY?
I ALWAYS THOUGHT SHE WAS MORE OF A VERONICA TYPE.
WE'D HAVE FUN ON A DATE, GUARANTEED.
ALL I NEED IS YOUR PHONE NUMBER.
JIMMY YOUR EX IS MY NEW BEST FRIEND. YOU'RE CUTE, BUT NO.
MAY I HAVE YOUR ATTENTION PLEASE.
SENIOR STUDENTS PLEASE NOTE
THAT GYM CLASSES ARE CANCELED TODAY FOR JUNIOR SCIENCE FAIR.
STORY OF MY LIFE, EH.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
CAN'T. MY BAT. IT'S WOODEN.
SORRY, MY EARS WERE PLUGGED. SORRY.
I HAVE A BONER.
AND IT'S BEEN LIKE THIS ALL WEEK.
A GIRL WALKS BY AND BAM!
IT'S ALL BECAUSE OF EMMA'S STUPID SCIENCE PROJECT.
WHAT DOES THE PROJECT HAVE TO DO WITH IT?
SHE MADE ME EAT GRANOLA. AND FRUIT.
BANANAS DON'T GIVE YOU BONERS. HORMONES DO.
ALL I KNOW IS I ATE SOME HEALTHY FOOD
AND I'M LIKE THE SEX SUPERMAN.
YOU'RE A SUPER FREAK. LET'S GO.
JIMMY, I'M STILL IN THE RED.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M DOING- HERE.
A BINDER-BONER-SHIELD. THANKS.
ALL RIGHT, THE FAIR IS TOMORROW AT NINE SHARP.
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE SOME OF YOU ALMOST FINISHED --
AND LOOKING AROUND, LOOKS LIKE SOME OF YOU ARE LAGGING BEHIND.
DOES ANY ONE NEED ANY HELP?
YES PLEASE, MS. HATZILAKOS.
EM, YOUR PROJECT IS GONNA BE SO AWESOME.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW MUCH WORK YOU DID.
YOU ARE SO GONNA WIN.
UM, NO.
MY PROJECT ON THE EFFECTS OF LIGHT DEPRIVATION
ON HOUSEHOLD PLANTS
IS SO DETAILED, SO THOROUGH, IT IMPRESSES EVEN ME. SORRY!
DON'T LET HER BUG YOU.
IT'S NOT HER. IT'S MY PROJECT.
IT'S NOT WORKING.
TWO OF THE KIDS DID BETTER EATING JUNK FOOD.
REALLY? WHO?
SPINNER MASON. AND GUESS WHO ELSE?
SORRY.
WOW, WHAT'D I DO NOW?
YOU DID BETTER AFTER EATING JUNK.
YOU FAKED MY TESTS AND RUINED MY PROJECT.
MOI? WHY WOULD I?
I ONLY DID YOUR STUPID PROJECT FOR THE FREE FOOD.
WELL, THERE'S NO OTHER EXPLANATION.
SURE THERE IS. THE HEALTH FOOD YOU EAT FOR BREAKFAST STINKS.
YEAH, AND IT'S TRYING TO ESCAPE.
(BURPING)
I'M NOT EATING ANY MORE GRANOLA.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
YOU ALREADY MESSED UP MY PROJECT.
YOU MESSED UP MY LIFE.
YOUR HEALTH FOOD UNLEASHED THE BEAST WITHIN.
SPINNER OPEN YOUR EYES.
SORRY, ELLIE.
I HAVE TO GO NOW.
WAIT. I WANTED TO GO OVER THESE RESULTS WITH YOU.
SPINNER -?
YOU WANT SOME ICE CREAM.
YEAH.
YEAH?
SO. HOW'S THE PROJECT?
HOW'S IT LOOK? A DISASTER.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
JT AND SPINNER ARE THE MATTER.
MY HYPOTHESIS FELL APART.
YOU KNOW EINSTEIN SAID IMAGINATION IS MORE KEY THAN KNOWLEDGE.
MAYBE YOU NEED TO GET A LITTLE CREATIVE.
LOOK AT THINGS FROM ANOTHER ANGLE.
GEE, THAT'S HELPFUL.
HOW HANDY TO HAVE YOU RIGHT HERE IN MY HOUSE!
WELL. GUESS I'LL LEAVE YOU TO IT THEN. GOOD NIGHT, EMMA.
MR. RADITCH? I GIVE YOU - THE WOMAN OF THE FUTURE.
DO I WANT TO KNOW WHAT THIS IS?
IT'S A REPLACEMENT FOR THE SILICONE IN BREAST IMPLANTS.
ONE-HUNDRED PERCENT NATURAL.
MADE OF WATER, FLOWER AND LARD.
MR. RADITCH, WOULD YOU LIKE TO SEE MY PROJECT?
YES PLEASE.
SURVEILLANCE: FRIEND OR FOE?
MY PROJECT WAS GONNA BE SO GOOD.
CHOCOLATE? IN THE MORNING?
I KNOW IT'S NO GOOD FOR ME. BUT IT TASTES LIKE... HAPPY!
MANY, WHAT DID YOU SAY?
I TASTES LIKE HAPPY. WHY?
MANNY, YOU ARE BRILLIANT!
THANK YOU.
HOUR ONE-HUNDRED AND FORTY SEVEN.
NOTICEABLE LACK OF GREEN ON THE FERN.
HOUR ONE-HUNDRED AND FORTY EIGHT.
EVEN THE CACTUS ARE BEGINNING TO DRYING UP.
HOUR ONE-HUNDRED --
THANK YOU, LIBERTY. THAT'LL DO.
BUT THERE'S FIFTY-TWO MORE HOURS -
I'M SURE THERE ARE.
IF WE ONLY HAD ENOUGH TIME.
TWO OF HER SUBJECTS HAVE IRREGULAR RESULTS.
PLUS SHE'S NOT EVEN HERE.
WAIT.
SORRY. LAST MINUTE BURST OF INSPIRATION.
NO PROBLEM AT ALL.
YOU'RE JUDGING?
YUP. I CAN'T WAIT TO HEAR ABOUT YOUR INSPIRATION. SO GO AHEAD.
OKAY. FOR MY PROJECT,
I SET OUT TO PROVE THAT HEALTHY FOOD IS GOOD FOR YOU.
BUT AS SCIENTISTS, WE MUST REMEMBER THE HUMAN FACTOR.
TAKE JT YORKE FOR EXAMPLE.
HIS RESULTS THREW ME.
UNTIL I REALIZED THAT CHOCOLATE AND BURRITOS MAKE HIM HAPPY.
BETTER MOOD? BETTER PERFORMANCE.
AND WHAT ABOUT SPINNER MASON? HOW DO YOU EXPLAIN HIS RESULTS?
MARGIN OF ERROR - IT MAKES SENSE, SINCE IT'S SPINNER...
IT'S A VERY ORIGINAL PROJECT.
OH I LOVE THOSE GIRLS.
YEAH ME TOO. I REALLY LOVE THEM.
STILL IN THE RED ZONE?
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
FIGHTING THE HEALTH FOOD MOLECULES.
CHEMICALS AND PRESERVATIVES ARE THE ANTIDOTE.
IT'S NOT HEALTH FOOD MOLECULES GIVING YOU BONERS,
YOU REALIZE THAT.
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
BECAUSE THAT'S STUPID.
YOU'RE STUPID.
ALL I'VE GOTTA DO IS GET BACK MY CHEMICAL-ENRICHED METABOLISM
AND I'LL BE MY OLD SELF.
WE'RE WAITING FOR YOU TO BEGIN. COULD YOU TWO MOVE ANY SLOWER?
MAYBE ONE DAY, PEOPLE WILL REALIZE
THAT THE WOLF IS ACTUALLY OUR FRIEND. THANK YOU.
CONGRATULATIONS ONCE AGAIN TO NADIA,
FOR WINNING FIRST PRIZE IN THE GRADE SEVEN CLASS.
AND NOW, OUR FINAL AWARD.
JUNIOR SCIENCE FAIR FIRST PRIZE.
HOPE THE ENGRAVER SPELLED MY NAME RIGHT. EXCUSE ME.
AND IT GOES TO EMMA NELSON
FOR MIND/BODY CONNECTION.
CONGRATULATIONS.
ALRIGHT EMMA!
YOU'RE SO JEALOUS.
I'M NOT JEALOUS. I'M APPALLED. TEACHER'S PET WINS AGAIN...
I'VE BEEN THINKING. YOU KNOW ABOUT MY CONDITION.
DO WE HAVE TO TALK ABOUT THIS?
OKAY LOOK IT'S NOT ALL BAD.
INCONVENIENT, YES. BUT IT DOES HAVE AN UPSIDE.
WHAT?
WELL, WHATEVER'S GIVING ME BONERS,
IS ALSO TURNING ME INTO A MAJOR CHICK MAGNET.
GIRLS HAVE BEEN LOOKING AT ME, DIFFERENT.
DIFFERENT. LIKE YOU'RE CRAZY.
NOW TAKE THIS.
SHEILA LET ME TAKE THIS FOR FREE.
SHE EVEN COMPLIMENTED ME ON MY ENSEMBLE.
WHAT'S YOUR POINT?
THAT THE ENTIRE FEMALE RACE IS A SLAVE FOR SPINNER.
SO WHY FIGHT IT? FRUIT AND ONLY FRUIT FROM NOW ON!
(WHISTLE) OKAY. WE ALL HAD FUN AT THE SCIENCE FAIR,
BUT BACK TO BUSINESS.
MOTHERBOARDS.
NOW, AS YOU CAN SEE, THIS ONE HAS NO FRONT-SIDE BUS.
OH NO. OH NO. OH NO. OH NO.
MANNY!
OH, SORRY.
OH LORDY.
EMMA WHAT'S WRONG?
DON'T LOOK AT YOUR E-MAIL.
MISS SANTOS. YOU WILL SEE ME IMMEDIATELY AFTER CLASS.
THANK YOU.
I'LL BE CALLING YOU.
ELLIE'S NUMBER!
JIMMY. I'M A LOVER NOT A FIGHTER.
OKAY, OKAY LISTEN. EVOLUTION CLASS?
CHARLES DERWIN SAID THAT
MANKIND MUST SPREAD HIS SEED TO SURVIVE.
SO DATING ELLIE IS JUST PART OF MY HUMAN DUTY.
ITS DARWIN. THE GUY'S NAME WAS DARWIN. THERE IS NO DERWIN.
WHATEVER.
HAVE YOU CONSIDERED CHANGING YOUR DIET?
BECAUSE WITH A LITTLE BIT OF HEALTH FOOD
THIS COULD HAVE BEEN YOURS.
AND NOW I HAVE TO WRITE A THOUSAND WORD ESSAY
ON INTERNET PRIVACY!
SO IT'S TRUE?
SIMPSON IS DATING MY MOM. YES.
AND NOW EVERYONE KNOWS. EMBARRASSING.
OF COURSE, I WAS A VICTIM OF GOSSIP LAST YEAR.
SO I SYMPATHIZE.
THANKS, LIBERTY.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
NOW LET'S TALK ABOUT WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO.
ABOUT WHAT?
THERE WAS A JUDGING BIAS IN YOUR FAVOUR.
SIMPSON'S DATING YOUR MOM.
SO?
SO HIS BIAS DOESN'T BOTHER YOU?
DON'T LISTEN TO HER, EM.
SHE CAN MAKE UP HER OWN MIND. IT SHOULD BOTHER YOU.
BECAUSE YOU, EMMA NELSON, ARE A WOMAN OF CONSCIENCE.
ONE SIMPLE SOLUTION - TURN IN THE AWARD.
MR. SIMPSON?
I KNOW. WHAT HAPPENED WITH MANNY WAS UNFORTUNATE.
YEAH IT WAS A MISTAKE.
WE'RE BOTH SORRY ABOUT IT.
OKAY. FAIR ENOUGH.
ANYTHING ELSE, EM?
SO I DON'T GET PUNISHED? JUST MANNY?
SHE SENT THE EMAIL -
YEAH BUT I TOLD HER ABOUT YOU AND MOM.
THERE'S NOTHING TO HIDE, EM. WHAT'S ALL THIS ABOUT?
KIDS ARE TALKING.
THAT I WON THE AWARD BECAUSE OF FAVORITISM.
WHAT?
WELL IT'S TRUE. WHEN GUYS LIKE YOU DATE SINGLE MOMS
THEY ALWAYS TRY TO BRIBE THE KIDS.
GUYS LIKE ME?
WE NEED TO DISCUSS THIS - LATER.
NO, WE'RE GONNA DISCUSS THIS NOW!
EMMA CLASS IS ABOUT TO START.
I DON'T CARE! YOU'RE BIASED! JUST ADMIT IT ARCHIE!
EMMA, YOU WON THE AWARD ON YOUR OWN MERITS.
THE RUNNER-UP, LIBERTY VAN ZANDT,
MADE A STRONG EFFORT BUT THE JUDGES THOUGHT IT LACKED FLAIR.
YOURS WAS EXCITING AND ORIGINAL.
ORIGINAL, EXCIDING. OF COURSE, YOU'RE GOING TO SAY.
BECAUSE IT'S THE TRUTH!
I'M NOT THE ONLY ONE THAT FELT THAT WAY.
LOOK AT THE JUDGING SHEETS.
OK. ENOUGH TIME LEFT FOR IMPROV!
WE NEED TWO VOLUNTEERS. NOMINEES?
I'M GONNA GO WITH PAIGE...
AND SPINNER!
DON'T! YOU KNOW I CAN'T! JIMMY!
WHAT'S THE SITUATION?
SITUATION. SPINNER'S DELIVERING A PACKAGE.
AND PAIGE IS A LONELY HOUSEWIFE. VERY LONELY.
MA'AM, I HAVE A PACKAGE FOR YOU.
I BET YOU DO, BIG BOY.
YEAH SO JUST TAKE IT AND SIGN, OKAY?
WHAT'S YOUR HURRY, YOU BIG HANDSOME HUNK OF MAN?
WHY DON'T YOU BRING THAT PACKAGE IN FOR A LITTLE DRINK?
NO, NO I CAN'T. BECAUSE I HATE YOU.
SHH. I WON'T SIGN UNLESS YOU COME IN - AND HAVE SOMETHING.
GAVIN. WE NEED TO SEE YOUR FACE SO WE CAN HEAR YOU.
MS. KWAN, I CAN'T.
OKAY. NOW THAT'S WHY NO ONE SHOULD EVER WEAR TRACK PANTS.
HEY SPIN. AND HOW'S LITTLE SPINNER DOING TODAY?
ARE YOU STILL IN THE RED?
LITTLE SPINNER IS HIDING.
AND YOU SHOULD BE TOO. BECAUSE I'M GONNA KILL YOU.
COME ON. IT WAS FUNNY.
FOR YOU. FOR ME IT WAS JUST BRUTAL.
YOU CAN'T SPEND THE REST OF YOUR HORMONAL LIFE LIKE THIS.
IT'S NOT MY FAULT. IT'S THE HEALTH FOOD.
FOR THE LAST TIME, FOOD HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH IT.
SHEILA? CAN YOU COME HERE FOR A SECOND?
WHAT CAN I DO YOU FOR, LADIES?
QUESTION. DOES FOOD- HEATH FOOD HELP GET MEN IN THE MOOD?
WELL THEY SAY CLAMS DO.
BUT I COOKED 'EM FOR THE HUBBY AND ALL HE GOT WAS GAS.
OKAY SAY YOU KNEW A TEENAGER AND HE WAS ALWAYS IN THE RED.
WOULD FOOD HAVE ANYTHING TO DO WITH IT?
FOOD?
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING.
AT YOUR AGE IT'S ALL ABOUT HORMONES.
SEE?
DON'T WORRY, JIMMY, IT'S JUST A STAGE.
A HORMONAL HICCUP.
IT'LL PASS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE SHE THINKS IT'S ME.
WELL I MEAN. WHY NOT? IT'S ALL ABOUT THE HORMONES, RIGHT?
COULD HAPPEN TO ANYONE.
I NEVER WIN ANYTHING!
LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE ON A STREAK.
FIRST ME AND NOW THE CENTREPIECE.
HEY EMMA.
I SHOULD PROBABLY GET GOING.
MR. SIMPSON - CAN I TALK TO YOU FIRST?
I WAS A BIT OF A FREAK TODAY.
YOU WERE CONCERNED.
YOUR MOM AND I PUT YOU IN AN UNCOMFORTABLE SITUATION.
NO KIDDING.
IT WOULD'VE BEEN NICE IF YOU HADN'T OF DONE IT IN FRONT OF MY CLASS.
YOU KNOW I CARE ABOUT YOUR MOTHER.
NO. IT'S NOT ABOUT THAT.
IT'S ABOUT ME, IN SCHOOL.
AND EVERYONE THINKING I'M YOUR LITTLE PET.
I PROMISE, I'LL TREAT YOU EXACTLY THE WAY I TREAT EVERYONE ELSE.
THAT WON'T MATTER. PEOPLE THEY THINK WHAT THEY WANT TO THINK.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW, MAYBE -
WE SHOULD JUST TRANSFER YOU OUT OF MY CLASS?
NO.
OR YOUR MOM AND I SHOULD STOP DATING.
I DON'T WANT THAT EITHER...
YOU KNOW I WAS PROUD OF YOU TODAY.
THE WAY YOU SAVED YOUR PROJECT AT THE VERY LAST SECOND?
WAS VERY, VERY COOL.
AND VERY DESERVING OF FIRST PLACE. OKAY?
OKAY. THANKS... SNAKE.
NO PROBLEM, EMMERS.
ARCHIBALD.
EMMALADA.
THE SNAKESTER.