C.S. LEWIS CALLED ROMANCE 'THE RELIGION OF LOVE'.
BUT FOR MANY WRITERS, ROMANCE ISN'T SO SIMPLE.
IT IS OFTEN A CONFUSING EXPERIENCE.
(Knocking)
EXCUSE ME, MS. KWAN? I'M SORRY TO INTERRUPT.
BUT UM...
BUT, I'VE COME TO COLLECT MY ONE AND ONLY TRUE LOVE.
♪ WON'T YOU BE MY CINDERELLA?
♪ COULD I KISS YOU MANUELA?
♪ YOU CAN SEE ME, HOWEVER
♪ YOU MUST LOVE ME FOREVER.
♪ FOREVER.
I NEED TO GET THAT.
PARDON ME?
THE AV CART BEHIND YOU.
MR. SIMPSON SENT ME TO GET IT.
AND UM, YOU'RE ON THE CORD.
YEAH, YOU COULD JUST MOVE IT.
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I know I can make it through
♪ If I hold out
♪ Be the best
♪ The best that I can be
♪ Hear what I say to you
♪ What ever it takes
♪ I know I can make it
♪ I know I can make it through
HE'S COMING!
MR. SIMPSON, SOMETHING HORRIBLE HAS HAPPENED TO YOUR COMPUTER!
JT, DID YOU EMAIL ME NAKED BABOON PICTURES AGAIN?
IT'S SERIOUS. I THINK YOUR COMPUTER HAS A VIRUS.
YOU HAD ME GOING.
WHO DID THIS?
SO, YOU'RE NOT UPSET THAT I TOLD EVERYONE
YOU AND MOM GOT ENGAGED?
NO, IT'S SWEET. THANK YOU.
BUT, HOW DOES IT FEEL, MR. SIMPSON,
I MEAN, TO FIND YOUR ONE TRUE LOVE?
WELL, I JUST HOPE ONE DAY ALL OF YOU FIND SOMEONE
WHO TRULY MAKES YOU HAPPY.
OKAY. WE STILL HAVE STUFF TO LEARN TODAY.
SO, BACK TO YOUR SEATS.
WHO CAN TELL ME THE SIZE OF A KILOBIT?
THE RING IS SO NICE.
A DIAMOND SOLITAIRE WITH A PLATINUM SETTING.
MR. SIMPSON LET ME HELP HIM PICK IT OUT.
HE CHECKED WITH YOU BEFORE HE PROPOSED?
NO. BECAUSE MR. SIMPSON DIDN'T PROPOSE.
MY MOM DID.
YOUR MOM DID?! OH, THAT'S COOL.
MANNY, WOMEN CAN PROPOSE TOO.
I KNOW. IT'S JUST NOT AS -
ROMANTIC.
BECAUSE MY MOM SAW WHAT SHE WANTED AND WENT FOR IT?
WHY NOT?
HEY GIRLS.
I THINK CRAIG REALLY LIKES YOU.
THEN WHY DOESN'T HE ASK ME OUT?
UGH! THIS IS TORTURE.
MANNY, THIS IS JUST WHAT WE TALKED ABOUT.
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU WANT. SO, GO FOR IT.
MY FAVORITE LETTER IS E.
"E IS FOR ERNEST WHO CHOKED ON A PEACH."
YOU LIKE EDWARD GOREY?
YEAH, I LOVE HIM.
I MEAN, HIS STUFF IS A PERFECT BALANCE BETWEEN DARK AND FUNNY.
KWAN THOUGHT IT WAS TOO MORBID FOR MY BOOK REPORT.
SO SMALL MINDED, HUH?
NOT LIKE ME AND YOU.
I'LL CATCH YOU LATER.
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF MARCO?
KINDA CUTE I GUESS.
I THINK HE'S REALLY CUTE.
WHICH POSES THE QUESTION:
CUTE, NICE, SMART AND STILL SINGLE?
NOT FOR LONG. HAZEL'S ON THE CASE.
THINK I NEED 'HELP' WITH MY MATH HOMEWORK.
HEY, MARCO, I WAS WONDERING IF YOU COULD...
PERSONAL E-MAIL DURING CLASS TIME?
YOU'RE SUCH A REBEL, NASH.
YOU KNOW ME.
NO. 'CAUSE I HAD NO IDEA YOU HAD A CRUSH ON SOMEONE.
WHO?
YOU'RE EMBARRASSED.
NO.
AND YOU'RE SHY.
ELLIE NASH. WOW.
I'VE NEVER LIKED ANYONE LIKE THIS BEFORE.
IT'S WEIRD.
IT'S LOVE.
IT'S NOT YOUR BUSINESS. SHUT UP.
SORRY I'M LATE.
FLOOD IN THE MEN'S WASHROOM. NOT A PRETTY PICTURE.
FOR YOU.
OH, CRAIG.
DO YOU LIKE ME?
LIKE YOU?
MANNY, I THINK I LOVE--
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
BYE.
CRAIG? I LIKE YOU.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I JUST SAID THAT.
WELL, NICE TALKING TO YOU.
WAIT.
MANNY?
I, UH, I LIKE YOU TOO.
ARRR!
OH, I'M SORRY! SORRY. I'M SUCH A DITZ!
NO, NO. IT WAS CUTE.
SO, CRAIG. TONIGHT? WANNA -
CATCH A MOVIE? AT THE MALL?
A MOVIE? SURE.
OH - YOU MEAN WITH YOU?
I DON'T KNOW.
KIDDING! I'M KIDDING.
OKAY. YOU SO HAD ME THERE.
I COULDN'T RESIST.
SO PICK ME UP AT EMMA'S OK? SEVEN?
I'LL TALK ABOUT HIGH AND LOW PRESSURE SYSTEMS COLLIDING.
YEAH, COOL.
UH, EL, I GOT THIS REALLY WEIRD EMAIL,
AND IT'S SORT OF CONFUSING ME.
WHAT DOES IT SAY?
'S AS IN SECRET, I ADMIRE.
YOU, FROM A - A FAR.
- XO BAD RHYMER'.
WOW. CRYPTIC.
YEAH, WELL, WHICH IS COOL.
BUT, WHAT DOES IT MEAN?
SOMEONE LIKES YOU?
OKAY. SO WHY TELL ME LIKE THAT?
E-MAIL'S ANONYMOUS.
AFRAID OF THE RESPONSE, IT KEEPS YOU A STEP AWAY.
YOU MEAN YOU'D DO THAT TOO?
TELLING SOMEONE YOU LIKE THEM'S HARD.
YEAH. YEAH, IT IS.
BIANCA, I'M SORRY, IT DIDN'T WORK OUT OKAY?
IT'S OVER. YOU HAVE TO STOP CALLING ME NOW.
ALRIGHT? GOODBYE.
SHOULD'VE ENDED IT WEEKS AGO.
LET THAT BE A LESSON.
WHAT ARE YOU ALL DRESSED UP FOR?
A DATE.
MY FIRST.
HEY, CONGRATULATIONS.
SO YOU FINALLY ASKED THAT ASHLEY GIRL OUT?
WELL, NO.
MANNY ASKED ME OUT.
MANNY? ISN'T SHE A BIT YOUNG FOR YOU?
IT'S JUST ELEVEN MONTHS, JOEY.
SHE'S JUST ELEVEN MONTHS YOUNGER.
ALRIGHT, AGE AIN'T NUTHIN' BUT A NUMBER.
LOOK AT MR. MOO-MOO, CRAIG!
MR. MOO-MOO, CRAIG!
VERY NICE.
SO SHE ASKED YOU OUT, HUH?
CHECK OUT CRAIG - SUPER-STUD.
TAKES AFTER HIS STEP-DAD.
JUST BE BACK BY 10, OKAY? I'M SERIOUS.
(Phone Ringing)
HELLO?
SO YOU KNOW WHAT TO SAY IF MY PARENTS CALL?
MANNY, WE'VE BEEN THROUGH IT.
AND WHAT IF YOUR MOM COMES HOME?
SHE'S OUT TILL 11:00 WITH MR. SIMPSON, DON'T WORRY.
SO?
CRAIG DOESN'T HAVE A CHANCE.
I'M TRYING NOT TO FREAK
BUT CRAIG'S THE FIRST BOY WHO'S EVER LIKED ME.
AND HE WON'T BE THE LAST, OKAY?
(Screaming)
HE'S HERE! HE'S HERE! I'M GOING TO GO GET IT.
HEY, I HEARD SCREAMING.
THAT WAS THE TV.
HE'S HERE, HE'S HERE...
MANNY -
YOU LOOK INCREDIBLE.
YOU TOO.
OH! I ALMOST FORGOT.
THIS IS FOR YOU.
THAT'S JUST TOO PICTURE PERFECT.
SMILE!
YOU READY FOR OUR DATE?
I AM SO READY.
SO? WHAT HAPPENED?
AT FIRST, I WAS SO NERVOUS.
BUT THEN I GOT INTO IT.
AND BY THE END? I JUST KNEW.
CRAIG WAS 'THE ONE'.
SO YOU'RE GIRLFRIEND-BOYFRIEND NOW?
IT'S OFFICIAL? YOU TALKED TO CRAIG?
NO. BUT I DON'T THINK I HAVE TO. I JUST KNOW.
I GUESS THAT'S WHAT FALLING IN LOVE IS ALL ABOUT.
CHECK OUT 'THE QUIET MAN'.
YEAH, DUDE HASN'T SAID A WORD ALL DAY.
SORRY. I UM, - I GOT A LOT ON MY MIND.
I GET IT.
CRAIG IS LOST IN LOVE WITH LITTLE MISS SANTOS.
MUST'VE BEEN A SERIOUSLY HOT DATE.
HOT?
NO. I'D SAY THE BEST WAY TO DESCRIBE OUR DATE IS -
BIZARRE.
THE ONLY WAY TO DESCRIBE OUR DATE WAS -
MAGICAL.
I THOUGHT WE'D JUST GO TO THE MALL, SEE A MOVIE,
NOTHING SPECIAL.
AND THEN WE GET THERE AND --
OH MY GOSH, THE CARNIVAL IS ON!
SO YOU DON'T WANT TO SEE THE MOVIE?
AND MISS ALL THIS!
I LOVE THE BALLOONS AND THE CLOWNS.
OH, LOOK.
AND COTTON CANDY? IT'S SO DELICIOUS.
I KNOW. IT'S SO DELICIOUS.
ONE COTTON CANDY PLEASE.
NO! NO, IT'S FOR YOU.
DON'T BE SILLY.
THEN THE MOST INCREDIBLE THING HAPPENED.
MY FINGERS BRUSHED HIS LIPS.
I THOUGHT I WOULD DIE.
MAYBE YOU CAN HELP FIGURE IT OUT.
MANNY LOOKED SO AWESOME.
AND I WAS HAPPY TO BE WITH HER.
BUT THEN -
THE CARNIVAL IS ON!
WAIT, SO YOU DON'T WANT TO SEE THE MOVIE?
AND MISS ALL THIS?
I LOVE BALLOONS AND THE CLOWNS.
UH, LOOK.
AND THE COTTON CANDY. YUMMY YUM YUM.
YEAH, YEAH.
YUMMY YUM YUM.
NO, NO, NO. IT'S FOR YOU.
DON'T BE SILLY.
THE COTTON CANDY INCIDENT.
SHE NEARLY CHOKED ME WITH IT.
LOOK AT THE BRIGHT SIDE, DUDE.
IF IT WAS A CANDY APPLE? YOU WOULD HAVE BE DEAD.
YOU THINK THAT'S FUNNY?
YEAH.
YOU'RE GONNA LOVE THIS.
WHOO! GO, CRAIG, GO.
TODAY BALL TOSS. TOMORROW THE WORLD!
YOU'RE LIKE, I DON'T KNOW -
THE NEXT FAMOUS PITCHER GUY OR SOMETHING.
THIS IS FOR YOU.
OH, THIS IS THE BEST!
IT'S SO CUTE.
HIS NAME IS HORSEY-HORSE.
I'VE ALREADY GOT PIGGY-PIG AND LAMBY-LAMB AND -
YOU KNOW? THE FLUFFIE FLUFF COLLECTION?
I THOUGHT SHE'D NEVER STOP TALKING.
THIS IS THE BEST GIFT. THANKS, CRAIG.
AM I TALKING TOO MUCH?
WHAT. NO, IT'S JUST -
IT'S YOUR TURN TO WIN ME WHATEVER.
JUST, DON'T THROW IT TOO HARD, OKAY?
AAAHHHHHHH!
OH, CRAIG.
I AM SORRY I HURT YOU.
DON'T, IT'S OKAY.
THEN I LOOKED INTO HER EYES.
AND I SAW HOW BEAUTIFUL SHE WAS.
I MEAN, THE THING IS, I DO LIKE HER.
IT'S JUST SHE'S A BIT YOUNG.
ONLY BY A YEAR, DUDE.
YOU WANNA KNOW THE REAL REASON I COULDN'T KISS HER?
SHE REMINDS ME OF MY FIVE YEAR OLD HALF-SISTER.
RIGHT.
THAT'S, THAT'S MESSED UP.
YEAH, THAT'S REALLY WEIRD.
YEAH, DON'T SAY THAT.
WELL, I KNOW. THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
'CAUSE SHE'S ALSO REALLY SWEET.
SO WHAT DO I DO?
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE BOUGHT YOU A ROSE.
CRAIG IS A TRUE ROMANTIC.
I JUST WISH OUR DATE HAD ENDED BETTER.
WHY? WHAT HAPPENED?
MORE LIKE WHAT DIDN'T HAPPEN.
TODAY BALL-TOSS, TOMORROW THE WORLD!
THIS IS FOR YOU.
OH, THIS IS THE BEST.
MY FAVOURITE THING, 'CAUSE YOU WON IT.
THANKS, CRAIG.
AM I TALKING TOO MUCH?
NOT AT ALL. IT'S YOUR TURN.
JUST TRY NOT TO THROW TOO HARD, OKAY?
OKAY.
OH DEAR! THAT SMARTS.
OH, CRAIG, I AM SO SORRY I HURT YOU.
NO, IT'S OKAY, IT'S OKAY.
I'M REALLY, REALLY, REALLY SORRY.
MANNY -
I SHOULD GET YOU HOME.
I'LL BET HE WANTED TO.
HE JUST WANTED TO GET YOU BACK TO MY HOUSE ON TIME.
WHICH I THINK IS COOL.
ABSOLUTELY.
CRAIG HAS MY TWO FAVOURITE QUALITIES:
PASSION AND PUNCTUALITY.
THAT'S WHY HE'S MY GUY.
OKAY, THAT WAS A GOOD ANALYSIS OF PRINT ADS, EVERYONE.
YOU'RE GETTING THE HANG OF READING
THE UNDERLYING SALES MESSAGE.
SO, LET'S MOVE ON TO TV. COMMERCIALS.
MOST OF US MAY SEE THEM AS AN OPPORTUNITY TO GET A SNACK,
BUT TV ADVERTISING CAN REAP HUGE PROFITS.
NOW TAPE THREE COMMERCIALS -
ONE FOR LAUNDRY DETERGENT,
ONE FOR THE LATEST LUXURY VEHICLE,
AND THE LAST FOR ATHLETIC SHOES.
WHILE YOU'RE WATCHING PAY SPECIAL ATTENTION TO THE IMAGES
HOW THEY'VE BEEN SHOT, EDITED...
MANNY...
HEY YOU! WHERE YOU BEEN?
DID YOU MISS ME? I MISSED YOU.
EVERYBODY'S TALKING ABOUT US.
YEAH, THEY SAY WE'RE DEGRASSI'S HOTTEST NEW COUPLE.
YEAH.
I'M EMBARRASSED, TOO.
PEOPLE TALKING LIKE THIS.
BUT I HAD SUCH AN AMAZING TIME.
THE CARNIVAL, THE GIFT.
IT WAS, LIKE - THE BEST NIGHT OF MY LIFE.
AND ALL BECAUSE OF YOU.
GREAT.
WELL, I'LL SEE YOU LATER?
GREAT. BYE.
THAT WAS - WEIRD.
MAYBE CRAIG'S NOT REALLY INTO THIS.
NO, NO. HE'S JUST MOODY.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD SLOW DOWN?
YOU KNOW, BEFORE YOU GET HURT.
NO. HE NEEDS IS CHEERING UP.
WHICH I'M GREAT AT!
HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
NOTHING.
BECAUSE I WAS SUPPOSED TO MEET HAZEL AND...
I KNOW.
YEAH?
I KIND OF KNOW FIRST-HAND, ACTUALLY.
EL, HAVE YOU BEEN THE ONE WRITING ME?
EL?
(Cell Phone)
HELLO?
ELLIE.
I HOPE YOU'RE CALLING TO TELL ME ABOUT YOUR SUDDEN CASE
OF AMNESIA.
NO.
I WISH I HAD AMNESIA.
DON'T TAKE REJECTION WELL.
ELLIE. TURN AROUND.
I DIDN'T REJECT YOU.
FELT LIKE IT.
WELL OF COURSE IT DID. YOU DIDN'T LET ME FINISH.
BUT YOU WERE -
I WAS GONNA MEET HAZEL TO TELL HER THAT -
WELL, TO TELL HER THAT SHE'S NOT MY TYPE.
I MEAN, I GO FOR COOL, ALTERNATIVE...
GIRLS LIKE ELLIE NASH.
OH.
I'M SUCH AN IDIOT.
NO.
IF YOU WERE, WOULD I STILL ASK YOU OUT?
FOR C,
AS IN COFFEE?
HOW WAS PHOTOGRAPHY CLUB?
FINE.
WHAT HAPPENED TO MY LOCKER?
I THOUGHT IT MIGHT CHEER YOU UP.
I, UH, HOPE I'M NOT INTERRUPTING.
YOU SAID YOU WANTED TO SIGN THIS?
YEAH, THIS IS THE PETITION PROTESTING GM FOODS, RIGHT?
GM FOODS?
STANDS FOR GENETICALLY MODIFIED.
DOES THAT -
MAKE THEM GOOD?
I'LL SEE YOU LATER, CRAIG.
I DON'T THINK YOU SHOULD TALK TO HER ANYMORE.
UH, SHE'S IN MY CLASS.
SO - WHAT'RE WE DOING FRIDAY NIGHT?
YOU'RE MOODY AGAIN.
IS IT YOUR LOCKER?
YOU DON'T LIKE IT?
NO, MANNY.
I'M SORRY -
BUT IT'S NOT MY LOCKER I DON'T LIKE.
IT'S YOU.