(CHEERING)
YES. YEAH.
GOOD GAME.
YEAH.
CAN YOU BELIEVE SPINNER SCORED THE WINNING GOAL?
PAIGE? PAIGE?
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I know I can make it through
♪ If I hold out
♪ If I do
♪ I know I can make it through
♪ Be the best
♪ The best I can be
♪ Hear what I say to you
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I can see it
♪ I know I can make it
♪ I know I can make it through.
IT AIN'T NEVER GONNA HAPPEN.
AIN'T NEVER? THAT'S A DOUBLE NEGATIVE.
YOU ARE A DOUBLE NEGATIVE.
AND YOU'RE RAINING ON MY LOVE PARADE.
HEY.
SPINNER. HEY.
YOU WERE TOTALLY AMAZING OUT THERE.
SEE? DOUBLE POSITIVE.
SO,YOU SAW ME WIN THE GAME?
MMM-HMM. YOU WERE GREAT.
SO. TOMORROW NIGHT.
UH, YOU WANNA HANG OUT WITH DEGRASSI'S NEW MVP?
MAYBE A MOVIE?
SATURDAY. RIGHT. I WAS GOING TO WORK ON MY M.I. PROJECT.
OH. COULDN'T YOU CAN'T DO THAT SUNDAY?
UM SURE... WHY NOT.
BUT SPINNER? NOTHING GORY, OKAY?
NO COPS, NO ALIENS, NO PSYCHOS WITH MASKS -
OKAY I PROMISE.
CHICK FLICK ALL THE WAY, OKAY.
HE'S SO IN LOVE WITH YOU.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WE'VE DONE STUFF TOGETHER BEFORE.
NOT LIKE THIS. SPINNER? CHICK FLICKS?
SO WHAT?
ANYWAY, I AM LOOKING TO DATE UP THIS YEAR, REMEMBER?
I DON'T CARE WHAT YOU SAY, SPINNER'S GOT A CRUSH.
HON, SPINNER AND I ARE JUST FRIENDS.
I KNEW YOU WERE MORE THAN FRIENDS!
I AM A WINNER ON THE FIELD AND WITH THE LADIES.
I COULDN'T HAVE PICKED A BETTER DAY TO ASK HER OUT.
PAIGE IS THE COOLEST GIRL IN GRADE NINE.
YOU ARE AWARE OF THAT.
OF COURSE.
YOU'RE THE MAN THESE DAYS -
BUT THE STAKES ARE STILL HIGH. PLANS?
I'M GOING WITH THE MOVIE OPTION.
CLASSIC, BUT CASUAL.
IT'S NOT BAD. BUT YOU GOTTA RENT, OKAY?
EMPTY REC ROOM, COMFORTABLE COUCH, HUH.
BEAUTIFUL. YOU, YOU ARE RIGHT.
YOU GOTTA LEAD THE HORSE TO WATER MY FRIEND.
YOU CAN'T MAKE HER DRINK. BUT YOU CAN MAKE HER THIRSTY.
HE'S HANDSOME, HE'S MATURE -
AND HE'S TOTALLY LEAVING!
PAIGE, YOUR LIFE IS CALLING.
AND I AM DEFINITELY GOING TO ANSWER.
I UH JUST WANTED TO SAY HI. PAIGE MICHALCHUK.
LET ME GUESS. CHEERLEADER?
HEAD CHEERLEADER. BUT UH, WE CALL IT SPIRIT SQUAD.
HEY SPIRIT, I'M DEAN.
I KNOW.
I MEAN - UH, YOU'RE THE COMPETITION -
KNOW YOUR ENEMY AND ALL THAT RIGHT?
DO YOU GUYS WANT TO COME TO A PARTY TOMORROW NIGHT?
HELP US - I DUNNO - CELEBRATE DEFEAT?
I DUNNO. WHERE?
122A PAPE. ANYTIME AFTER SEVEN.
WE SO NEED SOMETHING TO WEAR.
JT?!
YOU CALLED?
PHEW,OOH BUDDY. DEODORANT IS YOUR FRIEND.
IT'S YOUR LUNCH... FROM LAST WEEK?
HM. FROM SOLID TO LIQUID IN SEVEN DAYS.
FASCINATING.
OH, MY CLOWN WIG! THE POSSIBILITIES!
OH! HUMANE SOCIETY!
WE'RE NOT ANIMALS - WE'RE HUMAN BEINGS. AND THIS IS DISGUSTING!
IT'S A MAN-CAVE!
I, I, I, IT'S A TOXIC DUMP.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I VOLUNTEERED TO BE YOUR LOCKER MATE.
SHARE A LOCKER, DO SOMETHING FOR DEGRASSI,
RADITCH, OUR FRIEND.
IF YOU WANT US TO STAY FRIENDS, YOU'LL CLEAN THIS UP.
THEY'RE, LIKE, SIX FEET OFF THE GROUND.
FORGET IT.
TRUST ME. WE'RE GOOD.
IT'S SPINNER.
YOU DID CANCEL FOR TONIGHT, RIGHT?
YOU HAVE TO CANCEL.
"SPINNER. SORRY TO BAIL. GRANDMA IN HOSPITAL.
X O X. PAIGE."
THERE, WERE GOOD.
LOOK. I KNOW WHAT I WANT AND I WANT THOSE SHOES.
OKAY, SO I'VE GOT: TENDER EMOTIONS, LOVE AND STARDUST,
BREAKFAST IN THE SUN -
DUDE, IT'S A DATE. NOT A MARATHON, OKAY.
OKAY, I JUST NEED SOME CHOICES.
OO, HOO, HOO. FOOD, GLORIOUS FOOD. DORITOS.
OH UH, CHEETOS AND PRETZELS. HERE.
HEY, IT'S FROM PAIGE.
"DEAREST SPINNER-GOD.
EVER SINCE YOU SCORED THE WINNING GOAL, I -"
HEY DUDE, IT'S NOT FUNNY.
HER GRANDMOTHER'S IN THE HOSPITAL.
SHE'S CANCELING.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT, PARTNER.
I'VE GOT AN ALTERNATIVE. YOU TRUST ME. OKAY.
PAIGE YOU LOOK GREAT, RELAX.
HI DEAN.
SPIRIT, FRIEND. COME ON IN.
YOU DECIDED TO SHOW UP, AFTERALL.
YEAH WELL, AFTER YOUR TRAGIC LOSS
I FIGURED YOU COULD USE ALL THE CHEERING UP YOU COULD GET.
REALLY? YOU DID, HUH?
EDUARDO! WHERE YOU BEEN, MAN?
WE'RE TOTALLY OVER-DRESSED.
WE DO STAND OUT BUT THAT'S GOOD.
ALL WE NEED IS THE ATTITUDE TO BACK IT UP. WATCH THIS -
HE'S INTENSE. THAT ELECTROSLASH STUFF HE DOES WITH LUCKY...
AND W-ZONE IS A COMPLETE GENIUS.
OH. YEAH. HE'S TOTALLY GREAT.
I, PRETTY WELL LOVE ALL ELECTROSLASH.
DEAN ARE YOU A BIG TECHNO FAN?
I'D LOVE TO KNOW WHAT YOU THINK.
SURE. HOW ABOUT A DRINK FIRST?
PLEASE. I'M COMPLETELY PARCHED.
HEY. YOU MIGHT WANNA JUST CHILL.
EXCUSE ME?
JUST - HE'S A LITTLE OLD FOR YOU.
AND YOU'RE A LITTLE JEALOUS.
HEY SPIRIT. EVERYTHING COOL?
PERFECT.
IT'S ALL ABOUT THE RIGHT COMBINATION OF TASTES.
I HAVE YET TO DISCOVER THE PERFECT MATCH.
MARSHMALLOWS? IN KD?
JUST LIVING LIFE ON THE EDGE.
SO, I'VE BEEN PROCESSING WHAT YOU SAID YESTERDAY
AND I'VE DECIDED TO DO MY VERY BEST TO RESPECT YOUR NEEDS
WHEN IT COMES TO OUR LOCKER.
CHEESE-FLAVOURED CORN SNACK?
NO? AND WHILE SOME WOULD SAY
THAT CLEAN FREAKS LIKE YOURSELF ARE TOTALLY ANNOYING,
YOU'RE MY FRIEND AND I PLAN TO KEEP IT THAT WAY.
NOW, UM, WANT SOME.
YOUR WHOLE SQUAD WAS REALLY GREAT -
BUT YOU TOTALLY STOOD OUT.
I DID?
WHAT'RE YOU LOOKING AT?
YOUR EYES. ARE THEY GREEN OR BLUE?
IT DEPENDS ON THE LIGHT.
THE MOST AMAZING COLOURED EYES I'VE EVER SEEN.
THEY'RE VERY BEAUTIFUL.
YES?
LET'S JUST GO, OKAY?
NO WAY. I'M THIS CLOSE.
DEAN, UM, IT'S SO LOUD OUT HERE...
WANNA MAYBE GO SOMEPLACE A LITTLE MORE PRIVATE?
AFTER YOU...
YOU ARE SO CUTE.
I THINK MY FRIEND'S ROOM SHOULD BE QUIET.
I KINDA LIKE IT DARK.
BUT I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING - OW...
THERE'S THE BED. THERE'S THE DOOR. AND HERE'S THE PARTY.
WHY ARE WE WHISPERING?
BECAUSE MY FRIENDS ARE NEANDERTHALS.
WE DON'T WANT THEM TO HEAR US, RIGHT? OKAY?
OKAY.
YOU ARE SO ADORABLE.
I AM?
OH, YEAH. COME HERE.
IS THIS OKAY?
NO... YEAH.
JUST TAKE IT SLOW. OKAY?
DEAN I SAID SLOW?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING? I DON'T THINK SO.
DEAN. NO.
IT'S OKAY.
DEAN STOP, GET OFF.
IT'S ALL GOOD.
I SAID NO.
STOP. PLEASE.
DEAN GET OFF ME! STOP PLEASE. NO!
YOU ARE SO ADORABLE.
I AM?
OH YEAH.
HAZEL, GIVE ME A HEART ATTACK WHY DON'T YOU?
IT WAS A JOKE. WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
NOTHING. I'M FINE.
OK, WHAT'S THE BIG NEWS? DOES IT HAVE TO DO WITH DEAN?
MAYBE.
MAYBE? THEY WENT UPSTAIRS!
UPSTAIRS? LIKE ALONE?
UH, WHAT DO YOU THINK TER?
SO YOU DID?
YEAH. WE DID!
OKAY. THE "THEN AND NOW" PROJECT.
NOW PLEASE TELL ME YOU REMEMBER ME ASSIGNING THIS LAST WEEK.
TODAY, WE'RE GOING TO LOOK AT FIRST DRAFTS, TEXT ONLY.
THEN NEXT WEEK, WE'LL LAY IN OUR WEB GRAPHICS...
IT'S A, PRETTY SUCCINCT ESSAY, PAIGE.
YOU KNOW TEXT SOMETIMES INVOLVES THE ODD WORD.
I, UH... WORKED ALL WEEKEND.
BUT, SINCE I'M SUCH A DORK -
I FORGOT TO EMAIL IT TO MY SCHOOL ACCOUNT.
UM HMM.
IT WAS SO FASCINATING.
DID YOU KNOW PHARAOH PRINCESSES
MADE LIPSTICK OUT OF IRON OXIDE?
MMM? SOUNDS TOXIC.
LEAD EYELINER - HELLO.
NO WONDER THEY'RE ALL DEAD. TOMORROW, OKAY?
SOMEONE'S IN LOVE.
PLEASE. I'M NOT IN LOVE... DEAN'S NOT.
HE HASN'T CALLED.
SO? HE WILL.
HE WOULD HAVE BY NOW.
GIRL, GIVE HIM TIME.
HAZEL. YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND, HE DIDN'T JUST KISS ME... WE...
WHAT? PAIGE. YOU DIDN'T. YOU DID!
YOU DID IT WITH DEAN?
PAIGE, HAZEL? YOUR ASSIGNMENTS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH UH, YOU SNOOZE, YOU LOSE.
WHAT DOES THIS SAY TO YOU?
SEVERE MENTAL ILLNESS?
IT SAYS BOUNDARIES, JT. BOUNDARIES.
WHY DO YOU GET TO DECIDE WHAT MY BOUNDARIES ARE?
BECAUSE YOU HAVE NONE!
MY SIDE, YOUR SIDE.
FROM NOW ON, YOU WILL FOLLOW MY RULE.
IT'S MY WAY OR THE HIGHWAY.
MY WAY OR THE HIGHWAY.
OKAY I WAS THINKING STAR WARS AT THE CINESPHERE.
OKAY PAIGE IS GONNA FREAK!
WHAT, STAR WARS IS LAME?
NO. IT'S JUST - I'D COOL IT ON THE PAIGE FRONT.
SHE'S BUSY, MAN. I MEAN SHE'S GOT MEDIA IMMERSION
SHE'S GOT THE SPIRIT SQUAD...
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
NOTHING! FORGET ABOUT IT. I JUST HEARD... STUFF.
SHE HOOKED UP.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THAT PARTY WE WENT TO? SHE WAS THERE.
NO, NO NO NO. HER GRANDMA, HER GRANDMA WAS SICK.
I GOT THE, I GOT THE...
I...I DIDN'T SEE HER THERE.
YEAH UM, THAT'S 'CAUSE SHE WAS UPSTAIRS...
WITH DEAN FROM BARDELL.
PLEASE TAKE OUT YOUR NOVELS.
AS YOU READ QUIETLY, I'LL TAKE A LOOK AT YOUR JOURNALS.
HOW CAN YOU EVEN CONCENTRATE?
THIS IS VERY BIG NEWS, YOU KNOW!
IT'S NOT NEWS, OKAY?
HOW DID YOU KNOW IT WAS RIGHT?
IT'S NOT LIKE I PLANNED IT -
LADIES?
WAS IT TOTALLY ROMANTIC?
CAN WE TALK ABOUT THIS LATER? PLEASE?
I'M TRYING TO READ.
C'MON PAIGE, GIVE ME SOMETHING! I'M DYING HERE!
I'LL CHANGE SEATS IF YOU DON'T SHUT UP, OKAY?
PAIGE.
HEY, SPIN.
HOW'S YOUR GRANDMA?
WHAT?
YOU KNOW YOUR GRANDMA. THE ONE WHO WAS SICK ON SATURDAY NIGHT.
OH, UH SHE'S OKAY. THANKS.
AND DEAN? HOW'S HE DOING?
I KNOW WHAT HAPPENED, OKAY?
YEAH? WERE YOU IN THE ROOM WITH ME?
'CAUSE I DON'T THINK YOU WERE.
YOU LIED TO ME.
DON'T TOUCH ME. DON'T EVER TOUCH ME.
WHY NOT? EVERYBODY ELSE DOES.
JT!
WHAT?
YOU RUINED MY SWEATSHIRT!
IT WAS IN MY SPACE.
YOU THREW MY STUFF ON THE FLOOR!
IT WAS DISGUSTING!
IT WASN'T YOUR PROPERTY!
UH, BOYS.
WHAT SEEMS TO BE THE PROBLEM HERE?
PAIGE? I JUST SAW SPINNER.
HE WAS COMPLETELY OUT OF LINE.
IT WASN'T WHAT I THOUGHT, YOU KNOW.
FIRST TIME - I KINDA HOPED IT'D BE BEAUTIFUL OR SOMETHING.
IT'S SO STUPID.
IT'S NOT STUPID.
THOSE SHOES...I WANTED IT TO WORK.
I WANTED HIM TO WANT TO BE WITH ME.
HE DID!
YEAH. SURE.
HE'LL CALL YOU.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GET SO UPSET.
I DIDN'T EVEN WANT TO DO IT, HAZEL!
I SAID NO OVER AND OVER.
YOU SAID NO? AND HE DIDN'T LISTEN?
HE JUST - PUSHED ME DOWN HARDER.
HE DIDN'T STOP, HE WOULDN'T STOP.
PAIGE. HONEY. IF YOU SAID NO? THAT'S RAPE.
AND BOYS I WANT YOU TO KNOW
I APPRECIATE WHAT IT IS YOU ARE DOING FOR DEGRASSI
BY VOLUNTEERING TO SHARE. BUT YOU TWO ARE STUCK TOGETHER.
SO I WANT YOU TO REMEMBER WHAT THE THREE 'C''S ARE.
WHAT ARE THEY AGAIN?
COHABITATION REQUIRES COORDINATED COOPERATION.
EXCELLENT. VERY GOOD. SO, GET ALONG. END OF STORY.
MY PARENTS ARE GOING TO KILL ME FOR DOING THIS, BUT...
PAIGE. HEY WAIT UP.
WHATEVER HAPPENED TO GOING TO THE DOCTOR AFTER SCHOOL?
WHY WOULD I?
I DON'T KNOW - TO CHECK ON STDS, PREGNANCY...
HE WORE A CONDOM. SAFE SEX ALL THE WAY. I'M FINE.
WHAT DEAN DID WAS ILLEGAL. YOU KNOW THAT, RIGHT?
YEAH? AND WHAT ABOUT WHAT I DID?
YOU DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
SO I DIDN'T DRESS LIKE A SLUT? I DIDN'T DRINK?
I DIDN'T COME ON TO HIM IN FRONT OF THE WHOLE PARTY?
PAIGE.
I GUESS I DIDN'T ASK HIM TO GO UPSTAIRS EITHER?
YOU SAID NO.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
IT DOES MATTER. PAIGE, YOU HAVE TO TELL SOMEONE.
NO, I DON'T. I CAN DEAL WITH IT.
PAIGE, YOU WERE RAPED.
LOOK. MY BUSINESS. MY PROBLEM. I'M FINE.