"WHAT YOU DID CHANGED MY LIFE.
I STILL CAN'T SLEEP WITHOUT MY LIGHT ON.
SOMETIMES I LOOK UNDER THE BED, WORRIED YOU MIGHT BE THERE.
I MADE A MISTAKE GOING UPSTAIRS WITH YOU
BUT DEAN YOU MADE MORE THEN A MISTAKE.
YOU MADE A CHOICE."
AN IMPORTANT DISTINCTION.
WELL, YEAH.
BECAUSE THIS WHOLE THING BELONGS
ON MR. EVIL'S CONSCIENCE.
AND YOUR CONSCIENCE?
I SAID NO, SO HOW COULD I FEEL RESPONSIBLE?
YOU'VE STOPPED BLAMING YOURSELF.
YEAH. I HAVE.
EXCELLENT PROGRESS.
AND WE'LL KEEP WORKING ON IT.
SAME TIME, NEXT WEEK?
MISS SAUVE, THERAPY'S GREAT, BUT...
I STRONGLY RECOMMEND WE CONTINUE -
I'LL PENCIL YOU IN ANYWAY.
PENCIL AWAY. BUT IT IS A WASTE OF AN APPOINTMENT.
I'M OVER THIS.
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I know I can make it through
♪ If I hold out
♪ Be the best
♪ The best that I can be
♪ Hear what I say to you
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I can see it
♪ I know I can make it
♪ I know I can make it through
PAIGE! HELP!
I'M STUCK IN A BOX!
DOES IT SAY "CAUTION: FREAK INSIDE"?
WHAT?! CAN'T HEAR YOU. BOX!
THANKS.
A LITTLE MIME MAGIC FOR MY MASCOT ROUTINE.
YOU LIKE?
I ALWAYS LIKE YOUR STUFF.
JUST MAKE SURE YOU BRING THAT MAGIC
TO TOMORROW'S BASKETBALL TOURNAMENT.
WAIT A MINUTE, DID YOU JUST TALK TO ME
WITHOUT SAYING MIDGET, TWERP OR DWEEB?
I THINK I DID. LUCKY YOU.
HEY BOYS.
OH, HEY, PAIGE.
SPIN? I LOVE THE ROOTS. TRES COOL.
IT'S A COMPETITIVE MARKET.
BUT UNISEX COLOGNE DOUBLES OUR BUYERS.
'SHARE YOUR SCENT. SING A DUET.'
I'M IMPRESSED.
YOU GUYS THOUGHT THROUGH YOUR MOCK PRODUCT AND CAMPAIGN WELL.
AND FINISHED FIRST.
SO - TIME TO GO ON TO PART TWO OF THE PROJECT
AND FILM YOUR AD.
IT'LL BE GREAT. TOTAL CHEESE MUSICAL.
FUN AND FABULOUS.
SOUNDS GREAT. CAMERA'S ALL YOURS.
YOU'RE SURE YOU DON'T WANT TO DIRECT?
POSITIVE. LISTEN, I TRUST YOU.
YOUR LOVE BRINGS TEARS TO MY EYES.
JUST WISH EVERYONE COULD BE AS LUCKY.
NICE ONE, BOYFRIEND.
WHY, THANK YOU, GIRLFRIEND.
(Cheering) BLUE AND GOLD
SHOOT FOR TWO!
LET'S GO!
(Cheering)
THAT WAS GREAT GUYS. TAKE A BREAK.
PAIGE, THAT CHOREOGRAPHY KILLS.
I TRY.
THE CROWD TOMORROW WON'T KNOW WHAT HIT THEM.
SPINNER. FINALLY DECIDED TO JOIN THE SPIRIT SQUAD?
DREAM ON.
WE JUST GOT THE FINAL TEAM'S NAME IN FOR TOMORROW'S TOURNEY.
BARDELL.
YOUR BOYFRIEND'S BACK.
HAZEL. HE'S COMING TO MY SCHOOL.
PAIGE, BACK SO SOON?
YEAH.
I WANTED TO ASK ABOUT PRESSING CHARGES... AGAINST DEAN.
WOW - OKAY.
WE'LL HAVE SET UP A MEETING WITH YOUR MOM.
NO, I KNOW. BUT WHAT ACTUALLY HAPPENS?
WELL, THE POLICE WILL GET INVOLVED,
YOU'LL PROBABLY BE ASKED TO TESTIFY.
AND THEN WE SEND HIM TO JAIL?
IF THERE'S ENOUGH EVIDENCE, YES.
WELL I HAD ALL THOSE DOCTOR'S EXAMS.
AND THEY REASSURED US YOU WERE INJURY-FREE,
AND THAT YOU HADN'T DEVELOPED ANY STD'S, BUT-
THEY'RE NOT EVIDENCE.
UNFORTUNATELY, PAIGE,
THE LONGER YOU WAIT TO REPORT,
THE LESS PHYSICAL EVIDENCE THERE IS.
WE DON'T HAVE A DNA SAMPLES, OR PHOTOS OF BRUISING.
SO, WHAT?
I GO TO COURT, TELL THE TRUTH - AND I COULD STILL LOSE?
POSSIBLY.
BUT THAT'S SO UNFAIR!
HOLD ON...
DON'T GET TOO DISCOURAGED.
IF THIS IS WHAT YOU WANT,
THEN WE WILL MAKE THE BEST CASE WE CAN.
FORGET IT. I JUST THOUGHT I'D ASK.
WOW. THAT'S BRIGHT.
MARCO'S OBSESSED WITH BOLLYWOOD MUSICALS.
SEEMED FUN.
A SURPRISE FOR LA SIGNORINA...
IT'S MY MOM'S EGGPLANT PARMESAN.
I KNOW HOW MUCH YOU LIKE IT SO...
WOW. THANKS.
AND THERE'S ENOUGH HERE FOR THE BOTH OF YOU -
SO I'LL LEAVE YOU LADIES TO YOUR GIRL TALK.
THIS IS THE PERFECT VEGETARIAN DISH.
FROM YOUR PERFECT BOYFRIEND.
REALLY, COULD YOU TWO BE MORE MEANT FOR EACH OTHER?
HEY, COME ON, WIND-TUNNEL MAN? THAT'S COMIC GOLD.
HELLO, I THOUGHT MIMES WERE SUPPOSED TO BE SILENT.
PAIGE, ARE YOU MAD AT ME?
DID I DO SOMETHING WRONG, LIKE AT PRACTICE?
NO, FOR ONCE IT'S NOT ABOUT YOU.
IT'S ABOUT ME, NOT CHEERING TOMORROW.
WHAT? WE NEED YOU.
TOO BAD. DEAL WITH IT.
WHY?
IT'S REALLY NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
IF I'M SWEATING IN SOME MASCOT SUIT
AND YOU'RE HOME WATCHING TV - IT IS MY BUSINESS.
SOMEONE'S COMING TOMORROW.
FROM BARDELL.
AND I - CAN'T SEE HIM.
DID HE DUMP YOU OR SOMETHING?
OR SOMETHING...
WELL JUST, GIVE HIM SOME OF YOUR WORLD-FAMOUS ATTITUDE.
SHOW HIM WHO'S BOSS.
IS THAT WHY YOU'RE STALKING ME? TO GIVE ME A PEP TALK?
SO THEN YOU LEAN IN, CLOSE, ROMANTIC -
AND YOU SAY YOUR LINE.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S DO IT.
ACTION!
CUT! YOU'RE OUT OF FRAME.
WELL IT'S HARD TO KNOW WHERE TO STOP WITHOUT HEATHER HERE.
I'LL STAND IN, OKAY?
ACTION.
GREAT. NOW, ARM BEHIND ME,
RAISE THE PERFUME, AND SAY...
'SHARE YOUR SCENT - SING A DUET.'
YEAH, THAT WAS GREAT, LET'S MOVE ON.
(ALARM CLOCK)
ARE YOU GOING TO BE OKAY?
I'M STAYING FAR AWAY FROM HIM.
HEY PAIGE, ARE WE DOING THAT ELEVATOR FORMATION FIRST?
OR... PAIGE?
LET'S GO.
SPIRIT. HOLD UP.
SO WHAT'S IN TODAY'S PLAN?
A LITTLE RAH-RAH CHEERING,
OR ANOTHER SERENADE FROM YOUR LITTLE GIRL-BAND?
THIS IS MY SCHOOL.
AND I DON'T WANT TO SEE YOU, OR TALK TO YOU AGAIN.
LIGHTEN UP. WE HAD FUN.
FUN?
YOU THINK WHAT YOU DID TO ME WAS FUN?!
THE NIGHT OF THE PARTY.
YOU WERE THERE.
WHO DID SPIRIT COME TO SEE?
RIGHT. ME.
I SAID NO -
EVERYONE THERE SAW A GIRL WHO WANTED IT.
BAD.
AND SHE GOT IT.
GO SHAKE YOUR LITTLE POMPOMS AND LOOK CUTE, SPIRIT.
I GOT A GAME.
SO I WANT TO MOVE IT OVER.
SO LETS DO THAT.
YEAH OKAY.
HEY, MARCO.
HEY.
SO YOU'RE READY FOR YOUR DIRECTING DEBUT?
YEAH.
AND I'VE GOT A BIT OF A NEW DIRECTION.
WHO DIED?
IT'S CALLED MINIMALISM.
I'D CALL IT BORING.
WHAT HAPPENED TO HEATHER? AND ALL THE DANCING GIRLS?
UNNECESSARY.
DUET WAS GETTING LOST IN ALL THE GLITZ.
OKAY.
IF YOU SAY SO, WE'LL DO IT THIS WAY.
YOU'RE THE DIRECTOR.
YOU'RE FINE WITH IT?
YEAH. WHATEVER YOU WANT. HONEST.
WE RULE! THE TOURNAMENT IS OURS!
BARDELL HAS ABSOLUTELY NO CHANCE.
JIMMY SHOULD CALM DOWN. BARDELL'S A TOUGH TEAM.
WE CAN BEAT THEM.
YOU THINK SO, SPIRIT? GOOD LUCK.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
WHAT'S WITH HER?
IS SHE STILL HUNG UP ON DEAN?
NO.
COME ON, HAZEL.
I WAS AT THAT PARTY. I KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
AND WHAT'S THAT?
HE AND PAIGE...
PAIGE DUMPED ME, THEN DID IT WITH HIM.
WHAT IF IT WASN'T LIKE THAT?
WHAT IF SHE SAID NO?
GOOD ONE, HAZEL.
BUT THE ONLY ONE SHE SAYS NO TO IS ME.
DUET. WE ARE AS ONE. WE - SORRY...
MARCO! THAT'S THE SEVENTH TAKE.
I'M SORRY.
IT'S JUST THAT, WHEN I SAY "ABSORB EACH OTHER"?
IT SOUNDS LIKE WE'RE SELLING TAMPONS OR SOMETHING.
ARE YOU MAKING FUN OF MY WRITING?
BUT IT DOESN'T EVEN GO WITH OUR WHOLE CONCEPT.
A DUET WITH ONE PERSON.
I CAN GO FIND SOMEONE RIGHT NOW
AND WE COULD DO THE DANCE LIKE BEFORE.
NO, YOU CAN'T.
I SAID YES TO THIS WHOLE WEIRD CONCEPT,
BUT EVER SINCE THEN YOU'VE BEEN TREATING ME LIKE YOUR SLAVE.
FUNNY CAUSE THAT'S HOW I ALWAYS FEEL AROUND YOU.
YOU MAY NOT LIKE WHAT YOU'RE DOING HERE,
BUT IS WAY BETTER THEN SOME FLAMING-
SO THAT'S WHAT THIS IS ABOUT.
THE FACT THAT I CAN'T BE WHO YOU WANT.
CAN'T OR WON'T?
YOU TOLD SPINNER?
I WANTED HIM TO UNDERSTAND -
WELL, WHAT DID HE SAY?
HE DIDN'T BELIEVE ME.
HE THINKS I "WANTED" IT, RIGHT?
I'M GOING HOME.
PAIGE-
YOU WERE RIGHT, I SHOULD'VE STAYED THERE.
DEAN WINS AGAIN.
HEY, PAIGE!
CAN'T WAIT FOR HALF-TIME - I'M NAILING THAT FLIP.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
UM - EARLIER.
I SAW YOU AND DEAN TALKING OUTSIDE...
HE STARTED TALKING TO ME.
NO PROBLEM, JUST UH-
JUST DON'T BE ALONE WITH HIM, OKAY?
SOMEONE WARNED ME ABOUT HIM ONCE AND I SHOULD'VE LISTENED.
HE SEEMS NICE -
HE IS NICE.
MANNY, WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
YOU TALKED TO HIM FOR FIVE MINUTES.
I KNOW YOU GUYS HAD A DATE.
AND I KNOW HE NEVER CALLED YOU BACK.
AND I KNOW YOU'RE JEALOUS.
GET OVER IT.
WHERE'S PAIGE?
I DON'T KNOW.
SPOTS IS ON THE CASE.
OH FEARLESS LEEEEEA-DER!
GO AWAY.
PAIGE, YOU SAY THAT ALL THE TIME,
BUT WE BOTH KNOW YOU DON'T MEAN IT.
YEAH, WELL, THIS TIME I DO.
PAIGE, THE SQUAD NEEDS YOU -
LEAVE ME ALONE!
IT'S JUST SOME STUPID GUY, RIGHT?
OH, YOU MEAN DEAN?
BARDELL'S RESIDENT SPORTS HERO AND-
AND RAPIST?
YEAH. HE RAPED ME.
AND NO ONE IN THE WORLD
SEEMS TO BE ABLE TO DO ANYTHING ABOUT IT.
JT!
FOUL - BARDELL.
TOO MUCH FOR YOU, MR. RAPIST?
TIME OUT, NUMBER TWELVE, ON THE BENCH.
GAME SUSPENSION.
AND THE MASCOT -
IS GOING TO THE PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE. NOW.
PAIGE, WHAT'S GOING ON?
NOTHING.
JT, IN A MASCOT OUTFIT, ATTACKING DEAN?
THAT'S NOT NOTHING.
PAIGE, JUST -
SPIN, COULD YOU PLEASE -!
SOMETHING HAPPENED TO YOU.
I JUST GOT WHAT I ASKED FOR. RIGHT?
HE TOOK IT TOO FAR. LIKE HAZEL SAID. RIGHT?
DIDN'T HE?
HEY!
YOU'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
YOUR MASCOT CAME AT ME.
YOU THINK THAT'S WHAT THIS IS?
SPINNER! STOP.
WHAT! HE DESERVES IT.
SPINNER PLEASE?!
THE WATER BOY YOUR BOYFRIEND?
I HAVE ONE THING TO SAY TO YOU, DEAN.
GET READY, BECAUSE I AM COMING AFTER YOU THIS TIME.
NOT LIKE SPINNER OR THE MASCOT -
FOR REAL.
"DUET. THE PERFECT BLEND."
SO MUCH FOR US "BEING AS ONE," HUH?
I'M SORRY.
EL, YOU'RE MY BEST FRIEND.
BUT IF THAT'S NOT ENOUGH...
IT'S REALLY HARD, MARCO.
PRETENDING TO BE SOMETHING -
SOMETHING YOU'RE NOT. I KNOW.
BUT DID YOU EVER THINK ABOUT HOW HARD IT WOULD BE FOR ME?
ARE YOU STILL CONFUSED?
NO.
ELLIE, I'M GAY.
AND YOU AND ME -
WILL ALWAYS JUST BE FRIENDS.
YOU'RE SURE?
MOM AND I TALKED. I WANT TO PRESS CHARGES.
GOOD.
NOW IT'S A LEGAL MATTER.
SO NO MORE CONVERSATIONS WITH DEAN.
OKAY?
FINE BY ME.
SO - TUESDAY?
THREE O'CLOCK SHARP. YOU CAN WRITE IT IN PEN THIS TIME.
I WANT TO SCARE HIM, MISS SAUVE.
SO BAD, HE WON'T EVEN THINK OF DOING THIS TO SOMEONE ELSE.
HEY, WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
SHOULDN'T YOU BE IN YOUR HAIR-NET?
I TRADED A SHIFT
SO I COULD SPEND LUNCH WITH YOU.
WOW. LUCKY ME.
WE'RE NOT ALL LIKE DEAN, YOU KNOW.
SOME OF US ARE GOOD GUYS.
I KNOW.
THAT'S WHY I WANTED TO ASK.
YEAR-END DANCE - YOU GOING WITH ANYONE?
NO.
SO THEN - GO WITH ME.
I OWE YOU A DATE ANYWAY, RIGHT?
YEAH. YOU DO.