SO, AH, THIS IS THE PALACE.
I ALWAYS WONDERED WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE IN HERE.
YEAH.
OK, SO... CHEMISTRY.
I HATE CHEMISTRY.
RIGHT, PERIODIC TABLE. WHO CREATED-
CAREFUL. THAT CHAIR'S BROKEN.
OH.
UM, YOU GOTTA LEAN FORWARD.
OKAY.
YEAH, SO THE PERIODIC TABLE.
I DON'T CARE. LOOK, TELL THAT KNOB I DON'T GIVE A FLYING--
LOOK, HE WANTS TO TALK TO ME THAT WAY, THEN I QUIT.
AND THAT'S IT.
HEY. SORRY.
NICE TO SEE YOU.
HOW'S IT GOING, EM?
GOOD.
WELCOME TO OUR AH, VERY, VERY HUMBLE ABODE.
WHAT YOU GUYS DOING?
AH, WE'RE JUST DOING SOME-
SOME CHEMISTRY UH?
THAT'S COOL. DON'T GO BUILD NO BOMBS. SO, UM-
YEAH, UM, I GUESS WE'RE JUST GOING TO GO TO THE LIBRARY THEN.
THAT'S COOL, YEAH. YEAH, EM, GOOD TO SEE YOU.
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF, ALRIGHT?
YOU TOO.
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I know I can make it through
♪ If I hold out
♪ Be the best
♪ The best that I can be
♪ Hear what I say to you
♪ What ever it takes
♪ I know I can make it
♪ I know I can make it through
JIMMY, SEAN?
NOW THAT'S THE KIND OF TEAMWORK
I WANT TO SEE IN THE REGIONALS GENTLEMEN.
NO PROBLEM.
YOU GOT IT COACH.
GOOD WORK.
MAN, MAN YOU GUYS, YOU REALLY DO PLAY GREAT TOGETHER,
LIKE VINCE AND JYD.
OH, WAIT. DID I JUST BREAK THE-
'DON'T TALK TO SEAN AND JIMMY AT THE SAME TIME' RULE?
SHUT UP, SPINNER.
NO, YOU SHUT UP.
I MEAN OKAY, YOU TWO, YOU HAD A FIGHT, A LONG, LONG TIME AGO.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST LET IT GO.
ASK HIM.
I'M HAVING A PARTY TONIGHT,
TO CELEBRATE MAKING THE REGIONALS.
AND YOU CAN BRING EMMA IF YOU WANT TO.
COOL.
AH, YOU TWO, YOU'VE MADE ME VERY, VERY HAPPY!
DUDE, DUDE. ARMPITS - NEAR THE FACE.
SO IS SEAN EXCITED ABOUT TONIGHT?
EM, YOU DIDN'T TELL HIM, DID YOU?
IF I TOLD HIM LAST WEEK,
HE WOULD HAVE WORRIED HIMSELF INTO A COMA.
WELL, ENOUGH'S ENOUGH, YOU HAVE TO TELL HIM,
LIKE RIGHT NOW.
SEAN!
EMMA.
HI. UM, ARE YOU BUSY TONIGHT?
WHY AM I GETTING THAT WEIRD, SCARY VIBE?
UM, BECAUSE, AAHH. I KNOW THIS SOUNDS AWFUL,
BUT MY PARENTS WERE WONDERING
IF MAYBE YOU WANTED TO COME TO DINNER?
NO!
BUT YOU HAVE TO. I TOLD THEM YOU'RE COMING.
EMMA, WE HAVE JIMMY'S PARTY TONIGHT. WE WERE INVITED.
YEAH, I KNOW. BUT, I THINK MY PARENTS
WILL BE A LITTLE MORE DISAPPOINTED
IF YOU DON'T SHOW UP, THAN JIMMY WILL.
OOHH. HEY, ONE WORD FOR YOU -
CHATORO.
CHATU -? EMMA!
IT'S A KIND OF SUSHI, YOU KNOW, RAW FISH.
YEAH, I KNOW.
ANYWAY, MY MOM MAKES IT FOR SPECIAL OCCASIONS,
SO YOU HAVE TO COME.
WE'LL GO TO JIMMY'S AFTER, I PROMISE.
OH, PLEASE? PLEASSSSEE?
CHECKING OUT ASHLEY, HUH?
DUDE, COULD YOU BE MORE PREDICTABLE?
LOOK, ASH HAS CHANGED.
SHE'S NOT THE SAME GIRL HE WAS LAST YEAR.
OH, YEAH, YEAH, I KNOW. SHE'S BECOME A VAMPIRE!
I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT HER STYLE.
I MEAN SHE'S MORE DOWN TO EARTH.
YEAH.
OH, TER, I'M HAVING A PARTY TONIGHT AT MY HOUSE.
CAN YOU MAKE IT?
TOTALLY!
TELL ASH SHE CAN COME TOO. IF SHE WANTS.
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
AH, ASH TOO, NO BIG DEAL.
HM, UH, MY ARMPITS SMELL.
A VOTE. HANDS OR FEET?
ARE WE SUPPOSED TO UNDERSTAND WHAT THAT MEANS?
IT MEANS - MY WEEKEND AT THE SPA WITH MOM
INCLUDES EITHER A FREE MANICURE OR PEDICURE. MY CHOICE.
YOU'RE MISSING JIMMY'S PARTY FOR A PEDICURE?
NO, FOR A SPA WEEKEND.
IT'S MORE FUN THAN A ROOMFUL OF NEANDERTHALS.
SO EL? HOW ABOUT YOU?
I'D HAVE MORE FUN SCULPTING MY EARWAX.
WHY, ARE YOU GOING?
NO... I DON'T THINK SO.
ASH, YOU SO WANT TO GO.
BUT HE DIDN'T REALLY INVITE ME.
HE JUST SORT-OF INVITED ME.
I'VE SEEN THE WAY HE LOOKS AT YOU. HE STILL LIKES YOU.
I'M NOT SURE I BELIEVE THAT, TER.
WELL, ONLY ONE WAY TO FIND OUT.
SEAN, IT'S JUST A JOB, OKAY?
EVERYTHING'S GOING TO BE ALRIGHT.
YOU KNOW WHAT? THAT'S WHAT DAD SAID. AND IT NEVER WAS.
I KNOW. I KNOW, BUT ME AND YOU,
WE'RE NOT MOM AND DAD, RIGHT?
NO? WE LIVE LIKE THEM. YOU'RE OUT OF WORK.
YEAH, MONEY'S IMPORTANT SEAN, BUT SO'S MY PRIDE.
YOU KNOW WHAT TRACKER? YOU SOUND JUST LIKE DAD,
WHENEVER HE LOST HIS JOB OR WHENEVER HE QUIT
OR WHENEVER HE GOT FIRED AND HE JUST-
YEAH, EXCEPT FOR THEN HE'D GO AND TAKE ALL OF OUR MONEY
AND BLOW IT ON BOOZE.
YOU SEE ME DOING THAT?
NO.
THAT'S RIGHT.
LOOK, I'VE GOT A JOB INTERVIEW LINED UP FOR TOMORROW.
DOES THAT SOUND LIKE DAD?
AREN'T YOU SPECIAL.
I'M TRYING.
WHERE YOU GOING WITH MY PICKLED HERRING, PUNK?
TONIGHT I, I HAVE DINNER WITH EMMA'S PARENTS.
WELL, ISN'T THAT NICE.
SAY HELLO TO THE FAMILY FOR ME.
EM, NERVOUS?
NOT FOR ME, FOR SEAN.
YOU GUYS AREN'T GOING TO GRILL HIM, RIGHT?
JUST THE OCTOPUS. BUT I HEAR YOU, OKAY?
BLACK. AAAAHHH.
JUST RELAX.
YOU KNOW, I WAS READING THAT THE AVERAGE SUMO WRESTLER
WEIGHS AROUND FOUR HUNDRED POUNDS.
AND ONE OF THE BEST TIPPED THE SCALE AT SEVEN HUNDRED POUNDS.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
THAT'S BECAUSE THEY EAT LIKE A TON OF RICE,
MORNING, NOON AND NIGHT.
MMM. SPEAKING OF RICE,
I THINK I'M GOING TO HAVE SOME MORE OF THE KAMABOKO.
SO. SEAN. I HEAR YOU'RE QUITE THE BASKETBALL STAR?
AH, I'M OKAY I GUESS.
NOW DON'T BE MODEST.
I SAW YOU TEARING UP THE COURT THE OTHER DAY.
YOUR PARENTS MUST BE PROUD.
OH, EMMA, CAN YOU PASS THE NEGI TORO, PLEASE?
YEAH, SURE.
THEY'RE IN WASAGA BEACH. I LIVE WITH MY BROTHER.
OH, RIGHT.
AH, MOM - UM, THE CALIFORNIA ROLL LOOKS GREAT.
WHAT DOES YOUR BROTHER DO?
WELL HE'S-
SNAKE!
IT'S ALL RIGHT. EMMA, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
HE INSTALLS SIDE-VIEW MIRRORS ON MINI-VANS.
OH, HE'S AN AUTO-WORKER. IT'S A NOBLE PROFESSION.
YEAH. HE QUIT YESTERDAY.
OH... I'M SORRY TO HEAR THAT.
UM, YOU GUYS MIND IF I GET SOME WATER?
NO, NOT AT ALL. HELP YOURSELF.
YOU GUYS - I THOUGHT I ASKED YOU NOT TO DO THIS.
IT'S JUST THAT CHILDREN
SHOULDN'T HAVE TO LIVE WITH THAT KIND OF STRESS.
DOES ANYBODY ELSE WANT ANY WATER?
NO, I THINK WE'RE ALL FINE.
OKAY.
SO, SEAN. HAVE YOU SEEN ANY GOOD MOVIES LATELY?
MM - NO.
OH. I REALLY LIKE THEM. MR. SIMPSON, SNAKE AND I,
WE LIKE THEM. GOING TO THEM. DON'T WE?
YEAH, YES. A LOT.
POPCORN, SODA... GODZILLA.
COOL.
EMMA, YOU WANT SOME MORE PIE?
YEAH, SURE.
OOOHHH! OOHH!
I'M SORRY! I'M SORRY. HERE, LET ME HELP YOU CLEAN IT.
NO, IT'S OKAY. NO REALLY, I'LL JUST GO CHANGE.
YOU KNOW, I FEEL LIKE SOME COFFEE.
I'M GOING TO PUT A POT ON.
SO AH, SNAKE AND I ARE REALLY GLAD THAT YOU COULD COME.
IT'S GIVEN US A CHANCE TO GET TO KNOW EACH OTHER A BIT MORE.
NO PROBLEM.
ANYTIME.
HEY - WHY DON'T I PACK YOU UP SOME LEFT-OVERS?
YOU ALREADY MADE ME DINNER.
GIVE YOU A NICE HOME-COOKED MEAL.
BECAUSE I DON'T GET NICE, HOME-COOKED MEALS AT HOME?
SEAN, WE JUST HAVE EXTRA.
FOR A WELFARE CASE.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I WAS SAYING.
SEAN?!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
SEAN!
I SHOULDN'T BE HERE...
SPINNER!
HEY! TERRI. ASH. GREAT, YOU CAME.
WHERE'S PAIGE?
AT THE SPA. BUT WE'RE HERE.
OH-HO, YEAH. GREAT, THAT - OOH-
YOU SHOULD GO FIND JIMMY.
I ALREADY HAVE.
SO. YOU CAME.
I CAME.
THAT'S GOOD.
GOOD.
HEY JIMMY!
SORRY. I GOT GUESTS TO ATTEND TO. UM, I'LL CATCH YOU LATER.
WOW. I GUESS HE REALLY DIDN'T WANT ME TO COME AFTER ALL.
I KNOW THE FEELING.
HEY, I-
WHERE'S SEAN?
HE UH - HE LEFT.
WHAT? WHY?
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
NOTHING. I OFFERED HIM LEFTOVERS.
HE TOTALLY MISUNDERSTOOD.
AND THAT'S ALL. HONEST.
YEAH, REALLY.
EMMA -
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
TO FIND HIM.
(DOOR BELL)
WHOAH! WHAT'S GOING ON? THERE'S A PARTY HERE.
OH, I THOUGHT YOU WEREN'T COMING MAN.
NO, I AM. THIS IS A PARTY. I LOVE PARTIES! YEAH!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
YEAH, A PARTY! WHOO, HOO, HOOO!
HEY MAN, YOU KNOW, GOT TO GET TO MY LADIES, TEND TO THEM.
SEE YOU LATER.
SWEET NIGHT. HE'S GOT LADIES!
SO, WHAT'S GOING ON BUDDY? WHAT DO YOU SAY?
YEAH, UM,
HAVE YOU BEEN DRINKING?
NO. MAYBE A LITTLE.
COME ON MAN, LET'S GO.
NO, INTRODUCE ME TO SOME PEOPLE. JIMMY! WHAT'S GOING ON?
HEY. YOU MADE IT.
YEAH! HA, HA!
WHAT'S UP? WHAT'S UNDER-? UH, NAPKINS, I NEED NAPKINS.
CATCH YOU BOYS LATER?
YEAH.
SO AH, WHERE'S EMMA?
EMMA? AH, SHE'S AT HOME. WE'RE THROUGH.
WHAT? YOU GUYS JUST GOT BACK TOGETHER.
I KNOW, ALL RIGHT?
BUT HER MOM CALLED ME A TOTAL WELFARE CASE OR SOMETHING
SO I TOLD HER OFF AND I LEFT.
I TOTALLY FREAKED OUT AND WHATEVER, OKAY. IT'S OVER.
AND OBVIOUSLY EMMA'S NEVER GOING TO FORGIVE ME.
YOU DON'T KNOW THAT. CALL HER.
NO MAN. IT'S OVER. ALL RIGHT?
SEAN, JUST PICK UP THE PHONE.
OKAY?
OKAY.
YOU COMING?
YEAH, JUST GIVE ME A MINUTE.
YOU, PLUS ME - DESTINY.
OKAY, LET'S GO.
ASH! YOU CAN'T GO.
UH, YES I CAN.
NO, NO! WE DIDN'T TALK YET.
YOU'VE GOT A LOT OF GUESTS.
YOU'RE THE GUEST I WANT TO BE WITH.
I CAN STICK AROUND FOR A BIT.
THAT'S GREAT.
SEAN! SEAN!
HERE YOU ARE.
I'M SO SORRY ABOUT MY MOM. WHAT DID SHE SAY EXACTLY?
EXACTLY?
YEAH. I WANT TO CALL HER ON IT. WHAT DID SHE SAY?
SHE SAID THE TRUTH, ALL RIGHT? SHE SAID THE TRUTH.
SEAN ARE YOU DRUNK? WHERE DID YOU GET THAT?
MY HOST, JIMMY BROOKS. AND IT'S TIME FOR A REFILL.
SEAN!
NO, EMMA! CALM DOWN!
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO GIVE ME FOR IT?
SEAN! NO!
SEAN!
SO YOU COME TO MY HOUSE TO STEAL MY PARENTS' BOOZE?
JIMMY, COME ON MAN.
YOUR PARENTS ARE SO RICH THEY WON'T EVEN KNOW.
JUST GET OUT OF HERE.
AT LEAST LET ME CLEAN IT UP--
JUST GET OUT!
AGH!
HERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT? UM, TERRI'S WAITING.
I DON'T FEEL GOOD. I HAVE TO GO HOME.
WHY DO YOU EVEN BOTHER?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I'M JUST A BIG, STUPID LOSER.
MY PARENTS ARE DRUNKS. MY BROTHER'S OUT OF WORK.
JUST A BIG STUPID LOSER, LIKE THEM.
YEAH, SO IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT TO SAY?
DO YOU WANT ME TO CALL YOU A BIG, STUPID LOSER, SEAN?
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
WHO ARE YOU CALLING?
MY MOM.
WHAT? NO, HANG UP.
MOM? YOU KNOW YOU SAID IF I EVER NEEDED,
YOU'D PICK ME UP, NO QUESTIONS ASKED?
GREAT. WE'RE OUTSIDE JIMMY'S.
HOW'S YOUR HAND?
I'LL SURVIVE.
I'M SORRY ABOUT THE OTHER NIGHT.
AH, THE PARTY GOT OUT OF HAND. I GOT SERIOUS FLAK THOUGH.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEAN. I MEAN,-
OH. AH, LOOK, I GUESS IT'S KIND OF MY FAULT
BECAUSE I WEIRDED YOU-
SO NOW WE'RE EVEN.
HEY, JIMMY -
SEAN!
SEAN, SEAN, WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
BECAUSE I SCREWED UP, ALL RIGHT EMMA?
ONCE. EVERYBODY SCREWS UP ONCE.
EMMA, HOMEROOM IS ABOUT TO START.
I KNOW, BUT THIS IS MORE IMPORTANT. SO STOP.
THINGS ARE ALWAYS GONNA BE LIKE THIS.
LIKE WHAT?
ME SCREWING UP. IT'S IN MY BLOOD.
IT'S IN YOUR HEAD. AND THAT'S ALL.
YOUR MOM AND SIMPSON AREN'T GOING BE AS FORGIVING.
DID MY MOM GIVE YOU THE THIRD DEGREE?
NO...
I MEAN, IF SHE HAS TO DRIVE YOU HOME DRUNK A SECOND TIME,
IT MIGHT BE A DIFFERENT STORY.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT THAT, ALL RIGHT?
TRACKER GAVE ME A LECTURE AND I JUST DON'T-
OKAY, BUT THIS ISN'T ABOUT TRACKER,
OR YOUR PARENTS, OR MY PARENTS.
THIS IS ABOUT YOU AND ME.
SEAN, I LIKE YOU.
I LIKE YOU TOO.