ARE YOU SURE YOU DON'T WANT POPCORN?
IF I EAT POPCORN, I'LL GET GREASY FINGERS.
AND GREASY FINGERS MEAN A SLIMY KEYBOARD.
MMMMMMM, POPCORN!
MS. KWAN? POETRY ASSIGNMENT?
YOU'LL GET IT DONE. COME ON.
OKAY...
SO, YOU KNOW THAT MR. SIMPSON AND I HAVE BEEN FRIENDS
FOR A LONG TIME.
YEAH, AND HE'S BEEN HERE ALL THE TIME LATELY.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
THAT'S SORTA WHAT THIS IS ABOUT.
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
IT MEANS THAT WE'RE MORE THAN JUST FRIENDS, EM.
WE'VE BEEN DATING EACH OTHER.
MR. SIMPSON? HE'S MY TEACHER!
♪ WHAT EVER IT TAKES
♪ I KNOW I CAN MAKE IT THROUGH
♪ IF I HOLD OUT
♪ BE THE BEST
♪ THE BEST THAT I CAN BE
HEAR WHAT I SAY TO YOU
♪ WHAT EVER IT TAKES
♪ I KNOW I CAN MAKE IT
♪ I KNOW I CAN MAKE IT THROUGH
SO, DID YOU GET YOUR POETRY DONE?
NO.
IT'S DUE TODAY!
I KNOW, BUT - SOME STUFF CAME UP. WITH MY MOM.
SERIOUS STUFF?
SHE WANTED TO TALK TO ME ABOUT HER NEW BOYFRIEND.
AND YOU DIDN'T CALL ME? WHO IS IT?
GOT MYSELF A BIT OF A STICKY SITUATION HERE.
THAT'S WHO.
SIMPSON. MY MOM IS SEEING SIMPSON.
WHAT?!
IT'S NO BIG DEAL. REALLY.
EMMA. YOUR MOM IS DATING YOUR TEACHER.
THAT'S HUGE!
I KNOW.
AND I'D LIKE YOU TO KEEP IT QUIET, OKAY?
I'M FINE WITH THIS AND YOU CAN BE TOO.
AND LIBERTY SAYS, PUT ON YOUR RED SHOES ON...
AND DANCE THE BLUES!
THIS AFTERNOON 80'S DANCE FOR THE JUNIOR CLASSES
WILL BE HELD IN THE CAF AT 2:30,
WITH MR. SIMPSON PRESIDING.
THE SENIOR DANCE WILL BE AT 7:00 IN THE GYM,
WITH DJS MAD DOG AND BILLIE FROM KISS 92 PRESIDING.
OH. GET YOUR FREAK ON FOR THE BREAK-DANCING CONTEST -
FIRST PRIZE? RINK-SIDE TICKETS TO A LEAF GAME...
THOSE LEAF TICKETS BELONG TO US.
OF COURSE.
HOPE YOU GUYS HAVE A GREAT TIME BUSTIN' A MOVE TONIGHT.
MY BREAK-DANCING CD? THE ULTIMATE.
OH. MY 80S OUTFIT? EVEN MORE, THE ULTIMATE.
AS YOU WILL WITNESS TONIGHT.
MY HIP-HOP COLLECTION RULES.
BEST OLD SCHOOL MIX EVER.
GUYS, LIKE, TAKE A DOWNER.
EIGHTIES DANCE? REMEMBER?
ANYWAY, WE'VE GOT ALL THE MOVES!
LEAFS, HERE WE COME!
WELL UMM, YOU COULD ALWAYS BUY TICKETS.
COME ON! SURE MARCO'S GOOD.
BUT CAN HE BUST MOVES LIKE THIS?
UM SPINNER, NOT HERE, OKAY?
OKAY, I SAW BETTER DANCING AT HEATHER SINCLAIR'S
GRADE THREE SOCK HOP.
DO YOU WANT TO WIN THIS CONTEST?
OF COURSE I DO.
THEN TWO WORDS: GO SOLO.
...SO, FOR YOUR WEEKEND ASSIGNMENT,
FIND A FEW EXAMPLES OF FLASH ANIMATION ON THE WEB.
DON'T FORGET TO E-MAIL THE URL'S TO YOUR...
I THOUGHT HE AND YOUR MOM WERE FRIENDS.
WHAT CHANGED?
SHE HAD A THING FOR HIM BACK IN HIGH SCHOOL.
REKINDLED LOVE?
I CAN TOTALLY SEE YOUR MOM GOING FOR HIM.
HE IS KINDA CUTE.
YEAH, FOR AN OLD GUY.
HE'S GOT A NICE SMILE.
AND HE'S TALL. THAT'S ALWAYS GOOD.
HE'S FUNNY.
AND HE'S COOL - IN HIS DORKY MR. SIMPSON WAY.
HEY GUYS - LOOKING FORWARD TO THE JUNIOR
"BACK TO THE FUTURE" DANCE THIS AFTERNOON.
I'LL BE WORKING THE TURNTABLE.
THE DEFLECTS. FLECT FLECT FLECT FLECT...
UM, EMMA? I WANTED TO...
YOU KNOW... CHECK IN WITH YOU.
I'M GOOD THANKS.
BECAUSE YOUR MOM TOLD ME...
WELL, YOU KNOW - THAT YOU TALKED AND, UH -
I JUST DON'T WANT THINGS TO BE AWKWARD.
I'M FINE.
EMMA, ARE YOU UNHAPPY ABOUT THIS SITUATION
WITH ME AND YOUR MOM?
NO. I THINK IT'S GREAT.
REALLY?
ONE HUNDRED PERCENT.
WOW. LOOK AT THE TIME. I'VE GOTTA GO.
WHAT WAS THAT?
HE WANTED TO "CHECK IN" WITH ME.
THIS WHOLE THING IS GETTING REALLY CONFUSING
AND WEIRD AND - I CAN'T GET MY HEAD AROUND IT.
HEY EMMA!
CRAIG! SORRY.
SO, YOU TWO GOING TO THE DANCE TONIGHT?
WE CAN'T. SENIORS ONLY.
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
OH YEAH, SORRY, JUNIOR.
THANKS FOR RUBBING IT IN.
YOU KNOW HOW MUCH I LOVE SPENDING LAME NIGHTS
AT HOME ALONE.
MANNY AND I ARE HAVING A GIRLS' NIGHT WITH MY MOM.
NICE. WELL AH, MAYBE NEXT YEAR.
IT'S SO OBVIOUS CRAIG LIKES YOU.
YOU THINK?
ATTENTION STUDENTS.
THE JUNIOR DANCE IS STARTING NOW IN THE CAFETERIA.
YOU THINK MATS WILL TALK TO US?
NO. HE' GOTTA FOCUS ON HIS GAME, RIGHT?
UMM, THE LEAFS FOCUS ON THEIR OWN STRENGTHS, RIGHT?
SO MAYBE WE SHOULD, TOO.
LIKE UM, LIKE SAY, I DO THE DANCING, YOU DO THE MUSIC.
YOU DON'T WANT ME TO BREAK?
NO, NO... IT'S JUST -
JUST WHAT? YOU'RE JEALOUS?
YOU WANT THE SPOTLIGHT ALL TO YOURSELF?
SPIN, YOU - YOU MOVE LIKE A WOUNDED POLAR BEAR, BUDDY.
I'M SORRY.
YEAH, I GET IT.
I CAN'T DANCE 'CAUSE I'M WHITE.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I'M SAYING.
YES IT IS.
POLAR BEARS ARE WHITE.
I'M WHITE. AND YOU'RE RACIST.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING...
OKAY, I'M NOT SAYING YOU CAN'T DANCE CAUSE YOU'RE WHITE.
I'M SAYING YOU CAN'T DANCE CAUSE YOU SUCK.
FINE. I'M GOING SOLO. YOU'RE FIRED!
YOU CAN'T FIRE ME!
I'M GOING SOLO.
ENJOY THE LEAFS' GAME - ON TV!
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS WAS ACTUALLY CONSIDERED COOL.
I DON'T KNOW, I THINK I LOOK PRETTY GOOD.
I THINK YOU LOOK LIKE A BIG, RETRO LOSER.
SHUT UP.
HEY.
HEY LADIES.
HEY, WHAT'S UP?
THIS IS WHAT THE JUNIOR DANCE IS ALL ABOUT.
SERIOUS IMMATURITY.
NOW HERE'S A HOT LITTLE 80'S RETRO-NUMBER
FROM MY VERY OWN BAND - THE ZIT REMEDY!
UGH! I HATE THAT STUPID SONG!
WOW EM, YOU HATE EVERYTHING TODAY.
NO - JUST SIMPSON'S TASTE IN MUSIC.
I THOUGHT I SAW YOU GIRLS PLAYING WALLFLOWER BY THE DOOR.
THIS GIRL? SHE LIKES TO PARTY ALL THE TIME.
HEAD ON IN.
HOW ABOUT YOU GUYS? YOU GONNA COME IN AND GET DOWN?
WE'RE GONNA MORE LIKE - GET LOST.
MOM?
I'M IN HERE.
CAN YOU FEEL THE EXCITEMENT?
GIRLS' NIGHT IS JUST MINUTES AWAY.
WE'VE GOT ROMANCE, SUSPENSE...
A WHOLE RANGE OF EMPTY CALORIES.
AND A DRESS CODE?
I'M SO SORRY.
I COMPLETELY FORGOT.
MR. SIMPSON CALLED -
HE LUCKED INTO LAST MINUTE ELVIS COSTELLO TICKETS AND -
AS YOU KNOW WE BOTH LIVE FOR ELVIS.
GREAT. HAVE FUN.
I'M SORRY. I WAS EXCITED.
WE CAN RESCHEDULE, OKAY?
UNLESS, OF COURSE, ANOTHER ANTIQUE 80'S SINGER
ROLLS INTO TOWN.
SO, HOW WAS YOUR DANCE?
IT SUCKED. THANKS TO THE DJ.
WASN'T MR. SIMPSON DJ'ING?
THAT'S SORT OF MY POINT.
WELL, I'M SURE HE TRIED HIS BEST.
HAVE FUN TONIGHT. I WON'T BE LATE.
IT'S NO BIG DEAL, EM.
NOT TO HER.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE DESERVE SOME EXCITEMENT TOO.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE CRASH THE SENIOR'S DANCE?
AH YES!
WOW...
YOU LOOK EXACTLY LIKE YOUR MOM IN HER HIGH SCHOOL PHOTO.
NO I DON'T, I LOOK LIKE CYNDI LAUPER.
I'M CHANGING -
NO, DON'T! YOU LOOK GREAT.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WHEN SHE WAS MY AGE MY MOM WAS TOTALLY COOL.
SHE DIDN'T DATE DWEEBS LIKE MR. SIMPSON.
SHE DATED GUYS LIKE CRAIG.
SHE WISHES.
NO. BUT YOU DO.
"OOH CRAIG, I LOVE YOUR EYES. AND YOUR HAIR. AND YOUR SMILE."
WE ARE SO GOING TO HAVE FUN TONIGHT.
WE ARE SO GOING TO SEE CRAIG TONIGHT!
I THOUGHT YOU HAD A DATE TONIGHT.
I DID. SHE CANCELLED ON ME.
STORY OF MY LIFE.
WHO ARE YOU SUPPOSED TO BE?
SID VICIOUS.
UH, WHO?
SID VICIOUS?
THE SEX PISTOLS?
YOU WEREN'T TOO HIP BACK IN THE 80'S, WERE YOU, JOEY?
OH, YOU WANT TO SEE HIP?
OH, I'LL SHOW YOU HIP.
OH YEAH.
SO - YOU GOTTA HOT DATE FOR TONIGHT? GOT SOMEONE SPECIAL?
YEAH, THERE IS THIS ONE GIRL.
BUT SHE WON'T BE COMING TONIGHT.
LOOKS LIKE WE BOTH HAVE BAD LUCK TONIGHT.
THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT!
WOULDN'T BE AN 80'S DANCE WITHOUT THIS.
THIS IS YOUR DEFINITION OF HIP?
HIP AND COOL. TRUST ME.
NOT SO SURE I WANT TO.
THIS IS SO COOL. WE ARE SO COOL.
RADITCH ALERT!
HEY, YOU DIDN'T EVEN DRESS-UP.
LOOK, THESE GLOVES ARE SO TOTALLY RAD.
HI GUYS.
GROSS ME GREEN. LIKE, TOTALLY.
THERE IS CRAIG!
CRAIG OVER HERE!
HEY LOOK, VALLEY GIRLS!
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
WE WANT TO CRASH THE DANCE.
COOL.
BUT WE SORTA NEED YOUR HELP.
MEET ME AT THE EAST DOOR. TEN MINUTES.
YES!
GRODY. FOR SURE. NICE MOVES SPIN.
LADIES, YOU WANT MOVES? I'LL SHOW YOU MOVES.
THIS IS SO EXCITING I COULD BURST!
MANNY, SHHH!
KEEP YOUR HEADS DOWN OKAY?
IF RADITCH SEES US WE'RE BUSTED.
RADITCH.
COME ON...
HEY, WHAT'S UP DEGRASSI?
WE'RE MAD DOG AND BILLIE FROM KISS 92.
AND WE'RE SPENDING ALL NIGHT IN THE 80'S,
FROM BEFORE YOU WAS EVEN BABIES.
YOU ARE GOING DOWN, HOMIE.
I'M SO PUMPED. I CAN NAIL THIS!
CHECK IT OUT.
SO, AH, WHO'RE YOU SUPPOSED TO BE, VANILLA ICE?
OOH, WHO'RE YOU SUPPOSED TO BE - MICHAEL JACKSON?
UM YEAH SPIN, HE IS.
OH. WELL, HOW ARE YOU SUPPOSED TO BREAK IN THAT GET-UP?
WHO'S THE DUMB ONE NOW?
UH YOU ARE - STILL.
YOU SEE, THESE ARE FOR BREAK-DANCING.
YOU MAY HAVE THE GROOVES, BUT UM,
DO YOU HAVE THE MOVES?
WE DID IT!
WE'RE IN.
OH THE SENIORS DANCE. THIS IS THE MOST FUN EVER!
ALRIGHT EVERYBODY,
IT'S TIME FOR THE BREAK-DANCING COMPETITION.
FIRST PRIZE IS THIS:
A PAIR IF PRIMO GOLD SEATS
TO AN UPCOMING TORONTO MAPLE LEAFS HOCKEY GAME...
THAT'S RIGHT. FIRST UP WE HAVE JIMMY BROOKS. JIMMY?
WHAT'D YOU DO WITH MY CLOTHES?
CLOTHES? WHAT CLOTHES?
ANY DAY NOW, JIMMY.
RRRRIP!
(LAUGHTER)
THAT GIVES A WHOLE NEW MEANING TO DOING THE MOONWALK...
ANYWAY NEXT UP WE HAVE SPINNER MASON.
SPINNER? BRING IT ON, SPINNER...
PARTY PEOPLE, GET READY FOR SOME SERIOUS TUNAGE.
THAT'S NOT MY MUSIC.
DANCE! DANCE!
DANCE! DANCE! DANCE! DANCE!
ALRIGHT IT'S SLOW TIME FOR ALL YOU COUPLES OUT THERE.
HERE IS ONE OF MY FAVORITES.
CRAIG'S HEADED RIGHT THIS WAY.
HEY, CRAIG.
EMMA. MANNY. YOU HAVING FUN?
YEAH.
WE HAVEN'T HAD THIS MUCH FUN SINCE... WELL, NEVER!
GREAT!
GREAT.
YEAH SO. MANNY YOU, UH, WANNA DANCE?
ME?
YEAH.
YEAH GREAT. YOU TWO DANCE.
I'LL STAND HERE...
EMMA! WHAT ARE YOU DOING OUT HERE?
YOU SHOULD BE IN BED!
REALLY? SO SHOULD YOU TWO.
EMMA!
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU DID THAT TO ME.
I CAN'T BELIEVE MARCO.
YEAH. HE'S GOT THE TICKETS.
HE'S GOT THE GIRLS.
WHAT HAVE WE GOT?
PAINFUL AND HUMILIATING MEMORIES.
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD OF KNOCKING?
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD OF MANNERS?
I'M NOT THE ON PLAYING TONSIL HOCKEY ON OUR FRONT STEPS.
WHAT ARCHIE AND I DO TOGETHER IS NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
AND YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO BE HOME.
NOT DRESSED UP LIKE ME AT SOME DANCE -
I'M NOT YOU, I'M CYNDI LAUPER,
I DON'T CARE WHO YOU ARE, YOU WERE WAY OUT OF LINE TONIGHT.
ME OUT OF LINE?
WHAT ABOUT YOU, NOT TELLING ME ABOUT SIMPSON -
I DID TELL YOU.
YEAH, WHEN IT WAS TOO LATE.
IS IT SO WRONG THAT I'VE FINALLY FOUND SOMEONE I CARE ABOUT?
YES.
WHY?
BECAUSE YOU'VE GOT ME!
EM. YOU'LL ALWAYS BE THE MOST IMPORTANT PERSON IN MY LIFE.
JUST BECAUSE SNAKE AND I ARE DATING
DOESN'T MEAN THINGS BETWEEN US ARE GOING TO CHANGE.
THAT'S NOT TRUE. THINGS ARE ALREADY CHANGING.
YOU, AND MANNY -
MANNY?
WE BOTH LIKE THIS GUY. WE BOTH THOUGHT HE LIKED ME.
AND HE LIKED HER?
I FELT LIKE SUCH AN IDIOT.
I'M SURE SHE DIDN'T PLAN IT, EM. NEITHER DID I.
NICE WORK ON THE DO.
YOU DID THIS EVERY SINGLE DAY?
IMAGINE.
SO. ARE YOU GOING TO BE OKAY WITH THIS?
SIMPSON AND ME?
I'M NOT SURE.
THAT'S OKAY.