QUESTION 30. RAM. WHAT DOES IT STAND FOR?
RANDOM ACCESS MEMORY.
HMM? I'M SORRY?
YOU ASKED A QUESTION.
THE ANSWER IS RANDOM ACCESS MEMORY.
RIGHT, RIGHT. I'M SORRY GUYS.
I'M MORE THAN A LITTLE DISTRACTED TODAY!
I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M ACTUALLY GETTING MARRIED... TOMORROW.
OKAY, WELL, THAT'S IT. ANY FINAL QUESTIONS?
YES.
WHEN ARE YOU GOING TO OPEN THIS?
GUYS...
SPEECH, SPEECH, SPEECH, SPEECH.
OKAY, OKAY, UH WHERE TO START.
AHH, LOVE - EXCITING AND NEW.
DO WE REALLY HAVE TO HEAR THIS?
JT, SHUT UP? I'M TRYING TO LISTEN.
AND I'M ABOUT TO THROW UP.
SOMEBODY'S NEVER BEEN IN LOVE.
AND YOU HAVE SEAN?
REALLY? WITH WHO EXACTLY?
NOT EMMA BY ANY CHANCE?
(Screams)
AGH! MOM!
MOM?
THERE YOU ARE! I THOUGHT YOU LEFT WITHOUT ME.
AND REMEMBER, BREATHE.
I HAD TO GET SOMETHING FOR MY HEAD.
YOU DON'T HAVE A COLD?
NO, NO. JUST A HEADACHE.
OKAY. OKAY, I'M TRYING NOT TO PANIC, JUST BEING REALISTIC.
WE HAVE A LOT TO DO TODAY, BEFORE TOMORROW.
EM, LET ME JUST GO UPSTAIRS AND TAKE THIS FIRST.
NO.
TAKE IT IN THE CAR. GO.
OKAY.
OKAY. I'LL JUST RUN IN AND OUT, OKAY?
THEN WE'LL HIT THE ENGRAVER'S, THE CATERER'S AND HOME
BEFORE CAITLIN ARRIVES TO PERM MY HAIR.
AND DON'T FORGET TO TAKE YOUR HEADACHE STUFF.
I'LL BE BACK BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I know I can make it through
♪ If I hold out
♪ Be the best
♪ The best that I can be
♪ Hear what I say to you
♪ Whatever it takes
♪ I know I can make it
♪ I know I can make it through...
TRUE LOVE DOES TOO EXIST, JT.
YEAH, RIGHT.
JUST BECAUSE YOUR "QUEST" FOR AN OLDER WOMAN
HAS BEEN, LIKE, POINTLESS - IT DOESN'T MEAN IT'S NOT REAL.
IS SHE REAL?
HEY, I THOUGHT YOU WERE OFF TODAY, EMMA?
I AM. I HAVE TO TURN THIS IN TO KWAN.
MS. KWAN? ONE ESSAY. ONE ATTENDANCE SLIP.
IF ONLY ALL STUDENTS WERE AS HARD-WORKING AS YOU, EMMA.
SO EM, REMEMBER A CERTAIN SOMEONE YOU DATED LAST YEAR?
SEAN.
SEEMS HE'S STILL IN LOVE WITH YOU.
SEAN? IN LOVE WITH ME?
NO, SEAN AND I DATED. WE WEREN'T IN LOVE.
NOT WHAT HE SAYS.
SO YOU HAVE TO INVITE HIM TO THE WEDDING!
NO, I DON'T.
SEAN AND I ARE OVER. NO MATTER WHAT YOU HEARD.
WHAT DID YOU HEAR?
DOESN'T MATTER, RIGHT? IT'S OVER.
RIGHT. AND I'M LATE, SO BUTT OUT.
YOU'RE STILL STAYING OVER TONIGHT THOUGH, RIGHT?
YEAH. I GUESS.
OKAY, BYE.
PUT ON YOUR SHOES!
HEY SEAN.
HEY MANNY.
SO... TOMORROW - BIG WEDDING.
YEAH, GIVE MY BEST TO MS. NELSON.
ACTUALLY - YOU CAN TELL HER.
EMMA CAME BY EARLIER TO GET SOME BOOKS
AND SHE SAID THIS WAS FOR YOU.
EMMA WANTS ME AT THE WEDDING?
YEAH. SHE, MADE ME PROMISE I'D, LIKE, GET THIS TO YOU.
COOL. THANKS.
THANKS MANNY.
JT, MATH CLASS IS THAT WAY.
YEAH, I KNOW. BUT WE HAVE A VERY IMPORTANT PIT-STOP TO MAKE
OKAY...
I'VE BEEN THINKING.
THERE ARE SOME UPSIDES TO 'LOVE': EMMA GOT THE DAY OFF.
YEAH.
SIMPSON CANCELLED HOMEWORK.
TRUE.
AND STRIPPERS.
BECAUSE WHEN I THINK OF LOVE, I ALWAYS THINK OF STRIPPERS.
MARRIAGE EQUALS STAG PARTY EQUALS STRIPPERS
WHICH EQUALS TONIGHT.
A STRIPPER? TONIGHT?
JUST KEEP IT COOL. CRAIG MANNING.
JP... AND TONY. WHAT'S UP?
YEAH, IT'S ACTUALLY JT AND TOBY.
UM, SO WE HEARD THAT YOUR STEP-DAD IS HOSTING
A LITTLE GET-TOGETHER TONIGHT, HUH?
YEAH. A STAG.
RIGHT. WE WERE JUST HOPING THAT MAYBE WE COULD UH, DROP BY.
AND MAYBE WISH MR. SIMPSON GOOD LUCK.
AND IF THERE'S A STRIPPER THERE,
WE'D LOVE TO GIVE HER OUR BEST.
NO STRIPPERS, GUYS.
SIMPSON TOLD JOEY NOT TO GET ONE.
WHAT? IT'S LIKE A RITE OF PASSAGE!
IT'S SIMPSON'S LAST NIGHT OF FREEDOM.
HE CAN'T NOT HAVE A STRIPPER!
I KNOW, I KNOW. IT'S LAME.
IT'S UNFORGIVABLY LAME.
SO CRAIG, YOU WANNA DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT?
LET ME DO THE TALKING, BOYS.
TONIGHT IT'S SHOWTIME.
SHE'S THE ONE, CRAIG.
SHE HAS GOT TO BE THE ONE!
DOWN, BOY.
YEAH, TOBES, GROSS.
BUT WE CAN GET HER, RIGHT?
BOY SCOUTS ARE DOWN THE ROAD.
UH, WE'RE ACTUALLY HERE TO INQUIRE ABOUT MS. FANNY.
FANCY.
FANCY. IF SHE'S AVAILABLE TONIGHT.
YES, FOR AN OUTSIDE ENGAGEMENT.
FANCY DON'T DO NO SQUARE DANCING.
COME BACK WHEN YOU'RE LEGAL.
WAIT, NO!
THIS IS GOING TO TAKE SOME VERY DELICATE NEGOTIATING.
WHICH IS WHY YOU TWO ARE STAYING HERE.
HEY JOEY!
CRAIG. DID YOU GOT EVERYTHING I NEED FOR TONIGHT?
ALMOST EVERYTHING. IT'S LIKE THIS.
I'M AT THE STORE, FACED WITH A CHOICE.
S'CUSE ME.
YEAH. NOW DO I GET, LISTEN,
DO I GET PLAIN BORING CHIPS, OR HOT AND SPICY NACHOS.
AND WHAT DO YOU THINK I GOT?
I DON'T KNOW. ICE CREAM?
I GOT HOT AND SPICY.
GOOD.
LIKE, SAY, TONIGHT.
PLAIN BORING STAG EVENT,
OR HOT AND SPICY STAG PARTY.
ALL IT TAKES IS ONE FANCY STRIPPER.
AH NO, NO.
COME ON! IT'S TRADITION, JOEY.
YEAH. I KNOW IT'S A TRADITION, CRAIG.
YEAH! SO, HOW ABOUT IT?
NO! IT GOES AGAINST SNAKES WISHES, ALL RIGHT?
IT'S SEXIST, IT'S UN-PC...
YEAH, BUT...
AND IT'S PERFECT.
YOU KNOW WHAT? I'M GOING TO EMBARRASS THE HECK OUT OF HIM.
FINE. BUT TECHNICALLY, THIS WAS YOUR IDEA.
I'M NOT GETTIN' IN TROUBLE FOR IT.
ANGIE!
I'M GOING TO GRANDMA'S!
YES, YOU ARE. COME ON, BABY.
OKAY. SO YOU'RE SURE IT'LL JUST BE A BODY PERM, RIGHT?
LIKE THIS?
EM, I DO THIS FOR A LIVING. YES.
OKAY, 20 MINUTES.
ARE YOU OKAY IF I GO UP AND HAVE A SHOWER?
YES. JUST GO AND RELAX.
WEDDING CAKE.
OKAY.
JUST SIGN HERE, PLEASE.
NO...
THANK YOU.
"HAPPY BAT MITZVAH, RHODA?!"
MOM - MAJOR EMERGENCY!
THIS CAKE ISN'T YOURS.
UNLESS YOU CHANGED YOUR NAME TO RHODA?
JUST SEND IT BACK. NO BIG DEAL.
NO BIG DEAL? THIS IS YOUR WEDDING CAKE.
THERE'S WAY MORE IMPORTANT STUFF GOING ON, EM.
WAY MORE IMPORTANT.
YEAH, LIKE WHAT?
THE TEST IS POSITIVE.
I'M PREGNANT.
HEY EM.
EM, WHAT'S WRONG?
MY MOM IS PREGNANT.
WOW.
HOW DID IT HAPPEN?
I MEAN, I KNOW HOW IT HAPPENED BUT...
DID THEY PLAN IT?
NO. AT LEAST, I DON'T THINK SO.
WELL, IT'S KIND OF EXCITING.
ON SOME LEVEL.
HOW ABOUT SOME GOOD NEWS?
PLEASE. ANYTHING.
GUESS WHO'S COMING TOMORROW?
SEAN CAMERON! YOUR LOVE!
YOU'RE NOT SMILING.
MANNY, I TOLD YOU NO SEAN.
I WAS TRYING TO HELP.
BY PLAYING MATCHMAKER? GO HELP AND UN-INVITE HIM.
OKAY, BUT - WHAT'S THAT SMELL?
AHHH! MY PERM!
MOM?
MY HAIR!
YOUR HAIR!
MY HAIR.
HONEY, IT'LL BE OKAY, I PROMISE.
WHEN?
WELL...
AFTER THE WEDDING.
I CAN'T PUT ANY MORE CHEMICALS IN YOUR HAIR RIGHT NOW -
IT'LL FALL OUT.
(DOOR BELL)
I'LL GET THAT.
I'M GONNA BE YOUR MAID OF HONOUR, LOOKING LIKE THIS?!
IT'LL BE OKAY.
HEY, HOW ARE YOU?
HI. GOOD TO SEE YOU.
I MISSED YOU!
SO? WHAT DO YOU THINK?
GOOD ENOUGH FOR YOUR WEDDING PARTY?
I LOVE THEM. I JUST TOLD YOU GUYS, WEAR WHATEVER YOU WANT.
WE ARE - IT JUST SO HAPPENS WE BOTH LOVE THE SAME DRESS.
YEAH, WE WANTED TO DO IT. COME ON.
GUYS, IT'S JUST A WEDDING.
YEAH, YOUR WEDDING.
TO SNAKE. TO ARCHIE.
HOW ARE YOU?
AND WHAT HAPPENED?
SOMEBODY LEFT MY PERM SOLUTION IN TOO LONG.
SPIKE, YOU DIDN'T!
I THOUGHT YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO BE A PROFESSIONAL?
I AM, BUT -
GETTING MARRIED IS HUGE.
WELL, THAT'S WHY WE'RE HERE TO HELP.
THAT'S RIGHT. AND TO TAKE YOUR MIND OFF THINGS,
WE'RE THROWING A LITTLE GIRLS NIGHT OUT LATER.
BECAUSE IF SNAKE CAN GO OUT TONIGHT, SO CAN YOU.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THAT'S GREAT.
YOU GUYS ARE SO GREAT!
COME HERE, GIVE ME HUG!
DOIN' SOME GOOD WORK, MAN.
HUH?
OH, HERE, USE THIS.
SO I THOUGHT MAYBE WE'D UH, GET OUT OF THE CITY TOMORROW.
GO UP TO THE SPEYSIDE BACKROADS, UP NEAR ACTON.
NELSON? AS IN EMMA NELSON?
YEAH.
LOOKS LIKE YOU GOT SOME BETTER PLANS.
SEAN!
ARE YOU OKAY?
MANNY ARE YOU OKAY?
I'M FINE.
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
YEAH. SORT OF.
WHAT?
OH MY GOD, YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
YOU REMEMBER THAT INVITE I GAVE YOU?
YEAH. IT'S RIGHT HERE.
IT WAS SORT OF A MISTAKE.
SEAN, I'M REALLY SORRY. IT'S JUST-
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I'M SORRY.
NO, NO, NO. DON'T WORRY - IT'S NO PROBLEM.
EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, I'M FINE, FINE.
CAUSE MY OFFER FOR TOMORROW STILL STANDS, IF YOU WANT.
YEAH.
WE'RE BACK! HEY!
HEY!
HOW ARE YOU DOING? GOOD TO SEE YOU.
I'M GOOD! CONGRATULATIONS.
THANK YOU.
HEY.
HI. HOW ARE YOU?
GOOD.
YOU LOOK GOOD.
THANKS.
GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
LIKEWISE. UM, WHAT IS ALL THIS STUFF?
UH, IT'S MINE.
YOU KNOW, MY LEASE IS UP AT THE END OF THE WEEK.
SO I'M MOVING IN BIT BY BIT.
DON'T YOU HAVE ENOUGH TO WORRY ABOUT RIGHT NOW?
SNAKE WORRY? COME ON.
HA-HA, THAT'S FUNNY, JEREMIAH.
BETWEEN THE WEDDING AND MOVING IN,
I'M LIKE A HEART ATTACK IN MOTION.
I BELIEVE IT.
OH, OH NO. DOES IT BITE?
WEDDING GIFT FROM MY CLASS.
IT'S VERY UM...
VERY UGLY - I KNOW. SORRY.
UM SO GUYS, WHAT DO YOU GOT PLANNED FOR TONIGHT?
DOING THE TYPICAL GUY STUFF?
SCOTCH, CIGARS, STRIPPERS?
I TOLD JOEY - NO STRIPPERS. RIGHT?
NOPE, NOPE. WE'RE GOING BOWLING.
SNAKE, COME HERE. TALK TO ME.
YES MASTER, SOUNDS SERIOUS...
NO, NO. JUST WEDDING STUFF.
HEY GUYS!
HEY LUC!
CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS WEDDING?
SO, WHEN ARE YOU GUYS GOING TO HAVE A LITTLE
MINI-SPIKE OR MINI-SNAKE
TO ADD TO MINI-CAITLIN OVER THERE?
OH WELL, WE'VE DISCUSSED IT.
WE DEFINITELY WANT KIDS.
DEFINITELY. AND WHO KNOWS?
IT COULD HAPPEN SOONER THAN YOU THINK.
I SURE HOPE NOT!
JUST LIKE A MAN.
NEVER WANTS TO RUSH INTO ANYTHING.
WE'VE GOT A LOT ON OUR PLATES RIGHT NOW.
YOU KNOW, I'VE GOTTA SETTLE IN.
GET USED TO BEING A HUSBAND. AND A STEP-DAD.
RIGHT.
OH, I'M NOT SAYING NEVER. JUST NOT RIGHT NOW.
HEY - YOU WANTED TO TALK WEDDING?
NO. I'VE FIGURED IT OUT. THANKS.
HEY. WHAT'S UP.
WHAT'S UP? LISTEN MAN, CIGARS ARE OVER THERE
AND BEVERIDGE'S ARE SERVED 'TIL TWO A.M.
PERFECT.
HAVE A GOOD TIME.
THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
SNAKE!
WHAT'S GOING ON MAN.
LOOSEN UP, IT'S YOUR STAG.
I'M TRYING, I'M TRYING.
ALL RIGHT, HERE YOU GO.
I GOT SOMETHING PLANNED FOR YOU LATER
IT'S GOING TO CHEER YOU UP, OKAY.
OKAY.
I'LL GET IT.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, GUYS.
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
WELL, I HAVEN'T CLEARED YOU WITH JOEY YET.
LOOK GUYS, WHATEVER YOU'RE SELLING,
WE'RE NOT INTERESTED IN, OKAY? WHAT ARE YOU SELLING, ANYWAYS?
ACTUALLY, WE'RE UH, WE'RE HERE FOR THE SHOW.
YEAH.
FANCY WAS SORTA THEIR IDEA.
REALLY. OH WELL, IN THAT CASE - NO.
BUT - COME ON.
NO. GET OUT OF HERE.
BOTH OF YOUR AGES COMBINED WOULD NOT MAKE YOU OLD ENOUGH.
BUT, HOW COME CRAIG GETS TO STAY AND WATCH THE SHOW?
CRAIG GETS TO GO UPSTAIRS IN HIS BEDROOM AND WATCH TV, OKAY?
BUT JOEY -
NO. NO. NO. NICHT. NO.
LOOK, CRAIG, WE'RE IN THE SAME BOAT AS YOU, SO, YOU KNOW.
MAKE THEM STOP?
OR YOU'LL HAVE FOUR DEAD MEXICANS ON YOUR HANDS.
OKAY, THERE'S A PROBLEM HERE, SPIKE.
IS IT EMMA?
HERE, HAVE THIS. IT'LL HELP.
I CAN'T.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN YOU CAN'T?
THIS IS YOUR BACHELORETTE PARTY.
I JUST CAN'T, OKAY?
YOU KNOW THAT KINDA SOUNDS TO ME
LIKE YOU'RE PREGNANT, SPIKE.
OKAY, YOU'RE PREGNANT.
IT'S NOTHING TO BE ASHAMED OF.
YEAH, I MEAN TOTALLY.
LOOK, AT LEAST THIS TIME, YOU'VE GOT SOMEONE WHO LOVES YOU.
YEAH. SOME WHO'S GOING TO BE THERE FOR YOU.
A GUY WHO DOESN'T WANT KIDS.
YOU GUYS HEARD HIM.
YEAH, BUT...
HE MADE WHERE HE STANDS, VERY CLEAR.
HE DOESN'T WANT A KID RIGHT NOW.
SO WHAT'RE YOU GONNA DO?
I DON'T KNOW. CANCEL TOMORROW?
I MEAN, I LOVE SNAKE, BUT -
EM AND I HAVE GOTTEN THIS FAR ON OUR OWN.
MAYBE THIS WASN'T MEANT TO HAPPEN.
BUT SPIKE-
I'M SERIOUS, CAITLIN.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO ABOUT THE BABY?
THAT WASN'T MEANT TO HAPPEN EITHER.
SO MAYBE IT WON'T.
SO, SEAN.
YOU'RE SURE HE WASN'T TOO UPSET WHEN YOU TOLD HIM?
FOR THE MILLIONTH TIME, HE WASN'T UPSET.
GOOD.
I HOPE SNAKE WILL TAKE HIS NEWS JUST AS WELL.
MY PARENTS HAVE, LIKE, 20 SIBLINGS.
SO I SAY, THE MORE THE MERRIER.
ACTUALLY? I'D LOVE TO HAVE A LITTLE BROTHER.
OR A SISTER. I'M NOT PICKY!
I JUST WANT US TO FEEL LIKE A FAMILY.
AND A NEW BABY WOULD SO DO THAT.
HEY! HOW WAS YOUR LAST NIGHT AS A SINGLE WOMAN?
DID YOU GUYS GET ALL WILD AND CRAZY?
IT WAS FINE.
SO CAN I TAKE THIS OFF NOW?
SURE.
HERE.
HOW DOES IT LOOK?
I'VE RUINED EVERYTHING.
SPIKE!
I WOULDN'T - SHE PRETTY UPSET.
STILL?
WHY DON'T YOU STAY DOWN HERE,
AND WE'LL TRY AND IRON IT OUT.
I'LL JUST BE ONE MINUTE.
OKAY, I KNOW WHAT YOU FOUND OUT IS BEYOND WEIRD
BUT IT'S NOT THE END OF THE WORLD.
I'M FINE WITH THIS AND SNAKE WILL BE TOO.
WE JUST HAVE TO CONVINCE HIM THAT.
CONVINCE HIM? HOW?
I DON'T KNOW. HOWEVER YOU CONVINCED ME ABOUT YOU TOO.
IF I EVEN HAVE THIS BABY.
WHAT?
WE DON'T WANT ANYMORE KIDS RIGHT NOW.
END OF STORY.
END OF STORY FOR WHO?
YOU'RE NOT THINKING OF HAVING AN ABORTION.
I MIGHT.