ALL MY VEHICLES ARE CERTIFIED.
AND YOU GET A SIX MONTH ENGINE AND TRANSMISSION GUARANTEE, OKAY?
AND I'M GOING TO EAT THE TAXES. LET ME KNOW.
GENTLEMEN, HOW ARE YOU?
IT'S PRETTY SWEET, HUH?
YOU CAN'T WALK AWAY FROM THIS CAR, SIR.
NO?
FULL SPORT SUSPENSION.
YOU PITCH IT AROUND THE CORNER, IT'LL STAY GLUED.
REALLY?
IT'S SHARP.
HELLO!
HI.
HOW ARE WE TODAY?
OH, GOOD. YOUR ASSISTANT HERE WAS JUST SINGING THIS PRAISES
OF THIS CAR.
DO YOU MIND IF I UH -
OH, PLEASE, PLEASE DO.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK IN A SECOND, OKAY?
CRAIG, CAN I TALK TO YOU?
YEAH.
GREAT JOB, PARTNER.
THANKS. YOU THINK SO?
YEAH, YOU'RE A NATURAL.
LISTEN, I WANT YOU TO DO ME A FAVOUR.
A CUSTOMER'S COMING IN TO TAKE THIS CAR FOR A DRIVE.
IT NEEDS A SERIOUS CLEAN - ASAP.
TAKE THE KEYS. COME ON, COME ON, TAKE THE KEYS.
YOU MEAN - DRIVE IT?
YES, YES, JUST KEEP IT ON THE LOT.
YOU'LL BE FINE, ALRIGHT?
♪ WHATEVER IT TAKES
♪ I KNOW I CAN MAKE IT THROUGH
♪ IF I HOLD OUT
♪ BE THE BEST
♪ THE BEST I CAN BE
♪ HEAR WHAT I SAY TO YOU
♪ WHATEVER IT TAKES
♪ I KNOW I CAN MAKE IT
♪ I KNOW I CAN MAKE IT THROUGH
YEAH, BIANCA BOOKED THIS SURPRISE
SPA-RELAXATION WEEKEND THING.
AND I NEED YOU TO PICK UP ANG AT SK.
NO, I'LL BE BY ON SUNDAY TO PICK HER UP, OKAY?
THANKS, MA. BYE.
HEY.
WHAT'S UP?
NOTHING. JUST UH -
YOU'RE GOING AWAY. SO, WHERE DO I GO?
I FIGURED YOU'D STAY HERE.
ALONE?
YOU'RE FOURTEEN. YOU KNOW HOW TO COOK, YOU KNOW HOW TO CLEAN.
YOU'LL BE FINE.
WAIT. SO I REALLY GET THE RUN OF THE HOUSE,
FOR THE WHOLE WEEKEND?
YEAH.
IF YOU WANT, YOU CAN INVITE SOME OF YOUR BUDS OVER,
THAT'S COOL.
BUT, THREE GROUND RULES -
NO DRINKING. NO CHICKS. NO PARTIES - I MEAN IT.
GOT IT. YOU CAN TRUST ME.
I KNOW I CAN, PARTNER.
MY DAD'S BEEN WORKING ON KID ELRICK TIX ALL WEEK.
HE'S PULLED EVERY STRING HE HAS.
AND THE'RE TOTALLY SOLD OUT.
WELL, HOW ABOUT YOU MARCO?
I MEAN, YOUR MOM WORKS IN THE MUSIC BIZ.
SHE TEACHES PIANO, SPINNER.
WHO DIED?
OH, KID ELRICK'S SOLD OUT.
IT'S SO UNFAIR!
SO? JOEY'S GONE FOR THE WHOLE WEEKEND.
AND I GOT THE PAD ALL TO MYSELF.
AND YOU GUYS ARE ALL INVITED.
YES!
SO, WHO ELSE IS ON THE GUEST LIST?
YOU THREE PLUS SEAN.
OH, YOU INVITED HIM.
I'LL TAKE A PASS.
WELL, I CAN'T UNINVITE HIM NOW.
NO, NO IT'S COOL.
I MEAN, WE'LL JUST DO IT SOME OTHER TIME, RIGHT?
DUDE.
FINE. YOUR LOSS.
BECAUSE WE ARE GOING TO PARTY!
NO PARTIES, SPIN.
GIRLS?
NO GIRLS.
BOOZE?
NO BOOZE.
DONUTS?
THAT WE CAN DO.
THEN I'M THERE!
SWEET, THIS WEEKEND IS GOING TO BE AWESOME MAN!
YES!
DID YOU KNOW THERE'S NO WORD IN THE ENGLISH LANGUAGE
THAT RHYMES WITH ORANGE?
DID YOU KNOW IT'S FRIDAY? THE WEEKEND.
SURE DO. I THOUGHT TONIGHT WE'D GO SEE THAT NEW MOVIE
"STRANGE EVIL."
THE REVIEWERS SAID IT WAS 'EDGY'.
LAME. BESIDES, I'M GETTING MY CARTILAGE PIERCED.
HEY, ELLIE,
DO YOU THINK I SHOULD GET MY BELLY BUTTON PIERCED?
I'VE WANTED TO FOR A WHILE.
COME WITH ME AFTER SCHOOL.
AFTER SCHOOL?
HE'D BE ABLE TO SQUEEZE ME IN ON SUCH SHORT NOTICE?
LET'S FIND OUT.
AS YOU SHOULD ALL KNOW BY NOW A SIMILE IS A COMPARISON
USING 'LIKE' OR 'AS'.
WHILE A METAPHOR IS A FIGURE OF SPEECH
IN WHICH THINGS ARE COMPARED
BY STATING THAT ONE THING IS ANOTHER.
BOTH SIMILES AND METAPHORS ARE USED IN POETRY.
AND WE'RE GOING TO LOOK AT THEM TODAY.
SO, THE DAY IS DONE.
AND THE DARKNESS FALLS ON THE WINGS OF NIGHT.
WEEKEND HERE WE COME! WOO!
OKAY, NEXT TIME THE KID'S IN TOWN,
WE GOTTA BUY TICKETS MONTHS IN ADVANCE.
OH, HEY, MR. JEREMIAH.
WHAT'S THIS?
I GO AWAY FOR THE WEEKEND AND YOU INVITE THE WHOLE SCHOOL?
GOT YA!
YOU SHOULD'VE SEEN THE LOOKS ON YOUR FACES.
COME HERE.
WEEKEND SUPPLIES, GENTLEMEN.
OH, YES!
ALL BASIC FOUR FOOD GROUPS.
YOU'VE GOT CHIPS, CHIPS, CHIPS
AND KRAFT DINNER.
HAVE A GOOD WEEKEND, BOYS.
WOW!
YOU KNOW, HIS WEEKEND'S GOING TO BE GREAT.
HE'S ONE LUCKY GUY.
YEAH! YEAH! YEAH!
I KNOW IT LOOKS A LITTLE NASTY.
I KEEP TELLING ATTILA THAT WE SHOULD -
ATTILA?
IT'S A FAMILY NAME. COME ON.
SO ATTILA, IS THAT THE SAME KIND OF NEEDLE
YOU'LL BE USING TO PIERCE MY BELLY BUTTON?
NO, NO.
I'LL BE USING A MUCH LARGER ONE.
LIKE THAT.
OH. WOW.
THERE YOU GO. ALL DONE, CUZ.
SO WHAT'S THE WORD, ASHLEY? STILL INTERESTED?
BECAUSE I HAVE AN OPENING TOMORROW AT TEN.
OKAY. SIGN ME UP.
GREAT. NOW, JUST GET YOUR MOTHER TO SIGN
THIS PERMISSION SLIP FIRST.
PARLOUR ASSUMES NO RISK IN CASE OF INFECTION?
WELL, IT IS AN INVASIVE PROCEDURE.
BUT DON'T WORRY, EVERYTHING'S STERILIZED -
MY MOM WILL NOT SIGN THIS.
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
JUST BECAUSE SHE'S MY MOM.
AND SHE JUST WON'T. SORRY.
FISH.
YOU REALLY DON'T HAVE A QUEEN?
FISH!
HARK! A SOLDIER APPROACHES.
(Burps) ENCORE, MAESTRO. (Burps)
GUYS, THIS IS SO BORING.
YEAH. LET'S CALL JIMMY.
WHAT? YOU MISS YOUR GIRLFRIEND?
SHUT UP.
NO, YOU SHUT UP.
NO YOU SHUT UP.
YOU SHUT UP!
YOU BOTH SHUT UP!
WE HAVE A HOUSE TO OURSELVES. AND WE'RE WASTING IT.
I GOT IT!
YOU GUYS WANNA LIVE LIFE ON THE EDGE? COME WITH ME.
OKAY GUYS... ALRIGHT, ALRIGHT.
SPRAY CHEESE?
WE DID IT AT CAMP. IT'S A RACE.
DO WE GET CRACKERS?
NO. LOSER.
YOU DO IT LIKE THIS.
AH, COME ON MAN.
WHAT? YOU GUYS, WHAT?
I WAS THINKING ABOUT GETTING MY BELLY BUTTON PIERCED.
SEE, TOLD YOU.
TOLD ELLIE WHAT? I JUST REACTED.
RIGHT. YOU MADE A TOTAL FACE.
DO YOU WANT MY PERMISSION OR NOT, ASHLEY?
NOW YOU JUST HAVE TO CLEAN IT SCRUPULOUSLY. FOR WEEKS.
BUT IT'S WORTH IT.
IF ONLY I WERE TEN YEARS YOUNGER.
SPIN-NER! SPIN-NER! SPIN-NER!
YES! KING OF THE WORLD.
OKAY - WHO'S NEXT? I DARE YOU GUYS!
FORGET IT. OH, NO THANKS... I'M UH -
LOOK, COME ON. YOU GUYS SUCK.
OH! WAIT. I HAVE A DARE.
UH-OH. BATHROOM BREAK.
WHAT, THIS IS YOUR DARE? A PRANK PHONE CALL?
WHAT? YOU SCARED OF TALKING TO A STRANGER?
HELLO, THIS IS THE POWER COMPANY.
SO THIS IS WHAT YOU DO FOR FUN, SEAN?
PRANK YOUR EX-GIRLFRIEND?
YOU'RE DEAD, PHONE-BOY! YOU'RE DEAD.
YEAH. THIS IS THE LIFE.
YOU KNOW WHAT? I LIKE YOU GUYS.
WHAT, ARE YOU GONNA KISS US NOW?
SHUT UP, SEAN.
NO, I MEAN WITH MY DAD -
HE WOULD'VE NEVER LET ME HAVE YOU ALL OVER LIKE THIS.
NO. WELL, A LOT DIFFERENT HERE, I SUPPOSE, HUH?
YEAH, TOTALLY.
WITH JOEY - IT'S LIKE I CAN DO NO WRONG.
I GET TOTAL, ONE-HUNDRED PERCENT FREEDOM.
I MEAN, HE EVEN LET ME DRIVE.
UM, YOU DROVE?
UH, IT WAS NO BIG THING.
JUST SOME CLUNKER AT THE CAR LOT.
MAN, IT WAS A HUGE THING.
IT WAS THE COOLEST THING I'VE EVER DONE.
THAT'S SWEET. WINDOWS DOWN. TUNES PUMPING.
I'D GIVE ANYTHING FOR THAT!
IT WAS JUST ACROSS THE LOT.
SO? AND I BET YOU KNOW WHERE JOEY KEEPS THE KEYS
TO HIS DEALERSHIP.
MAN. YEAH, LET'S GO TAKE IT OUT FOR A TEST DRIVE.
YOU KNOW, JUST AROUND THE BLOCK.
WHAT? ON THE ROAD?
NO, WE'D SO GET CAUGHT.
WELL, WHAT ABOUT TOMORROW? WANT TO?
IT'S A GORGEOUS SATURDAY MORNING.
85 DEGREES AND NOT A CLOUD IN THE SKY.
I TELL YOU, I'M JEALOUS OF CARLA COLLINS.
SHE'LL BE OUT CRUISIN' IN THE MIX MOBILE...
HEY.
STILL GOING FOR THAT RIDE TODAY?
SURE, BUT MAYBE LATER.
LATER?
CRAIG, YOU'RE NOT CHICKENING OUT ARE YOU?
RIGHT HERE.
KEYS TO THE KINGDOM.
(Telephone Ringing)
ARRR!
WHOA!
DUDE, YOU GAVE ME A HEART ATTACK.
SORRY.
WHAT DO I DO?
ANSWER IT.
NO, YOU IDIOT - WE'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO BE HERE.
LET'S GO.
WHY ARE WE TAKING THIS ANYWAY? IT'S JUNK.
BECAUSE I'VE DRIVEN IT BEFORE - I KNOW HOW TO DRIVE IT.
LISTEN GUYS, MAYBE THIS ISN'T THE GREATEST IDEA.
COME ON, WE'RE JUST GOING TO TAKE IT
AROUND THE BLOCK A COUPLE OF TIMES.
GENTLEMEN? LET'S ROLL.
UH, SHORT RIDE, DUDE.
YEAH! ALRIGHT! YEAH, LET'S GO!
HEY, GIRLS.
OFF TO YOUR PIERCING?
YEP. WANNA COME? YOU COULD GET ONE TOO.
NO THANKS. NONE FOR ME PLEASE.
I'M NOT AS BRAVE AS YOU TWO.
WHOA. SLOW DOWN THERE. IT'S GETTING SCARY HERE.
KEEP TALKING, SPINNER.
YOUR IDEA OF A GOOD TIME IS SPRAY CHEESE.
AND THAT WAS THE LATEST FROM PARTY DIVISION.
NOW WE TAKE YOU LIVE TO CARLA COLLINS.
SO HOW DO YOU GET TICKETS
FOR THE SOLD OUT KID ELRICK SHOW TONIGHT?
GUYS, GUYS, GUYS! SHHH!
JUST COME DOWN TO MELDRUM PARK AND FIND ME IN THE MIX-MOBILE.
ANSWER A SKILL-TESTING QUESTION
AND YOU AND THREE FRIENDS ARE GOING TO KID ELRICK TONIGHT!
WOW!
PULL OVER.
MELDRUM PARK'S ONLY TEN MINUTES AWAY IF WE RUN FAST.
WHO'S RUNNING? WE'RE DRIVING.
YEAH, IN TEN MINUTES THAT PARK'LL BE FULL OF PEOPLE.
WE SAID WE WERE DRIVING AROUND THE BLOCK AND THAT'S IT.
YEAH, THAT WAS BEFORE THE CONTEST.
I SAY WE TAKE THE CAR.
YEAH, I'M DOWN WITH THAT.
GUYS, NO.
OKAY, IT'S TWO FOR, ONE AGAINST.
DECIDING VOTE TO CRAIG. WHAT DO YOU SAY?
YEAH! WOW!
I'M GOING TO PIERCE HERE.
AND FEED IT THROUGH UNTIL IT COMES OUT THERE.
THIS IS THE CLAMP I'M GOING TO USE TO HOLD YOUR SKIN
WHEN I DO THE PIERCING, OKAY?
THIS IS AN ANTISEPTIC GEL.
IT'S GOING TO FEEL A LITTLE COOL.
NOW I'M MARKING THE POINT OF ENTRY.
ASHLEY, YOU'RE GOING TO FEEL A LITTLE PRESSURE NOW.
I'M SORRY! I CAN'T DO IT!
I DON'T CARE HOW COOL IT'LL LOOK.
THAT THING IS NOT PIERCING MY BODY!
ALRIGHT NOW. HERE'S THE SKILL TESTING QUESTION.
NAME KID ELRICK'S WIFE.
YOU HAVE NO CLUE DO YOU?
NO.
THAT'S OKAY.
WE'RE HERE FOR THE CONTEST.
OKAY, TAKE A BREATH, CHAMP.
TELL US YOUR NAME FIRST.
MY NAME'S CRAIG.
OKAY, CRAIG.
NOW, TELL ME THE NAME OF KID ELRICK'S WIFE.
THAT'S A TRICK QUESTION, 'CAUSE KID ELRICK'S DIVORCED.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU CAN GIVE MY BEST TO THE KID TONIGHT,
BECAUSE YOU JUST WON FOUR TICKETS TO HIS SHOW!
(Yelling)
HAVE FUN!
MAN, I CAN'T BELIEVE WE'RE GOING TONIGHT!
WE HAVE TICKETS TO THE KID!
(Farting)
SPINNER! NOT IN THE CAR, MAN.
SORRY. EXCITEMENT MAKES ME FART.
OH. YOU ARE SICK. THAT IS DISGUSTING!
IT'S THE SPRAY CHEESE.
I SHOULDN'T HAD THAT THIRD CAN.
JUST DRIVE, JUST DRIVE.
AM I GETTING GOOD, OR WHAT?
JUST KEEP IT COOL, ALRIGHT?
ROGER.
WE'RE SO LUCKY.
SO LUCKY. SO LET'S GO BACK, OKAY?
OKAY.
YOU GUYS, TALK ABOUT AMAZING.
OH MY GOD, THAT WAS THE BEST DAY EVER! BEST DAY EVER!
SERIOUS. FIRST WE TAKE A CAR OUT FOR A JOY RIDE...
WE WIN KID ELRICK TICKETS...
THEN WE PULL UP RIGHT BESIDE THE COPS?
MAN, THAT PART WAS SO COOL!
NOW YOU SAY IT'S COOL.
BEFORE YOU WERE CRYING LIKE A LITTLE BABY.
SHUT UP, MAN.
I WAS CRYING BECAUSE OF YOUR CHEESE-FART. IT'S GROSS.
YEAH, IT WAS.
WHAT WERE YOU GUYS DOING?.
DO THE WORDS 'SILENT ALARM' MEAN ANYTHING TO YOU?
YOU, YOU, YOU. GONE. NOW!
ARE YOU GONNA SAY SOMETHING? EVER?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
WHY? WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
I ACTED LIKE AN IDIOT!
AND I TOTALLY EMBARRASSED MYSELF.
YEAH YOU DID.
KIDDING. SO, WHAT HAPPENED?
I'M JUST SCARED OF NEEDLES. I CAN'T EXPLAIN IT.
THEN WHY WOULD YOU TRY A PIERCING?
I DON'T KNOW I JUST - I THOUGHT IT'D LOOK COOL.
AND THOUGHT I'D GAIN SOME POINTS WITH YOU.
POINTS?
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
NO. I DON'T.
ASH, YOU'RE MY FRIEND.
YOU DON'T NEED A PIERCING TO IMPRESS ME.
SIT.
YOU'RE NOT MY DAD.
SIT!
WHAT YOU DID WAS SERIOUS.
YOU DROVE A CAR WITHOUT A LICENSE.
YOU COULDA KILLED SOMEBODY!
I KNOW -
NO, I DON'T THINK YOU DO.
IF YOU WERE SOME PUNK OFF THE STREET,
I WOULD HAVE HAD YOU ARRESTED AND PRESSED CHARGES.
CRAIG, I TRUSTED YOU.
IT WAS STUPID.
IT WAS SO STUPID, I ADMIT IT.
AND I'M SORRY. I'M REALLY SORRY.
YOU'RE GROUNDED. THREE WEEKS.
THREE WEEKS!?
AND ONE MORE THING -
WAIT, KID ELRICK?
WELL, WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO TELL MY FRIENDS?
SHOULD OF THOUGHT OF THAT BEFORE YOU TOOK THE CAR.