SPIKE:
IT'S TIME!
IT'S TIME?
(GASPS)
IT'S TIME!
SIMPSON:
UH...
LIZ! LIZ! IT'S SNAKE.
SPIKE'S GOING INTO LABOUR,
WE NEED YOU HERE ASAP!
SPIKE:
OKAY, THAT'S THE MIDWIFE.
NOW WHAT?
OKAY, REMEMBER MOM,
BREATHE!
ONE, TWO, THREE...
SIMPSON:
TELL ME WHEN YOUR NEXT
CONTRACTION IS.
NOW!
NOW.
OH! (CRASH)
OH!
JUST, JUST LEAVE IT!
I'LL GET THE SUPPLIES!
OKAY.
OKAY, WE'VE GOT A PLASTIC
DROP SHEET, HEATING PAD...
EM...
EMMA:
ALMOND OIL...
HONEY, THIS WAS JUST A DRILL.
AGAIN?!
(LAUGHS)
YOU'VE BEEN DRILLING US
ALL SUMMER.
'CAUSE HAVING A HOME BIRTH
IS A PRETTY HUGE DEAL.
SORRY IF IT'S PUTTING YOU OUT.
AND I'M SORRY FOR GETTING
IN THE WAY
OF YOUR PERFECT DELIVERY.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I can see it ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
EM? BETTER GET READY!
YOU'RE GONNA BE LATE
FOR YOUR FIRST DAY.
I KNOW MOM. THANKS.
AND DON'T FORGET THE BABY
SHOWER IS TONIGHT...
AT JOEY'S.
THE BABY SHOWER.
HOW COULD I FORGET?
(ALARM CLOCK RINGS)
(SCHOOL BELL)
(CAMERA CLICK)
SO, THIS IS IT!
START OF GRADE TEN.
A WHOLE NEW YEAR.
I'M JUST SO HAPPY
I HAVE YOU TO SHARE IT WITH.
ME TOO, HONEYBEE.
HONEYBEE?
DID HE SAY HONEYBEE?
CRAIG:
YEAH, I BET YOU GUYS
HAVE PET NAMES TOO.
(CAMERA CLICK)
SEAN:
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
YOU DIDN'T MIND MOVING.
EMMA:
IT'S NOT ABOUT THE ROOM, SEAN.
I'M JUST SICK OF THEM MAKING
ME FEEL LIKE
A SECOND CLASS CITIZEN.
WELL THEN MAYBE YOU
SHOULD TELL THEM.
RIGHT, MOM'S ALL CRAZY WITH
NINE-MONTHS-PREGNANT HORMONES,
AND SNAKE DOESN'T WANT
ANYTHING TO UPSET HER.
WELL THEN MAYBE HE'S RIGHT.
MAYBE FOR NOW,
YOU SHOULD JUST SUCK IT UP.
HAZEL:
I WONDER WHICH HOME ROOM
WE GET THIS YEAR?
I HOPE IT'S ARMSTRONG.
HE'S SO CUTE!
EASY THERE HORMONE-GIRL.
HE'S A TEACHER.
OH, SORRY.
SIMPSON AGAIN.
MARCO:
BELIEVE ME, GUYS,
IT COULD BE WORSE.
OH THE PAIN OF MY EXISTENCE.
THE WORD IS BANE, GAVIN.
DON'T WORRY, I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT IT MEANS IN CLASS.
GRADE NINE ENGLISH THAT IS...
AGAIN.
SPINNER:
YEAH, GO AHEAD, GUYS.
LAUGH.
LAUGH AT THE BIG FAT
FAILING DUMMY!
PAIGE:
NO ONE WAS LAUGHING, HON.
I WAS.
PAIGE:
DON'T LISTEN TO HIM, SPIN.
FAIL ENGLISH? NO BIGGIE.
FAIL GYM? THEN WE NEED TO TALK.
(KISS SMACK)
(SCHOOL BELL)
HATZILAKOS:
LIBERTY VANZANDT.
TOBY:
SO JT, WHICH LOVELY LADY WILL
YOU BE GOING AFTER THIS YEAR?
JT:
WELL, THERE'S MS. HOT-ZILAKOS -
ALWAYS TEMPTING.
HATZILAKOS:
JILL PATSON?
BUT THEN THERE'S THE TANGY
MS. KWAN.
MANNY:
JT, CHARMING AS ALWAYS.
CHRIS SHARPE?
HERE.
HATZILAKOS:
HERE'S YOUR LOCK CHRIS,
AND YOUR LOCKER NUMBER.
CHRIS:
THANKS.
EMMA SIMPSON?
YOU MEAN EMMA NELSON?
OH, I HAVE YOU DOWN AS SIMPSON.
THAT'S A MISTAKE.
HATZILAKOS:
OKAY.
I MEAN, JUST BECAUSE
MR. SIMPSON MARRIED MY MOM,
DOESN'T MEAN I AUTOMATICALLY
TOOK HIS NAME.
SHE DIDN'T EVEN DO THAT.
HATZILAKOS:
OKAY.
HELLO, FEMINISM?
HATZILAKOS:
EMMA, THERE WAS JUST SOME
CONFUSION AT THE FRONT OFFICE.
THAT'S ALL.
NOW REGARDING LOCKER
ASSIGNMENTS,
I'VE PLACED A MAP OF
THE CORRIDOR IN THE BACK.
PLEASE HAVE A LOOK AT IT BEFORE
YOU LEAVE TODAY,
AND IF YOU ANY QUESTIONS
OR PROBLEMS,
COME AND SEE ME AFTER CLASS.
PAIGE:
YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
THIS IS WHERE MY LOCKER IS?
SMACK DAB IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE WASTELAND?
WELL, IT'S GOT A NICE...
SMELL?
AAH!
(LAUGHTER)
THERE'S SOMETHING ALIVE
IN THERE.
SPINNER:
(SQUEAK) IT'S JUST A RAT,
HONEY.
THIS IS TERRIBLE!
I CAN NOT LIVE HERE!
IT'S JUST FOR ONE YEAR.
EASY FOR YOU TO SAY!
YOUR LOCKER'S OFF
THE GIRLS' BATHROOM.
I'D GIVE ANYTHING TO BE THERE.
I HAVE TO GO NOW.
SPINNER:
HAZEL.
YOU'RE PAIGE'S BEST FRIEND,
RIGHT?
YOU DON'T LIKE TO
SEE HER IN PAIN?
NO...
SPINNER:
WELL, THEN YOU WON'T HAVE ANY
PROBLEM GIVING HER YOUR LOCKER.
HAZEL:
UH, I'D RATHER DIE THAN
MOVE HERE.
OKAY. IT'S OUR FOUR MONTH
ANNIVERSARY IN FIVE DAYS.
I NEED TO GET HER A GREAT GIFT,
SO CAN'T YOU JUST-
HAZEL:
SO GO BUY HER A PONY.
SMITH: (OVER P.A.)
ATTENTION STUDENTS.
CLUB SIGN-UPS ARE STARTING NOW.
SIMPSON:
THERE ARE ALSO SEVERAL
FIELD TRIPS
THROUGHOUT THE SCHOOL YEAR...
YEAH, SO YOU GONNA... SIGN UP?
MAYBE LATER? COOL!
WOMAN:
GREAT, SIGN UP RIGHT HERE.
HEY, WHATCHA GOT?
JUST AN OLD YEARBOOK...
FROM THE 80s.
OKAY, THAT I GOTTA SEE.
OH MY GOD, IT'S JOEY WITH HAIR!
EMMA:
(LAUGHS)
ASHLEY:
IS THAT YOUR MOM?
HER HAIR'S INSANE.
I THINK THAT SHOULD BE
MY NEW STYLE.
NOW DON'T MAKE ME TAKE
THIS BOOK AWAY.
(LAUGHS) KIDDING.
FRIEND OF YOUR MOM'S?
EMMA:
NO.
EX-BOYFRIEND.
CAN WE DROP IT?
CRAIG:
WHY? WHAT'D HE DO?
OKAY, WELL UH... GUESS I'LL JUST
HAVE TO GO ASK MR. SIMPSON.
HEY MR. S?!
FINE.
HE GOT MY MOM PREGNANT
AND THEN TOOK OFF.
THAT'S YOUR DAD?
SHANE MCKAY.
BUT I ONLY MET HIM ONCE...
WHEN I WAS THREE.
WE VISITED HIM AT WORK.
HE'S A DOCTOR AND IT DIDN'T
GO WELL.
SPIKE:
I DIDN'T WANT EMMA
COMING HERE TODAY.
SHANE:
WELL I JUST THINK THAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT EMMA
LIKE SHE CAN'T HEAR YOU
RIGHT NOW,
AND THAT WASN'T THE DEAL
AT ALL.
SPIKE:
WELL YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK IT'S A LITTLE CONFUSING
FOR HER,
SO MAYBE YOU SHOULD THINK
ABOUT THAT.
SHANE:
WELL I THINK SHE CAN HEAR
YOU RIGHT NOW
AND YOU'RE PRETENDING
SHE CAN'T,
SO MAYBE WE CAN TALK ABOUT THIS
ANOTHER TIME.
I REFUSE TO NOT BE INVOLVED
IN THIS CHILD'S LIFE!
SHE NEEDS ME.
ASHLEY:
SO HE'S NOT AROUND AT ALL?
NEVER.
BUT I LIKE TO LOOK AT THIS
SOMETIMES JUST... TO WONDER.
SIMPSON: (SINGING)
♪ YOU'RE A STRANGE ANIMAL, ♪
♪ THAT'S WHAT I KNOW! ♪
(HUMS)
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE A STRANGE
ANIMAL... ♪
THE OLD ROOM'S LOOKING
PRETTY GOOD, HUH?
DID YOU CHANGE MY NAME
AT SCHOOL?
PARDON ME?
TODAY DURING ATTENDANCE
MS. HATZILAKOS SAID
EMMA SIMPSON.
SPIKE:
I'M SURE IT WAS JUST
A MISTAKE, EM.
THE OFFICE PROBABLY GOT
CONFUSED.
HOW? UNLESS SNAKE SAID
SOMETHING.
UH, NO. I MEAN UH,
THE NEW SECRETARY DOES KNOW
YOU'RE MY DAUGHTER.
BUT I'M NOT YOUR DAUGHTER.
EM, WHAT'S GOING ON?
I'M HIS STEP-DAUGHTER.
I ONLY HAVE ONE DAD
AND HE'S NOT HERE.
SHANE?!
EMMA:
YEAH.
HE'S HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH YOU
FOR TEN YEARS.
ELEVEN... AND A LOT CAN CHANGE
IN ELEVEN YEARS.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING WITH THIS?
I DUNNO, I JUST THOUGHT IT
MIGHT BE NICE
TO ACTUALLY KNOW WHO HE IS.
OR WHERE?
NO! I'M SORRY, BUT NO.
THAT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
MOM!
SPIKE:
END OF STORY!
HONEY.
ONE DAY YOU'RE JUST GONNA HAVE
TO TELL HER THE TRUTH.
YEAH, PIECE OF CAKE.
(DOORBELL)
DOOR!
MY BELLY!
(GIGGLES)
SPIKE:
I'M HAVING HIM AT HOME.
ERICA:
A HOME BIRTH?
WITH NO EPIDURAL?!
YOU DON'T NEED IT.
YOU CAN JUST BREATHE
RIGHT THROUGH THE PAIN.
STILL, SPIKE,
AREN'T YOU SCARED?
WHY WOULD I BE?
I'VE GOT THE BEST MID-WIFE
IN ALL OF CANADA - LIZ.
HEATHER:
WELL...
WELL, YOU'RE A BRAVER
WOMAN THAN I AM.
OKAY, IT'S GIFT TIME.
OPEN MY PRESENT.
HEATHER:
OR YOU CAN OPEN MINE.
SPIKE:
OKAY. (LAUGHS)
THERE'S TIME.
WOMAN:
LET'S SEE. OH.
THAT ONE'S FROM ME.
SPIKE:
OH YEAH?
OH UM,
TRY CLUB SODA ON IT.
(LAUGHS) I'M SYDNEY.
I ALWAYS DO THIS.
(LAUGHS) HI, CAITLIN.
I'M A VERY OLD FRIEND
OF SPIKE'S.
SYDNEY:
OH, THEN UH,
THEN YOU KNOW JOEY TOO?
DO I?
(LAUGHS) I GUESS YOU KNOW
HIM WELL.
CAITLIN:
IT'S ONE OF THOSE GREAT
UNREQUITED ROMANCES.
WELL, REQUITED,
THEN UNREQUITED,
THEN REQUITED AGAIN.
ON-OFF....
REVOLVING DOOR.
OH YEAH, ONE OF THOSE.
CAITLIN:
I ACTUALLY JUST MOVED BACK HERE
SO UH...
I GUESS WE'LL SEE.
JOEY:
HEY! YOU MADE IT! HI!
CAITLIN, THIS IS SYDNEY UH...
THE NEW GIRLFRIEND. RIGHT.
AH SIDNEY THIS IS CAITLIN-
AN OLD FRIEND.
YEAH, I KNOW.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
(NERVOUS LAUGH)
CAN I HELP WITH
THE SNACKS, JOE?
YEAH, THAT'D BE GREAT.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
COME ON, ANG.
IT WAS NICE MEETING YOU.
CAITLIN:
HAVIN' A GOOD TIME?
YEAH, GREAT. AMAZING.
UH, THIS IS CAITLIN
YOU'RE TALKING TO,
SO UH, FOR REAL.
WHAT'S ON YOUR MIND?
WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT
SHANE MCKAY?
THAT'S A QUESTION
FOR YOUR MOM.
I ASKED AND SHE WON'T ANSWER.
CAITLIN:
THEN I CAN'T EITHER.
CAITLIN!
I WANT TO OPEN YOUR GIFT NOW.
COME ON, I NEED TO KNOW.
I'M SORRY.
SPIKE:
ACTUALLY, WE JUST DID
THE NURSERY.
WOMAN:
AH, THAT ONE.
OH, DID YOU?
(TAPPING ON KEYBOARD)
DUDE! I CRACKED IT.
I KNOW HOW TO GET
HAZEL'S LOCKER.
HUH? OH, COOL! HOW?
OKAY, I WAS PLAYING
MONOPOLY LAST NIGHT.
I NEEDED PARK PLACE
FROM KENDRA
BUT I DIDN'T HAVE
ENOUGH MONEY.
SOUNDS FAMILIAR.
ANYWAY, SHE NEEDED ATLANTIC,
WHICH MY DAD HAD,
AND HE NEEDED VERMONT,
WHICH I HAD.
SO...
YOU TRADED YOUR DAD
FOR ATLANTIC...
SPINNER:
AND GAVE IT TO KENDRA
FOR PARK PLACE.
PROPERTY, DUDE. PROPERTY.
ANYWAY. SO I PLANNED OUT
A SERIES OF TRADES.
I CALL IT
"OPERATION LOCKER STORM".
MARCO:
SPIN? WHAT CAN I SAY?
YOU'RE A GENIUS!
SPINNER:
THANK YOU.
EMMA:
SEAN! I FOUND SHANE'S ADDRESS.
COOL.
I KNOW, I BARELY SLEPT
LAST NIGHT.
SO C'MON.
WE'RE GONNA GO FIND HIM.
WHOA, EASY.
I GOT GRADE 10 SHOP
AFTER THIS.
DON'T YOU THINK THAT
FINDING MY BIRTH DAD
IS A LITTLE MORE IMPORTANT?
EMMA, WHY SKIP?
WE'LL GO THIS WEEKEND.
(SIGHS) EMMA.
EMMA:
FINE, WHATEVER.
I WOULDN'T WANT YOU
TO GET IN TROUBLE.
(SCHOOL BELL)
MS. KWAN:
CLASS, CAN WE PLEASE SETTLE
DOWN AND GET TO WORK?
JT:
SO I SAID, I JUST HAVE
TO GO HOME. WHAT?
SPINNER:
JT! ISAACS!
I'M CONDUCTING A LOCKER POLL.
GRADE YOUR LOCKER FOR ME, JT.
JT:
OKAY.
UH, "A" FOR QUALITY,
"D" FOR LOCATION.
I ASK YOU,
WHERE ARE THE LADIES?
SPINNER:
WELL, I HAVE A LOCKER
THAT HAPPENS TO BE
GRADE "F" FOR QUALITY
BUT GRADE "A" FOR LADIES.
YOU LIKE TOUGH CHICKS?
JT:
YEAH.
SPINNER:
YOU LIKE TOUGH CHICKS?
DO I?!
GOOD.
CHRIS, I COULD GET YOU A LOCKER
RIGHT NEXT TO THE M.I. LAB.
I MEAN, I KNOW SOMEONE WILLING
TO GIVE THEIRS UP.
CHRIS:
IT WOULD SAVE ME TIME CARRYING
MY LP'S BACK AND FORTH.
BUT... NAH. THE LANES IS COOL.
P.A. ANNOUNCER:
THERE ARE A NUMBER OF OPENINGS
REMAINING
WITH MR. SIMPSON'S INSECT
CLUB...
SPINNER:
DJ MADD BULLETZ, HUH?
YOU HEAR THAT RARE JAM SESSION
HE DID IN PARIS LAST YEAR?
SOUNDS TOUGH STILL.
OH IT IS, AND UH,
I GOT A RARE BOOTLEG COPY
WITH YOUR NAME ON IT...
FOR THE LOCKER.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
T. DOT REPRESENT!
(LAUGHTER)
BEG, PLEAD, WHATEVER.
I'M NOT SLUMMING IT ALL YEAR
IN THE WASTELAND.
OKAY, THAT'S GOOD,
'CAUSE I GOT YOU A LOCKER
IN THE LANES,
DEGRASSI'S COOLEST
NEIGHBOURHOOD.
FOR BOYS.
FOR GIRLS THIS IS THE HOOD.
IT'S CLOSE TO OUR OFFICE.
NEAR THE COURTYARD,
NATURAL LIGHT...
YEAH BUT, COME ON.
THE LANES ARE SO PRETTY
WITH THE RED AND ORANGE
LOCKERS, AND YOU...
OKAY, FORGET PAIGE,
FORGET THE LANES,
I NEED THIS
BECAUSE IT'S THE ONLY THING
I CAN GIVE HER.
PLEASE?
FINE. WHATEVER.
YEAH!
YES!
EMMA:
CRAIG, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
RIGHT NOW?
CRAIG:
I'M GOING TO ART CLASS.
EMMA:
DO YOU REALLY WANT TO GO?
CRAIG:
INSTEAD OF...?
FINDING MY FATHER.
I'VE GOT HIS ADDRESS.
SEAN WON'T GO,
AND MANNY'S MOM WOULD KILL HER
IF SHE SKIPPED.
OH YEAH? AND WHAT DO YOU THINK
JOEY'S GONNA DO TO ME?
I CAN'T GO ALONE.
BUT WHY ME?
I MEAN, YOU COULD ASK JT,
OR TOBY...
BECAUSE I THOUGHT
YOU'D UNDERSTAND...
WITH YOUR DAD AND ALL.
SO WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR?
OKAY, UH, SO JUST GO UP,
RING THE BELL,
INTRODUCE YOURSELF.
AND I'LL BE HERE.
I CANNOT BELIEVE THIS IS REAL.
I'M ACTUALLY GOING TO MEET HIM.
(DOORBELL CHIMES)
HI... I'M EMMA.
DR. MCKAY:
AND I'M DR. MCKAY.
HOW MAY I HELP?
EMMA:
MY MOM'LL BE HOME ANY SECOND.
CRAIG:
THERE'S GOTTA BE A RECORD
OF THIS GUY SOMEWHERE.
OKAY, RECORDS. UM, HOSPITALS...
SCHOOLS... POLICE STATIONS,
I DON'T KNOW.
SNAKE IS THE CHAIR
OF THE ALUMNI COMMITTEE.
HE'S GOT THIS HUGE ADDRESS
LIST.
CRAIG:
OKAY, I'LL LOOK OUT
FOR YOUR MOM.
(TAPPING ON KEYBOARD)
FOUND IT!
SHANE MCKAY.
1405 SHAW AVENUE...
STOUFFVILLE?
SPINNER:
OKAY, OKAY.
COME ON, COME ON, COME ON.
PAIGE:
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
SPINNER:
NO TIME, NO TIME.
PAIGE:
I'M GONNA FALL!
SPINNER:
NO YOU WON'T- OH!
PAIGE:
(LAUGHING) STOP!
SPINNER:
OKAY.
'KAY.
NOW, I KNOW IT'S EARLY BUT...
HAPPY ANNIVERSARY!
PAIGE:
UM... THERE'S NOTHING INSIDE.
YEAH, WE HAVE TO,
WE HAVE TO MOVE
YOUR STUFF FIRST.
WAIT. LET'S THROW IT
IN REVERSE HERE.
THE LOCKER IS MY GIFT?
WELL, YEAH. I MEAN,
IT'S PRIME REAL ESTATE.
YOU HAVE YOUR OFFICE
RIGHT THERE.
OKAY. LOCATION: PERFECT.
THE LOCKER: NO.
OH, BUT, BUT YOU'RE SO SWEET
FOR TRYING.
(WHISTLING)
(ELECTRONIC BEEPING)
(LOCK OPENS)
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU HAD
A LOCKER HERE.
NOT A LOCKER...
THE LOCKER.
MMM, NOW THAT
IS PRIME REAL ESTATE.
JIMMY:
YEAH, WELL...
KEEP DREAMING.
'CAUSE IT'S NEVER GONNA HAPPEN.
WE'LL SEE. I HAPPEN TO KNOW
A MIRACLE WORKER.
♪♪♪
EMMA:
HI, WE'RE LOOKING FOR
SHANE MCKAY?
DO YOU HAVE AN APPOINTMENT?
NO.
HOLD ON.
CRAIG:
(UNDER HIS BREATH)
ROOM 209.
GO.
GO! COME ON,
I'LL COVER.
(KNOCKS)
HI, I'M LOOKING
FOR SHANE MCKAY?
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU?
I'M SHANE MCKAY.