LOOK, I DON'T KNOW WHY
YOU HATE PAIGE.
'CAUSE SHE'S PURE EVIL?
SHE'S VERY SWEET,
ACTUALLY,
AND DON'T WORRY
ABOUT TODAY, OKAY?
YOU'RE MY GUEST.
(SIGHS)
ELLIE, HON, I THOUGHT VAMPIRES
COULDN'T GO OUT IN THE SUN?
SPINNER:
I GUESS THAT LEAVES SHOTGUN
FOR DEL STUDLY,
UNLESS HE WANTS TO SIT
BACK HERE WITH HIS HONEY?
NO THAT'S COOL,
UH, SHOTGUN FOR ME.
PAIGE:
OH UH, MARCO,
MEET MY BROTHER DYLAN,
OUR CHAUFFEUR FOR THE DAY.
DYLAN:
HEY MARCO.
HEY.
(SHOUTS) LET'S GO!
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Hear what I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
JIMMY:
DYLAN,
THANKS FOR THE RIDE, MAN.
BRING ON THE BIKINIS.
SPINNER:
WOO! BEACH.
NICE BEACH.
WOW! WE'RE GONNA
HAVE SO MUCH FUN!
MARCO:
COME ON, EL,
CHEER UP.
PAIGE:
HAZE, DON'T FORGET
THE UMBRELLAS.
HAZEL:
OKAY.
UH YEAH,
I'M NOT CARRYING THAT.
WHY NOT?
WHAT? YOU WANT ME
TO LOOK LIKE SOME HOMO?
NO, NOT HOMO AS IN GAY.
HOMO AS IN UH...
MILK?
IT'S OKAY.
I TOLD HER NOT TO PACK THAT
RIDICULOUS PICNIC BASKET.
GEE, AND I TOLD SPIN NOT TO BE
AN INSENSITIVE JERK TODAY.
JIMMY:
GUYS, LET'S GO.
GUYS, WHERE'S THE WATER GUN?
MARCO:
HERE.
SPINNER:
WAIT, WHERE ARE
THE MARSHMALLOWS?
(LAUGHTER)
SPINNER:
WHAT?
(SNEEZES)
SHH! SHH.
SHH!
WHEN YOU GAVE BIRTH IT-
SPIKE:
SHH!
IT WAS TO A BABY,
NOT A JET ENGINE, RIGHT?
EMMA.
BETWEEN JACK'S ALL NIGHT CRYING
AND THE DRIP-DRIP-DRIP
OF THAT HOT WATER HEATER,
I'M NOT SLEEPING.
I'M ON IT!
FOAM, WRAPPED AROUND
THE HEATER?
NO MORE DRIP-DRIP-DRIP.
OW!
SHH!
FIDDLESTICKS!
OH! SNAKE!
(WHISPERING)
HERE HOLD THE BABY.
COME HERE SWEETIE.
OKAY.
AH...
GEE.
(SNEEZES)
IF YOU'RE SICK,
YOU CAN'T STAY HERE.
JACK JUST GOT OVER A COLD.
SPIKE-
I'M SERIOUS.
EMMA:
MOM, JACK'S NOT IN A BUBBLE.
REALLY?
DO YOU WANT TO BREAST-FEED HIM
WHEN HE'S RUNNING A FEVER?
SIMPSON:
NO AND NEITHER TO YOU.
SO...
(DIALS PHONE)
THERE WE GO.
YES, THAT'S A GOOD BOY.
SIMPSON:
JEREMIAH?
FEEL LIKE HAVING SOME
COMPANY THIS WEEKEND?
(SNEEZES)
SPIKE:
SHH! SHH.
DYLAN:
LET'S PLAY SOME
VOLLEYBALL, MAN,
SPINNER:
WHATEVER YOU LIKE.
OKAY, SO MAYBE IT WAS
A MISTAKE INVITING YOU TODAY.
WELL I COULDN'T LET MY "HONEY"
COME HERE ALL BY HIMSELF.
EARLIER?
SPINNER CALLED ME YOUR HONEY
AND YOU DIDN'T CORRECT HIM.
I DIDN'T THINK
IT WAS THAT BIG A DEAL.
LAST YEAR, FINE.
BUT I'M NOT LYING ANYMORE.
I'M NOT YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
OKAY, FINE THEN.
NO MORE LIES, OKAY?
WE'RE JUST FRIENDS
FROM NOW ON.
HEY GUYS, VOLLEYBALL GAME.
YOU IN?
I AM.
YOU PLAY. I'LL READ.
(LAUGHTER)
SPINNER:
I THOUGHT WE'D KILL THEM,
THE BOYS VERSUS THE GIRLS?
JIMMY:
YEAH PLUS A BIG JUNIOR "A"
HOCKEY STAR.
DYLAN:
GUYS, I'VE FOUR TICKETS
TO OUR EXHIBITION OPENER
ON TUESDAY. YOU WANT 'EM?
JIMMY:
YEAH, SURE.
THANKS WE'LL BE THERE.
PAIGE:
COME ON.
MAN, YOU TOTALLY CREAMED US,
LIKE... BAD.
THE TRICK IS TO TOSS THE BALL
LIGHTLY AND THEN SERVE.
DON'T SLAM...
CONTROL.
PRETEND I'M THE NET,
AND JUST CONCENTRATE
ON GETTING IT OVER.
OKAY.
(NERVOUS EXHALE)
SEE!
YOU'RE A NATURAL.
THANKS.
(ELECTRIC GUITAR)
OKAY, SO I'M THINKING UH,
PUT ANGE TO BED AT EIGHT,
JOEY WON'T GET BACK 'TIL
LIKE AT LEAST MIDNIGHT AND UH...
WE'VE GOT THE HOUSE
PRETTY MUCH TO OURSELVES.
MISSING THE BEACH?
NOT SO BAD AFTER ALL.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
JOEY:
STILL HERE.
WOW. YOU LOOK AWFUL.
NICE TO SEE YOU TOO,
JEREMIAH.
ANGELA:
UNCLE ARCHIE'S HERE! YAY!
HEY!
CRAIG:
UH, JOEY?
OH YEAH, I FORGOT TO TELL YOU.
SNAKE'S SPENDING
THE WEEKEND WITH US.
WHAT?
SIMPSON:
YEAH I GOT A COLD. UH...
SPIKE'S A LITTLE CRAZY
ABOUT GERMS AND THE BABY
RIGHT NOW SO...
OH, SO YOU CAN UH,
COME HERE AND INFECT US.
JOEY:
NO, HE GETS TO HELP OUT
WITH THE BABYSITTING, OKAY?
OKAY, I GOTTA GO,
I'M GONNA BE LATE.
I GO TO PICK UP SYDNEY.
I'LL SEE YOU GUYS LATER.
HAVE FUN!
DIDN'T PLAN ON SPENDING
SATURDAY NIGHT
WITH OL' MR. SIMPSON, HUH?
NO, NOT REALLY.
DYLAN:
LOOKS LIKE THE GUYS
ARE HAVING FUN.
LOOK AT THEM.
PAIGE:
MMM HMM.
SO YOU AND SPIN ARE LIKE
JOINED AT THE HIP.
JIMMY USED TO DATE ASHLEY.
AND... MARCO?
DATES ELLIE.
WHAT?
NOTHING, JUST...I THOUGHT
THAT MAYBE HE MIGHT BE...
YOU KNOW?
NOT EVERYONE IS GAY,
DYLAN.
I'M FREEZING!
WHO'S GAY?
PAIGE:
DYLAN THINKS MARCO IS,
EVEN THOUGH HE AND EL
HAVE BEEN DATING FOREVER.
LIKE I'VE NEVER
DATED ANY GIRLS.
WHAT'S YOUR TAKE
ON THIS HAZEL?
WELL, AS SOMEONE WHO HAD
THE MOST PATHETIC CRUSH
ON MARCO LAST YEAR?
JOIN THE LINE-UP.
HE AND ELLIE ARE SOUL MATES.
SORRY.
NO PROBLEM.
HMM, MOVING ON.
HEY.
PAIGE:
HELLO THERE.
LOOK AT THEM SWEAT.
PAIGE:
WOO! (CAT CALL)
DYLAN:
OH YEAH!
THAT'S JUST WRONG.
WHAT? HE'S GAY.
THAT'S WHAT THEY DO.
YEAH BUT... IT'S GROSS.
I MEAN, TOUCHING ANOTHER GUY,
AND KISSING HIM? IT'S...
BUT YOU WERE ALL OVER
MARCO JUST A SECOND AGO.
YEAH, THAT'S FUNNY.
(FORCED LAUGH)
I MEAN, THEY SHOULD JUST
PUT THEM ALL ON AN ISLAND
OR SOMETHING.
I DON'T KNOW.
JIMMY:
RIGHT, RIGHT,
'CAUSE, YOU KNOW,
THAT'S THE ANSWER, RIGHT?
SIMPSON:
EAT MY POWDER, MANNING.
CRAIG:
OH, NO YOU DON'T.
SIMPSON:
OH YEAH, HERE I COME.
HERE I COME!
CRAIG:
NO, COME ON-
THAT'S IT! THAT'S-
CRAIG:
(GROANS) COME ON.
SIMPSON:
I'M GOING ALL THE WAY
ON THIS ONE.
CRAIG:
NO YOU'RE GOING DOWN, SIMPSON!
SIMPSON:
NO NO NO NO NO! HERE I GO.
CRAIG:
OH NO!
SIMPSON:
YES, YES, YES...
YES! (LAUGHS) YES!
WHO IS THE SULTAN
OF THE SLOPES?
WHO IS THE MASTER
OF THE MOGULS?
(CRASH)
MR. SIMPSON?
I MUST HAVE TAKEN THAT LAST
TURN A LITTLE BIT TOO HARD.
UM... YOU'RE BLEEDING.
SHOULD I CALL SPIKE?
NO!
NO, I'M FINE.
I'M JUST A LITTLE
OVER-STIMULATED.
NEED TO TAKE IT EASY.
ARE YOU SURE?
SIMPSON:
YEAH, I'M FINE.
BUT SPIKE WILL JUST WORRIED
OVER NOTHING.
SO...
ONE MORE SLALOM?
(MUSIC OF VIDEO GAME)
COME ON, MANNING,
TAKE ME ON.
I'LL KILL YOU.
(GUITAR STRUMMING)
JIMMY:
WANT TO SPLIT THAT?
EW! (LAUGHS)
THAT'S JUST GROSS.
OKAY I WANT IT SOFT AND GOOEY,
BUT NOT BURNT CARCINOGENIC SO-
DON'T WORRY.
NOT SO CLOSE TO THE FIRE.
(DISGUSTED SIGH)
THANKS.
(MOCKING)
NOT CLOSE TO THE FIRE.
(LAUGHS)
MARCO, WHY ARE YOU ALL
THE WAY OVER HERE?
ELLIE'S OVER THERE.
GO BE A BOYFRIEND, COME ON.
SO UH...
WHAT YOU PLAYING?
I DON'T KNOW.
NOTHING. JUST...
STRUMMING.
MARCO!
PAIGE:
UM, HON IT'S OKAY,
HE'S YOUR BOYFRIEND.
HE'S NOT MY BOYFRIEND,
ACTUALLY.
WE... WE BROKE UP.
DIDN'T WE, MARCO?
YOU OKAY?
(TEARING UP)
SPINNER:
I CAN'T BELIEVE THEY BROKE UP.
PAIGE:
SORRY, BUT I'M NOT SURPRISED.
ELLIE MUST'VE BEEN
A BLAST TO DATE.
SPINNER:
YEAH, BUT WHY DIDN'T
HE TELL ME?
PAIGE:
'CAUSE MAYBE IT WASN'T
ANY OF YOUR BUSINESS?
UH, WE'RE LIKE
BEST FRIENDS NOW.
WELL, MAYBE THAT'S NOT
ALL HE'S LYING ABOUT.
IT'S STUPID, OKAY?
BUT DYLAN THINKS THAT
MARCO MIGHT BE GAY.
WHAT?
NO, HE'S BEEN WITH ELLIE,
HE'S...
YEAH, LIKE DYLAN NEVER DATED
GIRLS BEFORE HE CAME OUT.
THOUGH YOU GOTTA ADMIT,
THEY WOULD MAKE A CUTE COUPLE.
PAIGE-
WHAT? DYLAN'S A TOTAL CATCH.
SPINNER:
STOP.
MARCO'S NOT GAY,
END OF STORY.
HE SHOOTS, HE SCORES.
CRAIG:
TOO MUCH SUN ON THE WEEKEND,
MARCO?
WHAT ARE YOU WEARING?
JIMMY:
FIRST THE WHOLE
BREAK-UP MYSTERY
AND NOW YOU'VE GOT A SUDDEN
INTEREST IN HOCKEY?
MARCO:
HEY, I LIKE HOCKEY.
AND AS FOR EL...
LOOK MAN, I DON'T KNOW.
I WAS EMBARRASSED, OKAY?
DEL STUDLY, LOSING HIS GIRL.
OH PLEASE, THERE'S PLENTY MORE
FISH IN THE SEA, MY MAN.
SO UM, MARCO
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THE
ANTROPOV TRADE TO THE REDSKINS?
ANTROPOV?
OH MAN, I THINK IT'S GREAT,
I MEAN,
I REALLY THINK THAT HIS...
HIS SKATING SKILLS,
THEY'RE REALLY GONNA HELP.
JIMMY & CRAIG:
(LAUGH)
WHAT?
SPINNER:
REDSKINS ARE FOOTBALL.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
CRAIG:
O-KAY.
(KNOCKS ON WINDOW)
MARCO, HEY.
HEY.
YOU HAVE FUN AT THE BEACH.
YEAH. I MEAN,
IT'S THE BEACH, RIGHT?
FUN'S SORT OF BUILT IN
THERE AND...
YEAH.
COOL. YOU'RE A FAN
OF THE BUDS?
THE MAPLE LEAFS?
YOUR JERSEY.
YEAH, I LOVE 'EM.
UH, THEY'RE A GREAT
HOCKEY TEAM.
HEY BUDDY, BETTER NOT DROP
ANYTHING IN FRONT OF HOMOCHUK.
(LAUGHS)
WHATEVER.
THANKS.
NO PROBLEM.
CRAIG:
HEY, EMMA.
EMMA:
HEY.
DID YOUR HOUSE GUEST
TOTALLY DESTROY YOUR WEEKEND?
CRAIG:
NO, HE UH, HE WAS PRETTY COOL.
EMMA:
SINCE JACK WAS BORN,
MY MOM HAS BEEN
A TOTAL GERM FREAK.
SNAKE'S GOT A COLD,
BIG DEAL.
WHAT?
I JUST... I'M NOT SURE
THAT'S ALL THAT'S WRONG.
MARCO:
HEY GUYS, KELLY,
WHAT'S UP? HOW ARE YOU?
GIRL:
HEY, HOW ARE YOU?
MARCO:
NOT BAD.
HEY, WHAT TIME DID YOU GUYS
LEAVE THE PARTY LAST NIGHT?
GIRL:
REALLY LATE.
MARCO:
YEAH? ANYWAY,
I GOTTA JET, BYE.
YEAH, TAKE CARE GUYS.
GIRL:
SEE YOU HON, BYE.
HATZILAKOS:
OKAY THE FIRST STEP,
YOU'RE GONNA ADD TWO DROPS
OF THE PARAMECIUM CULTURE
TO YOUR SLIDE.
THEN YOU'RE GOING TO ADD ONE
DROP OF THE METHYL CELLULOSE.
THAT'S GOING TO HELP SLOW DOWN
THE MOVEMENT OF THE PARAMECIA.
SO YOU NEVER TOLD ME
WHY YOU AND ELLIE SPLIT.
OH... IT JUST WASN'T WORKING.
SHE WOULDN'T PUT OUT?
SPIN... NO.
WE JUST... WE FELT MORE LIKE
BROTHER AND SISTER.
FRIENDS.
SO UH, WHY DON'T WE GET YOU
A REAL GIRLFRIEND.
WHO? EVERYONE'S PAIRED UP.
NOT HAZEL.
WHAT? I MEAN,
SHE'S SINGLE,
SHE'S... HOT.
SHE, SHE LIKED YOU LAST YEAR.
I MEAN WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
NOTHING.
COOL. HAZEL, GREAT.
GREAT.
I'LL SET IT UP...
FOR TONIGHT.
MANNY:
IT'S A SILENT AUCTION.
ALL PROCEEDS ARE GOING
TO THE JUNIOR SPIRIT
SQUAD CHEER CAMPAIGN.
OUR ROUTINES ARE SO 2001.
I'M SORRY,
WHAT DO I HAVE TO DO AGAIN?
JUST DONATE SOMETHING
FOR OUR SILENT AUCTION,
AND BE THERE FOR THE BIDDING.
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
FINE, FINE, YOU GOT ME.
(SIGHS)
MANNY SHOULD GET INTO SALES.
YEAH.
HEY, IS SOMETHING WRONG?
I DON'T KNOW. IS THERE?
CRAIG TOLD ME YOU PASSED OUT.
(LAUGHS) YEAH AND UH...
THANK YOU FOR THE CONCERN,
BUT I'M NOT THE FIRST PERSON
WITH A COLD
TO GET A LITTLE DIZZY.
BUT WHAT IF IT'S NOT A COLD?
WHAT IF IT'S MORE SERIOUS?
EMMA, WOULD YOU STOP
THINKING THE WORST?
I'M OVER-TIRED,
I'M OVER-WORKED,
AND I- I'VE GOT A COLD.
SO WHAT?
THAT'S ALL IT IS, OKAY?
OKAY, I'M SORRY.
HI, THIS IS ARCHIE SIMPSON,
I'D LIKE TO MAKE AN APPOINTMENT
WITH DOCTOR MORAGODA.
4:30? THIS AFTERNOON, UM...
OKAY. THANKS.
(LAUGHTER)
MARCO:
AND THIS FILM IS ABOUT
THIS WOMAN IN A COMA, RIGHT?
AND HER MALE NURSE
IS HOT FOR HER.
(LAUGHTER)
FOR A CHICK IN A COMA?
THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING?
IT'S DYSFUNCTIONAL.
(LAUGHTER)
HAZEL:
IT SOUNDS HILARIOUS.
SO YOU WANT TO SEE IT AGAIN?
WE COULD GO TOGETHER.
UH, (NERVOUS LAUGH)
YEAH, SOUNDS GOOD.
UM, I'M GETTING KINDA DRY,
DOES ANYONE WANT ANOTHER DRINK?
ON ME?
OKAY.
(EXASPERATED SIGH)
HE'S SO CUTE.
SPINNER:
MAYBE HE NEEDS A LITTLE...
HELP.
HAZEL:
OH.
THOUGHT YOU MIGHT NEED SOME
HELP WITH THOSE DRINKS.
MARCO?
SORRY.
DUDE, JUST IGNORE HER.
TOTALLY.
WE SHOULD ALL GO TO THAT MOVIE.
YOU DON'T LIKE SUBTITLES,
SPIN, BUT...
PAIGE:
(LAUGHS)
YEAH, THEY INVOLVE READING.
HAZEL:
BUT IT MIGHT BE COOL, YOU KNOW,
ALL OF US, FREAKY COMA STORY.
I GOTTA GO.
MY MOM'S MAKING MARINARA SAUCE,
AND I ALWAYS HELP HER.
UH THANKS, HAZEL.
IT'S JUST GETTING KINDA LATE.
DID I DO SOMETHING?
SO DOC, SINCE WHEN HAS
BLOOD-LETTING
BECOME A CURE FOR THE COMMON
COLD, HUH?
DR. MORAGODA:
I WISH IT WERE THAT TRIVIAL.
OH BUT THERE'S NOTHING
TRIVIAL ABOUT A COLD.
SNEEZING, SNIFFLING...
I HAVE TO DO MORE TESTS
AND UH, A BONE MARROW BIOPSY.
BONE MARROW? WHY?
BECAUSE YOUR SYMPTOMS ALL POINT
TO ACUTE MYELOID LEUKEMIA.
CANCER OF THE BLOOD.
CANCER? BUT UH...
DR. MORAGODO:
IT'S A SCARY WORD, I KNOW,
BUT LIKE I SAID WE HAVE
TO RUN MORE TESTS.
THE IMPORTANT THING IS,
IF IT IS CANCER,
WE'VE CAUGHT IT EARLY,
AND WE CAN BEAT IT, OKAY?
SPINNER:
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
LEAVE ME ALONE SPIN.
YOU JUST WALKED OUT
ON YOUR DATE WITH HAZEL.
SHE'S SITTING THERE-
I MEAN IT, SPIN!
PLEASE, BACK OFF!
WHAT'S GOING ON?!
WHAT IS YOUR-
YOU WON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT, THAT YOU'RE PSYCHO?
YOU JUST WALKED OUT
ON A DATE
WITH ONE OF DEGRASSI'S
COOLEST GIRLS
FOR YOU MOM'S PASTA SAUCE?
IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
YES, IT DOES.
SPINNER:
OH YEAH? THEN STOP CRYING
AND EXPLAIN IT TO ME,
'CAUSE I'M OBVIOUSLY A MORON
AND DON'T GET IT.
JUST BECAUSE,
SPIN.
BECAUSE WHY?!
BECAUSE I'M GAY.
(CRYING)