SO... ENGLISH.
YOU READ THE CHAPTER?
CHAPTER TWO,
RIGHT?
YEAH.
(BELL RINGS)
ARMSTRONG:
OKAY, EVERYBODY TAKE YOUR SEATS,
PLEASE.
LET'S GET STARTED.
AMY:
SOUNDS LIKE A GOOD IDEA.
ARMSTRONG:
OKAY, I NEED A VOLUNTEER
TO COME UP
AND EXPAND THESE BRACKETS
AND COLLECT LIKE TERMS.
ANYONE?
EMMA?
EMMA:
OKAY, THE ANSWER
TO THIS PROBLEM IS...
8x SQUARED PLUS...
(CHAIR SCREECHING)
ARMSTRONG:
SEAN. AMY.
DO YOU TWO NEED SOME PRIVACY?
ARE WE IN YOUR WAY HERE?
THANK YOU, EMMA.
ARMSTRONG:
ALL RIGHT, CLASS.
LET'S CONCENTRATE ON OUR WORK.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Hear what I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
SPIKE:
COME LOOK AT SNAKES
BIRTHDAY GIFT.
YOU GOT HIM
A NEW LAPTOP?
A NEW USED ONE.
TO REPLACE
THE ALIENWARE HE LOST.
YOU WANT ME TO RESTORE
HIS BACKUPS?
DO YOU HAVE TIME?
I WANT TO GIVE IT
TO HIM
BEFORE HIS BIRTHDAY
PARTY.
ARE YOU GONNA
INVITE CHRIS TO COME?
MOM, HE JUST BROKE UP
WITH MELANDA
AND I DON'T WANT TO BE
HIS REBOUND.
ARE YOU SURE THERE'S NOTHING
ELSE HOLDING YOU BACK?
EMMA:
SEAN? ANCIENT HISTORY -
JURASSIC.
AND LIKE THE DINOSAURS...
HE'S NOW EXTINCT.
DID YOU SEE AMY
AND SEAN IN MATH?
IT WAS CLASSIC.
AND AWFUL, AND MEAN,
AND HORRIBLE.
AND I HATE SEAN.
THANKS, JT.
BUT YOU DON'T NEED
TO HATE SEAN.
I'M OVER HIM TOTALLY.
TOBY:
EVEN THOUGH HE CARRIES
ON WITH AMY
LIKE YOU NEVER EXISTED?
EMMA:
YES.
EVEN DESPITE
ALL THE RUMOURS?
EMMA:
WHAT RUMOURS?
THAT SEAN'S GANG
IS STEALING STUFF
FROM THE SCHOOL
LEFT AND RIGHT?
EMMA:
BAD KARMA FOR HIM.
WHAT'S IT HAVE
TO DO WITH ME?
WELL, SEAN BREAKS UP
WITH YOU,
SIMPSON'S LAPTOP
GOES MISSING...
SEAN'S DONE
A LOT OF STUFF.
AND AT FIRST, I EVEN
THOUGHT HE MIGHT HAVE...
BUT NO,
THAT'S JUST TOO EVIL.
JIMMY:
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO LEARN TO PARALLEL PARK
BY READING THAT BOOK
TEN MORE TIMES.
HAZEL:
I GET BEHIND THE WHEEL
THIS AFTERNOON.
I AM SO FREAKED!
I'M GONNA BE A DISASTER
ON THE ROAD.
OKAY.
ONE, FOOT ON BRAKE.
TWO, MIRROR CHECK.
THREE-
STOP! DON'T!
OKAY,
NOW'S THE PART
WHERE YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO TICKLE ME BACK
AND THEN WE LAUGH,
ET CETERA...
YEAH, BUT I'M FREAKING OUT,
OKAY?
I'VE BEEN STUDYING
THE BOOK AND I'M LOST.
I'M TOTALLY CLUELESS.
HON-
AND OUR DRIVING INSTRUCTOR,
MS. GONZALEZ, A.K.A. SATAN,
SHE DIDN'T EVEN LET
SULLY TAKE THE TEST.
SO?
SULLY'S A KNOWN DORK.
YEAH, BUT WHAT IF GONZALEZ
HOLDS ME BACK
AND YOU GUYS GET
YOUR LICENSES?
JIMMY:
THEN UH, ME AND PAIGE
WILL DRIVE YOU AROUND.
EVERYTHING WILL BE FINE,
HONEYBEE.
JUST TAKE A PAGE FROM
THE BOOK OF PAIGE
AND TRY A LOWER GEAR,
OKAY?
EMMA:
OKAY. SO I WAS THINKING WE
COULD START THE MEETING
WITH THIS DOCUMENTARY ON
POLLUTION IN THE GREAT LAKES.
ASHLEY:
SOUNDS GOOD.
I'LL PUT THE DVD IN.
UM, WHERE'S THE DVD PLAYER?
EMMA:
WHAT?
OH, IT'S JUST WITH-
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
HAVE ANY OF YOU GUYS SEEN
THE RESOURCE CENTER'S DVD
PLAYER?
IS THAT A QUESTION
OR AN ACCUSATION?
IT'S A QUESTION.
WHAT ABOUT YOU, SEAN,
DO YOU KNOW WHERE IT IS?
NO.
HOW COULD YOU EVEN
ASK ME THAT?
(VOCAL RAP BEATS)
WHAT'S WRONG?
EMMA:
I WAS JUST TRYING
TO REMEMBER
WHAT IT WAS I LIKED
ABOUT HIM.
CHRIS:
HIM?
DON'T BOTHER.
SLIM SHADY AIN'T WORTH
REMEMBERING.
SO... WANT TO GO GET A MILKSHAKE
OR SOMETHING?
EMMA:
YOU MEAN LIKE...
GO ON A DATE?
YEAH.
SO AFTER YOUR MEETING?
PLEASE?
COOL.
YES!
SPINNER:
SORRY. I'M JUST, I'M NERVOUS.
JIMMY:
IT'S OKAY.
MY COUSIN, MEERI,
WAS SO NERVOUS
HER FIRST TIME DRIVING,
THAT SHE RAN OVER HER MOTHER.
TWICE.
(HE PANTOMIMES A CAR CRASH)
SPINNER:
SHUT UP.
HEY, NO GONZALEZ!
("BE STILL MY BEATING HEART"
MUSIC)
♪♪♪
FALCONE:
AFTERNOON, GUYS.
WE HAD TWO FULL CLASSES,
SO YOU'RE STUCK WITH ME
FOR THE IN-CAR.
I'M MR. FALCONE.
PAIGE:
UM, PAIGE MICHALCHUK.
AND MIGHT I SAY,
HOW GOOD IT IS... TO HAVE...
DRIVING LESSONS WITH YOU.
MR. FALCONE:
WELL, I'M GLAD TO HEAR THAT.
WHY DON'T YOU START US OFF,
PAIGE?
OKAY.
SPINNER:
AH, YOU OKAY HONEYBEE?
YOU SEEM A LITTLE NERVOUS.
PAIGE:
ME? NERVOUS? AS IF.
FALCONE:
BEFORE PUTTING THE CAR
INTO DRIVE,
MAKE SURE ALL YOUR
PASSENGERS ARE SEATED
AND WEARING THEIR SEATBELTS.
THE DOORS SHOULD BE
SECURELY CLOSED.
PAIGE:
OKAY. UM, MIRROR CHECK.
SEATBELT. DRIVER
AND PASSENGERS. UM..
FALCONE:
ASSUME PROPER POSITION
ON THE STEERING WHEEL.
WHOA! WHOA!
CAR'S ALREADY RUNNING!
PAIGE:
SORRY!
FALCONE:
IT'S OKAY.
BUT IF THIS WAS A TEST,
YOU'D ALREADY HAVE FAILED.
♪♪♪
YOU'RE FINISHED ALREADY?
CHRIS:
MMM HMM.
SO WHAT ARE YOU DRINKING?
STRAWBERRY?
YOU KNOW, I'VE NEVER REALLY HAD
STRAWBERRY SHAKES AROUND HERE
OR ANYTHING.
OH, REALLY?
CHRIS:
YEAH.
SO, WHY DON'T YOU SLIDE
YOURS ON OVER?
EMMA:
I DON'T THINK SO.
WANT TO GO?
NO. SEAN'S NOT GONNA
RUIN THIS.
CHRIS:
COOL.
SO TELL ME MORE ABOUT THAT
PETITION YOU'RE COLLECTING.
WELL, A LOT OF CITY SEWERS RUN
INTO THE LAKE,
SO OUR BEACHES...
JUST LOOK AT THEM.
THEY THINK THEY CAN JUST
TAKE WHATEVER THEY WANT.
CHRIS:
EMMA.
SEAN:
GO AWAY, EMMA.
EMMA:
ARE YOU GONNA TELL THE MANAGER
WHAT YOU'VE GOT IN YOUR JACKET?
MANAGER:
AND WHAT WOULD THAT BE?
EMMA:
SO WHAT DO YOU DO
WHEN YOU'RE NOT SPINNING?
CHRIS:
WELL, I READ, LISTEN TO MUSIC.
UM... THERE'S THIS BIRTHDAY
PARTY TOMORROW FOR SNAKE.
MMM HMM.
EMMA:
AND I WAS WONDERING IF YOU
MAYBE WANTED TO COME.
BE MY DATE?
SURE.
THAT'LL,
THAT'LL BE COOL.
(HEAVY BASS THUNDERING
FROM A CAR STEREO)
JAY:
WHY ARE YOU ALWAYS GETTING
IN OTHER PEOPLE'S BUSINESS?
EMMA:
YOU WERE TAKING-
JAY:
JUST A FEW CHOCOLATE BARS.
BIG DEAL.
LOOK, WE'RE BANNED FOR LIFE.
CHRIS:
BRETHREN, THEN SO GO EAT
SOMEWHERE ELSE.
SEAN:
COME ON, JAY.
IF THESE GUYS WANNA RUIN MY FUN?
I'LL START RUINING THEIRS.
EMMA:
AND WHAT IS YOUR IDEA
OF FUN, JAY?
STEALING THE SCHOOL'S DVD
PLAYER?
JAY:
LOADS.
BUT STEALING A LAPTOP?
WAY BETTER.
SEAN:
JAY.
JAY:
WHAT'S SHE GONNA DO?
IF SHE'S SMART,
SHE'LL SHUT UP FOR ONCE.
WHAT'RE YOU DOING UP?
COULDN'T SLEEP MUCH.
JACK WAKE YOU?
NO. JACK'S A GOOD SLEEPER.
ME SINCE CHEMO?
NOT SO GOOD.
OH, PLEASE. NOT AGAIN.
WHAT A PIECE OF JUNK!
SIMPSON:
HEY, IT WAS THE BEST
YOUR MOM COULD AFFORD
AND I'M TOUCHED.
ALL IT NEEDS IS A LITTLE
FINE TUNING.
I'LL UPGRADE THE RAM.
EMMA:
SHE SHOULDN'T HAVE HAD TO BUY
YOU A NEW ONE
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
SIMPSON:
WELL, IF I HADN'T LOST
MY LAST ONE.
EMMA:
YOU DIDN'T LOSE IT.
SIMPSON:
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
EMMA:
NOTHING.
I DON'T MEAN ANYTHING.
I'M JUST TIRED.
I'M GONNA GO HAVE A SHOWER,
OKAY?
SIMPSON:
OKAY.
CHRIS:
EMMA, I GOT THE COOLEST CD
FOR SIMPSON'S BIRTHDAY-
WE NEED TO GET
THAT LAPTOP.
WELL GOOD LUCK.
THEY SOLD IT
THE DAY THEY STOLE IT.
SO WHAT ARE WE
SUPPOSED TO DO?
TELL MR. RADITCH?
THAT JAY SORT OF,
KIND OF CONFESSED?
WE NEED PROOF.
WE NEED
TO GET SEAN.
SPINNER:
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
I GIVE YOU A DRIVING LEGEND,
PAIGE MICHALCHUK.
JIMMY:
SHE'S KILLED MORE ORANGE
PYLONS THAN ANYBODY
IN DEGRASSI'S HISTORY.
SPINNER:
MURDERER!
YOU SQUISHED
MY PYLON MOMMY!
YOU FLATTENED
MY PYLON BROTHER!
SPIN, STOP IT!
(BELL RINGS)
ARMSTRONG:
OKAY, TODAY WE'RE GOING TO
DISCUSS FACTORING POLYNOMIALS.
WORD HAS IT,
YOUR DRIVING INSTRUCTOR
IS QUITE THE LOOKER.
REALLY.
I HADN'T NOTICED.
THAT'S WHY
YOU GOT NERVOUS.
YOU HAVE
THE HOTS FOR HIM.
HAZEL, SOME OF US
ARE TRYING TO GET
AN EDUCATION HERE,
OKAY?
ANNOUNCEMENT:
A SERIOUS ANNOUNCEMENT
WITH REGARDS TO THE ENGLISH
DEPARTMENTS MISSING DVD PLAYER.
IF ANYONE HAS SEEN THE PLAYER,
I'D LIKE TO HEAR ABOUT IT.
BE ASSURED THAT ALL TIPS
WILL BE MUCH APPRECIATED...
SEAN:
NANCY DREW.
WHY ARE YOU FOLLOWING ME?
EMMA:
I WASN'T.
SEAN:
THEY'RE FOR SHOP.
WHAT, DID YOU THINK THERE WAS
GONNA BE A DVD PLAYER IN THERE?
LOOK, I KNOW OUR BREAK-UP
SUCKED
AND I'M SORRY
YOU GOT HURT, OKAY?
BUT THAT WAS MONTHS AGO.
AND WHAT I DO
WITH JAY AND WITH AMY?
IS NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
SPINNER:
JIMMY, PUT ON YOUR CRASH
HELMET!
PAIGE:
SO I BLEW MY FIRST LESSON
WITH FALCONE.
IT COULD HAPPEN TO ANYBODY.
JIMMY:
AH, BUT IT DIDN'T.
IT HAPPENED TO YOU.
HAZEL:
PLEASE. SHE WOULDN'T HAVE HAD
ANY TROUBLE WITH GONZALEZ.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
FALCONE'S A GREAT
INSTRUCTOR. I LIKED HIM.
YOU'RE NOT
THE ONLY ONE.
HAZEL.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I GET IT.
FALCONE IS HOT, RIGHT?
OKAY, MARCO.
I'M NOT THE ONE
WHO THINKS SO.
YOUR GIRLFRIEND IS.
WAIT... YOU HAVE
A CRUSH ON FALCONE?
NO...
WAIT, HONEYBEE.
HEY.
WHAT'S UP?
SO, HOW ARE THINGS
GOING WITH EMMA?
SEAN REALLY MESSED
HER UP GOOD, DIDN'T HE?
JT:
YEAH.
I WOULDN'T WANT TO BE
HER NEXT BOYFRIEND.
NO OFFENSE.
REBOUNDS SUCK.
CHRIS, WE NEED
TO DO SOMETHING.
CHRIS:
EMMA, I TOLD YOU,
THE COMPUTER'S LONG GONE.
I KNOW, BUT THE DVD PLAYER
ISN'T.
OKAY.
I WAS BEEN THINKING.
IF WE CAN GET RADITCH
TO SEARCH JAY'S CAR,
WHO KNOWS WHAT
HE MIGHT FIND.
IF I HELP,
YOU'LL LET THIS GO?
I PROMISE.
RADITCH:
I WANT TO CATCH WHOEVER
IS RESPONSIBLE.
IF YOU KNOW ANYTHING,
ALL TIPS ARE ANONYMOUS.
CAN YOU BACK UP YOUR CHARGES?
CHRIS:
WELL, MR. RADITCH-
EMMA:
OF COURSE WE CAN.
RADITCH:
OKAY. THE DVD PLAYER.
WHEN DID YOU SEE THE CRIME
TAKE PLACE?
CHRIS:
SIR. WE DIDN'T EXACTLY-
EMMA:
UM, YESTERDAY...
AROUND 4:00 P.M.,
CHRIS AND I SAW SEAN CAMERON
AND JAY HOGART
LOADING SOME OF THE EQUIPMENT
INTO JAY'S CIVIC.
RADITCH:
MS. SMITH?
COULD YOU PUT A CALL IN
TO SERGEANT GRAHAM, PLEASE?
THANK YOU.
FALCONE:
THERE'S A STOP SIGN AHEAD.
YEAH, I SEE IT,
OKAY?
OKAY.
AND YOU'RE JUST GOING TO
MAKE A LEFT.
YEAH.
I KNOW WHAT I'M DOING!
DUDE, YOU THINK
YOU'RE SO GOOD?
PAIGE:
SPIN, STOP.
UH, PAIGE,
NO DISTRACTING GAVIN.
YOU DID EXTREMELY
WELL TODAY,
BUT GAVIN REALLY NEEDS
TO IMPROVE.
YEAH, EXTREMELY WELL,
HUH?
WHAT'S THE WORD...
OH! FAVOURITISM.
GAVIN.
SPINNER:
TEACHER'S PET.
FALCONE:
GAVIN, WATCH-
FOR THE INNOCENT FAMILY?
SHE'S MY GIRLFRIEND,
DUDE!
GAVIN, WATCH THE-
(CRASH)
THE CAR.
JAY:
LET ME GUESS,
NOTHING IN THERE?
RADITCH:
KEEP LOOKING, OFFICERS.
THE ANONYMOUS TIP -
IT WAS YOU.
YOU KNOW
I'M ON PROBATION.
RADITCH:
SOMETHING YOU WANT TO SAY,
MR. CAMERON?
SEAN:
YEAH. GO TO HELL!
RADITCH:
I'LL SEE YOU IN DETENTION
EVERY SATURDAY FOR
THE NEXT TWO MONTHS.
EMMA:
CHRIS, WHERE'VE YOU BEEN?
DID YOU HEAR THE NEWS?
THEY FOUND NOTHING
IN JAY'S CAR.
I MEAN ABOUT SEAN.
TWO MONTHS OF SATURDAY
DETENTION
FOR MOUTHING OFF
TO RADITCH.
SO WHAT ABOUT
SIMPSON'S COMPUTER?
WHAT ABOUT IT?
I THOUGHT THAT'S WHY
YOU DID ALL THIS.
IT WAS.
BUT NOW SEAN'S
FINALLY GONNA PAY
FOR WHAT HE DID TO ME.
OR SNAKE.
WHAT HE DID TO SNAKE.
YOU LIED TO RADITCH.
SO? EVERYBODY KNOWS
WHO'S BEEN STEALING.
SEAN'S FINALLY GETTING
WHAT HE DESERVES.
NO, HE ISN'T.
JUST FACE IT EM,
YOU'RE NOT OVER HIM...
CHRIS.
AND I'M JUST WASTING
MY TIME.
SPIKE:
HERE WE GO.
SIMPSON:
WOW.
THAT'S AWESOME.
SPIKE:
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
MAKE A WISH.
(CHEERING)
OH, I FORGOT A KNIFE.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
HEY, HOW IS IT GOING, MAN?
THANKS FOR COMING.
MAN:
HEY MAN, HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
SIMPSON:
SO, RUMOUR HAS IT YOUR NEW BEAU
IS COMING BY THIS EVENING.
UH, HE CAN'T MAKE IT.
HE'S BUSY HATING
MY GUTS RIGHT NOW.
TOTALLY MY FAULT -
I WENT PSYCHO.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED
WITH YOU AND CHRIS,
BUT IF HE'S WORTH HIS SALT,
HE'LL CUT YOU SOME SLACK.
I'M WORKING,
OKAY?
AND EVERY DOLLAR I MAKE
FOR THE NEXT TEN YEARS
GOES RIGHT TO FIXING
THAT STUPID CAR SO...
SO PRETEND
I'M A CUSTOMER, OKAY?
I'LL HAVE A CLUBHOUSE
SANDWICH,
WITH A SIDE ORDER OF -
SPINNER:
OF FALCONE?
ANYWAY, I CAN'T TAKE YOUR
ORDER.
I'M JUST THE DISHPIG,
REMEMBER?
PAIGE:
BUT YOU'RE MY DISHPIG -
MY INSANELY JEALOUS DISHPIG.
SPINNER:
I'M ONLY JEALOUS
'CAUSE I CARE.
PAIGE:
I KNOW, HONEY.
YOU PRACTICALLY DESTROYED
A CAR FOR ME.
SPINNER:
SO, I GUESS YOU WON'T BE MAD
WHEN YOU FIND OUT
I SWITCHED US BACK TO GONZALEZ?
NO.
ALTHOUGH I WILL MISS
THOSE DIMPLES,
AND THAT CHISELED JAW.
I'M KIDDING.
I'M TOTALLY KIDDING.
I LOVE THAT ONE.
TRACK THREE.
EM?
I WAS HOPING
YOU'D BE HERE.
LUCKY.
I LIKE IT BETTER
WHEN YOU SMILE,
AND I THINK YOU HAVE GREAT
TASTE IN HATS,
AND EVEN BETTER TASTE
IN MUSIC...
AND I LOVE IT THAT YOU
MAKE ME FEEL FUN AGAIN.
I THINK YOU SHOULD
GIVE ME ANOTHER CHANCE.
YOU DO?
I PROMISE NEVER TO TALK
ABOUT SEAN AGAIN.
YEAH?
OKAY, ONCE MORE.
ONLY TO SAY THAT
I ONLY DID WHAT I DID
BECAUSE HE BROKE MY HEART.
IS IT FEELING
ANY BETTER?
IT MIGHT...
IF YOU'D COME OVER
FOR SOME BIRTHDAY CAKE.
THAT'D BE NICE.