JIMMY:
KID ELRICK'S NEW CD IS AMAZING.
IT'S GOT A TOTALLY NEW SOUND.
CRAIG:
HEY GUYS.
CHECK THIS OUT.
JIMMY:
WHAT IS IT?
MARCO (READING):
"DOES YOUR BAND HAVE THE HEAT
TO MAKE HOT SOUNDS IN T.O.?"
JIMMY (READING):
"WIN TWO DAYS OF STUDIO TIME
AND RECORD YOUR OWN SINGLE?"
CRAIG:
IT'S EXACTLY THE KIND
OF EXPOSURE WE NEED RIGHT NOW.
JIMMY:
THEN WE GET THE LIMOS,
THE PRIVATE JETS,
THE BLINGITY BLING.
SPINNER:
THE PANTIES FLYING AT US
ON STAGE.
CRAIG:
MAN, WE HAVE TO WIN THIS.
ASHLEY:
EXCUSE US, POSERS.
ELLIE:
REAL MUSICIANS COMING THROUGH.
CRAIG:
OH YOU'RE SIGNING UP? COOL.
A LITTLE UH, COMPETITION
NEVER HURT.
ASHLEY:
'CAUSE NOTHING EVER GETS
IN THE WAY OF WHAT CRAIG WANTS.
NOT EMOTIONS, HONESTY,
OTHER PEOPLE'S FEELINGS...
CRAIG:
YOU HEAR THAT?
SHE STILL HATES ME.
AND THAT'S WHY
THE GIRLS AND I
ARE GONNA BLOW YOU RIGHT OFF
THE STAGE.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Hear what I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
CRAIG:
SUBTERRANEAN SEISMIC...
(SINGS) OVERLOADS THE CIRCUITS
OF MY...
BLAH BLAH BLAH BLAH
BLAH BLAH BLAH BLAH.
THIS BLOWS.
MARCO:
YEAH BUT ASHLEY'S BEEN PLAYING
PIANO FOR WHAT? TWELVE YEARS?
AND PAIGE IS REALLY GOOD.
AND THEN THERE'S HAZEL-
CRAIG:
MARCO, RELAX.
THERE'S NO WAY I'M GONNA
LET MY EX-GIRLFRIEND
BEAT ME IN A BAND COMPETITION.
SO YOU GUYS LEARNED THIS SONG?
JIMMY
YEAH. YEAH,
WE LISTENED ALL DAY.
ARE THE LYRICS READY?
WELL HOW ABOUT YOU JUST
CONCENTRATE
ON GETTING THE SONG DOWN, OKAY?
ONE, TWO. ONE, TWO, THREE.
(BAND PLAYS)
GUYS!
(EVERYONE STOPS BUT DRUMS)
GUYS! WHAT WAS THAT?!
(DRUMMING)
(WHACK)
DUDE, TAKE IT EASY!
JIMMY, HAVE YOU EVER HEARD
OF TUNING?
MARCO? IT'S A BASS, MAN.
YOU PLAY ONE NOTE AT A TIME.
AND SPINNER-
JIMMY:
OKAY. ALL RIGHT. JUST CHILL.
LOOK, IT'S JUST A SONG,
ALL RIGHT?
CRAIG:
RIGHT. IT'S JUST A SONG.
LET ME TUNE YOUR GUITAR.
HAZEL:
I TOTALLY GET HOW YOU FEEL,
ASHLEY.
I WAS CREEPED OUT BY THE WHOLE
HOSPITAL THING AT FIRST.
PAIGE
BUT TER IS LIKE 200% BETTER,
PINK CHEEKS,
SHE COULD WAKE UP ANY MINUTE.
ASHLEY:
ALL RIGHT, I'LL GO WITH
YOU GUYS NEXT TIME,
AFTER WE WIN THE BAND THING.
WE'LL TELL HER ABOUT IT.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
GOOD MORNING.
WE'LL BEGIN TODAY BY READING
CONTRIBUTIONS
FROM YOUR CREATIVE WRITING
JOURNALS.
WHO'S FIRST?
THESE ARE THE LYRICS
TO A SONG I JUST WROTE.
"BLACK TWISTED AGONY,
THE FIRES OF CHAOS BURN ON.
RUN FOR HER TOMBSTONE
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
THE BLOOD RUNS COLD
IN HER VEINS."
CRAIG:
(SNICKERS)
GREAT UH...
JUST GREAT.
LET'S SAVE OUR DISCUSSION UNTIL
WE'VE HEARD MORE, SHALL WE?
ASHLEY:
I CAN'T BELIEVE NOBODY SAID
A THING ABOUT MY SONG.
PAIGE:
UM, HON, I DON'T THINK ANYONE
GOT IT.
ASHLEY:
IT'S ABOUT A GIRL WHO DIED
IN THE SPANISH CIVIL WAR.
CRAIG:
YEAH, UM...
I FEEL HER PAIN. (LAUGHS)
ELLIE:
I HATE TO BE BRUTAL...
BUT YOU'RE GOING TO ANYWAY.
ELLIE
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO WRITE ABOUT
THINGS YOU'VE EXPERIENCED.
HAZEL:
YEAH, LIKE YOUR EX.
I JUST CAN'T PRETEND
TO FORGIVE OR FORGET.
GONNA MAKE THE DAY YOU MET ME
A DAY YOU'LL REGRET.
I THINK CRAIG'S IN TROUBLE.
JOEY:
UH ANGIE,
BE CAREFUL WITH THAT BAG
IT HAS THE EGGS IN IT, OKAY?
ANGELA:
I KNOW.
AUNTIE CAITLIN!
WATCH!
(SMASH)
ANGELA ELIZABETH,
WHAT DID I JUST SAY?
HEY.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
JOEY:
YOU SEE THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN LITTLE GIRLS
DON'T GO TO BED ON TIME.
CAITLIN:
DON'T CRY, ANGIE. COME ON.
OH SHE'S FINE.
CAITLIN
I KNOW.
YOU WANT TO SEE SOMETHING
REALLY COOL?
WATCH THIS!
WOO!
CAN YOUR FUDDY DUDDY DADDY
DO THAT? HUH?
ANGELA
NO!
HE'S OLD AND NO FUN!
REALLY?
WATCH THIS.
I AM A FUN MACHINE.
(CRASH) OH!
CAITLIN:
OH JOEY! ARE YOU OKAY?
JOEY:
OH. OH NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
(MUTED MUSIC PLAYS)
CRAIG:
ASHLEY.
WAIT.
LISTEN.
I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT
THINGS BETWEEN US AND...
I RESPECT YOU TOO MUCH
FOR THINGS TO KEEP GOING
ON LIKE THIS.
AND YOU'RE NOT
SHOUTING AT ME.
I'M GONNA TAKE THAT
AS A GOOD SIGN.
IF YOU HAVE SOMETHING TO SAY
THEN I WANT TO HEAR IT.
GOOD.
(SIGHS) SO...
I'M SORRY I MADE FUN
OF YOUR LYRICS EARLIER.
YOU'RE A REALLY GOOD WRITER,
AND MUSICIAN,
AND THAT WASN'T FAIR.
THIS IS ABOUT MY LYRICS?
YEAH. WHAT DID YOU THINK?
I DON'T KNOW,
WHAT WAS I THINKING?
ANGELA AND CAITLIN:
(PLAY AND SHOUT)
CAITLIN:
WATCH OUT BAD GUYS!
JOEY:
AH, NO, NO, NO. ANGIE PLEASE!
NO, NO, NO. OFF. OFF.
CAITLIN:
SWEETIE, HE'S A GOOD GUY.
JOEY:
OH.
ANGIE DO DADDY A FAVOUR, OKAY?
GO UPSTAIRS,
GO GET YOUR BARBIE SUITCASE
AND PUT SOME THINGS IN IT,
OKAY?
YOUR TOOTHBRUSH,
YOUR GOTCHIES...
ANGELA:
OOH, BARBIE SUITCASE!
JOEY:
CAITLIN, GET ME THE PHONE,
PLEASE.
ANGIE'S GONNA STAY WITH MY MOM
'TIL I FEEL BETTER.
CRAIG CAN HELP ME OUT
AROUND HERE.
WHY DON'T YOU LET ME HELP OUT?
(LAUGHS) UM, THANK YOU.
UH, BUT YOU'RE BUSY.
I CAN'T IMPOSE
ON YOU LIKE THAT.
I DON'T MIND.
WHAT?
JOEY:
WELL...
IT'S NOT ALL FUN AND GAMES.
SOMETIMES SHE NEEDS
A FIRM HAND.
YOU DON'T THINK I CAN DO IT,
DO YOU?
I THINK YOU'RE GREAT WITH HER.
I JUST THINK YOU'RE MORE
FRIEND-GREAT THAN PARENT-GREAT.
ANGIE, YOU CAN STOP PACKING!
I'M GONNA TAKE CARE OF YOU TWO.
(GUYS PLAY)
OKAY, GUYS,
UH, GOOD LUCK IN THE COMPETITION
TOMORROW NIGHT.
SPINNER:
YEAH, WE'RE GONNA HAVE LYRICS
BY THEN, RIGHT?
CRAIG:
I GOT IT COVERED.
ARMSTRONG:
UP NEXT,
HELL HATH NO FURY.
UM, THIS SONG, IT HAS LYRICS.
(GIRLS START TO PLAY)
♪ THIS SONG IS A PRIZE
FOR BREAKING MY HEART ♪
♪ SHOULD HAVE WRITTEN
THESE WORDS TO YOU ♪
♪ RIGHT FROM THE START ♪
♪ YOU SAY IT DOESN'T MATTER,
IT'S ALL IN THE PAST ♪
♪ MY PAIN DOESN'T SHOW
IT'S DISGUISED BY THIS MASK ♪
♪ BUT I CAN'T PRETEND
TO FORGIVE AND FORGET ♪
♪ GONNA MAKE THE DAY
YOU MET ME ♪
♪ A DAY YOU'LL REGRET. ♪
♪ CUZ YOU'RE THE DUST IN MY EYE
YOU'RE THE ROCK IN MY SHOE ♪
♪ YEAH, YOU LIE, LIE, LIE... ♪
CAITLIN:
EAT YOUR BREAKFAST, SCAMPY.
JOEY:
OH, YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THIS.
CAITLIN:
IT'S FINE.
I GOT JUST ENOUGH TIME TO DROP
HER OFF BEFORE MY MEETING.
ANGELA:
I DON'T LIKE THIS.
JOEY:
TOO BAD. EAT UP.
CAITLIN:
I CAN HANDLE THIS, THANK YOU.
UM, HOW ABOUT SOME TOAST?
NO.
CEREAL?
I WANT PANCAKES!
JOEY:
ANGELA!
PANCAKES WITH SYRUP!
JOEY:
ANGIE...
CAITLIN:
OKAY. UH, PANCAKES...
WE CAN DO IT. COMING UP.
UM... (DIALS CELL PHONE)
DOLLY, HI, IT'S CAITLIN. UM...
WOULD YOU TELL STEVE I'M GONNA
BE JUST A LITTLE BIT LATE.
AUNTIE CAITLIN!
(PLOP)
JOEY:
GOOD MORNING,
BREAKFAST CALLING.
PLEASE LEAVE YOUR BACON
AFTER THE TONE.
SIMPSON:
WELL, THAT DATABASE SEEMS
TO BE WORKING.
CRAIG:
THOSE LYRICS OF YOURS?
NOT COOL.
ASHLEY:
TYPICAL.
SELF-ABSORBED CRAIG ACTUALLY
THINKS THE SONG'S ABOUT HIM.
ELLIE:
WOW. SO VAIN.
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
YOU ATTACK ME EVERY TIME
I PASS YOU IN THE HALL
AND NOW YOU'RE PERFORMING THAT?
WELL, WHAT DID YOU EXPECT?
"FOR HE'S A JOLLY GOOD FELLOW"?
ASH, I SWEAR, IF YOU PLAY THAT
SONG IN THE COMPETITION, I'LL-
HAVE SEX WITH MORE GRADE NINES?
GUYS. SETTLE DOWN, PLEASE.
CRAIG:
YOU KNOW, IF YOU WEREN'T
SUCH A PRUDE,
I'D NEVER HAVE BEEN
WITH MANNY.
OH, BUT I THOUGHT
YOU LOVED HER.
OH YOU KNOW WHAT? GO-
SIMPSON:
HEY!
ONE MORE WORD,
DOUBLE HOMEWORK.
SPINNER:
DUDE, WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
I'M OUT OF THE CONTEST.
I JUST WANTED TO TELL YOU GUYS.
JIMMY:
WHAT? CRAIG, YOU CAN'T JUST-
CRAIG:
NO.
ASHLEY'S WON ALREADY.
SO JUST FORGET IT, OKAY?
NO. WE'RE NOT FORGETTING IT.
AND IF ASHLEY WANTS A WAR,
WELL, WE HAVE THE AMMO,
MY FRIEND.
WE HAVE THE AMMO.
HIT IT, BROOKS.
(MUSIC PLAYS)
(RAPPING) OUR HOMEY IS A PLAYA
AND THAT IS ALL
SO WHY'D YOU HAVE TO GO
AND KICK HIS-
SPINNER:
BALL AND CHAIN
AIN'T THAT YOUR NAME?
'CAUSE YOU A PLAYA-HATER
AND THAT'S A SHAME
JIMMY:
AND CHICKS LIKE YOU
AIN'T WORTH TOO MUCH.
SO SHUT UP GIRL-
JIMMY AND SPINNER:
AND MAKE MY LUNCH.
YEAH.
CRAIG. ME AND YOU. WALK.
CRAIG:
THAT RAP IS NEVER LEAVING
OUR GARAGE.
MARCO:
WHICH IS WHY YOU NEED
TO WRITE US LYRICS, OKAY?
A.S.A.P.
CRAIG:
MARCO...
MARCO
WELL, WHAT DO YOU HAVE SO FAR.
LOOK, MAYBE I CAN HELP.
CRAIG:
LOOK, I'M BLOCKED, OKAY?
I MEAN, THIS WHOLE THING
WITH ASH AND MANNY...
IT'S LIKE I TRY AND WRITE
AND NOTHING COMES OUT.
SO GLAD I'M NOT INTO GIRLS.
OKAY.
(YELLS)
HAVE YOU LOST IT?!
WHAT? CLEARS MY HEAD.
GO. TRY IT.
NO!
IT GETS THE CREATIVE JUICES
FLOWING. JUST-
NO. I'M NOT DOING THAT.
THEN IT'S SPINNER'S SEXIST RAP.
OKAY.
(PATHETIC YELL)
NO. YOU HAVE TO DO IT
LIKE YOU MEAN IT.
GO.
(HUGE YELL)
NO. SORRY. NOTHING.
JOEY:
SO DID YOU AND AUNTIE CAITLIN
HAVE FUN SHOPPING TODAY?
ANGELA:
IT WAS OKAY.
I'M GONNA GO OUT AND PLAY.
SWEETIE, I NEED YOU TO WASH
YOUR HANDS FOR DINNER.
ANGELA:
FIVE MINUTES.
CAILTIN:
NO. I NEED YOU TO WASH
THEM NOW.
ANGELA:
BYE!
STOP RIGHT THERE, MISSY!
WASH THOSE HANDS, NOW!
YOU HEARD ME.
I HATE YOU!
MARCO:
IS THAT CRAIG?
YOU LIKE? IT'S AMAZING WHAT
YOU CAN DO
WITH A COMPUTER THESE DAYS.
CRAIG:
I GIVE UP.
ASHLEY:
AND SORRY, I CARE WHY?
ALL YOU CARE ABOUT IS MAKING
MY LIFE A LIVING HELL.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT MY LIFE'S BEEN LIKE
FOR THE PAST FEW MONTHS?
PLEASE, NOT THIS AGAIN.
ASHLEY:
YOU THINK THIS T-SHIRT'S HARD
TO DEAL WITH, OR OUR SONG?
I WANTED TO DIE, CRAIG.
I FELT THAT BAD.
OKAY. WELL, YOU'RE NOT
LISTENING-
ASHLEY:
NO. IT'S NOT OKAY.
IT'LL NEVER BE OKAY.
CRAIG:
I'M SORRY.
OKAY?
I'M SORRY. I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY!
HOW MANY TIMES
DO I HAVE TO SAY IT?!
UNTIL YOU MEAN IT.
♪ YOU SAY IT DOESN'T MATTER,
IT'S ALL IN THE PAST ♪
♪ MY PAIN DOESN'T SHOW
IT'S DISGUISED BY THIS MASK ♪
♪ BUT I CAN'T PRETEND
TO FORGIVE AND FORGET ♪
♪ GONNA MAKE THE DAY
YOU MET ME ♪
♪ A DAY YOU'LL REGRET. ♪
♪ CUZ YOU'RE THE DUST IN MY EYE
YOU'RE THE ROCK IN MY SHOE ♪
♪ YEAH, YOU LIE, LIE, LIE... ♪
♪ BETTER WATCH WHAT YOU SAY
CUZ I'M ON TO YOU ♪
♪ MR. NICE GUY. ♪
♪ WHOA-OA-OA-OA-OA ♪
YOU'RE SO NICE.
AUDIENCE:
(ENTHUSIASTIC CHEERS)
OKAY, SO THEY'RE GOOD.
SPINNER:
EVEN IF THEY SUCKED,
WE DON'T HAVE A CHANCE
WITHOUT A SINGER.
LIBERTY:
I HAVE YOU DOWN
AS A ROCK QUARTET.
SHALL I DOWNGRADE
TO A POWER TRIO?
OUR SINGER WILL BE HERE
ANY SECOND.
WELL, IT BETTER BE
ONE OF THE NEXT 60.
ON IN ONE MINUTE!
ASH GOT TO HIM.
IT'S OBVIOUS.
SO, WE'LL DO IT WITHOUT CRAIG.
WITH MY LYRICS.
AUDIENCE:
(ENTHUSIASTIC CHEERS)
CHRIS WOODWARD:
WOW. THOSE GIRLS KNOCKED
THAT ONE OUT OF THE PARK!
NEXT UP TO BAT
WE GOT THE DOWNTOWN SASQUATCH.
AUDIENCE:
(SMATTERING OF APPLAUSE)
SPINNER:
UH, HI WE'RE DOWNTOWN
SASQUATCH.
WOO!
UH, OKAY, AND UH...
HERE'S A LITTLE SONG WE LIKE
TO CALL...
WE'RE STILL THINKING OF A NAME
FOR IT.
WOO!
AUDIENCE:
(LAUGHS)
SPINNER:
AND IT GOES A LITTLE SOMETHING
LIKE THIS.
(COUNTS BEATS ON DRUM STICKS)
SPIN!
CRAIG:
AND...
IT GOES LIKE THIS.
♪ I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU'LL FORGIVE ME ♪
♪ FOR BEING SO BLIND
TO HOW YOU FELT ♪
♪ DON'T ASK ME WHY
I COULDN'T SEE IT ♪
♪ AND THAT'D TAKE ME YEARS
TO FIGURE OUT ♪
♪ AND THAT'S NOT SOMETHING
I KNOW MUCH ABOUT ♪
♪ BUT THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
TO FIND OUT ♪
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH! ♪
♪ WHAT I KNOW
IS THAT I HURT YOU ♪
IS THAT I SUCK ♪
♪ AND WHAT I KNOW
IS THAT I'M SORRY ♪
♪ WHAT I KNOW
IS THAT I'M LOSER ♪
♪ AND YEAH, WHAT I KNOW
IS I SCREWED UP ♪
♪ AND THEN I NEVER EARNED
YOUR TRUST ♪
♪ WHAT I KNOW
IS THAT EVERYTHING I TOUCH ♪
♪ JUST TURNS TO DUST ♪
AUDIENCE:
(CHEERS WILDLY)
JOEY:
HOW'D IT GO?
CAITLIN
SHE STILL WON'T EVEN
OPEN THE DOOR.
I FEEL HORRIBLE.
JOEY:
WELL, AT LEAST SHE'S NOT
OLD ENOUGH TO STEAL YOUR CAR.
THAT WAS CRAIG'S VERSION
OF "THE TEST".
IT WAS LIKE MY MOTHER'S VOICE
CAME RIGHT OUT OF MY MOUTH.
JOEY:
WELL, IT HAPPENS TO
THE BEST OF US.
LOOK, I THINK IT'S GREAT
THAT YOU AND ANGIE GET ALONG
BUT YOU CAN'T JUST
BE HER FRIEND.
SHE'S JUST A KID.
YOU HAVE TO SET LIMITS.
YEAH.
BUT I CALLED HER MISSY.
(LAUGHS) IT'S CATCHY.
WELL, THAT'S SOMETHING.
YOU DID GREAT.
SHE MAY NOT LIKE YOU RIGHT NOW
BUT SHE RESPECTS YOU.
I'D RATHER HAVE THE LIKE
PART BACK.
YOU WILL.
JUST STICK AROUND, OKAY?
SPINNER AND MARCO:
(LAUGHS EXCITEDLY)
YEAH! WE WON! WE WON!
JIMMY:
YES. (LAUGHS)
MARCO:
GOOD JOB, BUDDY!
SPINNER:
OH, ARE YOU HERE TO BRING
US DOWN? BECAUSE...
WE WON FAIR AND SQUARE.
YEAH, YOU DID. CONGRATULATIONS.
AND CRAIG...
NICE LYRICS.
THEY WERE JUST RIGHT.
THANKS.