STUDENTS:
(CELEBRATORY CHATTER)
PAIGE:
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE BEAT THEM
SIX TO TWO.
AND DID YOU SEE SULLY
BEND THAT LAST KICK
BEFORE HE SCORED?!
SULLY:
PAM! WAIT UP.
HEY SULLY, SULLY.
UM...
YOU, YOU DID GREAT TODAY.
CONGRATULATIONS.
THANKS.
SOMEONE HAS A CRUSH.
SO YOU THINK
HE'D BE INTERESTED?
IN YOU? UH...
UM, SPIN DOESN'T WANT
TO BE BRUTAL, SO UH, I WILL.
SULLY? YOU'RE UM...
YOU'RE NOT REALLY HIS TYPE.
BUT I CAN THINK OF TEN GUYS
YOU WOULD BE ADORABLE WITH.
I DON'T WANT TO BE ADORABLE.
BUNNIES AND PUPPIES
ARE ADORABLE.
HON, IF YOU DON'T WANT
TO BE CUTE, DON'T BE.
JUST CHANGE YOUR IMAGE,
SIMPLE AS THAT.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Hear what I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I can see it ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
EMMA:
THIS CLUB WILL BE MY MISSION
FOR THE YEAR.
I'M CALLING IT SITE:
"STUDENTS IMPROVING
THE ENVIRONMENT".
MANNY:
COOL.
EMMA:
WE'LL HAVE LETTER WRITING
CAMPAIGNS,
AN ENDANGERED SPECIES WEEK...
YOU WANNA HEAR MY MISSION?
I WANT TO BE HOT.
NOT CUTE, NOT ADORABLE... HOT.
WOW.
MANNY:
THERE'S NO WAY I'M GETTING
DUMPED THIS YEAR
FOR BEING "TOO YOUNG".
♪♪♪
OOF!
ANGELA:
WHERE'S MY JUICE?
JOEY:
AW SHOOT, DADDY ALWAYS
FORGETS SOMETHING.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
I NEVER FORGET
THE ANGIE FUEL!
ATTA BOY!
HERE YOU GO.
YES.
JOEY:
SO, READY TO CELEBRATE
TONIGHT?
YOUR GROUNDING,
FOR SKIPPING CLASS?
FINITO.
YES! MAN OUR BAND SO
NEEDS THEIR LEAD SINGER BACK.
BAND? YOU GUYS HAVE A BAND?
WELL YEAH.
I MEAN WE DON'T EVEN
HAVE A NAME YET, BUT UH...
THIS IS SO COOL!
DID I EVER TELL YOU GUYS
I WAS IN A BAND?
LIKE A MILLION TIMES.
JOEY:
HEY, UH, YOU GUYS...
WHAT ABOUT REHEARSALS?
DO YA-
DO YOU NEED A SPACE?
I GOT A SPACE.
YOU CAN USE MY SPACE.
YOUR GARAGE?
JOEY:
YEAH. ANY TIME YOU WANT,
ALL RIGHT?
ROCK ON, DUDES!
(LAUGHS)
JOEY:
(SINGING)
♪ EVERYBODY WANTS SOMETHING
THEY WILL NEVER GIVE UP... ♪
FILM NARRATOR:
THE FROG, A MEMBER OF
THE AMPHIBIAN WORLD.
MANY FROGS ARE EQUALLY AT HOME
IN MARINE ENVIRONMENTS,
AS ON LAND.
THIS AMPHIBIOUS CLASS
OF CREATURES LIFECYCLE
INVOLVES SOME OF THE MOST
FASCINATING AND DRAMATIC...
SORRY. (LAUGHS)
I WAS UH, I WAS JUST
LOOKING AT YOUR...
AT MY WHAT?
CAN I, CAN I SEE THAT?
YEAH.
YOU KNOW, I DO DO DOODLE
INTERPRETATION.
DOODLE INTERPRETATION?
SHH!
YOUR DOODLES SAY A LOT
ABOUT YOU.
REALLY?
WHAT DO MY DOODLES SAY?
WELL, UH...
THIS FLOWER ONE HERE...
JT...
QUIET, PLEASE.
(SMALL LAUGH)
LOOK AT THIS PLACE.
CANDLES...
MUSIC...
YOU IN AN APRON.
JOEY:
(LAUGHS)
WHAT CAN I SAY?
I ENJOY CREATING
AN ATMOSPHERE.
MMM HMM?
MMM HMM.
(ROCK BAND MUSIC)
IS THAT ROAD WORK?
THIS LATE?
OH IT'S CRAIG'S BAND.
UM...
COULD WE...
POP IN, FOR JUST,
JUST A MINUTE?
SURE.
(ELECTRIC GUITAR) OH!
(ELECTRIC GUITAR)
(DRUMMING)
(OUT OF SYNC PLAYING)
(BAND PLAYS)
STOP! SHUT UP!
HEY GUYS! HOW'S IT GOING?
WOO! IT'S GOING GOOD!
IT'S REALLY GOOD!
STILL FINDING YOUR SOUND?
WELL ON THE ROAD,
MR. JEREMIAH.
(DRUMMING)
(CRASH)
(LAUGHS) ALL RIGHT.
BUT GUYS? THREE GUITARS?
AREN'T YA KINDA LIMITING
YOURSELVES?
NO, LET ME UH, LET ME SHOW YOU
WHAT I'M TALKIN' ABOUT.
I GOT UM...
THAT'S IT.
HUH? HUH!?
IT'LL PLAY PIANO,
IT'LL DO SAX, BELLS...
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
THIS THING'LL DO EVERYTHING!
WHAT? YOU THINK ASH
SHOULD JOIN THE BAND?
JOEY:
UH, NO, I WAS GONNA JUST, UH...
UH, JAM WITH YOU GUYS?
SHOW YOU WHAT YOU'RE MISSING.
WHAT?
UH-
THIS IS A WICKED LITTLE
NUMBER.
I'M GONNA DEDICATED IT
TO MY BABY ANGIE
AND MY SWEETIE, SYDNEY.
ALL RIGHT.
JIMMY:
JOEY?
WHAT'S THE KEY?
UH... H? I DON'T KNOW.
JUST GO. JUST GO.
ONE, TWO, THREE!
(KEYBOARD PLAYING)
THAT'S IT!
♪ EVERYBODY WANTS SOMETHING
THEY'LL NEVER GIVE UP. ♪
(BADLY OUT OF TUNE MUSIC)
♪ EVERYBODY WANTS SOMETHING
THAT'LL TAKE YOUR MONEY, ♪
♪ AND NEVER GIVE UP! ♪
(GRUNTS)
GIVE ME MORE!
COME ON!
YEAH!
EMMA:
DOODLE INTERPRETATION?!
MANNY:
I KNOW! HE WAS TOTALLY
FLIRTING!
IT WAS WEIRD,
BUT AT THE SAME TIME,
KINDA' NICE.
OH MY GOD.
YOU LIKE HIM!
NO! I MEAN, HE'S CUTE,
TOTALLY CUTER THAN LAST YEAR.
AND I'M GLAD
HE'S INTERESTED,
'CAUSE IT MEANS
MY NEW LOOK IS WORKING.
BUT...?
HE'S STILL JUST JT.
OH.
MY LOOK STILL FEELS TOO TAME
OR CUTE. IT'S NOT...
THIS! THIS IS WHAT I NEED.
(LAUGHS) A THONG?
IT'S PERFECT!
WHADDAYA THINK?
I THINK THEY SHOULDN'T
SELL THIS... AT THE MALL.
♪♪♪
I MEAN THIS WHOLE THING
IS JUST WEIRD, MAN.
I'VE KNOWN MANNY
SINCE I WAS ABOUT FOUR.
LAST YEAR IT WAS
HOT OLDER WOMEN,
THIS YEAR IT'S
HOT YOUNGER ONES.
SO WHAT?
YOU'RE RIGHT. SO WHAT?
SO I LIKE HER? BIG DEAL.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT LIKE
SHE'S BECOME...
(AWE STRUCK)
A TOTALLY DIFFERENT
PERSON.
(BANG)
OH!
PSST. MANNY!
ARE YOU AWARE I CAN SEE
YOUR UNDERPANTS?
ARE YOU AWARE
THAT I DON'T CARE?
MAYBE SOME PEOPLE DON'T WANT
TO HAVE TO SEE
YOUR UNDERPANTS ALL DAY.
IF SOME PEOPLE DON'T LIKE IT,
MAYBE THEY SHOULDN'T LOOK.
DO YOU HAVE SO LITTLE
CONFIDENCE,
YOU HAVE TO SHOW
YOUR ENTIRE BODY?
I DIDN'T ASK FOR
YOUR OPINION LIBERTY.
WHAT I WEAR IS NONE
OF YOUR BUSINESS.
LIBERTY:
FINE.
BUT IT'S AGAINST
THE CODE OF CONDUCT
AND IF SOMEONE WERE TO POINT
IT OUT TO MR. RADITCH
I'M SURE HE'D THINK
IT WAS HIS BUSINESS.
MANNY:
HEY.
HI.
ARE YOU SURE THIS
ISN'T TOO MUCH?
YOU LOOK GREAT!
YOU KNOW I WOULDN'T SAY IT
IF IT WASN'T TRUE.
AND APPARENTLY JT AGREES.
(LAUGHS)
JUST GO TALK TO HER.
UNH UH.
SO WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
WHEN HE ASKS YOU OUT?
LIBERTY:
WHEN WHO ASKS MANNY OUT?
JT! ISN'T IT SO CUTE?
OH.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU LIKED JT.
I MIGHT.
GO!
OKAY, OKAY.
BETTER HURRY UP AND DECIDE.
MANNY-
EMMA:
WE GOTTA GO TO A MEETING.
SO, BYE!
HI.
I GUESS, LET ME GUESS,
I JUST UM,
INTERRUPTED A BIG TALK ABOUT
ENDANGERED PLATYPUSES.
(LAUGHS) UM, SOMETHING A BIT
MORE SERIOUS.
JT:
WELL I MEAN UH...
WHAT'S MORE SERIOUS THAN
A MAMMAL THAT CAN LAY EGGS?
I DON'T KNOW, YOU TELL ME.
SULLY:
HEY.
MANNY, RIGHT?
THIS THING,
ARE YOU GONNA BE THERE?
YEAH. YEAH, WELL MY BEST
FRIEND IS ORGANIZING IT SO...
SULLY:
GREAT. WELL UH...
MAYBE I'LL SHOW UP.
JT:
MANNY?
OH, SORRY.
WHA-WHAT WERE
WE TALKING ABOUT?
PLATYPUSES,
WHAT'S MORE SERIOUS.
MANNY? HELLO?
(KNOCKING ON WINDOW)
EMMA:
WHAT I'M SAYING IS...
IF YOUR PARENTS WANT TO BUY A
TROPICAL HARDWOOD TOILET SEAT,
DON'T LET THEM.
EVERY YEAR MILLIONS OF HECTARES
OF TROPICAL RAIN FORESTS
ARE DESTROYED.
AND RAIN FORESTS ARE IMPORTANT
FOR SO MANY REASONS.
THEY'RE HOME TO MANY SPECIES
OF ANIMALS AND PLANTS.
THEY PROVIDE OXYGEN
AND FRESH DRINKING WATER.
(LAUGHTER)
OH YOU'RE SO SWEET.
MANNY.
WHAT'S THAT SHORT FOR?
MANNY:
MANNY? UH... MANUELLA,
ACTUALLY.
MANUELLA.
NICE.
(LAUGHS)
EMMA:
SO IF YOUR PARENTS
STILL INSIST
ON BUYING TROPICAL HARDWOOD,
TELL THEM THAT BY BUYING
THE TOILET SEAT,
THEY'RE DESTROYING
THE RAINFOREST...
OUR PLANET'S LUNGS.
JOEY:
CAITLIN!
JOEY! HEY, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING HERE?
UH ACTUALLY,
I WAS WONDERING
IF COULD BORROW
THAT VIDEO CAMERA
THAT YOU HAD
AT SPIKE'S SHOWER.
OH YEAH, SURE. UH...
WHAT IS IT FOR ANGELA?
ACTUALLY IT'S FOR
CRAIG'S BAND.
BAND?
YEAH.
OH, YOU MUST BE HAVING
SOME SERIOUS FLASHBACKS.
OH, AM I EVER.
WE WERE JAMMING
IN THE GARAGE LAST NIGHT,
IT WAS LIKE TOTALLY
LIKE THE ZITS AGAIN.
ALL OVER.
CATILIN:
UH... JAMMIN'?
JOEY:
YEAH.
CAITLIN:
(LAUGHS)
JOEY, YOU'RE NOT A TEENAGER.
I KNOW, I JUST THOUGHT
THAT THE BOYS
COULD USE SOME DIRECTION.
I KNOW YOU THOUGHT THAT
THE ZITS WERE A JOKE.
I DID NOT!
BUT IF WE HAD SOME
GUIDANCE BACK THEN,
MAYBE THINGS WOULD
HAVE BEEN DIFFERENT.
AND MAYBE IF YOU'D WRITTEN
MORE THAN ONE SONG.
(LAUGHS) THERE YOU GO.
CAMERA.
JUST UH...
UH, NEVER MIND.
WHAT?
JUST REMEMBER THAT
THEY'RE TEENAGERS.
THAT'S ALL I'M GONNA SAY.
BYE.
(ROCK BAND PLAYING)
OKAY, OKAY, GUYS STOP!
STOP! STOP.
CRAIG, I'M ONLY GETTIN'
YOUR PROFILE, MAN.
JOEY THIS IS JUST A REHEARSAL.
I REALLY THINK WE SHOULD
HOLD OFF WITH THE CAMERA AND...
WE TALKED ABOUT THIS GUYS.
THIS CAMERA IS YOUR AUDIENCE.
ALL RIGHT? AND STAGE PRESENCE
IS JUST AS IMPORTANT
AS YOUR SOUND.
AND... SPEAKING OF SOUND,
UH, I KNOW YOU GUYS WANT
TO PLAY YOUR OWN MUSIC,
AND I THINK THAT'S
A GREAT GOAL, OKAY?
BUT MAYBE WE SHOULD START
WITH SOME COVERS FIRST.
LIKE UH...
MAYBE SOME GEORGE MICHAEL?
CRAIG, I KNOW YOU KNOW
THE WORDS TO FAITH.
JOEY!
WHAT? (TELEPHONE RINGS)
JUST THINK ABOUT IT, OKAY?
I MEAN, YOU GUYS HAVE TO LEARN
TO WALK BEFORE YOU CAN RUN.
OKAY?
HELLO?
HOLD ON, I CAN'T HEAR YOU.
HOLD ON. YEAH...
MAN, JOEY'S BRUTAL.
(LAUGHING) GOTTA LEARN HOW
TO WALK BEFORE YOU CAN RUN.
(LAUGHTER)
MARCO:
LOOK, I'M SORRY, OKAY?
IT'S FUNNY,
IN A SAD AND PATHETIC
KINDA' WAY.
YEAH, DUDE, YOU REALLY NEED
TO TALK TO HIM.
GEORGE MICHAEL?
YEAH, FAITH?
HEY, SHUT UP!
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED
TO TELL HIM?
HE'S SO DELUDED,
HE THINKS HE'S IN THE BAND.
HE'S EMBARRASSING HIMSELF
AND HE DOESN'T EVEN KNOW IT.
P.A. ANNOUNCER:
ATTENTION ALL STUDENTS CLUB
ORGANIZERS, REMEMBER THAT...
HEY.
LOOK WHO'S HERE TO HELP.
I'M SORRY.
I REALLY WANTED TO GO.
BUT YOU WERE ABDUCTED
BY ALIENS?
CLOSE. I HAD TO HELP
MR. EHL IN THE SHOP.
HOW WAS IT?
WELL, YOU'RE PRACTICALLY
THE ONLY GUY IN THE SCHOOL
THAT WASN'T THERE.
SHOULD I BE JEALOUS?
HMM, THEY WEREN'T
THERE FOR ME...
NO?
OR THE ENVIRONMENT.
THEY ONLY WANTED-
MANNY:
HEY, EM! HEY, SEAN!
(LAUGHS) I-I'M JUST GONNA
TAKE DOWN THE REST
OF THE POSTERS IN THE HALLWAY.
THANKS.
THAT WAS AN AMAZING
TURNOUT, HUH?
YEAH, IF ANY OF THEM
COME BACK.
DON'T WORRY, I'LL MAKE THEM.
EMMA:
SO... WHAT'S HAPPENING WITH JT?
WHAT DO YOU LIKE BETTER:
MANNY OR MANUELLA?
SULLY LIKES MANUELLA,
HE SAYS IT'S... EXOTIC.
MANUELLA SANTOS.
OH YEAH, DID YOU SAY
SOMETHING?
YEAH, BUT IT WAS NOTHING.
RADITCH:
MANNY, I'VE BEEN MEANING
TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT YOUR ATTIRE.
IT CONTRAVENES THE CODE
OF CONDUCT.
BUT EVERYBODY WEARS
CROP TOPS.
RADITCH:
IT'S NOT ABOUT THE CROP TOP.
I EXPECT YOU TO SHOW UP
TOMORROW
IN AN OUTFIT THAT DOES NOT
REVEAL YOUR UNDERGARMENTS.
BUT LOW-RIDERS ARE IN,
AND I-
AND I'VE HAD COMPLAINTS.
SO NO MORE VISIBLE UNDERWEAR.
(ROCK BAND PLAYS)
HEY, DID YOU TURN EVERYTHING
OFF IN THE GARAGE?
UH-HUH.
WHAT'RE YOU WATCHING?
THE FOOTAGE THAT I SHOT.
YOU SHOULD CHECK IT OUT.
I WANT TO SHOW YOU
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT
WITH THAT STAGE-PRESENCE
THING.
(VIDEO FAST FORWARDS)
OH, I WENT TOO FAR.
SPINNER:
(LAUGHING) GOTTA LEARN HOW
TO WALK BEFORE YOU CAN RUN.
(LAUGHTER)
MARCO:
I'M SORRY, OKAY? IT'S FUNNY,
IN A SAD AND PATHETIC
KINDA' WAY.
SPINNER:
DUDE, YOU SERIOUSLY NEED
TO TALK TO HIM.
GEORGE MICHAEL?
JIMMY:
YEAH, FAITH?
CRAIG:
HEY, SHUT UP!
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED
TO TELL HIM?
HE'S SO DELUDED,
HE THINKS HE'S IN THE BAND.
I THINK I'LL...
CRAIG:
HE'S EMBARRASSING HIMSELF
AND HE DOESN'T EVEN KNOW IT.
P.A. ANNOUNCER:
THE ASTRONOMY CLUB'S PLANNING
A FIELD TRIP
TO THE OBSERVATORY NEXT
SUNDAY.
INTERESTED STUDENTS CAN
SIGN UP ON A FORM OUTSIDE...
MANNY.
I KNOW YOU WERE REALLY UPSET
THAT RADITCH BUSTED YOU.
ACTUALLY IT TURNED OUT
NOT TO BE SUCH A BAD THING.
DO YOU WANT
TO GET SUSPENDED?
WHAT? I'M NOT BREAKING
ANY RULES.
MANNY. MISTER RADITCH SAID-
HE SAID NO VISIBLE UNDERWEAR.
AND DO YOU SEE ANY UNDERWEAR?
NO, BUT-
MANNY:
THAT'S RIGHT.
BECAUSE I'M NOT WEARING ANY.
MS. HATZILAKOS:
SO FROGS... THEY'RE AMPHIBIANS.
THEY LIVE BOTH ON LAND
AND IN WATER,
AND THEY FIND FOOD
IN BOTH REALMS:
INSECTS, SMALL FISH,
AND EVEN OTHER FROGS.
SO WHO WANTS TO FEED
OUR WEB-FOOTED FRIENDS
A LITTLE SNACK?
MANNY.
SURE.
(LAUGHTER)
UH, STOP!
JT:
UM, WHY DOES MANNY GET TO FEED
THESE FROGS WHEN I DON'T?
BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T VOLUNTEER.
WELL, I UH,
I VOLUNTEER THEN.
OKAY. SO FEED THEM,
AND THEN SIT DOWN.
OKAY.
P.A. ANNOUNCER:
STUDENTS INTERESTED
IN PARTICIPATING
IN THE REGIONAL SCIENCE FAIR
SHOULD SEE MRS. HATZILAKOS.
(CLEARS THROAT)
UH, HEY MANNY.
HEY JT.
LOOK UH, I WAS JUST
WONDERING IF MAYBE
YOU WERE FREE TOMORROW?
IF WE COULD MAYBE UH...
GO SEE A MOVIE? OR SOMETHING.
UH, SEE THIS, JT?
BUH-BYE.
MANNY:
ACTUALLY JT...
I AM BUSY TOMORROW,
I'M SORRY.
MANNY, UM,
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
UM...
NOW.
SURE.
HOW COULD YOU DO THAT TO JT?
WHAT?
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
UH NO, YOU JUST
BROKE HIS HEART.
EMMA, C'MON.
YOU'RE GETTING
THIS HUGE EGO.
I AM NOT.
JUST BECAUSE
I'M DRESSING LIKE-
YOU'RE DRESSING
LIKE AN IDIOT.
BUT WHAT I REALLY CARE ABOUT
IS HOW YOU'RE ACTING.
I'M ALWAYS THERE
FOR YOU, EMMA.
WHEN YOU FIGHT WITH SEAN,
WHEN YOU FIND OUT YOUR
MOM'S PREGNANT,
FOR YOUR STUPID
ENVIRONMENTAL CLUB.
IT'S NOT STUPID.
BUT THE ONE TIME
IT'S NOT ABOUT YOU,
YOU DO THIS TO ME.
I'M JUST CONCERNED-
'CAUSE IT SOUNDS MORE
LIKE YOU'RE JEALOUS.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
JUST FORGET THIS.
MANNY:
FINE!
THIS IS WHO I AM NOW, EM.
AND IF YOU CAN'T
ACCEPT THAT,
THEN DON'T TALK TO ME.
JOEY:
HEY.
THOUGHT YOU WERE NEVER
COMING HOME.
CRAIG:
UH... I HAD REHEARSAL
IN MARCO'S BASEMENT, AND...
AND UH...
JOEY, I'M REALLY SORRY.
JOEY:
I SHOULDA KNOWN BETTER.
NO, YOU WERE TRYING TO HELP.
JOEY:
I WAS, I...
CRAIG, WHEN I WAS
IN HIGH SCHOOL,
MY BAND, THE ZITS,
MEANT EVERYTHING TO ME.
I MEAN, THEY WERE GOOD TIMES--
SOME OF THE BEST.
ANYTHING FELT POSSIBLE.
AND THEN ONE DAY I WAKE UP,
I'M IN MY THIRTIES,
AND I HAVE A DAUGHTER
AND A TEENAGE STEP-SON
AND I'M THINKIN' TO MYSELF
WHOA, WHEN DID THIS HAPPEN?
(SIGHS) I GUESS I WAS JUST
TRYING TO FEEL THAT WAY AGAIN.
SO MARCO'S BASEMENT, HUH?
YEAH.
YOU KNOW, THERE'S BETTER
ACOUSTICS IN THE GARAGE.
WHAT ABOUT THE KEYBOARD?
IT'S BACK IN THE BOX.
THANK YOU.
MANUELLA? SOMETHING WRONG?
NO.
EVERYTHING'S... JUST GREAT.