EMMA:
BUT YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
A DOCTOR, NOT A PATIENT.
THIS WAS SUCH A MISTAKE.
DON'T GO! PLEASE!
WAIT! DON'T GO!
YOU HAVE PRETTY BLONDE
HAIR LIKE EMMA.
STOP IT!
SHE'S MY DAUGHTER.
BUT SHE DOESN'T LOVE ME.
WHY WOULD YOU SAY THAT?
SHE NEVER COMES TO VISIT ME.
SHE DOESN'T CARE ABOUT ME.
MAYBE SHE COULDN'T FIND YOU...
UNTIL NOW.
I'M EMMA.
NO. EMMA'S JUST LITTLE.
SHE...
SH...
YOU'RE EMMA.
DON'T BE SAD.
EVERYTHING'S OKAY.
YOUR DADDY'S HERE NOW.
DADDY'S HERE.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Hear what I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I can see it ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
STILL MAD BECAUSE I STOLE
YOUR STUPID MP3 PLAYER?
JIMMY:
NO, IT'S ANCIENT HISTORY.
SPINNER:
GOOD, THEN LET'S JUST BURY
THE HAMMER.
JIMMY:
FINE. IS THAT IT?
SPINNER:
UH, WELL... NO.
I... I KIND OF NEED YOUR LOCKER.
JIMMY:
DO YOU NEED MY LOCKER
OR PAIGE DOES?
I JUST... I NEED IT, OKAY?
JIMMY:
(LAUGHS)
WHAT YOU NEED IS A BACKBONE.
"OH, OH PAIGE,
I'D DO ANYTHING-"
SPINNER:
HEY, SHUT UP, OKAY?
I'M NOT LIKE THAT.
JIMMY:
YOU KNOW WHAT?
ADMIT IT AND THE LOCKER'S YOURS.
OKAY, I HAVE NO BACKBONE.
NO.
SEE YOU'RE PREACHING
TO THE CONVERTED.
YOU NEED TO TELL EVERYBODY...
PUBLICLY.
TOMORROW BY NOON...
OR NO DEAL.
HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN HERE?
ABOUT SINCE I FELL
AND HIT MY HEAD.
YOU FELL?
YUP.
DON'T BE SAD.
MY HEAD'S OKAY NOW.
SEE?
IT DOESN'T HURT. I'M OKAY.
WHY DIDN'T ANYONE TELL ME THIS?
ELSPETH:
SHANE? CAN I BORROW
YOUR GUEST, PLEASE?
JUST WHO DO YOU THINK YOU ARE,
JUST BARGING IN HERE?
I'M HIS DAUGHTER EMMA,
ACTUALLY.
OH.
BUT YOU CAN'T SURPRISE
HIM LIKE THAT.
HE SUFFERED A TRAUMATIC
BRAIN INJURY
SO HE HAS CERTAIN ROUTINES
THAT HE NEEDS TO STICK TO.
BUT I THINK THAT'S ENOUGH
FOR TODAY.
OKAY, SHANE?
EMMA HAS TO GO HOME NOW.
SO STAND UP
AND SAY GOODBYE.
NO!
SHE'S STAYING!
SHANE.
SHANE:
SHE CAN'T GO! NO!
HERE.
NO, SHE CAN'T GO!
TAKE YOUR KNITTING.
NO!
YES.
IT'LL CALM YOU DOWN.
IT'S OKAY, SHE'LL BE BACK.
COME ON, TAKE YOUR KNITTING.
SHE'LL BE BACK.
IT'S OKAY.
COME ON.
I'M GONNA WRITE YOU,
AND YOU CAN WRITE ME TOO, OKAY?
AND I'M GONNA VISIT AGAIN,
SOON.
(CAMERA CLICK)
COME ON.
PROMISE?
I PROMISE.
EMMA:
MY MOM IS SUCH A LIAR!
CRAIG:
SHE'S PROBABLY GOT
AN EXPLANATION.
EMMA:
LIKE WHAT? SHE'S EVIL?
I HATE HER!
I SO WISH
SHE WASN'T MY MOM.
NO, YOU'RE OVERREACTING.
CRAIG, MY FATHER
IS BRAIN-DAMAGED!
WELL, AT LEAST
YOU HAVE A DAD.
LAST TIME I CHECKED
YOU HAD TWO.
I'M SORRY. I'M AN IDIOT.
CRAIG:
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
LET'S JUST...
LET'S JUST GO HOME.
(KNOCKS ON WINDOW)
GO TRAIN EMPLOYEE:
SORRY, YOU JUST MISSED
THE LAST TRAIN.
NO MORE 'TIL MORNING.
NOTHING?
GO TRAIN EMPLOYEE:
NO.
(RAIN AND THUNDER)
JOEY:
WHAT A GREAT WAY TO START OFF
THE SCHOOL YEAR, GUYS.
SECOND DAY OF SCHOOL AND LIKE,
"OH, OH, I KNOW, LET'S SKIP!
OH, AREN'T WE COOL!"
YOU KNOW IT TOOK ME OVER
AN HOUR TO GET HERE.
WHAT AM I A TAXI SERVICE?
JUST, JUST ONE QUESTION:
STOUFFVILLE?
WHAT ON EARTH IS
IN STOUFFVILLE?
MY DAD.
YOU HAVE A LOT
OF EXPLAINING TO DO!
YOU'RE NOT TALKING TO ME?
EMMA YOU START TALKING
RIGHT NOW!
YOU LIED TO ME, MOM.
I FOUND HIM.
SHANE?
YOU FOUND SHANE?
EMMA:
RIGHT WHERE YOU LEFT HIM -
IN THAT PRISON IN STOUFFVILLE.
HOW COULD YOU?
I DIDN'T PUT HIM THERE.
HIS PARENTS DID.
AND YOU DIDN'T STOP THEM?
SPIKE:
I WAS SIXTEEN!
(PAINED) OH!
SIMPSON:
HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY.
C'MON, SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN.
(BREATHES HARD)
FALSE ALARM.
EMMA, COME ON.
PLEASE, LET'S JUST TALK
THIS THROUGH RATIONALLY.
EMMA, SIT!
YOU DON'T TALK TO ME
LIKE THAT!
YOU'RE NOT MY DAD!
(DOOR SLAMS)
(CRIES)
ARMSTRONG:
B MINUS THREE TIMES 4B
MINUS SEVEN.
NOW IN THIS PROBLEM
WE NEED SOLVE B.
IT'S 11:45.
TIME'S RUNNING OUT,
MR. SPINELESS.
ARMSTRONG:
SO, WHO'S GONNA BE BRAVE
AND COME UP TO THE BOARD
AND SOLVE THIS ONE FOR ME, HUH?
GAVIN?
I CAN'T TELL YOU HOW EXCITED
I AM TO FINALLY SEE YOU UP HERE.
(STUDENTS CHATTER QUIETLY)
I HAVE NO BACKBONE.
EXCUSE ME?
(LAUGHTER)
I'M WHIPPED.
I'M TOTALLY SPINELESS.
MY GIRLFRIEND COMPLETELY
RUNS MY LIFE, OKAY?
ARMSTRONG:
OKAY, ALL RIGHT,
SETTLE DOWN, SETTLE DOWN.
I KNEW IT WAS TOO GOOD
TO BE TRUE.
GAVIN PLEASE TAKE
YOUR SEAT.
ANYONE ELSE?
MICHELLE, WHY DON'T YOU COME UP
HERE AND SHOW HIM HOW...
ARE YOU HAPPY?
CAN I HAVE THE LOCKER NOW?
YEAH, YOU EARNED IT.
(CLASSICAL MUSIC IS PLAYING)
(DOORBELL RINGS)
SPIKE:
ALL RIGHT, I'M COMING!
SHANE.
MISS ME?
P.A. ANNOUNCER:
THE BOY'S ATHLETIC ASSOCIATION
IS HOLDING TRYOUTS...
SIMPSON:
WE MISSED YOU AT BREAKFAST.
WASN'T UP TO IT.
CAN I TALK TO YOU
FOR A MINUTE?
PLEASE. THIS IS IMPORTANT.
YOU KNOW, FROM WHERE YOU SIT
YOUR MOM LOOKS TERRIBLE,
HEARTLESS...
BUT YOU DON'T KNOW
HER SIDE YET.
WHEN SPIKE GOT PREGNANT
SHANE WANTED TO BE INVOLVED
BUT HIS FAMILY
WOULDN'T LET HIM.
AND ONE NIGHT
HE TOOK ACID AND...
HE JUMPED OFF A BRIDGE
OR FELL, WHO KNOWS?
SHE TOOK YOU TO VISIT HIM ONCE.
SHANE:
HI EMMA.
NO, I WANT TO-
NO! NO! NO!
YOUR MOM WAS AFRAID
THAT HE MIGHT HURT YOU.
OKAY, BUT SHE COULD'VE
TOLD ME.
SHE WAS WAITING
'TIL YOU GOT OLDER AND,
AND MAYBE,
MAYBE THAT WAS WRONG.
JUST CALL HER, OKAY?
WHEN DID YOU MARRY SNAKE?
LAST YEAR.
YOU DIDN'T TELL ME.
NO, I DIDN'T HAVE TO.
HE DOESN'T HAVE TO BE
YOUR HUSBAND.
SPIKE:
HE IS.
SHANE:
BUT IF HE WASN'T
THIS COULD BE ME.
THIS COULD BE OURS.
(NERVOUS BREATH)
YOU'RE NOT CALLING ANYONE!
(BUSY SIGNAL)
(OFF THE HOOK PHONE BEEPING)
SHANE?
I HAVE A...
A PRENATAL CHECKUP.
WHY DON'T WE CALL YOU A CAB?
I'LL STAY.
I'M SORRY SHANE.
YOU CAN'T.
BUT THIS IS MY HOME.
NO IT ISN'T. LOOK AROUND.
SHANE:
NO!
NO! (GLASS BREAKING)
NO! NO! NO! NO!
NO!
NO! (GLASS BREAKING)
SPINNER:
PAIGE.
PAIGE:
LEAVE ME ALONE, SPINNER.
SPINNER:
JUST LET ME TALK TO YOU.
SO WHAT? YOU CAN CALL ME
A SHREW? OR A HAG?
OR SOME FREAKY, SHRIEKY
DEMANDING WITCH?
I DIDN'T MEAN IT!
PAIGE:
OH THEN WHY? (LOCKER SLAMMED)
WHY WOULD YOU DO SOMETHING
SO HORRIBLE?
SPINNER:
I MADE A DEAL.
IF I SAID I HAD NO BACKBONE
IN CLASS,
JIMMY'D GIVE ME HIS LOCKER.
PAIGE:
AND YOU DID IT?
YOU HUMILIATED ME
JUST TO GET A LOCKER?
SPINNER:
I DIDN'T HUMILIATE YOU.
PAIGE:
YOU DID SO!
SPINNER:
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I HAVE NO IDEA
HOW TO PLEASE YOU.
YOU TELL ME TO WORK A MIRACLE,
THEN YOU'RE MAD AT ME
FOR DOING IT.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
FROM YOU? NOTHING, EVER!
(BANG)
(KIDS LAUGHING)
(SCARED BREATHING)
SHANE, YOU HURT YOUR HAND.
WHY DON'T I GET SOME ICE
FOR IT?
NO.
SHANE, YOU HAVE THE PHONE.
IT'S NOT LIKE I CAN
CALL ANYBODY.
NO.
WILL YOU AT LEAST
LET ME LOOK AT IT THEN?
YOU LIAR!
SPIKE:
OW!
SHANE:
HOW COULD YOU LIE TO ME AGAIN?!
GIVE ME THE PHONE!
OW! OW!
AH!
OH NO.
(BANG, SMASH)
OH NO! THE BABY'S COMING!
EMMA:
MOM, WHAT'S HAPPENED?!
SHANE?
(HARD BREATHING)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
SHE TRICKED ME!
EM, THIS IS IT!
IT'S TIME.
SHANE:
NO! SHE'S A LIAR!
EMMA:
SHE'S MY MOM
AND IF YOU HURT HER,
I WILL NEVER EVER
SPEAK TO YOU AGAIN.
PHONE SNAKE! (BREATHING HARD)
NO, YOU'RE TRYING
TO SEND ME AWAY.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
BUT MOM NEEDS HELP.
SO GIVE ME THE PHONE.
(PANTING)
(HEAVY BREATHING)
EMMA:
TAKE MOM'S KNITTING.
YOU LIKE TO KNIT.
THANK YOU.
(PHONE DIALING)
DEGRASSI COMMUNITY SCHOOL,
FRONT OFFICE,
THIS IS MS. SMITH.
RADITCH:
I'M NOT WORRIED OVERLY
ABOUT CRAIG.
I SEEM TO RECALL YOU SKIPPING
CLASS A FEW TIMES.
MS. SMITH:
OH DEAR. I, I, MR. RADITCH!
MR. RADITCH!
I HAVE EMMA NELSON ON LINE TWO.
SHE'S LOOKING FOR MR. SIMPSON.
HIS WIFE'S IN LABOUR.
OH HE'S OUT BACK WITH
HIS INSECT CLUB.
AH, I'LL GO GET HIM.
MS. SMITH:
OKAY.
UH, EMMA, WE'RE GONNA
GET HIM NOW.
SPIKE:
(GRUNTS IN PAIN)
EMMA:
OKAY, REMEMBER MOM,
BREATHE IN THROUGH YOUR NOSE
OUT THROUGH YOUR MOUTH
ALL AT ONCE.
I'LL PHONE LIZ.
(PHONE DIALING)
SIMPSON:
MOVING SOFTLY...
MOVING GENTLY...
MOVING QUIETLY...
JOEY:
SNAKE!
SPIKE'S GONNA HAVE
THE BABY, MAN! COME ON!
SHE'S IN LABOUR!
LET'S GO!
SIMPSON:
I'M GONNA BE A DAD?
I'M GONNA BE A DAD!
JOEY:
SHE'S HAVING YOUR BABY!
(LAUGHS)
WAIT UP!
MR. RADITCH:
AND THE CODE OF CONDUCT SAYS
THAT STUDENTS THAT WISH
TO TRADE LOCKERS
MUSH ASK FOR PERMISSION
FROM THE OFFICE.
YOU ARE GOING TO MOVE BACK.
AND EVERYONE ELSE THAT'S
INVOLVED IN YOUR "SCHEME"
IS GOING TO BE BACK IN THEIR
LOCKERS BY THE END OF THE DAY.
SO CAN I STILL SIT HERE
OR DO YOU WANT ME TO MAYBE
TRADE WITH SOMEBODY?
OKAY. THANKS.
(SIGHS)
I WAS JUST TRYING
TO MAKE YOU HAPPY.
I WANTED YOU...
I WANTED YOU TO HAVE
THE PERFECT LOCKER.
I DON'T NEED
YEAH, THEN WHY DIDN'T
YOU TAKE HAZEL'S?
IT WASN'T...
IT WASN'T GOOD ENOUGH.
SPINNER:
YEAH, LIKE ME.
WHAT KIND OF LOSER FAILS
ENGLISH?
PLUS I'M TOTALLY BROKE.
OF COURSE YOU HATE ME.
I SO DO NOT HATE YOU!
I'M SORRY IF I WAS
DEMANDING, OKAY?
FEEL FREE TO SAY
I WASN'T, HON.
I NEVER NOTICED.
IT WAS A SUPER SWEET IDEA.
WELL HOW ABOUT A KISS THEN?
(SOUND OF A WHIP)
KISS ME NOW!
OH, POOR, LONELY,
JEALOUS JAMES.
IF ONLY HE HAD
SOMEONE TO KISS.
AS IF.
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE
MY GIRL.
SPIKE:
(GROANS IN PAIN)
LIZ:
THE BABY'S FINE.
YOU HAVE NOTHING TO WORRY
ABOUT.
(PAINED) EXCEPT FOR
THE MIND BLOWING AGONY!
OW! (PANTING)
EM...
EM, I'M SO SORRY
I DIDN'T TELL YOU.
I MEANT TO.
I WANTED YOU TO HEAR IT FROM ME,
NOT THIS WAY.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT NOW.
YOU'RE IMPORTANT.
YOU'RE SO IMPORTANT.
YOU'RE IMPORTANT TO ME.
(GRIMACES IN PAIN)
OW!
(BREATHING HARD)
WHAT HAPPENED IN HERE?
HI SNAKE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT NOW.
WE'RE ALL OKAY.
ARE YOU OKAY?
(PANTING) YEAH.
(GRIMACES IN PAIN)
EMMA:
YOU FIXED IT. IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
SHANE:
YOU'RE MOM'S NOT VERY GOOD
AT KNITTING.
SHANE, IT'S TIME GO.
WAIT.
CRAIG TOOK IT.
IT'S A PHOTO OF ME AND YOU.
BYE BYE, EMMA.
BYE.
SIMPSON:
HEY.
WHO'S THAT PRETTY GIRL?
THAT'S YOUR SISTER.
HER NAME'S EMMA.
(SOFTLY) HELLO.
SPIKE:
EM.
WHAT I SAID BEFORE,
HOW I WANTED TO TELL YOU...
YEAH I KNOW. THANKS.
LIZ:
EMMA, COME SIT DOWN
SO WE CAN TAKE A PICTURE.
YOU KNOW WHAT, JACK?
YOU LOOK JUST LIKE OUR DAD.
VERY NICE.