MARCO:
I CAN'T WAIT.
RICK:
YOUR SEAT, M'LADY.
TERRI:
WHY, THANK YOU.
YOU'RE SO SWEET.
KWAN:
SHHH. ALL RIGHT CLASS,
TODAY WE'RE GOING TO START
OUR SCENE STUDIES.
I WAS PLEASED THAT ONE GROUP
IS EVEN PERFORMING
AN ORIGINAL SCENE,
WRITTEN BY OUR BUDDING
PLAYWRIGHT MARCO.
SO, LET US START REHEARSING.
MARCO:
OKAY GUYS, SINCE I WROTE THIS,
I SORT OF DON'T FEEL
LIKE DIRECTING.
JIMMY:
AND I DON'T WANT TO ACT.
SO SAY HELLO TO YOUR
NEW DIRECTOR.
WELL UH, NO OFFENCE, JIM,
BUT THE THEATRE IS IN MY BLOOD.
MY MOTHER WALKED THE BOARDS
AT STRATFORD FOR TEN YEARS.
UM, WELL, MAYBE YOU CAN
STAGE MANAGE.
ALL RIGHT.
WHO KNOWS?
I MIGHT EVEN TEACH JIM
A FEW TRICKS OF THE TRADE.
CASTING.
MARCO WILL PLAY RAY.
HAZEL, WILL PLAY NURSE MEG,
AND OUR FEMALE LEAD WILL BE
PLAYED BY TERRI MACGREGOR.
ME? REALLY?
JIMMY:
COOL, SO LET'S GET STARTED.
MAYBE I SHOULDN'T
PLAY THE LEAD.
I COULD BE YOUR ASSISTANT.
UH, NO, THANK YOU,
BUT-
YOU'RE THE STAR.
YOU'LL BE BRILLIANT.
THE STAGE MANAGER SAYS SO.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Hear what I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
MAMA?
TERRI:
YES, SON? I AM HERE.
JIMMY:
CUT!
OKAY, TERRI?
TRY TO BE A LITTLE MORE
NATURAL.
I'M SORRY.
I'M JUST NERVOUS.
JIMMY:
IT'S OKAY, THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
JUST TRY TO THINK ABOUT-
BREATHING. ALWAYS BREATHING.
(BREATHING SOUNDS)
JIMMY:
GREAT, THANKS. FROM THE TOP.
MAMA?
TERRI:
YES, SON...
I AM HERE.
OKAY GUYS, WE HAVE
A LOT OF WORK TO DO.
SO MEETING AT THE DOT
AFTER SCHOOL, OKAY?
IT'S HARD BEING
A FIRST-TIME DIRECTOR,
BUT YOU'LL GET THERE.
SPINNER:
SO MY BOSS HAS ME ON PROBATION
TO SEE IF I'LL WORK OUT
AND MY FIRST CUSTOMER
GOES AND COMPLAINS.
CRAIG:
SPIN, HE ORDERED A HAM SANDWICH
AND YOU BROUGHT HIM
A HAMBURGER.
SPINNER:
YEAH, BUT HE STILL ATE IT,
AND HE DIDN'T EVEN LEAVE ME
A TIP, I MEAN LIKE-
JT:
JUST THE DOG WAS JUST
LIKE LYING THERE.
GREAT. JT AGAIN.
JT WANTING PAIGE AROUND,
I CAN GET.
BUT PAIGE WANTING JT AROUND?
WELL, SHE HAD A HARD TIME LAST
YEAR AND JT WAS THERE FOR HER,
SO SHE FEELS SHE OWES HIM.
CRAIG:
BUT YOU DON'T.
TELL HIM TO GET LOST.
JT:
SO I SAID TO GAVIN,
WHOSE DOG IS IT ANYWAY?
PAIGE:
HI, HON.
SPINNER:
HI PAIGE.
BYE JT. RUN ALONG NOW
AND JOIN THE OTHER CHILDREN.
SPINNER:
DUDE, DON'T.
I REALLY HATE THAT.
SPINNER:
THAT MAKES ME CRAZY.
JT, SHUT UP OR I'LL-
NOT DO ANYTHING.
GEEZ, MIGHT WANT TO CUT BACK
ON THE RED MEAT THERE, TIGER.
EVER HEARD OF ANGER MANAGEMENT?
PAIGE, WHEN ARE YOU GONNA
CUT YOUR LAPDOG LOOSE?
SPIN, JUST GIVE HIM
A CHANCE, OKAY?
TRY SOME MALE-BONDING.
RICK:
SO HOW LONG HAVE
YOU KNOWN JIMMY?
HMM...
SINCE SEVENTH GRADE.
GOOD FRIEND?
SURE.
I LIKE HIM.
BUT NOT LIKE THAT.
YOU'RE THE ONLY GUY
I CARE ABOUT.
YOU SURE?
TERRI:
I'M POSITIVE.
YOU MAKE ME SO HAPPY.
HAPPIER THAN
I'VE EVER BEEN.
YOU MAKE ME HAPPY, TOO,
M'LADY.
COME ON, THEY'RE CUTE.
JIMMY:
THEY'RE NAUSEATING.
NO. HE'S NAUSEATING.
WHAT?
WHAT RICK DOESN'T CREEP
YOU OUT?
HAZEL:
YEAH, HE'S A LITTLE STRANGE,
BUT THEY'RE IN LOVE.
AND HE'S TERRI'S FIRST
BOYFRIEND.
SO DEAL, OKAY?
SIMPSON:
GOOD MORNING ONE AND ALL.
THE VIDEO ANNOUNCEMENTS
ARE DOWN THIS MORNING,
SO I'LL BE READING THEM TO YOU
WITH THE OLD SCHOOL METHOD.
RICK:
THE FIRST THING THAT ACTORS
ARE TAUGHT
IS THE THREE QUARTER RULE.
YOU MUST ALWAYS HAVE
THREE QUARTERS OF YOUR BODY
FACING THE AUDIENCE.
OR WHAT?
ONE, THE AUDIENCE
WON'T SEE YOU.
TWO, THE AUDIENCE
WON'T HEAR YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
THANKS FOR THE TIP.
SPINNER:
ALL RIGHT, IS EVERYONE READY?
OH UM, I DON'T KNOW UM...
WHAT ABOUT A BURGER?
WHY NOT A SALAD?
YOU SAID YESTERDAY
YOU WERE CRAVING ONE.
DOES ANYONE REALLY
CRAVE SALAD?
WHAT KIND SHOULD
I ORDER?
GO FOR GARDEN.
LIGHT DRESSING.
HEALTHIEST CHOICE
ON THE MENU.
TERRI:
SOUNDS PERFECT.
MAKE THAT TWO,
MY GOOD MAN.
OKAY.
YOU'RE ALWAYS LOOKING OUT
FOR ME.
MORNING MANNY,
LOOKING LOVELY AS USUAL.
RADITCH:
MR. YORKE.
SOMETHING YOU WANT
TO TELL ME?
UH, NO SIR.
I FOUND THIS NOTE UNDER
MY OFFICE DOOR THIS MORNING.
ROSES ARE RED,
VIOLETS ARE BLUE,
MY NAME IS JT YORKE
AND I LOVE YOU.
P.S. LOVE THE PANTS.
MR. RADITCH,
I DID NOT WRITE THAT.
IT'S SOME KIND OF PRANK.
I'M RELIEVED TO HEAR THAT.
OH!
SOMETHING WRONG
WITH YOUR LOCKER?
UH NO, NO.
IT'S FINE.
IT'S PERFECTLY FINE.
SPINNER:
(LAUGHS)
WELL, I GUESS YOU SHOULD ALWAYS
ACTUALLY LOCK YOUR LOCKER.
THAT WAS YOU?
I'M MALE-BONDING.
DO ME A FAVOUR,
DON'T BOND ANYMORE, OKAY?
BUT I ALWAYS BOND
WITH ALL MY FRIENDS.
OF COURSE IF YOU WOULD
STOP HANGING AROUND,
I WOULDN'T HAVE TO.
GET IT?
MAMA!
RAY, YOU MUSTN'T GIVE UP HOPE!
JIMMY:
CUT!
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
YOU'RE TALKING STRAIGHT
TO THE AUDIENCE.
IT'S THE THREE-QUARTER RULE.
RICK?
CAN I STEAL YOU FOR A MINUTE?
FOR YOU, I GOT FIVE.
JIMMY:
LOOK, I REALLY APPRECIATE
YOUR HELP.
BUT SOME OF YOUR TIPS
ARE GETTING IN THE WAY.
UM, EXAMPLES?
WELL, THE BREATHING?
I MEAN, TERRI SOUNDS
LIKE SHE'S SMOKING.
AND THIS THREE-QUARTER RULE?
OH I WAS ONLY TRYING TO HELP.
I'LL GO TALK WITH HER--
NO, YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE'RE GOING ON THIS AFTERNOON
SO I WILL
BECAUSE I'M THE DIRECTOR.
PAIGE:
ROSES ARE RED,
VIOLETS ARE BLUE,
MY NAME IS JT YORKE
AND I LOVE YOU?
YEAH?
C'MON, IT'S CLASSIC!
KIDS:
(LAUGHS)
JT:
OH YEAH!
SPINNER:
WELL, THAT'S IT!
JT:
YEAH!
RICK:
CAUSE I'M THE DIRECTOR.
CAN YOU BELIEVE HE ACTUALLY
SAID THAT TO ME?
I'M SO SORRY.
ONE, IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT
JIMMY IS A CONTROL FREAK.
TWO, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO LISTEN TO HIM.
I CAN'T JUST IGNORE
WHAT JIMMY WANTS.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
HE IS THE DIRECTOR.
A NOVICE DIRECTOR
THAT HAS ABSOLUTELY NO IDEA
WHAT HE'S DOING BUT-
RICK.
I'M SORRY BUT,
I JUST DON'T WANT YOU
TO EMBARRASS YOURSELF
IN FRONT OF ALL THOSE PEOPLE.
IT COULD BE SO HUMILIATING
FOR YOU.
TERRI:
I WANT MY SON TO SEE
THE SUN RISE.
HAZEL:
I'M AFRAID THAT WON'T HAPPEN.
BUT IT MUST!
I WANT HIM TO LIVE.
WHAT WE WANT,
ISN'T WHAT WE ALWAYS GET.
AND WHAT WE GET,
ISN'T WHAT WE WANT, IS IT?
MARCO:
MAMA?
ARE YOU THERE?
YES, SON.
MAMA IS HERE.
MAMA IS HERE, RAY.
MAMA WILL ALWAYS BE HERE.
I AM YOUR ROCK...
CLASS:
(LAUGHING)
AND YOUR SHELTER
IN THE STORM.
(LAUGHS)
RICK:
SO WHAT FILM SHOULD WE SEE?
THAT BRITISH IMPORT GOT
FABULOUS REVIEWS IN THE-
TERRI:
ARE WE GONNA TALK ABOUT IT?
RICK:
ABOUT WHAT?
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED
IN THEATRE CLASS.
WHAT'S THERE TO TALK ABOUT?
I LOOKED LIKE AN IDIOT
BECAUSE OF YOU.
EXCUSE ME?
EVERYONE WAS LAUGHING.
I SHOULD'VE LISTENED
TO JIMMY.
WHAT?
RICK:
LET ME MAKE ONE THING CLEAR.
I DON'T LIKE THAT
TONE OF VOICE.
IT MAKES ME FEEL STUPID,
ALL RIGHT?
OKAY, SORRY.
RICK, LET GO.
PLEASE.
RICK:
TERRI?
TERRI, PLEASE.
JUST LOOK.
FOR YOU.
IT DOESN'T EXCUSE WHAT
HAPPENED, I KNOW.
I FLEW OFF THE HANDLE.
YOU DID WAY MORE THAN THAT.
RICK:
WILL YOU LET ME APOLOGIZE?
PLEASE.
I WAS JEALOUS OF JIM.
HE HAS A THING FOR YOU.
WHY ELSE DID HE CAST YOU
IN THE LEAD?
WE'RE FRIENDS.
RICK:
AND HE'S SINGLE.
HE DOESN'T LIKE ME
THAT WAY.
TERRI, YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL.
AND SMART AND SWEET,
TALENTED.
CAN YOU BLAME ME FOR THINKING
EVERY GUY LOVES YOU LIKE I DO?
OH, WHAT'S THE OCCASION?
NO OCCASION - JUST BECAUSE.
WHAT'S WITH THIS GUY
AND THE ROSES?
WHY?
YOU THINK IT'S WEIRD?
TRY LUCKY.
HE TOTALLY SPOILS YOU.
GUESS HE'S JUST
A BIG ROMANTIC.
A BIG ROMANTIC WITH
A DISPOSABLE INCOME.
THE BEST KIND.
TER, YOU NEED TO FILL US
IN ON CETTE GRANDE ROMANCE.
SO AFTER SCHOOL.
MY HOUSE, MAJOR DEBRIEFING.
I SHOULD CHECK
WITH RICK FIRST.
PLEASE, THE WAY YOU HAVE HIM
WRAPPED AROUND YOUR FINGER?
I DON'T THINK
IT'LL BE A PROBLEM.
HEY, WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR ARM?
TERRI:
OH UH, VOLLEYBALL SERVE.
ANOTHER REASON TO HATE GYM.
SPINNER:
UH JT?
I WANTED TO APOLOGIZE.
YOU DO?
YEAH, UM, PRANKING YOU
WAS IMMATURE.
AND WELL, YOU GOT ME BACK.
SO, IT'S OVER.
OKAY,
I'M SORRY I PANTSED YOU.
SPINNER:
HEY WHATEVER, I'M OVER IT.
THING OF THE PAST.
JT:
RIGHT, OKAY.
ARE WE COOL?
WE'RE GOOD.
YEAH, OKAY.
ALL RIGHT. BYE.
SPINNER:
BYE.
JT:
HEY MANNY!
MIGHT I SAY YOU'RE LOOKING
LOVELY TODAY?
(FART SOUND)
MANNY:
THANK YOU.
DID YOU JUST...?
(MORE FARTING SOUNDS)
NO, NO. THAT WASN'T,
THAT WASN'T ME.
I DON'T KNOW, I DON'T KNOW
WHERE THAT'S COMING FROM.
UGH.
JT, THAT'S GROSS!
JT:
IT'S NOT ME!
IT'S, IT'S NOT!
MANNY:
THAT'S DISGUSTING.
JT:
BUT IT'S NOT ME!
(CONTINUING FART SOUNDS)
CRAIG:
OH MANNY! OH MANNY!
RICK:
STRIKING THE SET,
DEFINITELY THE WORST PART
OF STAGE MANAGING.
HEY RICK, DO WE HAVE
ANYTHING AFTER SCHOOL?
PAIGE INVITED ME AND HAZEL OVER
FOR, FOR A GIRL'S NIGHT THING.
SO, I CAN'T COME?
WELL IT'S SORT OF
JUST FOR GIRLS.
I UNDERSTAND WHAT GIRLS NIGHT
MEANS, TERRI.
I JUST DON'T SEE WHY
YOU NEED ONE.
IS IT SO YOU CAN TALK ABOUT ME?
WHAT? NO.
SO YOU CAN PICK UP GUYS?
NO!
RICK:
THEN WHY CAN'T I COME?
EXPLAIN IT TO ME BECAUSE
IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
RICK, YOU'RE BEING CRAZY.
DON'T EVER CALL ME THAT.
EVER.
TERRI, I'M SO SORRY.
SPINNER:
HERE YOU GO.
HELLO, GAVIN.
JT, YOU'RE HERE TO EAT,
RIGHT?
JT:
ABSOLUTELY.
WHY WOULD I WANT TO CAUSE
TROUBLE FOR YOU AT WORK?
I THINK I'LL HAVE
THE DOT-BURGER SUPREME,
PICKLES ON THE SIDE,
HOLD THE MAYO, TONS OF KETCHUP,
MUSTARD, DIJON,
NOT ON THE TOP BUN, BOTTOM BUN.
AND SPEAKING OF BUNS TAKE THOSE
LITTLE SESAME SEEDS OFF THEM.
I DON'T LIKE THEM GETTING
CAUGHT IN MY TEETH.
AND OF COURSE I WANT CHEESE.
TERRI:
IT WAS AMAZING.
HE COOKED DINNER,
FLOWERS, CANDLES.
AND EVEN FOLDED THE NAPKINS
AS LITTLE FANS.
THAT IS TOO CUTE.
OKAY, WHO'S EATING
ALL THE GOOD STUFF
AND LEAVING THE PRETZELS?
I THOUGHT YOU LIKED
PRETZELS.
HEY, YOU WANT ME TO DO
YOUR NAILS?
SURE.
SO THINGS SOUND PRETTY
AMAZING WITH YOU AND RICK.
NO PROBLEMS AT ALL?
NOPE.
WHY?
YOU NEVER FIGHT?
SOMETIMES...
ONLY WHEN
I HURT HIS FEELINGS.
HE'S SO SENSITIVE.
HM.
TERRI, WHAT'S THAT ON YOUR LIP?
IT'S JUST A COLD SORE.
SO GROSS.
SO THEN,
WHAT'S THIS?
IT'S NOTHING.
JUST-
I MEAN, IF HE'S HURTING YOU,
YOU'D TELL ME, RIGHT?
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
I'M JUST CONCERNED.
YOU'RE JEALOUS.
JEALOUS?
TERRI:
NOBODY LOVES YOU
AND HE LOVES ME.
AND YOU WANT TO TAKE THAT AWAY?
PAIGE:
TERRI?
I SAID CORN RELISH.
TAKE IT BACK.
THAT IS THE THIRD TIME.
THE BURGER IS FINE.
EAT IT.
THE CUSTOMER IS ALWAYS RIGHT.
TAKE IT BACK.
OOPSY-DAISIES.
SPOON FELL.
BE A GOOD BOY,
GET ME A CLEAN ONE.
JT, RUN ALONG HOME
BEFORE I GET MAD.
DON'T DO THAT.
IT MAKES ME INSANE!
SPINNER:
JT!
MANAGER:
GAVIN, IN MY OFFICE NOW!
RICK, WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
I WAS WAITING FOR YOU
TO COME HOME.
I HAVE SOMETHING TO TELL YOU.
WELL, NOW'S NOT A GOOD TIME.
I WANTED TO TELL YOU
THAT I LOVE YOU.
AND THAT YOU'RE SPECIAL.
THAT'S REALLY SWEET,
RICK.
BUT I NEED TO BE ALONE.
ME AND HAZEL HAD A FIGHT.
RICK:
WELL, ONE,
I'M NOT SURPRISED.
TWO, LET'S MAKE A RULE.
YOU SEE HAZEL AND PAIGE
IN SCHOOL, ONLY.
I NEED TO GO.
I NEED TO THINK.
ABOUT WHAT?
LEAVING ME?
I DON'T WANT TO, RICK.
I LOVE YOU.
IT JUST THAT YOU'RE
SUFFOCATING ME!
I'M SORRY, TERRI.
THAT WAS-
THAT WAS THE LAST TIME
YOU EVER TOUCH ME.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
TO APOLOGIZE.
LOOK, I'M SERIOUS,
SPINNER.
PAIGE TOLD ME THAT
YOUR BOSS DEMOTED YOU.
YEAH, TO DISHPIG.
THANKS.
WELL THANKS FOR HUMILIATING ME
IN FRONT OF MANNY.
I THINK OUR WAR'S GONE
FAR ENOUGH, HM?
WHAT DO YOU SAY
TO A PEACE SETTLEMENT?
FINE.
IF YOU STOP CROWDING ME
AND PAIGE ALL THE TIME.
OKAY, IF YOU STOP TREATING ME
LIKE I'M SOME HUMAN PLAGUE.
DONE.
WORKING OUT
YOUR DIFFERENCES?
YEAH, SOMETHING LIKE THAT,
HONEYBEE.
GAVIN.
IF ONLY YOU COULD APPLY THIS
PASSION TO YOUR POEMS IN CLASS.
O MISS KWAN YOUR HAIR,
KISSED BY THE WIND
YOUR LIPS, KISSED BY ME,
SPINNER MASON.
LET ME SEE THAT.
LOOK I MEAN IT, TERRI.
IF THIS GUY EVER
BOTHERS YOU AGAIN,
LET ME KNOW, OKAY?
THANKS, JIMMY.
I JUST FEEL
SO STUPID.
HE WAS YOUR FIRST
BOYFRIEND.
YOU WANTED IT
TO WORK OUT.
PROBABLY MY LAST.
YOU'LL FIND SOMEONE ELSE,
TER.
WHEN YOU'RE READY.
IF I'M EVER.
THE TERRIBLE PART IS
I STILL CARE FOR HIM.
BUT YOU HAVE TO STOP.
YOU KNOW THAT, RIGHT?
I KNOW.