PAIGE:
CALL IT "THE PAIGE PARTY
ON WHEELS."
MY PARENTS MINIVAN,
ONE BEAUTIFUL SATURDAY
AND WE ARE NOT WASTING
A SECOND OF IT.
ALL:
SHOTGUN!
SPINNER:
UH... SHE'S MY GIRLFRIEND.
MY BEST FRIEND.
I SMELL BETTER
THAN BOTH OF YOU SO...
PAIGE:
NO BICKERING, PASSENGERS.
I'LL JUST HAVE
TO ASSIGN SHIFTS.
TERRI:
HEY GUYS, WHAT'S GOING ON?
PAIGE:
ROAD TRIP.
MY FOLKS ARE AWAY
AND I'VE GOT THE CAR KEYS!
TERRI:
HAVE FUN.
HAZEL:
WHAT?
TER, YOU'RE TOTALLY COMING.
TERRI:
YOU'LL BE WITH JIMMY,
SPIN WILL BE WITH PAIGE,
AND I?
WILL BE WITH ALL YOUR FRIENDS,
IDIOT.
IT'S NOT EXACTLY THE SAME.
PAIGE:
SO THEN BRING SOMEONE.
WHATEVER.
SPINNER:
YEAH.
UM, CAN I PLEASE HAVE
THE FRONT SEAT?
PAIGE:
YOU'LL JUST HAVE TO WAIT
YOUR TURN, OKAY?
SPINNER:
NO. COME ON. COME ON.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Hear what I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
KWAN:
OKAY GUYS, GREAT WORK.
BUT NOW IT'S TIME TO MOVE ON
TO TRUST EXERCISES.
SO, FIND YOURSELF
A NEW PARTNER
AND DECIDE WHO'S "A"
AND WHO'S "B".
OKAY, LET'S BREAK UP
INTO GROUPS.
ONE GROUP OVER HERE.
ANOTHER GROUP BEHIND YOU.
WHICHEVER YOU WANT.
KWAN:
FIND OUT WHO'S "A"
AND WHO'S "B".
FINE.
I'LL BE "A".
KWAN:
OKAY, NOW I WANT THE "A"'S TO
STAND IN FRONT OF THE "B"'S.
AND I WANT YOU TO TURN YOUR
BACKS TO "B"'S LIKE THIS.
"B"'S OPEN UP YOUR ARMS,
CAUSE THE "A"'S ARE GONNA
FALL BACK INTO YOUR ARMS.
SPIN:
LET'S GO AGAIN.
PAIGE:
OKAY.
DO YOU HONESTLY THINK
I'M GONNA DROP YOU?
BECAUSE I'M NOT.
TRUST ME.
THAT WASN'T SO BAD,
WAS IT?
(BELL RINGS)
I'M JUST DESPERATE
FOR A REAL OPPORTUNITY
TO DEVELOP OUR REAL
ACTING SHOPS.
WELL, WE DID DO
MARCO'S PLAY.
OKAY, I DON'T MEAN LIKE
AMATEURISH THEATRICS,
I MEAN THE CLASSICS.
LIKE BRECHT, OR IBSEN.
HEY THERE'S A MIME
UNIT NEXT WEEK.
OH YEAH, GREAT.
JUST WHAT THE WORLD NEEDS.
MORE PEOPLE WALKING
AGAINST THE WIND.
I WANTED TO CALL YOU...
SO MANY TIMES.
I JUST DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY
EXCEPT I'M SORRY -
FOR MY TEMPER
AND WHAT I DID.
I NEVER MEANT
TO HURT YOU.
LOOK, I MISSED YOU.
I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
IT WAS ALL MY FAULT,
BUT IF THERE'S ANY,
ANY WAY THAT YOU THINK-
I'LL- I'LL SEE YOU
IN BIO, OKAY?
SIMPSON:
HEY, BEFORE YOU ALL SCATTER,
HERE ARE YOUR POP QUIZZES BACK.
WELL DONE.
MARCO:
UM, JUST SO YOU KNOW,
MR. SIMPSON?
THE SUBSTITUTE WASN'T NEARLY
AS MUCH FUN AS YOU.
WE'RE ALL GLAD
TO HAVE YOU BACK.
(APPLAUSE)
AW, JUST SO YOU KNOW,
APPLAUSE WILL NOT IMPROVE
YOUR GRADE...
BY MORE THAN
A FEW PERCENT.
MARCO:
SO EL, TOMORROW?
PATHER PANCHALI
AND PARASH PATHAR?
ASHLEY:
YOU GUYS ARE ORDERING
INDIAN FOOD?
ELLIE:
CLOSE. SEEING A DOUBLE BILL-
MARCO:
OF CLASSIC INDIAN CINEMA.
ASHLEY:
AND YOU REALLY THINK SEAN'S
GOING TO SIT THROUGH THAT?
ELLIE:
WHY WOULD SEAN COME?
ASHLEY:
WELL, IT IS SATURDAY,
RIGHT?
YOU GUYS ARE SEEING
EACH OTHER.
ELLIE:
SO?
DOESN'T MEAN THINGS
CHANGE WITH MY FRIENDS.
ASHLEY:
CHANGE ISN'T AUTOMATICALLY
BAD, EL.
CAITLIN ON TV:
THERE SEEMS TO BE ONE
FOLLOWING YOU
EVERYWHERE YOU GO THESE DAYS.
THE SUPERMARKET, THE WORKPLACE,
THE PARKING GARAGE...
ELLIE:
IT'S FANTASTIC, CAITLIN.
CAITLIN:
I ALWAYS CRINGE
AT MYSELF ON TAPE.
CAITLIN ON TV:
WE'VE GOT TO ASK OURSELVES,
JUST WHO'S WATCHING?
DON'T ALLOW YOURSELF TO BE
LULLED INTO BLIND ACCEPTANCE.
SECURITY CAMERAS?
I THOUGHT TAPE RECORDERS
WERE THE NEXT BIG THING.
CAITLIN:
I THINK I HEARD TOMAS CALLING.
ELLIE:
SURPRISE DROP IN.
UNEXPECTED,
BUT NICE.
SEAN:
ELLIE NASH JUST
SAID NICE.
SO TOMORROW...
YES?
IT'S THE OPENING WEEKEND
OF "ELIMINATION ROUND THREE".
IT'S A MOVIE -
AN ACTION FRANCHISE.
DO- DO YOU WANNA-
YES.
YOU CAN TAKE
YOUR TIME.
OH, BUT-
WHAT?
IS THERE A PROBLEM?
NO.
THAT WOULD BE...
NICE.
SPINNER:
ANYWAY, WHATEVER YOU DO,
DON'T ORDER CHILI.
TERRI:
HEY GUYS.
SORRY I'M SO LATE.
RICK:
SO TERRI CAN I BUY YOU
A LATTE?
TERRI:
SO SWEET.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
I MUST BE HALLUCINATING.
I HOPE SO.
PAIGE:
I SO WILL REFUSE TO DRIVE
THAT FREAK AROUND ALL DAY.
SPINNER:
PAIGE, NO-
SPIN, SHE'S RIGHT.
YEAH, BUT IF WE LEAVE
HIM BEHIND,
GUARANTEED WE LEAVE HER
BEHIND, TOO.
WITHOUT ANY OF US
TO LOOK OUT FOR HER.
AND THEN IT'S OPEN SEASON
FOR RICK AGAIN.
ELLIE:
MARCO, COME ON.
MARCO:
WHAT! WE WOULDN'T WANT
TO MISS A SECOND
OF ELIMINATION ROUND...
WHATEVER.
ELLIE:
SORRY.
MARCO:
HELLO, JAY.
JAY:
UH... YEAH.
YOU KNOW WHAT,
ALEX?
I'M HUNGRY.
WHY DON'T YOU GO
GET ME SOME POPCORN?
GIVE ME TWENTY BUCKS
AND I WILL.
I ALREADY HAD PLANS
WITH MARCO,
SO I THOUGHT I'D ASK HIM.
IS THERE A PROBLEM?
LET'S GET SEATS.
TERRI:
IT'S A GREAT DAY.
EW! SPIN, YOU ARE TURNING
MY STOMACH.
COULD YOU PLEASE EAT
LIKE A PERSON?
RICK:
COME ON, TER,
WHY DON'T YOU SIT HERE?
PAIGE:
UH, RICK, I WOULD RATHER YOU
NOT DENT MY PARENTS VAN
WITH YOUR BUTT.
I'M NOT HURTING IT.
TERRI:
RICK?
COME SIT OVER HERE,
WITH ME.
JUST DON'T EVEN WORRY
ABOUT IT.
YEAH,
I'M TRYING NOT TO.
(BATTLE AND GUNFIRE SOUNDS)
ELLIE AND MARCO:
(LAUGHING)
ELLIE:
SHHH.
RICK:
I'LL BE OVER THERE,
SO IF YOU NEED ME.
TERRI:
OKAY.
PAIGE:
HEY, WANT TO PLAY
FRISBEE WITH US?
I NEED TO SHOW SPIN
A THING OR TWO.
MAYBE LATER.
RICK WANTS TO TALK.
YOU KNOW, YOU SHOULD
COME OVER TONIGHT.
JUST HANG OUT,
DISH WITH THE GIRLS.
I'M FINE, PAIGE.
THERE'S NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
SO WHAT, YOU'VE JUST
FORGIVEN CREEP-BOY
FOR BEATING YOU UP?
HE APOLOGIZED.
OF COURSE.
HIS TYPE ALWAYS DOES
SO THEY CAN GET ANOTHER
SHOT IN AT YOU.
RICK:
ONE, YOU HAVE NO RIGHT
TO DICTATE
WHO TERRI'S FRIENDS ARE.
AND TWO, YOU'RE A VICIOUS
BACK-STABBER.
OH, I'M VICIOUS?
EVERYTHING YOU SAY
IS A JUDGMENT.
YOU THINK YOU'RE SO PERFECT.
PAIGE:
WHAT?
WELL, I'D RATHER BE THAT
THAN A PSYCHO.
RICK'S RIGHT.
I'M SO TIRED OF YOU
PUSHING ME AROUND,
TELLING ME WHAT TO DO.
I'M SICK OF IT!
FINE.
IF I'M SUCH A BAD FRIEND,
GO AFTER HIM.
GO!
I'M SO SORRY
ABOUT PAIGE.
IT DOES NOT MATTER.
SHE DOES NOT MATTER!
PLEASE, RICK.
CALM DOWN.
I'M SORRY.
I'M JUST-
I'M JUST SO HAPPY.
YOU KNOW, JUST-
WE'RE TOGETHER AGAIN.
WE WERE MADE
FOR EACH OTHER.
COME BACK.
WE'LL IGNORE PAIGE-
NO. NO, LET'S WALK.
IT'S REALLY FAR.
SHE CALLED ME
A PSYCHO.
THAT'S JUST PAIGE
BEING PAIGE.
THAT MAKES IT OKAY?
MY FEELINGS MEAN
NOTHING TO YOU?
WHOA!
RICK.
DON'T YOU DARE CHOOSE
PAIGE OVER ME AGAIN.
DON'T YOU DARE!
I'M GOING BACK, OKAY?
YOU C-C-C-CAN'T LEAVE,
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
RICK,
YOU'RE HURTING ME!
YOU'RE NOT GOING!
YOU'RE NOT!
(FRIGHTENED GASP)
HAZEL:
THAT WAS AN EVEN STUPIDER MOVIE.
EARTH TO PAIGE.
TERRI'S NOT BACK
YET.
NO?
BE RIGHT BACK.
SPINNER:
THERE'S RICK.
MAYBE TERRI'S...
PAIGE:
OH MY GOD!
TERRI!
OKAY, GET YOUR CELL NOW!
PLEASE, TERRI, WAKE UP.
PLEASE.
OH MY GOD, TERRI!
TERRI, PLEASE.
RADITCH:
AND FINALLY...
AS SOME OF YOU MAY KNOW,
TERRI MACGREGOR
IS IN THE HOSPITAL
WITH INJURIES THAT SHE
SUSTAINED OVER THE WEEKEND.
AND I KNOW I SPEAK
FOR ALL OF DEGRASSI
WHEN I WISH HER A SPEEDY
RECOVERY.
THANK YOU.
MARCO:
UH, SIR?
WAS IT, LIKE,
AN ACCIDENT OR-
SPINNER:
IT WAS NO ACCIDENT.
ASHLEY:
SO, THEN IS RICK IN JAIL?
SIMPSON:
I KNOW EVERYONE'S UPSET,
BUT WE'RE NOT ALLOWED
TO TALK DETAILS.
SPINNER:
YEAH, OKAY, I WAS THERE.
I KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
GAVIN.
SPINNER:
IF RICK STEPS ONE FOOT
IN DEGRASSI,
HE'LL BE THE ONE
IN INTENSIVE CARE.
SIMPSON:
THOSE INVOLVED WERE MINORS,
SO ONCE AGAIN,
WE CAN'T TALK DETAILS.
WHAT WE CAN DO IS DISCUSS
OUR FEELINGS TOGETHER.
WHY SHOULD WE PROTECT
THAT PIECE OF-
WE CAN BRAINSTORM
WHAT WE CAN DO FOR TERRI.
ANY THOUGHTS?
PAIGE:
WE MADE A CARD.
WE THOUGHT EVERYBODY
COULD SIGN IT .
SIMPSON:
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA, PAIGE.
THANKS.
WHY DON'T YOU PASS IT
AROUND.
ELLIE:
I COULD GO WITH ASH,
BUT I DIDN'T REALLY
KNOW TERRI.
FEELS MORBID.
MARCO:
WELL, WE CAN GO TOGETHER,
IF YOU WANT.
SEAN:
HEY.
ELLIE:
HI.
MARCO?
MARCO:
LOOK, IT'S FINE.
I'LL JUST SEE YOU
IN ENGLISH.
SEAN:
WHAT?
I JUST WANTED TO SPEND
TIME ALONE.
GOT YOUR WISH.
MR. MCGREGOR:
HEY PAIGE. SPINNER.
WHAT YOU GOT THERE?
PAIGE:
IT'S A CARD FOR TERRI.
THE SCHOOL SIGNED IT.
MR. MCGREGOR:
OH, THAT'S GREAT.
THANKS.
THANKS FOR COMING.
PAIGE:
HOW IS SHE?
SURGERY TONIGHT.
THEY FOUND A BLOOD CLOT.
BUT SHE'S GONNA
BE OKAY?
IT'S A BIG OPERATION.
BUT HEY YEAH,
SHE'S GONNA PULL THROUGH.
SHE'S A FIGHTER,
MY LITTLE BABY.
HOW COULD ANYBODY
DO THIS TO HER?
PAIGE:
I KNOW.
MR. MCGREGOR:
RICK.
I MEAN, TERRI WAS OVER
THE MOON FOR THE GUY.
WHAT?
YOU KNEW HE WAS ABUSIVE?
SPINNER:
NO, MR. MCGREGOR...
FOR HOW LONG?
WE TRIED TO TALK TO HER.
WHAT ABOUT ME?
WHY DIDN'T YOU TO TALK TO ME?
WE THOUGHT IT WAS UNDER
CONTROL.
YOU STILL THINK
IT'S UNDER CONTROL?
HEY, SHE'S GONNA
BE OKAY.
WHAT? WHAT!
I SHOULD GO.
WE SHOULDN'T DO THIS.
NOT- NOT TONIGHT.
EXCUSE ME?
YOU'RE UPSET
BECAUSE OF TERRI.
THIS HAS GOT NOTHING TO DO
WITH TERRI.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
NONE OF THIS
WOULD'VE HAPPENED
IF YOU'D HAVE LET ME LEAVE
RICK BEHIND AT "THE DOT".
I'M NOT THE ONE WHO TOLD HER
TO GO OFF WITH HIM.
(SOBBING)
ELLIE:
I SHOULD DUMP HIM.
MARCO:
SEAN?
ELLIE:
YOU'RE WORTH SIX SEANS.
HE CAN'T BE THAT RUDE
AND EXPECT ME
TO STICK AROUND.
SEAN'S RUDE, EL?
WHAT DO YOU CALL BRINGING MARCO
THE-HUMAN-SECURITY-BLANKET
ON A DOUBLE DATE?
MARCO THE WHAT?
LOOK...
I KNOW YOU WANT EVERYTHING
TO STAY THE SAME.
BUT SEAN COULD BE
GREAT FOR YOU...
IF YOU'D LET HIM.
SPINNER:
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
TERRI'S IN THE HOSPITAL
AND YOU'RE JUST
SITTING HERE?!
RICK:
SPINNER, STOP! PLEASE!
SPINNER:
OH, DID TERRI TELL YOU TO STOP?
DID YOU LISTEN?
PAIGE:
SPINNER! JUST-
JUST LET IT GO!
PLEASE, SPINNER.
STOP IT!
LET HIM GO!
YOU STAY AWAY FROM MY SON!
BOTH OF YOU!
SPINNER, HONEY...
I'M JUST LIKE HIM -
VIOLENT.
PAIGE:
NO. YOU STOPPED YOURSELF.
YOU'RE DIFFERENT, OKAY?
YOU ARE.
RADITCH OVER P.A.:
THE MCGREGOR FAMILY WOULD LIKE
TO THANK ALL THE STUDENTS
FOR THEIR GET WELL WISHES
AND SUPPORT IN THIS TIME.
IF ANY STUDENTS WOULD LIKE TO
SEND A CARD TO MR. MCGREGOR
DROP THEM OFF IN THE OFFICE
TO BE DELIVERED
AT THE END OF THE WEEK.
ELLIE:
SEAN.
LISTEN... I'M...
AREN'T WE THROUGH?
OKAY, ARE YOU, LIKE,
DUMPING ME?
DIDN'T YOU
ALREADY DUMP ME?
LET'S TRY THIS AGAIN.
I'M HERE TO APOLOGIZE.
I HAVEN'T BEEN A VERY GOOD
GIRLFRIEND.
BUT YOU HAVEN'T BEEN THAT
GREAT A BOYFRIEND, EITHER.
LOOK, I DON'T HATE MARCO,
OKAY.
IT'S JUST...
WELL, I'M DATING YOU.
I'VE NEVER DONE
THIS BEFORE.
LIKE, A REAL
RELATIONSHIP THING.
SO IF I DON'T TOTALLY
KNOW HOW IT WORKS...
THEN YOU CAN ASK ME.
PAIGE:
SPIN, LET'S JUST GO,
OKAY?
SPINNER:
NO, LET'S STAY.
WE'LL BE FINE.
MR. MCGREGOR:
UM, WE STILL DON'T KNOW
THE EXTENT OF THE DAMAGE,
BUT SHE CAME THROUGH
THE SURGERY.
THAT'S ONE BIG HURDLE.
PAIGE:
WELL, WE ARE SO GLAD.
AND... WE'RE SO SORRY.
OH, NO. I WAS WAY
OUT OF LINE YESTERDAY.
SPINNER:
YOU WERE UPSET.
MR. MCGREGOR:
AT YOU AND AT MYSELF.
RICK WAS AT OUR PLACE
ALL THE TIME.
I DON'T KNOW WHY
I DIDN'T I SEE.
PAIGE:
BUT WE SAW AND WE SHOULD'VE
SAID SOMETHING.
MR. MCGREGOR:
I'D BETTER GET BACK TO HER
IN CASE SHE COMES AROUND.
THANKS FOR COMING, GUYS.
YOU'RE GOOD FRIENDS.