YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
TAKE IT EASY, GUYS.
SO...
SO WHAT?
LOOK SPIN, UM...
YOU DIDN'T TELL ANYBODY,
DID YOU?
TELL ANYONE WHAT?
ABOUT WHAT I SAID
YESTERDAY.
AT THE CAFE...
MAN, AFTER THE DATE
WITH HAZEL.
YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
(LAUGHING)
DUDE, I CAN'T READ YOUR MIND
SO JUST SAY IT.
THAT I'M GAY.
(LAUGHING)
OH, THAT.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
MAYBE I DID...
MAYBE I DIDN'T.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Hear what I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
ELLIE:
I'M SURE HE DIDN'T
TELL ANYONE.
WHY WOULD HE?
MARCO:
TO MAKE MY LIFE
A LIVING HELL?
CRAIG:
ALL RIGHT, SPIN ASKED US
TO KEEP IT A SECRET,
TILL HE'S THOUGHT
ABOUT IT MORE
SO YOU CAN'T TELL ANYBODY,
ALL RIGHT?
JIMMY:
PROMISE.
KEEP WHAT A SECRET?
YEAH, WHAT'S
THE BIG NEWS?
OKAY, UM...
PAIGE TURNS 16
IN A FEW WEEKS,
AND SPIN'S PLANNING
A SURPRISE PARTY.
CRAIG:
YEAH, MEANING YOU TWO
CAN TELL NO ONE.
GUYS...
I'LL CARRY THE SECRET
TO MY GRAVE, OKAY?
SEE YOU IN HOMEROOM, HUH?
OH, SORRY.
(TAPS ON WINDOW)
(SIGHS)
HEY, JUST WANTED TO CHECK IN.
SEE HOW YOU'RE HOLDING UP.
GOOD. WELL MY LAST MEAL
WAS 14 HOURS AGO
SO I'M A LITTLE HUNGRY,
BUT UH...
I WASN'T GOING
TO LUNGE AT IT.
YOU KNOW,
I AM NOT AN ANIMAL.
SO, UH, MOM'S PICKING YOU
UP THIS AFTERNOON.
FOR MY BIOPSY, YES.
AND YOU CAN SAY LEUKEMIA TOO,
'CAUSE I DON'T HAVE IT YET.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD JUST GO HOME.
NO, NO, I'M FINE.
I'M FINE.
BESIDES UH, MANNY'S SILENT
AUCTION'S IS AT LUNCH.
NOTHING SAYS JACKPOT LIKE
A PERSONAL ASCII PORTRAIT.
HEY LOOK,
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
HE LOOKS MORE LIKE ME,
OR SPIKE?
HE LOOKS LIKE
A BUNCH OF CODE.
ACTUALLY, I'M GONNA LOOK A LOT
LIKE JACK IF CHEMO HAS ITS WAY.
BALD, BALD, BALD.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
CRAIG:
WHY ARE THEY TEACHING US
ABOUT SOIL EROSION?
I'M NOT A FARMER.
I'M NEVER GONNA
BE A FARMER.
DYLAN:
HERE'S THE JUNIOR "A"
TICKETS I PROMISED.
HEY NICE!
DYLAN:
YOU GUYS STILL COMING
TO SEE ME PLAY?
JIMMY:
I WOULDN'T MISS IT.
DYLAN:
ALL RIGHT,
SEE YOU TONIGHT.
OH, REMEMBER,
ONE OF THOSE IS FOR MARCO.
OH MAN, HOCKEY,
THE GARDENS...
BOYS NIGHT OUT!
BOYS NIGHT.
OOH HOCKEY!
OOH BOYS NIGHT OUT!
COULD YOU TWO
BE BIGGER FAGS?
JIMMY:
OKAY, NOW I DON'T KNOW.
WHO'S THE BIGGER WEIRDO TODAY,
SPINNER OR MARCO?
MARCO,
AND HE'S NOT COMING.
WHAT? SINCE WHEN DOES
MARCO LIKE HOCKEY?
HE'S DOING SOME GAY ARTSY
THING WITH ELLIE ANYWAY.
JIMMY:
UH, THEY BROKE UP.
RIGHT. BROKE UP.
FUNNY.
JIMMY:
MARCO.
WHAT'S THIS I HEAR ABOUT
YOU BAILING ON US TONIGHT.
MARCO:
BAILING?
YEAH, DYLAN'S GAME.
YOU'RE CHILLIN'
WITH ELLIE, RIGHT?
THAT'S TOO BAD, MAN.
ARMSTRONG:
OKAY, GUYS IN YOUR TEAMS,
I WANT YOU TO SPREAD OUT
ON EITHER SIDE OF THE NET.
THIS IS A VOLLEYING DRILL,
MEANING...
I WANT TO SEE THREE SUCCESSFUL
VOLLEYS AMONG YOUR OWN PLAYERS
BEFORE PUTTING IT OVER.
LET'S GET STARTED.
MARCO:
SO, WHAT NOW, HUH?
WHAT, ARE YOU FREEZING ME
OUT WITH THE GUYS?
WHY DO YOU WANNA
COME ANYWAY?
IT'S HOCKEY,
NOT BALLET.
DYLAN INVITED ME.
YEAH, AND THAT'S THE ONLY
REASON YOU WANT TO GO.
YOUR BIG GAY CRUSH.
ARMSTRONG:
YOU GUYS GONNA GOSSIP OR PLAY?
LET'S GO.
THIS SIDE SERVES FIRST.
GAVIN!
DID I SAY TO SPIKE?
ALL:
WOO.
HEY, NICE GOING,
SPINNER!
THEN VOLLEY LIKE I TOLD YOU.
OKAY MATT, YOU SERVE.
GAVIN! CHANGE ROOM, NOW.
GOOD THING SPIN
SPIKES LIKE A GIRL.
SIMPSON:
LIBERTY, COME ON,
TWO DOLLARS?
OKAY, I GUESS IT
COULD GO UP TO FIVE.
YOU CAN GO UP TO TEN.
COME ON.
MANNY'S COUNTING ON ME
TO BRING IN THE BIG BUCKS.
MANNY:
EVEN FIFTY BUCKS
WOULD BE NICE.
LOOKS LIKE SOMEONE'S
ALREADY THERE.
SO I WANT YOU
TO PLACE YOUR BIDS
AND THE HIGHEST BIDDERS
GET TO SPEND A DAY WITH ME
AND WE'RE GOING TO
THE SCIENCE CENTRE
AND IT'LL BE A LOT OF FUN,
OKAY? HERE YOU GO.
ALL RIGHT, WATCH THIS.
DEGRASSI.
(CLEARS THROAT)
DEGRASSI!
I ISSUE YOU A CHALLENGE.
RAISE $250 BUCKS
BY THIS TIME TOMORROW?
AND I'LL SHAVE MY HEAD,
RIGHT HERE IN THE FOYER.
ALL:
(EXCITED CHATTER AND APPLAUSE)
MAKE ME PROUD, PEOPLE.
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM
WITH MARCO?
WHAT'S MY PROBLEM?
THAT'S MY PROBLEM, OKAY?
AND IT'S TRUE.
HE TOLD ME HIMSELF.
MARCO'S GAY?
YEAH, AND IF YOU
DON'T BACK OFF,
I MAY START TO THINK
YOU ARE TOO.
JIMMY;
SO WHAT'RE YOU
GONNA WRITE NEXT?
SOMETHING ABOUT ME
BEING BLACK?
ELLIE:
HEY, I HEARD ABOUT GYM CLASS.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA
TAKE THAT, ARE YOU?
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED
TO DO, EL?
I DON'T KNOW,
GET DYLAN TO USE SPINNER
AS A HOCKEY PUCK TONIGHT?
YEAH. I'M NOT GOING.
DYLAN INVITED YOU.
YOU HAVE TO.
WHY?
ELLIE:
MARCO, COME ON.
I'M NOT BLIND.
GO TO THE GAME.
YOU BETTER BE COMING,
DEL ROSSI.
PIZZA AT THE DOT FIRST,
THEN A NIGHT OF
OUR NATIONAL SPORT.
BUT SPIN-
JIMMY:
SPIN'S AN IDIOT.
OKAY, SO COME.
FINE, BUT I'LL MEET
YOU AT THE ARENA, OKAY?
BECAUSE PIZZA AND SPIN...
ALWAYS A BAD COMBO.
OKAY, I'LL SEE YOU THERE.
CRAIG:
NO WAY.
JIMMY:
SO I SAYS TO HIM, I SAYS...
SPINNER:
JIMMY, WHAT DOES
TOUGH STILL MEAN?
JIMMY:
TOUGH STILL?
I DON'T KNOW,
IT'S TOUGH STILL, DUDE.
UM, I THOUGHT THIS
WAS BOYS' NIGHT.
FOR YOU.
FOR ME IT'S WATCH-
DYLAN-PLAY-HOCKEY-
FOR-THE-GAZILLIONTH-TIME NIGHT.
WHERE'S MARCO?
SPINNER?
JIMMY:
UM, ACTUALLY HE'S GONNA
MEET US AT THE ARENA.
DO YOU WANT TO GO
SETTLE THE BILL?
OKAY, HON,
GET OVER IT ALREADY.
PAIGE...
PAIGE:
I'VE BEEN THERE WITH DYLAN
AND IT'S HARD, I KNOW.
SPINNER:
YEAH, BUT DYLAN'S YOUR BROTHER,
YOU HAD TO DEAL.
AND YOU HAVE
TO DEAL WITH MARCO.
NO, ACTUALLY,
I DON'T.
(SIGHS)
JOEY:
OKAY, I THINK
THAT'S EVERYTHING.
SALAD, SYDNEY'S
SEAFOOD JAMBALAYA...
SYDNEY:
I KNOW, SOUNDS SUSPECT,
BUT THE OMEGA 3 FATTY ACIDS
WILL DO WONDERS FOR
SNAKE'S IMMUNE SYSTEM.
COOL.
JOEY:
SALAD, BREAD AND DESSERT.
OKAY, WE SHOULD GO
BEFORE THEY ARRIVE.
RIGHT.
THAT WAS A PAIN IN THE...
SURPRISE?
WHAT ARE YOU
GUYS DOING HERE?
UH, WE'D JUST THOUGHT
WE'D DROP OFF SOME FOOD,
AND NOW WE'RE
GONNA LEAVE.
'CAUSE WE KNOW YOU'VE
HAD A HARD DAY-
SIMPSON:
WHAT? NO. WHAT, THIS?
NO, IT'S NOTHING.
STAY, STAY.
ARCHIE, C'MON,
YOU'RE EXHAUSTED.
NO, I'M NOT.
FINE, BUT I WANT
YOU TO SIT.
OH, SIT, RIGHT.
THE BIOPSY WAS FROM
MY PELVIC BONE,
SO I WON'T BE COMPLAINING
ABOUT HEMORRHOIDS
ANY TIME SOON.
THAT WAS A JOKE.
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT DEAD YET.
SNAKE...
WHAT? WHAT?
WE'VE GOT GOOD FOOD,
MY FRIENDS ARE HERE
AND I JUST HAD MARROW
TAKEN OUT OF MY BUTT.
SO SUE ME IF I WANT
TO HAVE A GOOD TIME.
COME ON.
LET'S GET THIS
PARTY STARTED!
THE FOOD SMELLS GREAT.
(MUSIC FROM BOOM BOX)
MARCO: (INTO CELL)
HEY, JIM, IT'S MARCO.
I GOT OFF AT THE WRONG STOP.
I KNOW, I JUST TURNED
ONTO CHURCH STREET.
I'LL BE THERE SOON. CIAO.
TOUGH GUY 1:
OH, WHAT ARE YOU LOST? HUH?
MARCO:
UH NO, ACTUALLY I'M JUST
MEETING SOME FRIENDS
FOR A HOCKEY GAME.
(LAUGHS)
TOUGH GUY 1:
BOYS NIGHT OUT IN UH,
BOYS TOWN, HUH? HUH?
MARCO:
UH...
UH, YEAH.
ACTUALLY I THINK
I CAN FIND IT, THANKS.
TOUGH GUY 1:
LOOK, I DON'T CARE
WHAT YOU WANT, FAGGOT!
DO YOU KNOW KNOW
WHAT I WANT?
HUH?!
PAIGE:
DYLAN! DYLAN!
WOO, LET'S GO!
LET'S KICK SOME HOCKEY BUTT!
WOO! WOO!
SPINNER:
YOU ARE SUCH A CHEERLEADER.
JIMMY:
OPEN YOUR EYES.
SPINNER:
DUDE, IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
JIMMY:
NO, IT WAS YOU BEING A LOSER.
SPINNER:
WHAT?
JIMMY:
IF MARCO GETS HERE
BEFORE I'M BACK,
JUST DON'T ACT LIKE A PSYCHO?
SPINNER:
AH YES MOM, I'LL BE NICE
TO YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
PAIGE:
WOO! COME ON, BOYS! LET'S GO!
DYLAN! COME ON!
(DIALS CELL PHONE)
TOUGH GUY 1:
YOU ARE PRETTY,
AREN'T YOU?
YES.
ALMOST...
ALMOST GIRL PRETTY.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
OH, I THINK THAT'S
HIS BOYFRIEND.
THAT'S WHAT I THINK.
ANSWER IT.
ANSWER IT, COME ON.
MARCO:
GUYS, HELP ME,
I'M IN THE PARK!
TOUGH GUY 2:
OH, NO ONE'S HELPING YOU.
MARCO?
MARCO?!
MARCO:
(GRUNTS IN PAIN)
TOUGH GUYS:
(SHOUT TAUNTS)
(WHACK)
GET OFF OF ME!
TOUGH GUY:
COME ON!
MARCO:
STOP! (CRYING)
GET AWAY.
TOUGH GUY:
GET UP!
MARCO:
GET OFF OF ME!
(POLICE SIREN)
POLICE WOMAN:
HOLD IT! STAY RIGHT THERE!
MARCO:
(CRIES)
POLICE WOMAN:
YOU'RE GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
YOU'LL BE ALL RIGHT, OKAY?
DON'T MOVE, DON'T MOVE,
YOU'LL BE OKAY.
DON'T MOVE, JUST STAY.
STAY THERE,
YOU'RE GONNA BE FINE.
YOU'LL BE FINE.
MARCO:
HEY, IT'S MARCO'S CELL.
JUST DO YOUR THING. CAIO.
(POLICE SIRENS)
POLICE WOMAN:
THAT LOOKS OKAY.
YOU'RE GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE GONNA BE OKAY,
THAT'S IT.
JIMMY:
MARCO!
POLICE WOMAN:
HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY.
JIMMY:
MARCO... I'M A FRIEND.
POLICE WOMAN:
DON'T WORRY,
YOUR FRIEND'S GOING TO BE
JUST FINE, ALL RIGHT?
WE'LL GET THE CREEPS
THAT DID THIS TO HIM.
IT'S OKAY.
IT'S OKAY, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE GONNA BE...
JIMMY. (CRYING)
OKAY, YOU'RE GONNA
BE JUST FINE.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'M HERE, AND I'M NOT
GOING ANYWHERE, OKAY?
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
(CRYING)
YOU'RE GONNA BE OKAY.
BIG NEWS, DEGRASSI.
MR. SIMPSON'S SPUR OF
THE MOMENT FUNDRAISER?
A HUGE SUCCESS.
SO AFTER SCHOOL IN THE FOYER,
THERE'S GONNA BE SOME
HEAD-SHAVING GOING ON.
NICE TO KNOW SOMEONE
IN YOUR FAMILY
HAS A SENSE
OF HUMOUR, EMMA.
SO YOU'RE WALKING THROUGH
THE GAY VILLAGE,
ALONE AT NIGHT,
AND YOU GET SWARMED
FOR YOUR SHOES?
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
LOOK, YOU DON'T
BELIEVE ME, EL?
WHATEVER.
I DON'T.
YOU SHOULD TALK
TO THE POLICE.
I DID. LAST NIGHT.
AND YOUR PARENTS?
WHAT DON'T YOU GET, EL?
WITH SPIN AND
AFTER LAST NIGHT?
I'M NOT TELLING ANYBODY
ANYTHING, EVER AGAIN.
SO WHAT? YOU'RE JUST
GOING TO PRETEND?
NO. I'M JUST-
I'M JUST NOT GONNA
BE ANYTHING, OKAY?
GAY OR STRAIGHT.
AND SO WHAT ABOUT DYLAN?
ELLIE...
JUST DROP IT, PLEASE.
IT'S OVER.
WOW! THEY REALLY
DID A NUMBER ON YOU.
YEAH.
MARCO...
LOOK, I'M FINE, OKAY?
SO JUST LEAVE ME ALONE.
STUDENT:
SHAVE THAT SNAKE!
MR. SIMPSON,
THANKS SO MUCH FOR DOING THIS.
THE SQUAD OWES YOU.
YEAH, A TOUPEE.
SO? WHO'S THE LUCKY
HAIRDRESSER?
STUDENTS:
(LAUGH AND CHEER)
I SPENT TEN YEARS
FILLETING COD
OUT ON THE GRAND BANKS,
PRINCESS.
HANDS STEADY AS A SURGEON.
OKAY...
SIT BACK, RELAX.
♪♪♪
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
WHOA!
THANK YOU,
THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
REMEMBER GUYS UH...
BALD IS BEAUTIFUL.
THANKS FOR COMING OUT
AND SUPPORTING
THE JUNIOR SPIRIT SQUAD
FUNDRAISER!
(APPLAUSE)
EVEN YOU GOTTA ADMIT
THAT WAS COOL.
OKAY, WHAT NOW, EM?
HOW HAVE I OFFENDED
YOU THIS TIME?
EMMA? WHAT IS IT?
NOTHING.
MANNY:
THEN WHY DO YOU LOOK
LIKE YOU'RE GONNA CRY?
HOME'S NOT TOO GOOD
RIGHT NOW, OKAY?
MANNY:
IS IT THE BABY?
ARE YOUR,
ARE YOUR PARENTS FIGHTING?
SNAKE IS SICK
AND IT MIGHT BE BAD.
BUT THEY'RE JUST
DOING TESTS,
THERE MIGHT BE NOTHING
WRONG AT ALL, RIGHT?
YEAH, HE'S GONNA BE FINE, EM.
I KNOW IT.
DIDN'T TOUCH THE RIM,
SO SIXTEEN TO FOUR
EXTRA POINT POUR MOI.
DUDE, I KNOW BASKETBALL'S
NOT YOUR GAME
BUT COME ON, AT LEAST TRY.
OH! WHAT'S THAT?
SIXTEEN TO FIVE?
NO. NO IT'S NOT BECAUSE THIS
IS TWENTY-ONE WE'RE PLAYING.
YOU SHOOT AND YOU SCORE.
THERE ARE NO LAY-UPS.
OH WELL, WE MUST FOLLOW ALL
THE RULES TO THE LETTER
OR MR. TEACHER WILL GET MAD.
DUDE, YOU'RE WORSE THAN MARCO.
WHAT'S BUGGING YOU NOW?
SPINNER:
WHAT'S BOTH-
THE GUY GETS A BLACK EYE,
AND IT'S THE END OF THE WORLD.
OH, OH, MY PRETTY LITTLE FACE.
(MOCK CRYING)
HEY!
LOOK, YOU WEREN'T THERE LAST
NIGHT WHEN I FOUND HIM, OKAY?
OKAY, CALM DOWN, HERO.
JUST RELAX.
YOU'RE SUCH A LOSER.
SPINNER:
WHY? 'CAUSE I'M NOT
ALL BROKEN UP
OVER MARCO AND HIS
STOLEN DANCING SHOES?
LOOK IF HE WOULD HAVE WALKED
TO THE GAME WITH US,
NONE OF THAT WOULDA HAPPENED.
LAST NIGHT WAS HIS FAULT,
NOT MINE!
SO WAS IT THE HOSPITAL?
AND...?
BETTER GET USED
TO THE NEW LOOK.
MY FIRST ROUND OF CHEMO'S
IN A COUPLE OF DAYS.
IT LOOKS PRETTY SEXY, I THINK.
YOU KNOW,
GET ME SOME FANCY DUDS,
BUY ME A NEW SPORTS CAR,
I'LL BE STYLIN'.
EM, DON'T CRY.
DON'T CRY.
THERE'S NOTHING
TO CRY ABOUT.
SNAKE, YOU HAVE CANCER!
YOU'RE SICK AND YOU'RE
ALWAYS JUST SO CALM,
OR JOKING OR SHAVING YOUR HEAD
LIKE NOTHING'S WRONG.
BECAUSE I HAVE TO BE LIKE THIS,
EMMA, IF I'M GONNA BEAT IT.
AND ARE YOU?
YES.
I PROMISE YOU,
AND JACK,
AND YOUR MOM.
YES.
JAY:
HEY MARCO.
I ALWAYS KNEW YOU AND DYLAN
WERE MEANT FOR EACH OTHER.
WHAT?
(LAUGHS)
NO, HUH?
YOU DIDN'T TELL ANYBODY
MY SECRET, DID YOU SPIN?
I DON'T NEED THIS.
MAN, ALL I DID
WAS TELL YOU THE TRUTH.
SPINNER:
I NEVER ASKED YOU TO.
AND JUST LIKE I
DIDN'T ASK TO BE GAY.
OR YOU DIDN'T ASK
TO LIKE PAIGE,
OR CRAIG DIDN'T ASK
TO LIKE ASH!
IT'S NOT THE SAME.
NO, YOU GET IT EASY.
THEN STOP BEING GAY!
OH RIGHT, SPIN.
I'M JUST GOING TO GO DO THAT.
WELL, WHY NOT?
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU'VE
ACTUALLY DONE ANYTHING YET.
NOT THAT I NEED TO KNOW.
SPIN.
SPINNER:
AND NOBODY ELSE
NEEDS TO KNOW EITHER.
I MEAN, YOU CAN TRY
DATING HAZEL, FOR REAL.
WHY NOT?
EVEN STRANGERS KNOW, SPIN.
AND LAST NIGHT WASN'T
ABOUT MY SHOES.
THOSE GUYS... THEY KNEW.
AND THEY BASHED ME,
BECAUSE THEY HATE IT.
JUST LIKE YOU DO.
DUDE, THAT'S BRUTAL,
BUT YOU CAN'T COMPARE
ME TO THOSE GUYS.
REALLY?
WHY NOT?