(SNEEZE)
HATZILAKOS:
WELL DONE, MANNY.
OKAY KENDRA,
YOU'RE UP NEXT!
MANNY GET YOUR PHOTO
DONE PLEASE.
KENDRA:
MS. H?
I DON'T FEEL SO GOOD.
OH NO,
NOT YOU TOO, KENDRA!
ALL RIGHT, NO MORE BREATHING.
OKAY, GIRLS?
THERE ARE GERMS EVERYWHERE,
AND I'M NOT ABOUT TO LOSE
ANOTHER ONE OF YOU
TO THE STOMACH FLU GOING AROUND.
MANNY, COME ON.
CRAIG:
IT'S FOR THE YEARBOOK.
DON'T YOU WANT TO SMILE?
MANNY:
LOOKING AT YOU DOESN'T REALLY
MAKE ME FEEL LIKE SMILING.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Hear what I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
ANNOUNCEMENT:
COULD A CUSTODIAL STAFF MEMBER
PLEASE REPORT
TO THE SECOND FLOOR BOYS
WASHROOM IMMEDIATELY.
ASHLEY:
HEY ELLIE, DO YOU SMELL
SOMETHING?
ELLIE:
I THINK IT'S THE PECULIAR
STENCH OF A BOYFRIEND THIEF.
MANNY:
YOU KNOW, I DON'T WANT CRAIG.
HE'S-
PAIGE:
IT'S TOUGH BEING YOU
RIGHT NOW, HUH?
IF IT MAKES YOU FEEL
ANY BETTER
EVERYONE'S TALKING ABOUT
HOW YOU KICK SERIOUS
GYMNAST BUTT.
HONESTLY?
PAIGE:
WELL, ONLY WHEN THEY'RE
NOT DISCUSSING
YOUR INFINITELY MORE
FASCINATING PRIVATE LIFE.
GREAT.
DON'T WORRY HON,
IT'LL BLOW OVER.
BUT, IN THE MEANWHILE,
WHY DON'T YOU CONSIDER
RUNNING DAMAGE CONTROL.
AND SWEETIE, YOU'RE
LOOKING A LITTLE PALE.
IT'S NOT GOOD.
OH, YO, JT,
ARE YOU STILL INTERESTED
IN THE TRIP NEXT WEEKEND?
UH YEAH,
THE BUFFALO TRIP?
YEAH. ALL THE GUYS.
HOT WINGS.
THE CONCERT OF THE YEAR.
TOBY:
HEY, JIMMER!
WHAT'S REALLY GOOD?
JIMMY:
NOTHING. DON'T CALL ME THAT.
YOU IN OR WHAT, T?
JT:
YEAH. SO IN, IT HURTS.
MAN, I DON'T GET IT.
JIMMY USED TO BE
MY FRIEND.
YEAH, BUT THAT WAS BEFORE
YOUR HOT STEPSIZZLE
DUMPED HIS AZZLE.
LOOK,
I KNOW YOU HATE ME...
MANNY...
JUST A SEC.
I'M REALLY SORRY, OKAY?
SORRY DOESN'T MAKE UP
FOR ALL THE PAIN YOU CAUSED.
I KNOW.
BUT HE TOLD ME
I WAS THE ONE,
I BELIEVED HIM.
AND THAT'S THE ONLY REASON
I LET IT GO ON.
CRAIG LIED TO ME TOO.
AND I'D ERASE IT ALL
IF I COULD.
(BELL RINGS)
YOU'RE GOING TO BE
LATE.
KWAN READING:
"THE CHIPS OF CHEWED BOATS
AND THE SINKING LIMBS
OF TORN COMRADES.
THEY SWAM OUT
OF THE WHITE CURDS
OF THE WHALE'S DIREFUL WRATH,
AND INTO THE SERINE
EXASPERATING SUNLIGHT THAT-"
YES.
MAY I BE EXCUSED?
KWAN:
LET ME GUESS,
YOU'RE SICK TOO?
MANNY, CHOOSING TO COME
TO SCHOOL ILL IS DESPERATELY...
PLEASE!
JIMMY:
I'VE BEEN STUDYING
LIKE A MANIAC.
MARCO'S TUTORING ME,
AND EVEN SPINNER'S PASSING,
BUT ALGEBRA'S STILL
KICKING MY BUTT.
MID-TERMS
COME OUT FRIDAY.
YEAH, I KNOW.
MY DAD GOING TO FREAK
WHEN HE SEES MY GRADE.
PROBABLY GONNA CANCEL
THE CONCERT TRIP.
TOBY
YO DAWG,
WHAT'S UP?
YOU GOT ANY MORE TIX
FOR THAT CONCERT?
I LOVE DJ CRAZY GUNS.
JIMMY:
YOU MEAN,
DJ MADD BULLETZ?
NO.
CAR SPACE'S TOO TIGHT.
PLUS YOU DON'T EVEN LIKE RAP.
TOBY:
WHAT IF A CERTAIN HOMEY
KNEW OF A HOLE
IN THE SCHOOL'S FIREWALL -
THE FIREWALL THAT PROTECTS
THE COMPUTER SYSTEM
WITH YOUR GRADES IN IT?
JIMMY:
THEN I'D BUY HIM A MADD BULLETZ
CONCERT TICKET,
AND GIVE HIM THE SHOTGUN SEAT.
PEACE.
OKAY.
EMMA:
HEY MANNY, WHAT'S WITH
THE MAD DASH OUT OF ENGLISH?
NOTHING.
YOU KNOW IF YOU'RE SICK,
YOU CAN'T COMPETE.
OKAY.
WHO DIED AND
MADE YOU MY MOTHER?
COACH, SHOULD KNOW.
EMMA! WAIT.
MY LIFE SUCKS OKAY.
THIS MEET MEANS
EVERYTHING TO ME.
I'M JUST NERVOUS.
I'M JUST REALLY
NERVOUS, OKAY?
(APPLAUSE)
HATZILAKOS:
ALL RIGHT, GIRLS.
OKAY, THIS OUR LAST PRACTICE,
AND I WANNA SEE WHAT YOUR GONNA
BRING TO THE MEET TOMORROW.
I WANT YOU TO FOCUS,
GIVE TWO HUNDRED PERCENT,
AND OF COURSE HAVE SOME FUN.
SO WHO THINKS MANNY SHOULD
SHOW US HOW IT'S DONE?
COME ON, MANNY! LET'S DO IT.
(APPLAUSE)
MANNY, I'VE GOT TO SAY,
THAT WAS INCREDIBLE.
I TOLD YOU I WAS FINE.
SO FINE, THAT YOU'RE
GOING TO WIN US
THE GOLD MEDAL
IN BEAM TOMORROW?
HEY, I HEARD
ABOUT MR. SIMPSON
BEING IN THE HOSPITAL.
SORRY.
HE'S DOING FINE,
ACTUALLY.
SOME MORE INTENSE CHEMO
MIGHT BE GOOD.
IT'S AMAZING
THAT YOU'RE HERE
JUST GETTING ON WITH IT.
YOU KNOW ME.
I'M ALWAYS DOING SOMETHING.
HAZEL:
FIFTY BUCKS TO ANYONE
WHO CAN GIVE ME A TAMPON
RIGHT NOW.
WHAT HAPPENED?
HAZEL:
I CAN'T BELIEVE NO ONE NOTICED.
I JUST DID A FRONT WALKOVER
THAT BELONGS IN A HORROR MOVIE.
FORGOT TO STOCK UP.
OH, HERE.
I HAVEN'T USED MINE
IN FOREVER.
REALLY?
WELL, YEAH.
I'VE BEEN TRAINING REALLY HARD.
HAZEL:
HELLO? TRIAGE, URGENT!
SORRY.
EMMA:
MANNY, I KNOW THIS IS TOTALLY
NONE OF MY BUSINESS,
BUT YOU WERE SICK EARLIER
AND...
ARE YOU SURE IT'S NOT,
SOMETHING ELSE?
MANNY:
YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT IS NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
THREE, FOUR, FIVE, FOUR, FIVE,
SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT.
NINE...
SPINNER:
OH! OH! COME ON! CRAIG!
(GRUNT)
(KNOCKING) PAIGE?
PAIGE:
OH, SURE, HON.
THERE YOU GO.
YOU KNOW IF THEY HAD FEMALE
CUSTODIANS, I BET...
MANNY:
PAIGE.
PAIGE:
OKAY, YOU'RE WELCOME ALREADY.
MANNY:
HOW DO I KNOW IF A GUY...
IF HE USED A CONDOM?
PAIGE:
WHAT?
WELL, WERE YOU THERE, HON?
I MEAN, IT'S JUST
A TINY BIT OBVIOUS.
OH NO.
YOU'RE SERIOUS?
WELL, DID YOU, LIKE,
HEAR HIM OPEN IT?
OR EVEN FEEL IT MAYBE?
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T THINK SO.
WELL. OKAY. IT'S OKAY.
IF YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT WHO
I THINK YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT?
THEN I'M SURE YOU'RE FINE.
HE'S SEEMS LIKE THE
SEMI-RESPONSIBLE TYPE.
PROMISE YOU WON'T TELL
ANYONE OKAY?
OF COURSE NOT.
BUT TO BE SURE,
YOU SHOULD REALLY
JUST ASK HIM.
AND HON REMEMBER,
NEXT TIME ASK QUESTIONS FIRST,
GET NAKED LATER.
RADITCH:
A REMINDER THAT THE GYMNASTICS
MEET WILL BE STARTING
IMMEDIATELY AFTER LUNCH.
ALL STUDENTS WHO PURCHASED
TICKETS
SHOULD REPORT TO THE GYM
INSTEAD OF CLASS.
TOBY:
THERE'S THIS UNUSED
LIBRARIAN PORT BACK THERE
INTO THE ADMIN.
JUST SQUEEZE IN
AND JUICE ME UP.
YOU DO REALIZE
THIS IS SUICIDE?
TOBY:
WELL, IT'S SAFER THAN
LOGGING IN
FROM A TEACHER'S COMPUTER.
I'LL WHISTLE IF SHE'S
GETTING CLOSE.
I'M NOT DOING THIS, OKAY?
I'LL JUST TELL JIMMY
TO BRING YOU WITH US.
TOBY:
THAT'S NOT THE POINT, JT.
HE'S BRINGING YOU,
BECAUSE HE LIKES YOU.
JT:
FINE. OKAY.
JUST GIVE ME THE THING.
OKAY, THE THING
IS IN THE THING.
TOBY:
OKAY, I'M IN THE ACCOUNT.
I'M ON.
KWAN:
JOANNE, DO YOU NEED SOME HELP?
HURRY UP!
TOBY:
IT'S AN OLD LAPTOP,
IT'S STICKY.
KWAN:
BOYS?
WHAT? WHAT?!
WHAT'S HAPPENING HERE?
I TRUST THE SHENANIGAN ANTICS
ARE RELATED TO YOUR MOBY DICK
PROJECT.
JT:
UH... YEAH!
AND MAY I SAY, WE'RE HAVING
A WHALE OF A GOOD TIME.
WELL, MAYBE YOU SAILORS SHOULD
TAKE THOSE TWO NICE SPOTS
OVER AT THE CENTRE TABLE.
NOW.
YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
YOU'RE THE IDIOT.
(APPLAUSE)
HATZILAKOS:
SO HOW IS OUR STAR DOING?
I'M GOOD.
I'M TOTALLY FINE. GOOD.
YOUR SURE?
YOU SEEM A BIT SHAKEN.
OH, NO, NO.
'CAUSE NOTHING IS WRONG.
OKAY, WELL DON'T WORRY.
YOU GONNA MAKE US ALL PROUD.
INCLUDING YOUR MOM.
ANNOUNCER:
REPRESENTING DEGRASSI
ON THE BALANCE BEAM,
MANUELA SANTOS.
(CHEERING)
GO FOR IT!
(BABY CRIES IN THE STANDS)
HATZILAKOS:
MANNY!
ARE YOU OKAY?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
COME ON.
DID YOU HURT YOURSELF?
NO.
OKAY, THEN GET BACK UP.
YOU CAN DO THIS.
ARMSTRONG:
FORFEITURE BY DEGRASSI.
WHAT?
WAIT A MINUTE,
YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
CRAIG
HEY, YOU OKAY?
MANNY:
NO.
CRAIG:
IT'S NOT THAT HORRIBLE.
WHEN WE...
DID YOU USE A CONDOM?
WHAT?
I'M SORRY,
I JUST...
UM MANNY...
YOU SAID IT WAS OKAY.
AND I THOUGHT THAT MEANT,
YOU KNOW,
YOU WERE ON THE PILL.
IT WAS MY FIRST TIME.
I MEANT THAT IT WAS OKAY.
MANNY. MANNY,
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
NO. IT'S NOT.
IT CAN'T BE.
WELL, WHICH IS IT?
NOTHING'S WRONG
OR NOTHING CAN BE WRONG.
BECAUSE YOUR NOT
MAKING ANY SENSE.
MANNY:
NOTHING'S,
NOTHING'S WRONG, OKAY?
OKAY.
WELL, UH, SEE YOU.
JIMMY:
TOBES!
WE HAVE SUCCESS?
A LITTLE TOO MUCH
SUCCESS.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
I GAVE YOU
A QUADRUPLE EIGHT.
AS IN 8888...
PERCENT.
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
IT'S LIKE THE BIGGEST
TYPO EVER.
AND YOU'RE
GONNA FIX IT.
TOBY:
IT'S NOT THAT EASY.
MY LAPTOP IS FRIED,
I CAN'T GET IN FROM OUTSIDE-
JIMMY:
FROM INSIDE THEN.
BEFORE I GET CAUGHT.
TOBY:
I CAN'T JUST LIKE-
SOMEONE COULD WALK-
NOW TOBY!
COME ON, COME ON.
RADITCH:
MR. ISAACS, JUST THE FELLOW
I'M LOOKING FOR.
I'M HAVING SOME TROUBLE
WITH MY USER ACCOUNT.
WITH MR. SIMPSON AWAY,
I WAS-
WELL HERE,
LET ME SHOW YOU.
UH SIR, DON'T YOU THINK
WE WOULD BE
MORE COMFORTABLE
IN YOUR OFFICE?
NO.
THIS UH... CURIOUS.
CAN YOU EXPLAIN TO ME
WHY I'M LOGGED ON HERE ALREADY?
OH, WELL...
YOU SEE, UM...
♪♪♪
SPIKE:
WHEN DID YOU GET TO BE
SO HEAVY, HUH?
MANNY:
SPIKE!
SPIKE, I THINK I'M PREGNANT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I HAVE
TO GO THROUGH THIS.
I'M SO STUPID.
NO YOU'RE NOT.
EVERYONE MAKES MISTAKES.
JUST TRY TO LEARN
FROM THIS ONE.
HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT
WHAT YOU MIGHT DO...
IF...?
I CAN'T.
IT'S JUST WAY TOO MUCH.
SPIKE:
I COULD ALWAYS GO WITH YOU
TO TALK TO YOUR PARENTS?
NO. I COULDN'T TELL THEM.
MY MOM SURPRISED ME.
SHE WAS INCREDIBLY SUPPORTIVE.
MINE WOULD KILL ME.
OR SEND ME TO LIVE
AT SOME CONVENT
BACK IN THE PHILIPPINES.
HONEY, THEY WOULDN'T.
REALLY? BECAUSE THAT'S
WHAT THEY DID TO MY COUSIN.
(CLOCK RINGS)
READY?
NOT EVEN A LITTLE BIT.
GIRL:
THANKS FOR THE RIDE, MOM.
(BELL RINGS)
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
JIMMY:
MR. RADITCH,
YOU WANTED TO SEE ME?
MR. BROOKS,
PLEASE JOIN US.
MR. ISAAC'S HERE,
WAS JUST TELLING ME
A VERY INTERESTING STORY
ABOUT YOUR MATHEMATICS GRADE.
SIR,
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
MR: RADITCH:
YOU'RE BOTH GOOD KIDS.
AT LEAST, I THOUGHT SO.
COMPUTER CRIME
IS A SERIOUS OFFENCE.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO CALL
YOUR PARENTS.
AND INVITE YOU TO MY SPECIAL
SATURDAY DETENTION.
KWAN:
MR. RADITCH,
MAY I HAVE A MOMENT?
STAY.
JIMMY,
I FREAKED OUT.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT
ELSE TO TELL HIM.
DO YOU KNOW
WHAT SATURDAY IS?
DJ BAD BULLETZ?
YOU'RE SUCH A FAKE,
MAN.
YOU'RE A FAKE
COMPUTER HACKER.
YOU'RE A FAKE RAP FAN,
YOU'RE JUST 100 PERCENT
FAKE.
CRAIG:
I GOT YOUR MESSAGE.
SORRY, I'M LATE.
LOOK, I CAN'T STAY LONG,
I HAVE THIS BIO LAB...
SOMETHING BAD HAPPENED.
CRAIG:
WHAT?
WHAT'S WRONG?
MANNY:
I HAVE A DOCTOR'S
APPOINTMENT TO MAKE SURE,
BUT I TOOK THIS TEST AND...
I'M PRETTY SURE I'M PREGNANT.
LOOK, I KNOW YOU'RE MAD
AND I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY.
IT'S OKAY.
I STARTED THINKING
ABOUT IT.
YOU KNOW AFTER YOU ASKED ME
THAT QUESTION YESTERDAY.
AND WHAT IF WE HAD IT?
WE COULD BE
A LITTLE FAMILY.
ALL OUR OWN.
MANNY?