RADITCH:
GOOD MORNING, STUDENTS.
GLAD YOU COULD ALL MAKE IT
ON A BEAUTIFUL SATURDAY.
BUT THEN, IT'S NOT LIKE
YOU HAD MUCH CHOICE.
WELCOME TO DETENTION.
NO TALKING.
NO CHEWING GUM.
NO GETTING UP.
NO FEET ON THE TABLE.
NO DOING YOUR NAILS.
NO EATING, UNTIL I SAY.
THERE IS ONE BATHROOM PASS
WHICH YOU MUST CARRY WITH YOU.
YOU GET ONE HALF HOUR
FOR LUNCH.
THE REST OF THE TIME
IS SPENT DOING HOMEWORK.
THIS IS A TIME TO REFLECT
ON PAST BEHAVIOR.
I AM ALL EYES, ALL EARS.
(BURPS)
RADITCH:
I HEARD THAT, MR. CAMERON.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Hear what I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
JIMMY:
CAN YOU STOP BEING AN IDIOT?
SEAN:
I MISSED THE PART
WHEN YOU BECAME RADITCH.
ELLIE:
RIGHT ON MY BAG.
THANKS.
SEAN:
IS ANYTHING BROKEN?
HAZEL:
OKAY, A LITTLE TO THE LEFT.
NO, THE OTHER LEFT.
SEAN:
DO YOU WANNA DO THIS, PRINCESS?
JIMMY:
SHE'S TRYING TO HELP.
OKAY, LAY OFF.
TOBY:
UH, I DON'T REALLY LIKE
HEIGHTS.
JUST SHUT UP AND DO IT.
TOBY:
WHOA...
SEAN:
WATCH IT.
TOBY:
WHOA...
ALL:
AGH! OW.
HAZEL:
ARE YOU OKAY?
JIMMY:
AT LEAST IT'S FIXED, RIGHT?
RADITCH:
(CLEARS THROAT)
YOU, THERE.
YOU, OVER THERE.
FAR CORNER,
LADIES IN THE MIDDLE.
SOMEONE TELL ME
THAT CLOCK IS WRONG.
UH, SOME OF US HAVE SOCIAL
ENGAGEMENTS?
LIKE WHAT?
DOES PAIGE NEED YOU TO LICK HER
BOOTS BEFORE SHE GOES OUT?
BACK IT UP, SEAN.
SEAN:
STILL, A GUY'S GOTTA WONDER
WHY YOUR GIRLFRIEND,
MISS CONFORMITY,
ENDED UP IN DETENTION.
ME?
I'M PLEASED TO ANNOUNCE THAT
I'M HERE FOR EIGHT SOLID WEEKS -
FOR ANTI-SOCIAL BEHAVIOR.
HAZEL:
SURPRISE, SURPRISE.
AND I'M NOT HIS GIRLFRIEND.
I SKIPPED CLASS.
WHAT?
I DIDN'T FEEL LIKE GOING.
JIMMY:
WOW, THAT'S A GREAT STORY,
ELLIE.
SEAN:
IS YOURS ANY BETTER?
JIMMY:
I SHOULD BE AT THE CONCERT
OF THE YEAR TODAY. BUT-
I HACKED THE SCHOOL COMPUTER
TO CHANGE HIS GRADES.
WE GOT BUSTED.
NO, YOU GOT BUSTED
AND YOU RATTED ME OUT.
ANYWAYS, BACK TO HAZEL.
WHY DO YOU THINK I'M HERE?
YOUR SHOES DIDN'T
MATCH YOUR PURSE?
HAZEL:
YEAH, THAT'S IT.
I'M OUTTA HERE.
♪♪♪
(GIGGLE)
IT'S A SWISS BALL,
FROM SWITZERLAND.
OKAY.
RADITCH:
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
HAZEL:
SEE YOU, SIR. (LAUGHS)
JIMMY:
DO THE RADITCH IMPRESSION
AGAIN.
SEAN:
IT'S A SWISS BALL. (LAUGHS)
HAZEL:
I'M BORED OF DOING IT.
I'M BORED OF THIS ROOM.
I'M BORED OF EVERYTHING.
FINE.
TRUTH OR DARE.
TRUTH.
HAZEL,
TRUTH OR DARE?
TRUTH.
SO WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN DETENTION?
OUT WITH IT,
ADEN.
ELLIE:
IT'S EITHER THAT
OR TAKE A DARE.
SO WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN DETENTION?
I'VE CHANGED MY MIND.
GIVE ME A DARE.
FINE. I DARE YOU
TO KISS TOBY.
TOBY:
JIMMY!
HAZEL:
SEAN:
YES! ON THE LIPS.
LIKE YOU MEAN IT.
♪♪♪
WHOA!
OH! (LAUGH)
SATISFIED?
YEAH.
WELCOME BACK, SIMPSON.
TOBY:
HE SCORES!
SCORES AGAIN THAT IS.
WAIT'LL I TELL JT.
HE'S GOING TO BE SO JEALOUS.
HAZEL:
NO. BECAUSE YOU'RE
NOT TELLING HIM.
SEAN:
WHY NOT?
IT WAS JUST
SOME STUPID DARE.
BECAUSE SHE'S TOO EMBARRASSED
TO HAVE ANYONE KNOW
THAT SHE MACKED
A TOTAL GEEK.
EVEN AS A JOKE.
SEAN:
THAT'S GREAT, HAZEL.
VERY EVOLVED.
HAZEL:
HEY, I DON'T MAKE THE RULES.
SEAN:
NO, YOU JUST FOLLOW THEM.
YOU KNOW, YOU DON'T EVEN
HAVE THE BALLS TO TELL US
WHY YOU'RE HERE.
LEAVE HER ALONE.
SHUT UP, JIMMY.
WHY ARE YOU HERE? HMM?
PAIGE PULL YOUR PUPPET STRINGS,
MAKE YOU DANCE?
PAIGE CAN'T MAKE ME
DO ANYTHING.
SEAN:
WHATEVER.
WHY-
CAUSE I GOT CAUGHT SURFING
PORN, OKAY?
ALL:
(LAUGHING)
HAZEL:
I GOT SOME SPAM IN MY E-MAIL
AND I WAS CURIOUS.
OH.
(CHEERS)
(GIGGLES)
SIMPSON:
WHAT'S GOING ON IN HERE?
JIMMY:
IT'S RADITCH'S BAD KIDS
DETENTION ROUND-UP.
OH.
ARE YOU HERE, MR. SIMPSON,
BECAUSE YOU'RE COMING BACK?
YOU'RE OKAY?
FOR THE MOMENT.
CHEMO'S DONE.
I'M STARTING TO GET
A BIT ANTSY.
AND I MISSED ALL YOU
BAD KIDS.
TOBY:
SO, ARE WE PLAYING?
I'M BORED.
YOU GUYS CAN GO AHEAD.
TOBY:
OKAY, LET'S GO.
HAZEL:
OKAY, I'M IN.
ELLIE:
WANT SOME?
SEAN:
THANKS.
TOBY:
YOU'RE GONNA GET KILLED
BY HAZEL. WOW.
HAZEL:
MY SHOE... (LAUGHS)
WHAT'S WITH
THE ELASTIC BANDS?
YOU DON'T WANT
TO TELL ME.
THAT'S FINE.
I JUST THOUGHT YOU
WEREN'T HIDING IT.
IT'S A THERAPY TECHNIQUE.
TO STOP ME FROM...
YOU KNOW.
I GUESS EVERYONE
KNOWS ABOUT ME?
THEY KNOW ABOUT
THE RUMOURS.
ELLIE:
I'M SURE THE RUMOURS
ARE MORE INTERESTING.
SEAN:
I DOUBT IT.
SO WHY DO YOU CUT?
ELLIE:
WHAT, YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO SCARE IT OUT OF ME
LIKE YOU DID WITH HAZEL?
NO.
ELLIE:
I THINK...
IT WAS THE ONLY PAIN
I COULD CONTROL.
THAT MAKES SENSE.
YOU'RE THE FIRST PERSON
WHO'S EVER SAID THAT.
PEOPLE TALK ABOUT YOU, TOO.
WHY?
CAUSE STUFF GETS STOLEN?
ELLIE:
YEAH.
BUT IT'S ALL TALK THOUGH,
RIGHT?
YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
I DO...
BECAUSE I'M STEALING IT.
JIMMY:
INCOMING!
HAZEL:
TAKE THAT, TOBY!
RADITCH:
(CLEARS THROAT)
SORRY TO CRASH THE PARTY.
ELLIE ON TAPE:
BUT IT'S ALL TALK THOUGH,
RIGHT?
YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
SEAN ON TAPE:
I DO...BECAUSE I'M STEALING IT.
(REWINDS)
♪ (SINGS) DO DO-DO DO-DO... ♪
I CAN'T SIT IN A ROOM BY MYSELF
FOR THE NEXT THREE HOURS.
RADITCH SAYS WE STAY SEPARATE.
AND I SAY SCREW IT.
LET'S GO.
YOU'RE PRETTY COOL,
MISS NASH.
TOBY:
WE'RE GONNA GET CAUGHT.
HAZEL:
LIVE A LITTLE, TOBY.
JIMMY:
DO WE REALLY NEED SEAN?
ELLIE:
NO ONE GETS LEFT BEHIND,
RIGHT?
HAZEL:
WE'RE TAKING A WALK.
JIMMY:
COME ON, CAMERON.
YOU CHICKEN?
I'M NOT A JOINER.
I DON'T DO GROUP ACTIVITIES.
JIMMY:
OKAY.
TELL JAY THAT NEXT TIME YOU
TWO DECIDE TO STEAL SOMETHING.
HAZEL:
WHAT IF ELLIE WANTS YOU
TO COME?
ELLIE:
HAZEL!
♪♪♪
ELLIE:
I DIDN'T KNOW WE
HAD AN ELEVATOR.
JIMMY:
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
WE HAD A BASEMENT.
SEAN:
CHEE-CHEE-CHEE CUH-CUH-CUH.
TOBY:
YOU'RE FREAKING ME OUT, SEAN.
COOL.
ELLIE AND HAZEL:
CHEE-CHEE-CHEE CUH-CUH-CUH.
TOBY:
STOP IT.
HAZEL:
WE NEED A KEY.
JIMMY:
WAIT A SEC.
I-I THINK IT'S A SIGN.
I THINK WE SHOULD GO BACK.
NO WAY.
HAZEL:
OKAY, THAT ELEVATOR
IS POSSESSED.
SEAN:
SICK!
TOBY:
GUYS? I DON'T THINK THIS
IS SUCH A GOOD IDEA.
STOP WHINING AND CLIMB.
WHOA!
WE'RE ON THE ROOF.
HEY GUYS?
I HAVE ACROPHOBIA,
REMEMBER?
F-FEAR OF HEIGHTS?
GUYS, I'M SCARED.
WH-WHERE YOU GOING?
HAZEL:
I WONDER IF WE'RE THE ONLY
KIDS TO EVER COME UP HERE.
JIMMY:
I DON'T THINK SO.
HAZEL:
WOW! IT'S PRETTY!
WELL, YOU FOUND IT,
SO YOU SHOULD KEEP IT.
JIMMY:
NO. YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK IT WOULD LOOK
A LOT BETTER ON YOU.
THANKS.
AND THANKS FOR STANDING UP
TO SEAN THIS MORNING, TOO.
WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
FOR MAKING YOU
KISS TOBY, I GUESS.
I KISSED TOBY!
OH MY GOSH.
ELLIE:
I DIDN'T EXPECT SO MUCH...
SPACE.
YOU CARRY THAT BAG WITH YOU
EVERYWHERE, HUH?
IT'S A PSYCHO
GIRL THING.
EMPHASIS ON PSYCHO.
I THINK YOU'RE CUTE.
GUESS I GOT TO YOU?
DREAM ON.
YOU DON'T SEEM
SCARED OF ME.
NO.
YOU DON'T SEEM
FREAKED BY ME.
NOPE.
ARE YOU FREAKED NOW?
RADITCH:
SO YOU'RE BACK
NEXT WEEK?
SIMPSON:
AND GLAD OF IT.
RADITCH:
LOTS OF BEHAVIOURAL PROBLEMS
AROUND HERE LATELY.
BIG CRACKDOWN GOING ON.
I'LL FILL YOU IN
ON MONDAY.
SIMPSON:
ARE SATURDAY DETENTIONS
PART OF THIS CRACKDOWN?
RADITCH:
YESIREE. ZERO TOLERANCE.
SIMPSON:
SO NOW WE'RE THE POLICE.
RADITCH:
SURELY YOU BELIEVE WE GOTTA
CONTROL THESE KIDS.
SIMPSON:
EDUCATE THEM, YES.
DISCIPLINE THEM?
SURE.
BUT CONTROL?
RADITCH:
ARCHIE-
OH, COME ON.
WHAT'S THE WORST THAT ANY
OF THEM HAVE EVER DONE?
YOU'VE GOT JIMMY
AND HAZEL AND TOBY?
AND SEAN.
THIS IS THE FIRST SATURDAY
IN MONTHS
I HAVEN'T FELT LIKE DYING,
DAN.
AND LIFE?
IT'S WAY TOO SHORT.
TOBY:
GUYS! GUYS, HE'S COMING!
JIMMY!
YOU LOCKED IT?
SEAN:
I-I DON'T KNOW!
JIMMY, COME ON!
SEAN:
HE'S COMING, HE'S COMING.
JUST GO. JUST GO.
THANKS.
JUST TELL ME
WHO TOOK THE KEYS.
OKAY, FINE.
YOU ALL HAVE SATURDAY DETENTION
FOR THE NEXT THREE WEEKS.
I'M TRYING TO DO
THE RIGHT THING HERE.
HELP ME OUT.
MR. RADITCH-
TOBY:
I DID IT.
I TOOK THE KEYS.
TOBY, I'M DISAPPOINTED,
BUT I APPRECIATE
THE HONESTY.
GO HOME - ALL OF YOU.
ENJOY YOUR WEEKEND.
DETENTION IS OVER.
HE DIDN'T EVEN
FREAK ON YOU.
JIMMY:
TOBY, THAT WAS COOL.
I DIDN'T EXPECT IT.
HAZEL:
AWWW! YOU GUYS - GROUP HUG!
WAIT.
I'VE GOT AN INSTANT CAMERA IN
HERE SOMEWHERE FOR POSTERITY.
SEAN ON TAPE:
GUESS I GOT TO YOU.
ELLIE ON TAPE:
DREAM ON.
SEAN ON TAPE:
YOU DON'T SEEM SCARED OF ME.
ELLIE ON TAPE:
NO. YOU DON'T SEEM
FREAKED BY ME.
SEAN ON TAPE:
NOPE.
ELLIE ON TAPE:
ARE YOU FREAKED NOW?
WHY WOULD YOU TAPE US
LIKE THAT?
ELLIE:
IT'S FOR A TV PIECE -
FOR CO-OP.
BUT I WASN'T GOING
TO USE ANY NAMES!
TOBY:
A PIECE ABOUT WHAT?
US? DETENTION?
SEAN:
NO.
ABOUT THEFT AT DEGRASSI.
NOT COOL, ELLIE.
(THWACK OF ELASTIC BAND)
HAZEL:
HEY TOBY.
TOBY:
HEY GUYS.
JT:
WHAT HAPPENED HERE
ON SATURDAY?
TOBY:
WOULDN'T YOU LIKE
TO KNOW.
JIMMY:
SEAN, WHAT'S UP, MAN?
SEAN:
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
ELLIE:
HI.
LISTEN...
I KNOW I WAS WRONG.
BUT WHAT HAPPENED
BETWEEN US ON THE ROOF...
I REALLY,
REALLY WANT THAT
TO BE THE REAL TRUTH.
HERE'S THE TAPE YOU
WANT TO STOMP ON.
THERE'S NO STORY.
SEAN:
SO I DON'T FREAK
YOU OUT EITHER?
NO.
NOT AT ALL.