(SOUND OF SHOWS FROM THE TV)
(DIALING PHONE)
EMMA:
THIS IS THE SIMPSON-NELSON
RESIDENCE,
PLEASE LEAVE A MESSAGE.
(SOUND OF DOOR OPENING)
(SEXY GIGGLING)
NEED HELP WITH THAT?
OY. (LAUGHS)
UM, SEAN, THIS IS UH...
WENDY.
THAT'S MY LITTLE
BROTHER, SEAN.
BATHROOM?
FIRST DOOR ON THE RIGHT.
SORRY 'BOUT THAT, BRO.
FIGURED YOU'D BE OVER
AT THE GIRLFRIEND'S,
YOU KNOW? AS USUAL.
HAVEN'T BEEN THERE
IN A MONTH.
THANKS FOR NOTICING.
WHAT, YOU GUYS BREAK UP
OR SOMETHIN'?
HER STEP-DAD IS SICK.
TRACKER:
YEAH WELL, THAT'S TOO BAD.
LOOK, WHY DON'T YOU UM...
WHY DON'T YOU GO BUY HIM A
GET-WELL CARD OR SOMETHIN' HUH?
AH!
(DIALING PHONE)
EMMA:
THIS IS THE SIMPSON-NELSON
RESIDENCE,
PLEASE LEAVE A MESSAGE.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Hear what I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
TOBY:
MY BUBBIE AND ZADIE
SHOULD JUST BUY STOCK
IN THE PHOTO COMPANY.
THEY ORDERED LIKE
TWO DOZEN PRINTS.
ARE THEY BLIND?
JT:
YOU SEE THAT GUY JAY?
100% PURE PSYCHO.
PARK THERE,
YOU'LL GET A TICKET.
OOH, NOT A TICKET!
TOBY:
HEY! GIVE THOSE BACK!
WHAT ARE YOU?
HIS BODYGUARD?
HIS FRIEND.
(DISGUSTED GRUNT)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
GOOD JOB.
SIMPSON:
SPELL-CHECK.
TRY IT SOMETIME.
HE'S IN A GREAT MOOD.
HE STARTED CHEMO
LAST WEEK.
OH, SORRY.
EMMA:
IT'S OKAY.
THE LAPTOP WAS A SURPRISE
FROM MOM, TO CHEER HIM UP.
'CAUSE NOTHING SAYS HAPPY
LIKE A NEW COMPUTER.
TRUE, IF YOU'RE
ARCHIE SIMPSON.
DID YOU CALL LAST NIGHT?
THERE WERE SOME HANG-UPS.
NO, WASN'T ME.
I WAS THINKING,
WHY DON'T WE GET
TOGETHER TONIGHT?
YOU KNOW, WATCH SOME TV,
ORDER A PIZZA...
LIKE WE USED TO.
I DON'T KNOW IF I CAN.
C'MON. A MOVIE, A COUCH,
DOUBLE CHEESE, ME.
(LAUGHS)
HOW COULD I RESIST?
(LOUD SMASH)
JAY:
YO, WHAT'S UP?
(LAUGHS)
JAY:
GET OUT OF HERE.
RADITCH:
REMEMBER TO HAVE YOUR
CLASS PHOTO FORMS
HANDED IN BY THE END
OF THE DAY.
PLEASE BRING YOUR COMPLETED
FORMS AND PAYMENT...
SEAN:
HEY.
WHAT IS THIS?
TEMPEH, ALFALFA,
AND PEANUT SAUCE.
(LAUGHS)
HELLO, VITAMINS?
HOW ABOUT TASTES GOOD?
EMMA, THEY'VE CALLED A SUB.
I'M GOING HOME.
NOT FEELING WELL?
YOUR MOM'S STUCK
AT THE SALON TONIGHT,
SO YOU GOTTA COME STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER SCHOOL.
I CAN'T.
SEAN AND I ARE-
ARE GONNA HAVE
TO RESCHEDULE.
(SIGHS)
YOU GUYS EVER HEAR
OF BABYSITTERS?
SEAN.
YEAH, I KNOW,
IT JUST...
SUCKS.
I KNOW.
WHOA, EN PASSANT?
YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
OH, I CAN.
A RARE, BUT LEGAL MOVE
OF OPPORTUNITY
BY THE LOWLY PAWN.
NADIA:
TOBY? IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
JT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE HERE.
THEN WHY'S HE SITTING
OVER THERE?
HE PROBABLY JUST FORGOT
TODAY'S THE INAUGURAL MEETING
OF THE ROOKS
AND KNIGHTS SOCIETY.
HEY JT! OVER HERE!
YEAH, HE REALLY FORGOT.
TOBY:
HOPE HE HASN'T FORGOTTEN
HE'S STAYING OVER
AT MY PLACE TONIGHT.
KENDRA:
CHECKMATE IN FOUR.
LIBERTY:
(SIGHS)
CRAIG:
HMM...
WHEN I TRIED DOING THAT
WITH THE WRENCH,
IT JUST GOT LOOSER.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
STICK TO SELLING CARS.
HEY, SHUT UP!
MAN, THIS WAS
SUPPOSED TO BE
MY BIRD COURSE
FOR THE SEMESTER.
I DON'T KNOW MANY BIRDS
THAT CAN CHANGE
A TRANSMISSION.
EHL:
AH...
NICE JOB, SEAN.
YOU CAN WORK MY PIT ANY DAY.
SEAN?
WHAT'S HIS PROBLEM?
DON'T MESS WITH HIM, MAN.
YOU'RE DOING THAT WRONG.
TRY REMOVING THE
INJECTOR LINE FIRST.
RIGHTY-TIGHTY,
LEFTY-LOOSEY.
YOU GOT GUTS,
CAMERON.
ARMSTRONG:
NOW IN AN OBTUSE TRIANGLE,
ONE ANGLE IS GREATER
THAN 90 DEGREES,
WHEREAS IN A SCALENE
TRIANGLE...
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
CAN I SEE SEAN CAMERON,
PLEASE?
ARMSTRONG:
SURE, SEAN?
RADITCH:
SOMEONE BROKE INTO A VENDING
MACHINE NEAR YOUR LOCKER.
DID YOU SEE ANYTHING?
NO.
REALLY? SOME STUDENTS SAID
THAT THEY SAW YOU-
THEY SAW ME WHAT?
I'M JUST TRYING TO GET
TO THE BOTTOM OF THIS.
SO THAT POINTS TO ME,
THE POOR KID.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I SAID.
THEN WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
WATCH YOUR TONE.
SEAN, I'M JUST TRYING TO
GET TO THE BOTTOM OF THIS.
WELL, I'M NOT AT
THE BOTTOM OF IT.
THE WAY YOU'RE ACTING,
I'M BEGINNING TO THINK
THAT MAYBE YOU ARE.
I'M WATCHING YOU,
MR. CAMERON.
(SCHOOL BELL)
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
YOU.
RADITCH IS ALL OVER ME
BECAUSE OF THAT
STUPID VENDING MACHINE.
JAY:
DID YOU TELL HIM ANYTHING?
SEAN:
NO.
BUT HE THINKS I DID IT.
OOH, I'M IN TROUBLE
WITH RADITCH.
I'M GONNA GET
A DETENTION!
I SAID COOL IT!
JAY:
TECHNICALLY,
THE SIDEWALK IS CITY PROPERTY.
THE FIGHT WAS OFF
SCHOOL GROUNDS.
WE'LL JUST GET A WARNING.
SEAN:
DON'T TALK TO ME.
YOU HANDLE YOURSELF
PRETTY GOOD.
I SAID DON'T TALK TO ME.
LOOK AT YOU.
ALL EMINEM ON THE OUTSIDE,
BIG SCARED BABY ON THE INSIDE.
I'VE GOT A RECORD, OKAY?
YOU'RE THAT GUY, AREN'T YOU?
YOU YOU NEARLY KILLED
A KID IN WASAGA.
IT WAS A FIGHT,
AND I DEAFENED HIM IN ONE EAR.
SORRY WHAT?
I CAN'T HEAR YOU.
(LAUGHS)
YOU KNOW YOU'RE
A REAL COMEDIAN
FOR SOMEONE'S SITTING
IN THE PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE.
CHAIR'S GOT MY IMPRINT IN IT.
LOOK.
YOU EVER WANT TO HANG
WITH SOME REAL PEOPLE?
YOUR PEOPLE--NOT GEEKS--
YOU LET ME KNOW.
RADITCH:
JASON, YOU FIRST.
IN MY OFFICE,
NOW.
♪♪♪
(SLEEPY SIGH)
(SLEEPY MUTTERINGS)
LIBERTY.
(GASPS)
TOBY:
JT, GET UP,
WE'RE GONNA BE LATE.
COME ON.
TOBY, QUIT IT.
STOP!
WHAT, DID YOU PEE THE BED
OR SOMETHING?
YOU HAD A WET DREAM?
THREE FEET ABOVE MY HEAD?
CAN YOU KEEP IT DOWN?
WHO WAS IT ABOUT?
YOUR MOM.
TOBY:
IT WAS LIBERTY WASN'T IT?
RIBERTY! RIBERTY!
TOBY, I SWEAR,
IF YOU TELL ANYONE...
I'LL SLAUGHTER YOU.
OKAY, SHOOTER.
SO...
WHAT TIME DO WE MEET
THE COOL KIDS FOR LUNCH?
LUNCH?
NO, YOU'RE NOT HAVING
LUNCH WITH US, OKAY?
OH YES I AM,
UNLESS YOU WANT EVERYONE
TO FIND OUT ABOUT YOUR UH...
STICKY SITUATION.
(HUGE SIGH)
SEAN:
COLD AIR INTAKE.
JAY:
YEAH. HOW DID YOU KNOW?
SEAN:
IT'S A SIMPLE MOD.
SUCKS AIR INTO THE ENGINE,
ADDS ABOUT FIVE HORSES.
JAY:
YOU KNOW YOUR CARS.
SEAN:
YOU DON'T.
IT'S LOOSE.
NOW, A COLD AIR
INTAKE'S A START,
BUT IF YOU REALLY
WANT TO TWEAK THIS,
ADD A FULL CAT-BACK SYSTEM.
IT'S A PIPE RUNNING FROM
THE CATALYTIC CONVERTER
TO THE EXHAUST.
ADDS ABOUT 15 HORSEPOWER.
SWEET.
HOW MUCH?
IN PARTS, A FEW HUNDRED.
BOY:
(WHISTLES)
SEAN:
THE PARTS AIN'T CHEAP,
BUT IF YOU WANT,
I CAN DO THE LABOUR FOR FREE.
(LAUGHTER)
PAIGE:
OH IT MIGHT BE A TRUMP NINE,
BUT IT DOES NOT BEAT
THE LEFT BOWER.
I- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I MEAN, TRUMP?
BOWER? EUCHRE?
IS THIS EVEN ENGLISH?
TOBY:
ACTUALLY "EUCHRE"
IS AN ENGLISH WORD
BUT ITS ORIGIN ARE UNKNOWN.
TOBY:
I LOVE EUCHRE.
I ALWAYS PLAY WITH MY BUBBIE.
DEAL ME IN.
I'M TOBY ISAACS,
I KNOW EVERYTHING.
I WAS JUST MAKING
AN OBSERVATION.
JT:
REALLY.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO HEAR
MY OBSERVATION, TOBY?
NO ONE CARES.
WELL, I KNOW SOMETHING
EVERYONE HERE MIGHT
CARE ABOUT.
TOBY...
THE NOCTURNAL EMISSION,
BETTER KNOWN AS THE WET DREAM.
I'VE HAD THEM,
SPINNER'S HAD THEM,
EVEN UH, MR. RADITCH
HAS HAD THEM.
OKAY, I SO DID NOT
NEED THAT MENTAL IMAGE.
KNOW WHO ELSE
HAS HAD THEM?
HEY GUYS,
LET'S GET BACK TO THE CARDS.
JT YORKE.
OKAY, IS THERE
A POINT TO THIS?
OH, THERE'S A POINT.
RIGHT THERE.
GIRL:
LIBERTY!
OKAY, THAT MAY MAKE
SENSE IN YIDDISH,
BUT I'M STILL LOST.
SO WAS JT, THIS MORNING...
IN DREAMS OF LIBERTY.
(GIGGLES)
HAZEL:
GROSS. CAN WE CHANGE TOPICS?
PAIGE:
NO WAY, THIS IS SUCH
JUICY GOSSIP.
OH PARDON THE PUN.
GIRLS:
(GIGGLE)
WE HAVE ONE HOUR
TO PICK UP
EACH AND EVERY LAST
PIECE OF GARBAGE.
REMEMBER GUYS,
TODAY WE'RE GONNA...?
CLEAN THE RAVINE!
WOO HOO!
THIS IS HOW YOU'RE
GONNA SPEND LUNCH?
PICKING UP GARBAGE?
I PROMISED
I'D HELP OUT.
FINE, HELP OUT.
WE'RE GOING FOR A DRIVE.
EMMA:
I'LL MEET YOU
OVER THERE, OKAY?
SEAN? I WAS THINKING
YOU AND I
COULD START ON THE
NORTH-EAST SLOPE.
UH-OH, CHEMICAL SPILL.
(LAUGHS)
WELL I'M GONNA GO START.
JAY:
GREAT SENSE OF HUMOUR.
LOOK MAN, IT'S YOUR CHOICE.
YOU CAN COME FOR A RIDE,
OR "CLEAN THE RAVINE".
WANT A DRINK?
THANKS FOR HELPING.
I KNOW THIS ISN'T EXACTLY
YOUR IDEA OF FUN.
ONLY HALF AN HOUR LEFT, SO...
SEAN!
WE HAVE TO-
THE GARBAGE ISN'T
GOING ANYWHERE.
(GASP)
UH, LOT, LOT OF GARBAGE.
(NERVOUS LAUGH)
EMMA!
ANYBODY COULD WALK BY.
WHO CARES?
I DO.
SEE YOU IN CLASS.
FINE, BE LIKE THAT.
LIKE WHAT?
SULKY.
YOU'RE SO UPTIGHT.
WHY? 'CAUSE I DIDN'T
WANT TO LIKE,
MAKE OUT IN FRONT
OF OTHER PEOPLE?
NO, BECAUSE YOU NEVER
WANT TO DO ANYTHING.
NOT WITH ME.
I JUST SPENT MY ENTIRE
LUNCH WITH YOU.
YEAH,
CLEANING THE RAVINE.
WELL, SORRY THAT
I CARE ABOUT
STUPID, UNIMPORTANT THINGS
LIKE THE ENVIRONMENT.
SEAN:
THAT'S ALL YOU CARE ABOUT.
EMMA NELSON,
ENVIRONMENTAL CRUSADER,
A BABYSITTER,
A NURSE!
SNAKE HAS CANCER, SEAN.
SEAN:
YEAH, I HEARD.
FINE. TOMORROW YOU SPEND
LUNCH WITH THOSE LOSERS.
YOU KNOW WHAT? I WILL.
'CAUSE AT LEAST THEY'RE FUN.
FUN? AND YOU?
YOU'RE JUST PATHETIC.
EHL:
THIS IS NOT A BARNYARD,
I AM NOT YOUR MOTHER.
SO CLEAN UP, OKAY?
ALL OF YOU WHO HAVE
CLEANED UP,
GET OUTTA HERE!
RIGHTY-TIGHTY,
LEFTY-LOOSEY, HUH?
HEY, REMEMBER THE
CAT-BACK SYSTEM?
I'VE BEEN WORKING ON
A SCHEME TO GET THE CASH.
YEAH?
IT'S PRETTY GOOD.
GOOD, LET'S DO IT.
DON'T YOU NEED PERMISSION
FROM THE BOSS?
SHE'S NOT MY BOSS.
LET'S GO.
ALL RIGHT.
(WHIR OF FLOOR POLISHER)
ALL RIGHT, I'LL VIC IT
YOU GUYS MAKE SURE THE
JANITORS ARE OCCUPIED.
YO.
THE KEYBOARD WILL GET YOU
50 BUCKS, IF YOU'RE LUCKY.
NOW THAT...
THAT'LL BUY YOU
A CAT-BACK SYSTEM.
SINCE IT WAS YOUR IDEA...
SEAN:
ALL RIGHT, BACK OUT.
I GOT THIS.
ALL YOU GOTTA DO
IS CLAMP HERE.
BOY:
UP FRONT?
SEAN:
AND ANOTHER ONE AT THE CAT,
SHOULD BE IN THE BACK.
EMMA:
SEAN?
CAN I TALK TO YOU
FOR A MINUTE?
ALONE?
NO.
JAY:
GO AHEAD AND TALK.
WE'RE ALL INTERESTED.
IT'S ABOUT YESTERDAY.
WE BOTH SAID A LOT...
I WAS HOPING WE COULD TALK,
REALLY TALK ABOUT EVERYTHING.
GOT NOTHING TO SAY.
SHE REALLY IS FLAT
AS A BOARD, HUH?
(MEAN LAUGHTER)
HOW COULD YOU DO THAT?
ME?
WHAT ABOUT THE WAY
YOU'VE BEEN ACTING?
YOU TOLD THEM I HAD
A WET DREAM OVER LIBERTY.
YOU TREATED ME LIKE
CRAP FOR NO REASON.
YOU STOOD ME UP FOR LUNCH,
YOU ACT LIKE I'M
SOME BIG LOSER.
WHAT DID I DO TO YOU?
LOOK...
THEY'RE MY FRIENDS,
YOU'RE MY FRIEND.
BUT YOU AND THEM...
NEVER GONNA HAPPEN.
NO.
TOBES...
TOBES. TOBES! WAIT UP.
LET'S HAVE LUNCH
TOGETHER TODAY, OKAY?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
MY...
MY NEW LAPTOP, I...
I THOUGHT I LEFT IT
LOCKED IN HERE LAST NIGHT...
I MEAN, I KNOW THE CHEMO'S
MAKING ME STUPID BUT...
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I ACTUALLY LOST IT.
EMMA:
MAYBE IT'S NOT THE CHEMO.