SIMPSON:
MY DILIGENT LOCKER CUSTODIANS,
I'LL BE BACK IN FIFTEEN MINUTES
TO INSPECT ALL YOUR HARD WORK.
AND ONCE THEY'RE CLEAN...
HELLO SUMMER!
JIMMY:
TWENTY-THREE HOURS
AND TEN MINUTES
AND I'LL BE ON A PLANE
TO L.A.
AND THE BEST SUMMER
BASKETBALL CAMP IN THE U.S..
SPOILED MUCH?
IF MY PARENTS REALLY
WANTED TO SPOIL ME
THEY'D LET ME CANCEL,
RIGHT?
BECAUSE WHEN THEY BOOKED
IN DECEMBER -
YEAH.
OKAY, IT WAS COOL,
BUT THAT WAS
BEFORE YOU.
PAIGE:
AND THE FINAL SACRIFICE -
LAST FALLS WAY PASSE MASCARA
AND LIP GLOSS.
SPINNER:
AND HONEYBEE'S EXILE TO THE
WASTELAND IS OFFICIALLY OVER.
WELL, THAT'S WORTH
CELEBRATING.
JIMMY:
IT IS.
AND TONIGHT IS GONNA
BE A DREAM,
A NIGHT THAT YOU'LL
NEVER FORGET.
HAZEL:
YOU GOT US A LIMO?
JIMMY:
WELL, WE NEED SOMETHING
TO GET US
FROM MY PLACE
TO THE RESTAURANT.
OH AND BY THE WAY,
MEAL'S ON ME.
HAZEL,
WANNA SWITCH BOYFRIENDS?
(SARCASTIC)
OH YEAH.
OH, AREN'T YOU
THE BIG HERO?
THAT'S THE PLAN.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Hear what I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
I GOT YOUR NOTE.
YOU WANTED TO SEE ME?
HAVE A SEAT.
I THOUGHT SCHOOL WAS OVER.
SIMPSON:
YOU STARTED THE YEAR OFF WELL,
BUT YOUR GRADE
JUST KEPT DROPPING.
AND GIVEN THAT YOU'RE ON
STUDENT WELFARE-
SEAN:
WAS.
TILL THEY FIND OUT
I FAILED A COURSE.
THANKS A LOT, MR. SIMPSON.
SIMPSON:
CREATE A PARTS DATABASE
FOR THE AUTO SHOP
BY END OF DAY.
DO A GOOD JOB,
AND YOU DON'T FAIL.
CLOCK'S TICKING.
JOEY:
OKAY. CREDIT REPORTS,
CREDIT REPORTS...
GOT IT.
LEASE AGREEMENTS...
(KNOCKING)
HEY.
THANK GOODNESS
YOU'RE HERE.
I HAVE A MEETING,
AND I LEFT MY BRIEFCASE-
THERE YOU GO.
YOU ARE A MODEL
OF EFFICIENCY.
JOEY:
YEAH. IF I WAS,
I WOULD HAVE BEEN BACK AT WORK
TWENTY MINUTES AGO.
CAITLIN:
WE'RE LIKE TWO PEAS IN A POD.
WELL, YOU SHOULD MOVE
INTO THIS POD.
SERIOUSLY.
YOU'RE ALREADY A HUGE
PART OF THE KIDS LIVES.
I KNOW THEY WOULD LOVE IT
IF YOU MOVED IN.
MORE IMPORTANTLY,
I WOULD LOVE IT.
WHOA.
THIS IS SUDDEN.
THINK ABOUT IT.
YOUR STUFF IS HERE
AND... YOU SHOULD BE TOO.
I GOT TO GET
TO THIS MEETING.
UH... WE'LL TALK AT DINNER,
OKAY?
BYE.
SPINNER:
AH, JIMMY...
YOU COMING OUT
OF THE BATHROOM?
JIMMY:
UM, THIS THING DOESN'T
FIT RIGHT.
MAYBE CAUSE YOU'RE
WEARING A SARI?
YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO ASK FOR A KURTA -
WHAT INDIAN MEN WEAR.
JIMMY:
NO, NO.
BECAUSE I ASKED FOR
TWO KURTAS AND TWO SARIS...
AND THEY GAVE ME
THREE SARIS.
AND YOU DIDN'T CHECK
BEFORE YOU LEFT THE STORE?
SLOPPY WORK, DUDE.
JIMMY:
SO I LOOK OKAY, RIGHT?
SPINNER:
(SNICKER) YEAH DUDE,
YOU LOOK GREAT.
YOU'LL BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
AT THE SEMI-FORMAL.
(SARCASTIC LAUGHTER)
I'VE NEVER BEEN
IN A LIMO BEFORE.
DO WE GET CHAMPAGNE,
TOO?
I HOPE SO.
(CHEESY HORN HONK)
DUKE:
HOWDY GIRLS.
I'M DUKE, YOUR CHAUFFEUR
FOR THE EVENING.
I THINK THERE'S
BEEN A MISTAKE.
YOU JIMMY BROOKS?
AIN'T NO MISTAKE,
HOUND DOG.
LET'S GIDDY-UP.
NO, NO,
LADIES FIRST.
I LIKE YOUR HAT.
WATCH YOUR DRESS.
TOMAS:
HIS AND HERS TOWELS?
JOEY ASKED ME TO MOVE IN
AND THE TOWELS ARE SAYING,
"WHY YES, I WOULD LOVE TO,
MR. JEREMIAH."
THIS IS WHERE YOU SAY CONGRATS.
I WAS JUST ABOUT TO...
FOR AN ENTIRELY DIFFERENT
REASON.
THE DOCUMENTARY SERIES ON
UNICEF'S WORK WITH HIV/AIDS?
THE STATION GAVE US
THEIR ANSWER TODAY.
THEY SAID YES?!
CONGRATULATIONS!
WE SUBMITTED THAT WHAT,
A YEAR AGO.
IT'S FOR GENEVA.
LEAVING TONIGHT.
EXCUSE ME?
YEAH. THERE'S A WORLD
CONFERENCE
NEXT MONTH ON HIV/AIDS.
AND YOU'RE OFF TO AFRICA,
INDIA, SOUTHEAST ASIA,
THE CARIBBEAN.
IT'LL BE A HECTIC
NINE MONTHS.
I...I CAN'T.
SORRY.
THIS IS YOUR PROJECT.
IT'S YOUR BABY.
THE MAN I LOVE
ASKED ME TO MOVE IN
AND I'M NOT GOING
TO TURN HIM DOWN.
NOT FOR THIS,
NOT FOR ANYTHING.
SIMPSON:
THE DATABASE
SEEMS TO BE WORKING.
THERE'S A COUPLE OF
REDUNDANCIES IN THE TABLES,
BUT UH...
THAT'S AN EASY FIX.
SO...
53.
NOT THE BEST MARK,
BUT IT'S A PASS.
NICE WORK, SEAN.
THANK YOU, MR. SIMPSON.
REALLY...
OH, YIKES!
IT'S 6:00 P.M.
I'M CHAPERONING
YOUR PARTY TONIGHT.
I'M NOT GOING.
IT'S NOT MY SCENE.
A GOOD TIME'S
NOT YOUR SCENE?
SEAN, LIFE CAN BE ROUGH,
AND I KNOW YOU'VE BEEN DEALT
SOME CRAPPY HANDS.
BUT IT CAN ALSO BE PRETTY
AMAZING IF YOU LET IT.
MR. SIMPSON...
SIMPSON:
YOU USED TO COME TO ME
WITH PROBLEMS,
AND I'D TRY AND HELP OUT.
YOU DON'T ANYMORE.
THAT'S COOL.
IT'S YOUR BUSINESS.
BUT IT DOESN'T MEAN
I'VE GIVEN UP ON YOU.
I'LL ALWAYS BE HERE
FOR YOU, SEAN.
I STOLE YOUR COMPUTER.
YOUR ALIENWARE LAPTOP.
I STOLE IT
TO GET BACK AT EMMA.
BUT I...
I LOST IT.
MY...
MY CHEMO...
IT WASN'T YOUR CHEMO,
AND YOU DIDN'T LOSE IT.
I STOLE IT.
AND I'M SORRY.
I'M SO SORRY.
YOU BETTER GO.
NOW.
THIS RESTAURANT LOOKS
INCREDIBLE.
PAIGE:
MORE LIKE INCREDIBLY MEDIOCRE
SO LET'S JUST GO.
JIMMY:
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU TWO?
OKAY, UM...
WHEN WE SKIPPED SCHOOL,
WE ALSO SKIPPED OUT
ON HIM.
JIMMY:
UH, SIR?
WE HAVE RESERVATIONS,
UNDER BROOKS.
WAITER:
PARTY OF FOUR.
RIGHT THIS WAY.
SO MS. RYAN,
I WOULD LIKE
TO DISCUSS THE OFFER
THAT WAS TABLED
THIS AFTERNOON.
HAVE YOU COME
TO A RESOLUTION?
I HAVE.
AND MY DECISION
IS YES.
(SIGH) I'M SO HAPPY.
ME TOO.
IT'S BEEN ONE HELL
OF A DAY,
LET ME TELL YOU.
A REAL ROLLERCOASTER.
REALLY?
YOU WEREN'T SURE
ABOUT MOVING IN?
NO, NO.
OF COURSE NOT.
TOMAS HAD BIG NEWS.
THEY WANT TO DO
MY HIV/AIDS SERIES.
THAT'S AMAZING!
YEAH.
AND AMAZINGLY BAD TIMING.
BECAUSE I'D HAVE
TO LEAVE TONIGHT
ON A MIDNIGHT FLIGHT
TO GENEVA.
SO FORGET ABOUT DINNER.
LET'S GO PACK
YOUR THINGS!
SIR, COULD WE GET
THE BILL?
JOEY, I TURNED IT DOWN.
JOEY:
WHAT?
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
BECAUSE I'M MOVING IN
WITH YOU.
NO, YOU HAVE TO GO.
I MEAN...
THIS IS THE OPPORTUNITY
OF A LIFETIME.
I SORTA THOUGHT YOU WERE
MY OPPORTUNITY OF A LIFETIME.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
GREAT.
THEN I GUESS I...
I GOTTA,
I GOTTA GO.
DYLAN
I THINK IT'S PERFECT, MARCO.
MARCO
YEAH, ALMOST PERFECT.
EMMA:
I CANNOT BELIEVE THIS
IS OUR GYM.
MANNY:
I KNOW. THEY DID AN AMAZING JOB.
JT:
THOUGH THEY'RE NOT DOING
VERY WELL
IN THE BEVERAGE
DEPARTMENT.
I NOTICED A DISTINCT
LACK OF ICE.
I'M ON IT.
I'M OFF TO THE STORE.
SEAN:
MR. SIMPSON...
OKAY, ON A SCALE OF ONE TO TEN,
THAT MEAL WAS A TWENTY.
UH SIR?
I THINK YOU CHARGED US
FOR THREE EXTRA DINNERS.
YOU FOUR, PLUS THREE LUNCHES
FROM A FEW WEEKS AGO.
DON'T FORGET TO TIP.
SPIN, LEND ME FORTY BUCKS?
PAIGE?
JIMMY:
HAZEL, I'LL PAY YOU BACK.
HAZEL:
IT'S NO BIG DEAL, REALLY.
DUKE:
I SWEAR I PAID
THOSE PARKING TICKETS -
ALL THIRTY OF 'EM!
I'VE BEEN RAILROADED!
PAIGE:
WELL, LET'S START WALKING.
HEY, HOLD ON HERE
A MINUTE.
FOLKS JUST HOLD
YOUR HORSES.
THE DUKE DON'T LIKE TO LEAVE
HIS CUSTOMERS HIGH AND DRY.
(WHISTLES)
WE'RE GONNA PULL UP
TO THE PROM IN A COP CAR?
FORGET IT.
SON, YOU'RE ALREADY
IN DEEPER
THAN A STABLE BOY
AFTER A MONTH OF SUNDAYS.
I'D TAKE THE CAR.
WE'LL TAKE IT,
DUKE.
MY PLEASURE.
YOU FOLKS HAVE FUN
AT YOUR PROM.
LETS DANCE, COP.
COME ON!
I CAN HELP.
POP THE HOOD.
I WON'T STEAL
YOUR ENGINE.
PROMISE.
SO I'M COVERING
SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA FIRST?
AROUND THE WORLD
IN NINE MONTHS.
ARE SURE YOU WANT
TO DO THIS?
TOMAS. YES.
TOMAS:
THIS AFTERNOON YOU WERE
PRETTY SURE YOU DIDN'T.
WE'LL TALK MORE
LATER.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
PLANE LEAVES
IN A COUPLE HOURS,
SINCE I'M TAKING THE JOB.
YOU WALKED OUT ON ME.
WHY?
I DON'T KNOW.
CRAZY ME,
I THOUGHT YOU ACTUALLY
WANTED ME TO MOVE IN.
I DO.
BUT IF IT TAKES
A COUPLE OF MONTHS, SO WHAT?
IT'S NOT A COUPLE OF MONTHS.
JOEY, IT'S ALMOST A YEAR.
AND IF YOU REALLY LOVED ME,
YOU WOULDN'T WANT ME TO GO.
I WANT YOU TO GO
BECAUSE I DO LOVE YOU.
AND THAT'S NEVER
GONNA CHANGE.
I PROMISE.
YOU'VE MADE PROMISES BEFORE,
JOEY.
PROMISES YOU DIDN'T KEEP.
YOU HAVE TO ASK YOURSELF
ONE THING -
DO YOU WANT TO TAKE
THIS JOB OR NOT?
YEAH. I DO.
THEN I'LL BE HERE
WAITING FOR YOU.
YOU'VE GOT SERIOUS PROBLEMS.
I'LL CALL FOR A TOW.
YOU GO HOME.
NO, I WANNA HELP.
HELP?
IT'S A LITTLE LATE FOR THAT,
ISN'T IT?
I WAS ON DEATH'S DOOR.
SPIKE BLOWS HER SAVINGS
ON A LAPTOP TO CHEER ME UP,
AND YOU STOLE IT.
WHAT KIND OF A PERSON
DOES THAT?
THE STARTER'S GONE,
AND YOUR HEAD GASKET TOO.
THERE'S OIL AND COOLANT
ALL OVER ON MY HANDS.
DID YOU HEAR ANYTHING
I JUST SAID?
SEAN:
THE HEAD MAY EVEN BE CRACKED.
IT'S A LOT OF WORK,
WEEKS,
BUT IF YOU BUY THE PARTS,
I'LL DO ALL THE LABOUR
FOR FREE.
I WANT TO, MR. SIMPSON.
SO?
SEAN:
SO I OWE YOU.
YOU KNOW,
YOU MIGHT HATE ME,
BUT THIS IS THE ONLY WAY
I CAN MAKE IT UP.
PLEASE.
YOU SURE YOU'RE UP
TO DOING THIS?
IT'S A PRETTY BIG
COMMITMENT.
I KNOW.
BUT I'M DOWN WITH IT.
I GOTTA GET BACK
TO THE DANCE.
WE'LL SEE YOU
MONDAY MORNING?
YEAH.
BETTER?
I THINK IT'S GONNA BE.
YEAH.
♪♪♪
MARCO:
ALL RIGHT!
SHUBHA RAATRI DEGRASSI,
AND WELCOME TO OUR
BOLLYWOOD NIGHTS!
ARE WE ALL HAVING
AN AMAZING TIME OR WHAT?!
(CHEERING)
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
SO LET'S DECIDE HOW
WE'RE GONNA CHOOSE
TONIGHT'S KING AND QUEEN.
YOU'LL NOTICE SOME
VOTING BOXES OUT-
LIBERTY
FIRE!
SIMPSON:
ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE,
YOU KNOW THE DRILL.
(FIRE ALARM RINGS)
YOU ALL NEED TO MOVE
TO THE DOOR
IN A CALM, QUIET-
AND VERY WET FASHION.
(CHAOS - FIRE ALARM IS RINGING,
PEOPLE ARE YELLING)
(FIRE ALARM'S STILL RINGING)
SIMPSON:
GUYS, KEEP MOVING PLEASE.
LET'S GET DOWN,
ALL THE WAY DOWN THE STAIRS.
WE'RE GONNA WANT TO LET THESE
TRUCKS TO GET THROUGH,
ALL RIGHT?
CRAIG!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
AH, THOSE CURTAINS
THAT MARCO PICKED OUT
THERE'RE LIKE
TOTALLY FLAMMABLE.
(SIRENS)
WELL, I GUESS THIS IS IT?
FOR NOW.
♪♪♪
MARCO:
LOOK, THIS IS GREAT
AND EVERYTHING,
BUT I KNOW THIS
AMAZING STATION
THAT PLAYS NOTHING BUT
SOUTH ASIAN MUSIC.
SO MAYBE IF I TOLD
EVERYONE-
MARCO!
JUST LET IT GO.
BROOKS,
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
UH, LET'S SEE.
I'M WEARING A SARI,
OUR LIMO DRIVER
WAS ARRESTED,
AND THE SCHOOL
ALMOST BURNED DOWN.
I MEANT WITH YOU.
JIMMY:
TONIGHT WAS ALL ABOUT ME
SHOWING YOU
THAT I CAN DO IT RIGHT.
AND EVERYTHING WENT WRONG.
AND I DON'T CARE.
I DON'T.
HERE YOU ARE!
C'MON,
YOU'RE MISSING IT.
YOU WANT TO MAKE ME
HAPPY?
THERE'S ONLY ONE THING
YOU HAVE TO DO.
DANCE WITH ME.
♪♪♪