(WHIR OF HELICOPTER)
(MILITARY BAND PLAYS
IN THE DISTANCE)
HEY.
SAYING GOODBYE
IS THE WORST PART.
SERIOUSLY.
I'M GONNA BE FINE.
IT'S JUST A
PEACEKEEPING MISSION.
I KNOW, BUT-
YOUR MOTHER'S FINE.
SHE'S UNDER CONTROL.
THERE'S MY GIRL,
COME ON.
IT'LL BE FINE.
HEY.
MRS. NASH:
HI.
YEAH, I'LL SEE YA.
OKAY.
COLONEL NASH:
HEY, KEEP THAT SMILE,
OKAY?
ELLIE:
BYE, DAD.
BYE!
MOM? YOU OKAY?
DON'T MAKE A SCENE,
ELEANOR.
JUST SHUT UP,
SMILE AND WAVE.
CROWD:
BYE! BYE!
OH, THERE HE IS!
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Hear what I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
ELLIE.
HEY, HOW ARE YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU,
MY COUNSELOR?
SORRY. IT'S JUST,
YOUR DAD LEFT YESTERDAY, AND-
HE'S IN THE ARMY.
HE LEAVES. IT HAPPENS.
SO DO YOU WANT TO GO
TO A MOVIE AFTER SCHOOL?
SWEET. AND I WOULD,
BUT I GOT MY CO-OP INTERVIEW.
RIGHT. YOU NERVOUS?
INTERVIEWING FOR
MY DREAM JOB?
WHY WOULD THAT
MAKE ME NERVOUS?
NOT THAT IT MATTERS.
PAIGE IS GONNA GET IT.
WELL, CAITLIN'S TV SHOW IS
ABOUT SOCIAL ISSUES, RIGHT?
PAIGE PROBABLY THINKS
IT'S ABOUT SOCIAL LIFE.
"HI, I'M PAIGE M.
REPORTING FOR STYLE FACTOR."
YOU'LL GET IT.
JUST BE YOURSELF.
LIKE THAT'S GONNA
GET ME THE JOB.
HAZEL:
BY THE TIME SCOTT
CALLS ME BACK?
I'M ON THE OTHER LINE
WITH PAIGE.
YOUR SECRET ADMIRER
STRUCK AGAIN!
THAT'S THE FOURTH ONE.
AND YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHO IT IS?
CAN'T YOU JUST ASK
YOUR TAROT CARDS?
TAROT DOESN'T WORK
LIKE THAT.
BESIDES, WITH MY LUCK
IT'S PROBABLY THE JANITOR.
PLEASE,
IT COULD BE ANYONE.
I KNOW WHO I WANT IT
TO BE.
YOU'VE GOT THE HOTS
FOR RICK?
SHHHH!
YOU SHOULD ASK HIM OUT.
BUT WHAT IF IT'S NOT HIM?
COME ON...
TERRI:
I GOT TO GET TO CLASS.
ELLIE:
HOMEWORK.
TALK TO ME.
MARCO:
WHAT? YOU DIDN'T DO IT?
ELLIE,
READY FOR THE INTERVIEW?
I AM SO NERVOUS.
MY MOM WAS LIKE,
"PAIGE, YOU'VE GOT THE CLOTHES,
YOU'VE GOT THE BRAINS,
YOU'RE FINE."
OF COURSE.
PAIGE:
PLEASE. MOTHERS ALWAYS
SAY THAT.
IT IS SO TEDIOUS.
ARMSTRONG:
OKAY FOLKS,
PUT YOUR BOOKS AWAY.
NO WAY.
ARMSTRONG:
WE'RE STARTING TODAY
WITH A POP QUIZ.
NOW IF YOU DID YOUR HOMEWORK,
YOU SHOULD BE FINE.
PAIGE? CAN YOU HAND THESE
OUT FOR ME, PLEASE?
BREAK A LEG, HON.
MARCO:
OKAY SO, WHY DO TEACHERS LIE?
I DID THE HOMEWORK,
LIKE HE SAID.
I WAS NOT FINE.
MARCO,
YOU GOT A B-PLUS.
YEAH,
BUT MY AVERAGE IS-
ELLIE:
IT'S ONLY WORTH WHAT?
TWO PERCENT OF OUR FINAL GRADE?
WE'RE BOTH GONNA PASS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE
THIS COOL ABOUT IT!
ACTUALLY, MARCO, I-
OH DIO MIO. (MY GOD)
UM, YEAH,
HOLD THAT THOUGHT.
PAIGE:
(SIGHS) SUCKS TO BE STRAIGHT.
COME ON, IT'S GOTTA BE HARD
WATCHING YOUR EX-BOYFRIEND FALL
MADLY IN LOVE WITH MY BROTHER?
SAUVE:
HI GIRLS, SORRY TO INTERRUPT
YOUR LUNCH.
I NEED YOU TO FILL THESE OUT
BEFORE YOUR CO-OP INTERVIEWS.
AND ASHLEY, CONGRATS.
IT'S REALLY HARD TO GET
THOSE RECORD COMPANY JOBS.
BUT REMEMBER SCHOOL
IS YOUR FIRST PRIORITY.
SINCE WHEN DO YOU WEAR GLASSES?
ALL RIGHT,
WHAT'S MY GOAL?
HELLO - ON-CAMERA, ANCHOR DESK.
IT'S NOT AN ON-CAMERA JOB.
IT'S TELEVISION - SAME DEAL.
WHAT'S YOUR GOAL?
ELLIE:
PAIGE-
PAIGE:
WHAT? I'M JUST-
OH ELLIE, I AM SO SORRY-
DON'T. IT'S FINE.
PAIGE:
WHAT? IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
I AM THRILLED THAT I FINALLY
GOT TO MEET YOU, CAITLIN.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
THE AMAZING INTERVIEW.
CAITLIN:
OH YOU'RE VERY WELCOME.
BYE, BYE.
ELLIE, HI.
IS THAT FOR ME?
GREAT.
YOU CAN TAKE THE COAT OFF.
RIGHT.
SO I REALLY LOVED
THE PIECE ON TENT CITY.
I ACTUALLY INTERVIEWED ONE OF
THOSE GUYS FOR THE GRAPEVINE.
OH REALLY?
WHICH ONE?
AH, I FORGET HIS NAME.
YOUNG. BROWN HAIR, GLASSES...
ANDREW LISTER?
THAT'S IT.
I-I ACTUALLY-
SORRY.
I'M REALLY NERVOUS.
THAT'S OKAY.
HERE.
HAVE A SEAT,
AND JUST TELL ME WHAT
YOU WERE GOING TO WISH FOR.
JUST IT'S PROBABLY
STUPID BUT...
IT'D BE COOL TO SEE THOSE
ACTIVISTS NOW,
NOW THAT THE TENTS ARE GONE.
ACTUALLY? WE'RE DOING
A FOLLOW-UP.
OKAY. WELL, UH...
TELL ME ABOUT THE GRAPEVINE.
HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN
WRITING FOR THEM?
UM, A WHILE.
CAITLIN:
IT'S A GREAT PAPER
TO BE WRITING FOR.
HAZEL:
STOP BEING SUCH A CHICKEN.
ANYONE ELSE WOULD JUST ASK HIM.
HEY MANNY, HELP ME OUT HERE.
SAY YOU LIKE A GUY-
IS HE SINGLE?
WE THINK SO.
DO YOU GO FOR IT?
COMPLETELY.
LIFE'S TOO SHORT.
TERRI:
FINE.
TOMORROW, IN GEOGRAPHY
I'LL--
TOBY:
HELLO, THERESE.
HELLO.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M THINKING?
NO.
OH. I THINK YOU DO.
MANNY:
TOBY, STOP BEING WEIRD.
UNTIL NEXT WE MEET.
HAZEL:
OR MAYBE YOUR ADMIRER IS TOBY.
BOTH:
UGH.
ELLIE:
MOM?
SORRY I'M LATE.
MOM? YOU OKAY?
MMM...
I BROUGHT US SOME DINNER
LIKE YOU ASKED.
HAD MY INTERVIEW.
TOTAL DISASTER.
MY WHOLE DAY WAS A DISASTER.
LOOK AT MY SHIRT.
UGH, THE SMELL.
OKAY.
MRS. NASH:
(CRASH) OH NO...
(THROWING UP SOUNDS)
(CRYING)
(ALARM)
PAIGE:
CAITLIN IS AWESOME.
SHE IS SO SMART,
SHE'S TOTALLY PRETTY.
WE REALLY CONNECTED.
I MEAN, CAITLIN AND I HAVE
SO MUCH IN COMMON.
HEY.
SO HOW'D IT GO?
AW, COME ON
YOU KNOW YOU GOT IT.
NO, I DON'T.
EL, THEY'D BE ABSOLUTELY
CRAZY NOT TO LOVE YOU, OKAY?
CAN I JUST STEAL ELLIE
AND PAIGE FOR A MOMENT?
ARMSTRONG:
SURE.
SO, I HEARD FROM CAITLIN RYAN.
AND UH SHE MADE A DECISION.
CONGRATULATIONS, ELLIE.
DON'T WORRY, PAIGE,
WE'RE GOING TO FIND YOU
SOMETHING GREAT.
WOW, I GUESS SHE REALLY
DID FEEL SORRY FOR YOU.
ASHLEY:
TERRI ISAACS.
HAS A CERTAIN RING TO IT.
TERRI:
I CAN'T BELIEVE HAZEL TOLD YOU.
ASHLEY:
BUT I HAVE TO KNOW.
I'M GOING TO BE YOUR FUTURE
SISTER-IN-LAW.
C'MON, TER, IT'S CUTE.
TERRI:
IT'S AWKWARD AND-
ASHLEY:
STRANGELY DISAPPOINTING?
TERRI:
JUST A BIT.
TOBY,
ARE YOU FOLLOWING ME?
I DON'T KNOW.
AM I?
CAN WE TAKE THE LONG WAY
TO MUSIC CLASS?
CAITLIN:
ELLIE?
I AM SO THRILLED
TO HAVE YOU HERE.
ELLIE:
YOU ARE?
CAITLIN:
OH YEAH. ABSOLUTELY.
I'M JUST SORRY IT'S ONLY
GOING TO BE ONCE A WEEK.
I CAN DO MORE.
MORNINGS, AFTERNOONS,
WEEKENDS.
YOU SOUND JUST LIKE ME.
AH BUT AS MY THERAPIST SAYS,
IT'S IMPORTANT
TO HAVE A LIFE.
I'LL FACT CHECK,
I'LL FILE,
PICK UP YOUR DRY-CLEANING,
GET YOU COFFEE,
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
SORRY, THIS IS
THE BEST WE COULD DO.
SO LET'S START
WITH A PROJECT.
UH, TEEN HOTLINES.
MANNED BY TEENS,
FOR TEENS.
LET'S SEE IF THEY WORK.
AND GO.
I'LL CHECK IN
ON YOU LATER.
ELLIE:
I'M CALLING FROM
CAITLIN RYAN UNSCRIPTED.
COULD I TALK TO THE HEAD
OF YOUR YOUTH HOTLINE?
IT'S FINE. I'LL WAIT.
MAN:
AW MAN, WE DEAL
WITH EVERYTHING.
ABORTION, SUICIDE,
ALCOHOLICS,
SCHOOL WORK,
CUTTING, ANOREXIA.
WOW,
THAT MUST BE HARD.
MAN:
IT'S AMAZING TO ACTUALLY
BE ABLE TO HELP.
IT'S THE BEST THING
IN THE WORLD.
ELLIE:
HI DAD. SO YOU'RE OKAY?
YOU'VE MADE IT TO KABUL?
I'M SO RELIEVED.
HOW'S MOM?
SHE'S FINE.
TOTALLY FINE.
NO, SHE CAN'T MAKE IT
TO THE PHONE RIGHT NOW,
BUT I'LL TELL HER
YOU CALLED.
OKAY.
ME TOO. BYE.
CAITLIN:
HI ELLIE, GO THROUGH
ALL OF THEM, PLEASE.
ESPECIALLY THAT ONE.
OKAY. THANK YOU.
♪♪♪
I NEED A LATE SLIP,
PLEASE.
WOMAN:
NOTE?
I WAS AT MY CO-OP AND-
BOARD POLICY STATES THAT ALL
STUDENTS MUST PROVIDE A NOTE.
ELLIE:
IT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
PLEASE, CAN I JUST GO TO CLASS?
YOU WERE LATE TWICE LAST WEEK.
THREE TIMES THE WEEK BEFORE.
YOU COULD LOSE YOUR PLACEMENT
OVER THIS.
YOU'RE NOT SERIOUS?
LET ME GUESS,
YOUR LATEST EXPOSE,
THE HYGIENE OF DEGRASSI'S
BATHROOMS.
I'M RUNNING LATE.
EW. ELLIE, YOU'RE BLEEDING.
OH. YEAH.
I HIT MY ARM ON THE... THING.
WHAT?
ELLIE, I SAW.
I HIT MY ARM.
I'M GONNA FILE A COMPLAINT
WITH THE JANITOR.
BULL.
PARDON ME?
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT
TO YOURSELF?
DOES IT FEEL GOOD?
OR WHAT?
LOOK.
OKAY, I TOTALLY GET THAT YOU
DON'T WANT TO TALK TO ME BUT-
MY ARM'S FINE.
PAIGE:
I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT YOUR ARM!
YOU NEED TO TALK TO SOMEONE,
LIKE MISS SAUVE-
ALL I NEED IS FOR YOU
TO LEAVE ME ALONE,
LIKE YOU NORMALLY DO.
THIS HAS BEEN GOING ON
FOR TWO WEEKS.
BREAK THE LITTLE NERD'S
HEART ALREADY.
TERRI:
HIS HEART OR HIS NECK?
THERESE!
DID YOU LEAVE THIS ROSE?
I DON'T KNOW,
DID I?
STOP TALKING LIKE THAT,
IT'S DRIVING ME CRAZY!
IF THAT'S LIKE SOME
KIND OF TERRI SCRAPBOOK,
I'M CALLING THE POLICE.
SCRAPBOOK?
IT'S A SCIENCE REPORT.
TERRI:
ON WHAT?
TOBY:
E.S.P.
ASH TOLD ME YOU WERE PSYCHIC
OR SOMETHING,
BUT I'VE BEEN TESTING YOU
AND YOU FAILED, THERESE.
SO, YOU'RE NOT
MY SECRET ADMIRER?
YOU WISH.
SAUVE:
HEY, PAIGE.
GIVE ME A MINUTE AND WE'LL
TALK ABOUT YOUR FRIEND, OKAY?
ABOUT WHO?
ME?
LOOK, I DON'T CARE
IF YOU GET MAD.
WHAT YOU'RE DOING
IS DANGEROUS, OKAY?
IT'S SCARY.
YOU CAN'T HANDLE IT.
YOU HAVE TO TAKE AWAY
THE ONE THING THAT MATTERS.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT?
YOU WANT MY CO-OP JOB.
I DON'T CARE ABOUT
THE STUPID JOB!
YOU'RE HURTING YOURSELF.
THIS IS BEYOND ME.
I DON'T KNOW HOW
TO HELP YOU,
BUT SAUVE WILL.
I DON'T NEED HELP.
THEN SHOW ME YOUR ARM.
ELLIE:
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG WITH ME.
THEN SHOW ME YOUR ARM.
ELLIE.
ELLIE, PLEASE,
SHOW ME YOUR ARM.
OH, ELLIE...
IT'S OKAY.
UH, HI.
UM... YES,
YOU'VE CAUGHT ME.
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR HOURS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HOW SNEAKY YOU ARE.
WELL, FOR ONE,
A SECRET ADMIRER
IS A DEMANDING OCCUPATION.
AND TWO,
YOU'RE WORTH IT.
I DO HOPE LEAVING ROSES
WASN'T INTRUSIVE.
I'M A LITTLE SHY.
ME TOO.
AND I THINK IT'S SWEET.
RICK:
YOU HAD NO INKLING IT WAS ME?
TERRI:
NOPE. GUESS I'M NOT PSYCHIC.
SAUVE:
WELL, THAT'S ALL THE TIME
WE HAVE FOR TODAY.
SORRY.
I WASTED YOUR TIME.
NO.
YOU'LL TALK
WHEN YOU'RE READY.
BUT RECOGNIZING THAT YOU
NEED TO TALK, AND NOT CUT -
THAT'S A BIG FIRST STEP.
SO TOMORROW?
TOMORROW.