CRAIG:
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK IT IS?
MANNY:
I DON'T KNOW.
I HOPE IT'S A GIRL.
ANGIE'S ALWAYS
WANTED A SISTER.
I THINK SHE'D BE
THE BABY'S AUNT?
AT SEVEN?
IT'S SO WEIRD.
ELLIE:
I'M WALKING HERE.
SORRY.
CRAIG:
CAREFUL IN SCIENCE.
MANNY:
DON'T WORRY.
OKAY.
PAIGE:
SO, THAT LOOKED RATHER COZY.
I GATHER EVERYTHING WAS PEACHY,
WHEN YOU ASKED THE FAMOUS
CONDOM QUESTION?
MANNY:
NO.
WELL, SORT OF.
PAIGE:
UM... WE HAVE CHEER PRACTICE
THIS AFT-
MANNY:
I DON'T THINK-
I CAN'T.
ASHLEY:
HOW COULD HE DO THAT?
ELLIE:
I DON'T KNOW.
ASHLEY
YOU'RE NEVER GOING TO BELIEVE
WHAT ELLIE JUST TOLD ME.
ABOUT MANNY
AND CRAIG?
HE'S ACTUALLY GOING
OUT WITH HER.
IT MIGHT BE WORSE.
AS IF IT COULD BE.
WHAT WOULD YOU DO
IF I TOLD YOU,
I THINK CRAIG
GOT MANNY PREGNANT?
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Hear what I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
PERINO:
IN THE LINGO OF THE 1950S,
I THINK IT'S A NIFTY
KEEN-O PROJECT.
LIBERTY:
AND WE HAVE TO WORK
IN PAIRS?
PERINO:
SORRY, LIBERTY.
BUT YOU'LL BE RESEARCHING
1958 WITH-
JT:
PLEASE, ANYONE BUT ME,
ANYONE BUT ME, PLEASE?
PERINO:
WITH SEAN CAMERON.
JANE, YOU'LL BE TEAMING UP
WITH NICOLE FOR 1955...
GREAT.
BROWNNOSING-WHIPCRACKING-
LOSER-FREAK-VAN-ZANDT.
GREAT.
HELLS ANGEL-IN-TRAINING-
SLACKER-BACKSIDE-CAMERON.
I ALREADY HAD A MILK.
HAVE ANOTHER.
LOOK WHAT I FOUND.
PICK A NAME, OKAY?
DON'T LOOK.
NO.
ANYONE NAMED MAUDE WILL PICK
THEIR NOSE AND EAT GLUE.
ASHLEY:
WHAT ARE YOU READING,
GUYS?
SO YOU NEED A NAME?
HEY! EVERYBODY!
THESE TWO HAVE AN ANNOUNCEMENT
TO MAKE!
GUYS?
AH, THEY'RE TOO MODEST.
SO I'LL HELP SPREAD THE JOY.
THESE TWO IDIOTS...
ARE PREGNANT.
THAT'S RIGHT.
BECAUSE IS WAY TOO DIFFICULT
TO USE A CONDOM
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU SLEPT WITH HER.
TERRI:
MANNY'S SO LUCKY.
BABIES ARE BUNDLES OF LOVE.
I'M ALMOST JEALOUS.
PAIGE:
TER, YOU SHOULD BE FIXED
FOR EVEN THINKING THAT.
TERRI:
EXCUSE ME?
PAIGE:
I LIKE MANNY,
BUT THIS IS THE MOST LOSERISH
MOVE EVER.
SHE'S GONNA BE SOMEBODY'S MOM.
SHE'S TOTALLY RUINING HER LIFE,
AND PROBABLY HER FIGURE.
THAT'S A REALLY CUTE
COLOUR ON YOU, HON.
WHAT IS IT, WATERMELON?
(KNOCKING)
EMMA:
MANNY, I KNOW YOU'RE IN THERE.
I WISH YOU COULD'VE
TALKED TO ME.
YOU WEREN'T EXACTLY INTERESTED
IN HEARING ABOUT ME AND CRAIG.
MOM'S AT THE SALON LATE
TONIGHT,
I'M SITTING.
DO YOU WANT TO COME OVER?
I WISH I COULD.
BUT CRAIG-
BRING HIM IF YOU WANT.
LIBERTY:
HAVE A NICE TRIP?
MY GREAT-GRANDPA USES
THAT JOKE.
IT'S A CLASSIC!
SPEAKING OF CLASSICS,
THREE STOOGES FILM FESTIVAL
AT THE ROYALE TONIGHT.
MY TREAT?
JT:
I'M NOT IN THE MOOD.
WHY I OUGHTA...
OKAY, NEWSFLASH.
I DON'T WANT TO GO OUT
WITH YOU.
BECAUSE OF MANNY?
LOOK JT, SORRY YOU'RE UPSET,
BUT IT'S CLEARLY TIME
TO MOVE ON.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT,
LIBERTY?
THIS THREE YEAR CRUSH
YOU'VE HAD ON ME
IS GETTING A LITTLE BORING.
CRAIG:
HE'S SO GORGEOUS, HUH?
MANNY:
YEAH, HE'S LIKE AN ANGEL.
COME HERE.
EMMA:
SEE?
BABY MAUDE LOOKS LIKE
A BEAN.
(LAUGHING)
DON'T USE THAT NAME.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE
GOING TO GET THAT HUGE.
SO...
CAN WE, LIKE,
TRADE MOTHERS?
BECAUSE I CANNOT DEAL
WITH TELLING MINE.
MY MOM'S AMAZING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE SHE WENT
THROUGH EVERYTHING
YOU'RE GOING THROUGH
JUST TO HAVE ME.
(JACK CRIES)
EMMA:
UGH! WE'LL NEVER GET HIM
QUIET AGAIN.
CRAIG:
PIECE OF CAKE.
EMMA:
YEAH, RIGHT.
CRAIG:
WELL BABIES AREN'T EXACTLY
ROCKET SCIENCE.
(DOORBELL)
EMMA:
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE CARE OF THAT
LITTLE PIECE OF CAKE THEN, DAD?
(JACK CRIES)
YOUR BOOK, MADAME.
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
(JACK CRIES)
CRAIG:
EW. I'M NOT TOUCHING THAT.
MANNY:
YOU HAVE TO WIPE HIM!
CRAIG:
BUT IT'S GREEN!
CHRIS:
OOH, WHAT ARE YOU
LISTENING TO?
EMMA:
PARENTS IN TRAINING.
(JACK CRIES)
MANNY:
YOU SHOULDN'T HOLD HIM LIKE
THAT UNTIL HIS DIAPER IS-
CHRIS:
PARENTS IN BASIC TRAINING?
HI, HI BABY.
EMMA:
HOW'D IT GO?
CRAIG:
OH, GREAT. IT WAS GREAT.
MANNY:
THANK YOU.
EMMA:
GRAB A DIAPER,
I'LL SHOW YOU.
(JACK CRIES)
(EMMA BABY TALKS)
THERE WE GO...
YOU WANT THAT?
YOU WANT THIS, HONEY?
(JACK CRIES)
LIBERTY:
YOU GOT BOOKS FOR US?
SEAN:
DON'T LOOK SO SURPRISED.
WELL, 1958 WAS
THE FIRST YEAR
THEY STARTED IMPORTING
JAPANESE CARS.
THAT'S KIND OF COOL.
JT?
I'D RATHER NOT TALK ABOUT IT,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I'M FINE.
I GOT DUMPED LAST WEEK.
YEAH?
YEP.
AMY MET SOME GUY
AT MOTOCROSS.
HOPE SHE LIKES MUD.
I'M SORRY.
SEAN:
IT'S OKAY.
MOVING ON.
WHICH IS EXACTLY WHAT
YOU GOT TO DO WITH JT.
CRAIG:
HAVE YOU SEEN MANNY?
SPINNER:
NO.
AH, SEAT IS OPEN
THOUGH.
CAN I ASK YOU
A QUESTION, DUDE?
SURE.
SPINNER:
ARE YOU ON CRACK?
CRAIG:
WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
SPINNER:
DUDE, YOU GOT A GIRL PREGNANT!
AND YOU'RE JUST WALKING
AROUND LIKE LA, LA, LA...
I'M GONNA BE A DAD.
NO SCHLEBOGGLE.
NO, I'M NOT.
SPINNER:
WHERE IS YOU FUTURE, DUDE?
I MEAN, NO KEG PARTIES,
NO SPRING BREAK IN FLORIDA.
FOR ONCE I WANT TO DO
THE RIGHT THING, YOU KNOW?
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE
TO KEEP THE KID.
THERE ARE OTHER THINGS
YOU CAN DO.
THIS, THIS IS WHAT
I WANT TO DO, SPIN.
YOU DON'T GET IT.
NO, I DON'T...
AT ALL.
YOU'VE GOT A FAMILY,
ALL RIGHT?
I JUST, I STAY
AT SOME GUYS HOUSE.
BUT MANNY AND THE BABY...
THEY'RE MINE.
THEY'RE FOR ME.
(KNOCKING)
SPIKE:
MANNY. DEJA VU.
MANNY:
I COULDN'T CONCENTRATE
IN CLASS.
SPIKE:
MAKE YOURSELF A SPACE.
I WANT TO KNOW WHAT
BEING A SINGLE MOM
IS REALLY LIKE?
SPIKE
MAYBE JUGGLING SIX THINGS
ALL AT ONCE...
PLUS ALL SIX THINGS
ARE ON FIRE,
AND YOU'RE STANDING UP,
RIDING A BUS.
AND YOU CAN'T STOP FOR
AT LEAST TWELVE YEARS.
THAT SOUNDS HORRIBLE.
SPIKE:
BUT YOU GET STICKY
CANDY KISSES
AND CHRISTMAS ORNAMENTS MADE OUT
OF TOILET PAPER ROLLS.
GREAT.
LOTS OF WOMEN RAISE KIDS
ON THEIR OWN.
BUT DOING IT AT FOURTEEN
WAS EXTRA HARD.
ALL MY FRIENDS WENT OFF TO
COLLEGE, UNIVERSITY, EUROPE,
BUT I STAYED HOME.
I WANT TO STUDY FASHION.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE NEW YORK
OR PARIS.
THAT SOUNDS WONDERFUL.
MANNY:
BUT CRAIG WANTS ME TO KEEP IT.
SPIKE:
AND HE'S ALWAYS GONNA BE THERE?
ULTIMATELY,
THE RESPONSIBILITY IS YOURS.
SO THE DECISION IS YOURS,
NO ONE ELSE'S.
YOU MEAN...
I DON'T HAVE TO DO THIS
IF I DON'T WANT TO?
YOU LIKE?
UH...
JT:
WELL, WELL, WELL.
LET ME GUESS.
HALLOWEEN'S EARLY.
OR ARE YOU PLAYING RIZZO
IN THE DRAMA CLUB PRODUCTION
OF GREASE?
LIBERTY:
ACTUALLY, I WASN'T GOING FOR
A VENERATION OF THE 50s.
PERHAPS I WAS SUBCONSCIOUSLY
INSPIRED
BY SEAN'S MASTERLY WORK
ON OUR ASSIGNMENT.
WORK I LOOK FORWARD
TO CONTINUING.
WHAT IS GOING ON?
YOU'RE THE REBOUND CRUSH.
SEAN:
WHAT?
NO. NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
ON A CERTAIN LEVEL,
I'M RELIEVED.
BUT ON ANOTHER?
I FEEL YOUR PAIN.
THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
OUT OF THIS.
YOU'VE GOT TO BE BRUTAL.
THE WORD HINT IS NOT
IN LIBERTY'S VOCAB.
MOM, I DON'T-
I DON'T WANT A SANDWICH.
JULIETTA:
CHEESE AND TOMATO.
YOU LOVE IT.
WE CAN WAIT FOR DADDY?
MANNY:
NO, NO.
IT'S OKAY.
MOM, I JUST SAW
DR. JOHNSON AND...
MOM, I'M PREGNANT.
OKAY, I, I DON'T CARE
WHAT YOU SAY.
AND I DON'T CARE WHAT DAD SAYS,
OKAY?
MANUELLA.
MANNY:
I'M NOT A LITTLE GIRL
ANYMORE.
AND I'M NOT GOING AWAY
LIKE MARY HAD TO.
JULIETTA:
STOP, PLEASE.
IT'S A SHOCK.
I KNOW, AND I'M SORRY.
(CRYING)
MOM...
I'VE THOUGHT ABOUT IT.
AND I CAN'T GO AWAY.
I CAN'T BE PREGNANT.
I CAN'T BE,
I CAN' BE A MOM YET.
WHAT ELSE CAN I DO?
(CRYING)
MOMMY,
I'M SO SORRY...
JAY:
THAT NEON PLATE HOLDER
IS SWEET.
LIBERTY:
ALL YOUR FAVOURITES, SEAN.
WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE DITCH SCHOOL
AND GO CHILL
IN THE RAVINE?
LIBERTY.
I CAN GET US A FIVE-FINGER
DISCOUNT ON A PACK OF SMOKES.
A FIVE FINGER DISCOUNT?
(LAUGHING)
OH, I'M EDGY.
I'M ON FIRE.
LIBERTY, YOU'RE ABOUT AS
EDGY AS A BUTTER KNIFE.
I'M NOT INTERESTED IN YOU,
AND I NEVER WILL BE.
GOT IT?
JAY:
HEY MAN, YOU SHOULD GO FOR IT.
I MEAN, I HEAR SHE'S REALLY
GREAT... AT CHESS.
(JAY LAUGHS)
HEY EM,
YOUR MOM HOME?
SHE'S UPSTAIRS.
IT'S JACK'S BATH TIME.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
MY MOM WAS SO MUCH BETTER THAN
I EVER THOUGHT SHE'D BE.
WHAT A HUGE RELIEF.
YOU'RE NOT KIDDING.
I THOUGHT I WAS GOING TO WET
MY PANTS BEFORE I TOLD HER,
BUT THEN IT JUST CAME OUT.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
SHE'S EVEN DRIVING ME.
EMMA:
WHERE?
SHE'S DRIVING ME
TO THE CLINIC.
I'M GETTING AN ABORTION.
YOU CAN'T.
LOOK, I KNOW YOU THINK
IT'S WRONG.
AND YOUR CHILD WOULD TOO.
MANNY:
I'M JUST TRYING TO DO
THE RIGHT THING HERE...
FOR ME.
YOU KNOW, FOR EVERYONE,
I GUESS.
I WOULDN'T WANT TO GIVE A BABY
SOME CRAPPY LIFE
WITH A MOM WHO ISN'T READY.
YEAH. WELL AT LEAST
IT WOULD HAVE A LIFE!
WHAT ABOUT ADOPTION?
THERE ARE AGENCIES
WITH GREAT COUNSELLORS.
MANNY:
I KNOW, BUT I CAN'T GO
THROUGH GIVING BIRTH.
IT'S SO TERRIFYING.
AND THEN GOING TO SCHOOL HUGE,
AND EVERYONE KNOWS ABOUT IT.
YOU CAN GET THROUGH
ALL THAT.
MANNY:
I CAN'T.
I SWEAR.
I'M FOURTEEN.
EMMA, PLEASE.
PLEASE,
YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND.
MY MOM WILL BE DOWN
IN A MINUTE.
KWAN:
DOES ANYONE ELSE HAVE
AN EXAMPLE
OF THE SYMBOLISM
IN MOBY DICK?
ANYONE?
HOW ABOUT YOU MR. MASON?
SPINNER:
WELL, UM... THERE'S THE OCEAN.
KWAN:
OKAY. WHY DON'T YOU EXPAND
ON THAT FOR US.
SPINNER:
UM... OKAY,
WATER REPRESENTS LIFE.
IN MOBY DICK ISHMAEL,
HE GOES ON THE SHIP...
LOOKING FOR THE MEANING
OF LIFE.
(BELL RINGS)
THERE SHE IS!
DON'T CRAIG.
CRAIG:
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
I CAN'T DO THIS.
I THOUGHT I COULD,
BUT HAVING A BABY NOW
IT'S JUST...
YOU'RE NOT MAKING
ANY SENSE.
SOMEDAY, YOU'RE GONNA
BE A GREAT DAD.
AND SOMEDAY
I HOPE I'LL BE A MOM.
BUT NOW,
NOW ISN'T SOMEDAY YET.
NO.
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
MANNY, STOP!
NO, I WON'T LET YOU!
MANNY:
PLEASE!
CRAIG!
CRAIG:
EMMA, YOU BUTT OUT.
WHAT SHE'S DOING IS WRONG.
I AGREE WITH YOU, OKAY?
IF SHE WAS JUST SOME STRANGER,
I WOULD BE FURIOUS WITH HER.
BUT SHE'S MY FRIEND,
AND IT'S HER CHOICE.
BUT IT'S MY BABY.
EMMA:
AND MANNY'S BODY.
WHAT ABOUT HER?
MANNY:
I JUST, I JUST...
I CAN'T.
THANK YOU.
I'LL FINISH THE PROJECT
AND PUT YOUR NAME ON IT.
DON'T WORRY.
HEY...
LIBERTY:
I SHOULD'VE KNOWN.
YOU'RE JAMES DEAN,
I'M JUST SOME
SQUARE GIRL
THAT NOBODY EVER ASKS
TO THE SOCK HOP.
WHAT IF SOMEBODY DID
WANT TO ASK YOU OUT?
HA. NOBODY LIKES ME.
SOMEBODY DOES.
AND YOU HAVE TO FORGIVE ME
OR HE SAYS HE'S GONNA KNOCK
MY TEETH OUT.
YEAH, HE'S GOT THIS
SMART GIRL THING.
HE LIKED THE WAY YOU SAID
VENERATION AND MASTERLY.
COUNSELLOR:
ALL RIGHT THEN.
DO YOU HAVE ANY LAST QUESTIONS?
MANNY:
UM... IS-
WILL IT HURT?
MAYBE A LITTLE.
LIKE THE CRAMPS YOU HAVE
WHEN IT'S YOUR PERIOD.
AND IT'S SAFE?
SHE'LL BE OKAY?
COUNSELLOR:
AS THE CONSENT FORM STATES,
THERE IS SOME RISK OF
COMPLICATION.
BUT IT'S VERY LOW,
ABOUT THREE PERCENT.
SO, IF YOU'RE READY...
UM, HOW WILL I FEEL...
AFTER?
COUNSELLOR:
EVERYBODY FEELS DIFFERENTLY.
LOTS OF WOMEN CRY
A LITTLE.
MANY FEEL RELIEVED.
AS LONG AS YOU'RE SURE
OF YOUR DECISION, THEN...
I'LL BE OKAY.