SPINNER:
WHOA! WHO KNEW YOU COULD BUY
SO MUCH WITH ONLY A DOLLAR?
WHATEVER. MY SISTER
WILL LIKE IT
AND AT LEAST I DIDN'T SPEND
A HUNDRED BUCKS
ON SOME USED BLOUSE.
CRAIG:
HEY, IT WAS EIGHTY BUCKS
AND IT'S A ONE-OF-A-KIND
RAMONES TEE FROM '79, OKAY?
SPINNER:
OKAY.
WELL, ONE GIRLFRIEND DOWN,
ONE TO GO, RIGHT?
SPINNER, SHUT UP.
I'LL TAKE THIS ONE,
PLEASE.
YES, LORD STUD.
CAITLIN:
EXCUSE ME. I'M SORRY.
EXCUSE ME.
EXCUSE ME, PLEASE.
SPIKE!
CAITLIN!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
CAITLIN:
I HAD TO TALK TO YOU.
I WAS UP ALL NIGHT.
I MEAN,
I DIDN'T SLEEP AT ALL.
I WAS TOSSING AND TURNING-
ELF GIRL:
MA'AM, MA'AM, WE'RE ABOUT
TO TAKE THE PICTURE
SO ARE YOU GONNA...
LISTEN, ELF GIRL,
I'M HAVING A SERIOUS
DISCUSSION HERE.
SPIKE:
UH, SHE CAN BE IN THE PICTURE.
OKAY, WHAT'S THE
BIG EMERGENCY?
JOEY AND I...
WE KISSED ON HIS PORCH
LAST NIGHT.
(CAMERA CLICK)
ELF GIRL:
THANK YOU!
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
NEXT.
YOU AND JOEY WERE KISSING?
WHAT ABOUT SYDNEY?
I KNOW.
I MEAN, HE'S DATING
A WOMAN THAT IRONS HER SHEETS.
I MEAN,
THAT'S NOT RIGHT.
DO YOU STILL HAVE
FEELINGS FOR JOEY?
THAT'S CRAZY, RIGHT?
NEXT!
OKAY, YOU GOTTA THINK
THINGS THROUGH.
WRITE DOWN ALL YOUR
THOUGHTS IN A LETTER
AND WHEN YOU'RE CALMER,
RE-READ IT.
CAITLIN:
WHY?
BECAUSE THIS TIME OF YEAR
IS CRAZY ENOUGH AS IT IS.
YOU NEED TO KNOW FOR SURE,
BEFORE YOU DO ANYTHING.
IF YOU DO ANYTHING.
WHAT?
SPIKE:
YOU CAN'T SEE BABY JACK.
OOPS!
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Hear what I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(CLACK OF KEYS ON KEYBOARD)
CAITLIN:
(WHISTLING)
(GASPS)
OH!
THAT WAS SO STUPID.
WHY DID I DO THAT?
OH NO!
THIS IS SO BAD.
OKAY, OKAY,
THINK, THINK, THINK, THINK.
OKAY, MAYBE...
SYDNEY:
WHY DO YOU WAIT UNTIL THE
ONE RIGHT BEFORE CHRISTMAS?
JOEY:
BECAUSE I DON'T FEEL LIKE
SHOPPING IN JUNE.
CAITLIN:
HELP!
STUCK...
JOEY:
CAITLIN?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
CAITLIN:
IT'S MY PALM PILOT.
I CAN'T FIND IT EVER SINCE
I BABYSAT LAST NIGHT.
JOEY:
SO YOU BREAK-AND-ENTER?
WELL, IT'S, IT'S MY LIFE.
IT'S GOT EVERYTHING IN IT.
I MEAN, I COULDN'T WAIT
FOR YOU GUYS TO GET HOME.
WELL, I HAVEN'T SEEN IT.
HAVE YOU, SYD?
MAYBE IT'S UPSTAIRS!
MIGHT BE.
JOE, WHY DON'T YOU TAKE ANGE
UPSTAIRS AND LOOK FOR IT
AND CAITLIN AND I WILL
HUNT AROUND DOWN HERE.
OKAY.
COME ON, ANGE.
WHO KNEW JOEY'S HOUSE WAS
SO EASY TO BREAK INTO, HUH?
YEAH. WHO KNEW?
(GUITAR MUSIC)
I'M FREEZING.
OH, DO YOU WANT ME TO GET
YOU SOMETHING HOT TO DRINK?
PLEASE.
SOME HOT CHOCOLATE?
SYDNEY:
DON'T THINK IT'S HERE,
CAITLIN.
CAITLIN:
THAT'S SO WEIRD.
'CAUSE YOU KNOW WHAT'S
REALLY WEIRD, CAITLIN?
IS WALKING INTO THIS HOUSE,
AND SEEING YOU SUSPENDED
FROM THE KITCHEN WINDOW.
I TOLD YOU-
A LIE.
I'M NOT STUPID, OKAY?
I KNOW YOU STILL
HAVE FEELINGS FOR JOE
AND I GET IT.
HE'S AMAZING.
SYDNEY-
SYDNEY:
BUT HERE'S WHAT I ALSO KNOW.
JOE AND THIS FAMILY,
THEY NEED ME -
NOT SOME CHARMING, CLUTZY,
FUN-AND-GAMES BLAST
FROM THE PAST -
ME.
JOEY:
SYDNEY, I CAN'T FIND IT.
I'LL BE RIGHT UP.
HEY.
CRAIG, GIVE THAT TO ME.
CRAIG:
IT'S FOR JOEY.
I SAID GIVE IT TO ME!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
CAITLIN:
MERRY CHRISTMAS!
(CRIES)
(SCHOOL BELL)
SIMPSON:
OKAY GUYS, TODAY'S ASSEMBLY
IS GOING TO BE LOTS OF FUN.
BUT FIRST, IT'S THE ARCHIE
SIMPSON SEMI-ANNUAL
WORK STATION CLEAN-UP MARATHON!
YES, TERRI?
WE ALL PITCHED IN.
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
VARIOUS STUDENTS:
MERRY CHRISTMAS, SIR.
WE WERE GONNA GET YOU A REAL
ONE BUT THEY'RE NOT CHEAP.
WELL...
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT,
THIS IS A REAL WIG.
IT'S GREAT.
(IMITATING ELVIS)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
CLASS:
(LAUGHS AND CLAPS)
I'M THE LUCKIEST GUY
IN THE WORLD.
(KNOCKING)
CAITLIN:
YEAH, I KNOW, THE PARTY'S
STARTED, I'LL BE THERE-
JOEY.
NICE PARTY.
YEAH. WE'RE CLOSING
EARLY TODAY.
UH, YOU RAN OFF SO QUICKLY
YESTERDAY,
WE DIDN'T HAVE A CHANCE
TO TALK ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED.
WELL, THERE'S NOT MUCH
TO TALK ABOUT, RIGHT?
I MEAN...
IT'S JUST YOU AND ME
CAUGHT UP IN THE MOMENT.
RIGHT?
RIGHT.
TOMAS:
OKAY, CAITLIN. HEY.
SO, I PULLED SOME STRINGS,
CALLED IN SOME FAVOURS AND...
VOILA!
A SEAT ON CQJH'S
CORPORATE PLANE.
WE'RE TAKING OFF TONIGHT FOR
MONTREAL AT 8:00 P.M. SHARP.
(CHUCKLES)
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
CAITLIN:
OH, YOU'RE AWESOME.
THANK YOU.
TOMAS:
I WANT YOU TO REST,
AND NOT THINK ABOUT ANYTHING,
OKAY KIDDO?
THANKS.
TOMAS:
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
WELL, LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE OFF.
YOU WON'T BE SPENDING
CHRISTMAS ALONE AFTER ALL?
TOMAS?
YEAH, WELL, YOU NEVER KNOW.
SO YOU AND ME...
WE'RE OKAY, RIGHT?
WE'RE GREAT.
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
MANNY:
HEY. SO, READY FOR
YOUR BIG PERFORMANCE?
MMM-HMM.
YEAH, I AM.
BUT FIRST...
WHAT'RE WE DOING?
WELL, YOU'RE GOING
AWAY TOMORROW,
AND I MAY NOT BE ABLE TO SEE
YOU BEFORE CHRISTMAS,
SO...
(GASPS)
(EXCITED SQUEAL)
OH IT'S PERFECT.
THAT'S SO NICE.
OH AND UH-
OH!
OH CRAIG,
YOU SO GET ME.
THAT'S GOOD,
RIGHT?
YEAH, IT MEANS YOU REALLY
DO CARE ABOUT ME AFTER ALL.
OKAY, DEL ROSSI,
IT GOES HEATHER SINCLAIR'S
CELTIC WINTER SOLSTICE DANCE,
THEN YOUR ACCORDION RENDITION
OF GREENSLEEVES, GOT IT?
YES, MASTER.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M SO NERVOUS.
I MEAN, I HAVE PERFORMED
LIVE BEFORE.
WELL, I'M SURE YOU'RE
GONNA BE GREAT.
MAYBE IT'S 'CAUSE
I'M SINGING WITH CRAIG.
OKAY, UM, WELL, HOLD STILL
AND CLOSE YOUR EYES.
WELL, I GUESS YOU JUST HAVE
TO SEPARATE YOURSELF FROM HIM.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL, YOU KNOW,
YOUR EMOTIONS.
THEY SEEM TO BE GETTING
IN THE WAY.
JUST LET THEM GO.
ASHLEY:
THAT'S A PRETTY BRACELET.
WHERE'D YOU GET IT?
JUST A GUY.
YOU KNOW, A GUY
I'VE BEEN DATING AWHILE.
REALLY?
WHO?
JUST A GUY.
WAS IT CRAIG?
ASHLEY, I'M SORRY.
HE DIDN'T WANT ME
TO SAY ANYTHING.
'CAUSE HE KNEW YOU'D BE UPSET
ABOUT HIM MOVING ON SO QUICKLY.
MOVING ON?
WE'RE STILL TOGETHER.
TOBY:
AND WHILE WE ARE PLAYING
THE CANDLES ARE GLOWING BRIGHT
ONE FOR EACH NIGHT,
THEY SHED A SWEET LIGHT
TO REMIND US OF DAYS LONG AGO.
CRAIG:
DON'T WORRY.
WE'RE GONNA BE GREAT.
TOBY:
...THEY SHED A SWEET LIGHT
TO REMIND US OF DAYS LONG AGO.
AUDIENCE:
(APPLAUDS)
AND NOW FOR SOMETHING
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT,
WE HAVE ASHLEY AND CRAIG,
HERE TO SING
THEIR ORIGINAL SONG,
"I'LL SPEND CHRISTMAS
WITH YOU."
(APPLAUSE)
♪ YOU'RE EVERY PRESENT
I NEVER GOT... ♪
ASH? WE'RE ON.
(SLAP)
AUDIENCE:
(GASP)
JT:
UH, MAYBE THEY WON'T BE
SPENDING CHRISTMAS TOGETHER.
ANYWAYS, IT'S MY PLEASURE
TO INTRODUCE,
A LITTLE EARLIER THAN EXPECTED,
KENDRA MASON AND HER CHINESE
NEW YEAR DRAGON DANCE.
(CHINESE MUSIC AND DRUMS)
AUDIENCE:
(APPLAUDS)
CRAIG:
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
ME? WHAT AM I DOING?
WHAT ABOUT WHAT YOU DID?
WHAT?
MANNY? MANNY SANTOS!
HOW COULD YOU?
ASH-
I MEAN, YOU AND ME...
CRAIG...
KEEP YOUR HANDS OFF ME!
YOU TOLD HER.
NO.
NO, I DIDN'T.
WELL, THEN HOW DID
SHE FIND OUT?
BECAUSE YOU WERE STUPID,
CRAIG.
YOU DIDN'T THINK THAT
SHE'D FIND OUT ABOUT ME
AND YOU DIDN'T THINK THAT
I'D FIND OUT ABOUT YOUR LIES.
JOEY:
CRAIG.
CRAIG, WAIT UP!
HOLD UP!
I WRECKED EVERYTHING,
OKAY,
AND I DON'T NEED A LECTURE.
I DON'T WANT TO LECTURE YOU.
I JUST WANT TO KNOW
WHAT'S HAPPENING.
I CHEATED ON ASHLEY.
OH CRAIG,
I THOUGHT YOU GUYS-
JOEY, STOP.
STOP. I KNOW.
AND NOW THE OTHER GIRL
HATES MY GUTS, TOO.
SO MERRY CHRISTMAS.
DID I EVER TELL YOU
THAT CAITLIN AND I WERE
ENGAGED ONCE?
THOUGHT I HAD IT ALL.
BUT I WAS YOUNG AND STUPID,
AND I CHEATED ON HER
WITH A GIRL NAMED
TESSA CAMPANELLI.
CAITLIN FOUND OUT,
AND IT WAS ONE OF THE BIGGEST
REGRETS OF MY LIFE.
SO?
SO I KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE GOING THROUGH.
AND YOU'LL GET OVER IT.
I- I KNOW IT DOESN'T
FEEL THAT WAY NOW,
BUT TRUST ME,
YOU'LL BE OKAY.
WHAT, LIKE YOU'RE OKAY?
LIKE CAITLIN'S OKAY?
YOU GUYS NEVER GOT OVER
EACH OTHER, JOEY.
CAITLIN AND I
ARE FRIENDS NOW.
OH, COME ON!
I CAN SEE HOW
IT IS BETWEEN YOU GUYS.
EVEN SYDNEY CAN.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT?
AUDIENCE:
(LAUGHS)
JT:
OKAY, THAT'S THE END
OF OUR SHOW.
THANK YOU EVERYONE
FOR COMING OUT,
AND HAPPY HOLIDAYS,
ONE AND ALL!
SYDNEY:
HEY JOE, THERE YOU ARE.
DID YOU FIND CRAIG?
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
YEAH.
UH, SNAKE, CAN YOU WATCH
ANGIE FOR A SECOND?
SYDNEY, CAN I TALK TO YOU
OVER HERE, PLEASE?
SYDNEY:
SURE.
SYD, I FEEL STRANGE EVEN
BRINGING THIS UP,
BUT I HAVE TO.
JOE, YOU'RE MAKING ME
NERVOUS OVER HERE.
CRAIG SAID HE OVERHEARD YOU
TALKING TO CAITLIN YESTERDAY.
OH?
DID YOU SAY ANYTHING
TO MAKE HER GO AWAY?
YES.
AND WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
BECAUSE EVERY TIME
I TURN AROUND
THERE'S CAITLIN.
SHE'S SUPPOSED TO BE
YOUR EX.
SHE IS.
YOU SURE?
I'VE PUT A LOT INTO THIS,
JOE.
I WANT THIS TO WORK.
I NEED THIS TO WORK.
BECAUSE I LOVE YOU.
BUT YOU DON'T FEEL
THE SAME.
SYD-
THEN TELL ME
I'M YOUR FIRST CHOICE.
TELL ME YOU LOVE ME
MORE THAN CAITLIN.
RIGHT.
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
PILOT:
YOUR CELL PHONE SHOULD BE OFF.
CAITLIN:
OH, I KNOW.
PILOT:
MAKE IT QUICK.
CAITLIN:
I'M SORRY.
HELLO, CAITLIN RYAN.
JOEY:
JOEY?
I'M ON THE PLANE.
I CAN'T TALK.
JOEY:
JUST LOOK OUT YOUR WINDOW.
CAITLIN:
THEY GAVE ME THREE MINUTES.
THIS BETTER BE GOOD.
JOEY:
I DON'T WANT TO SPEND
CHRISTMAS WITHOUT YOU.
CAITLIN:
BUT SYDNEY...
IT'S NOT ABOUT SYDNEY.
THAT'S OVER.
IT'S ABOUT YOU AND ME.
UH, ANGIE?
LET'S GO SEE SANTA.
ANGELA:
MAYBE SANTA WILL HAVE SOME
PRESENTS FOR DADDY.
CRAIG:
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE HE'S
GETTING HIS CHRISTMAS PRESENT
EARLY THIS YEAR.
CAITLIN...
WHEN I BROKE YOUR HEART
ALL THOSE YEARS AGO,
I WAS SURE THAT
I'D LOST YOU FOREVER,
AND I MOVED ON.
AND YET HERE YOU ARE,
STANDING IN AN AIRPORT
AT CHRISTMAS...
WITH ME.
YEAH, WITH YOU.
I MOVED ON,
BUT I NEVER REALLY LEFT.
I GUESS I SHOULD GET MY STUFF
OFF THAT PLANE THEN, HUH?
MERRY CHRISTMAS.