♪♪♪
ASHLEY:
CRAIG.
I'M SORRY.
IT'S JUST-
I LOVE YOU.
WHAT?
WELL, DO YOU, YOU KNOW,
FEEL LIKE THAT?
NAH, NOT REALLY.
I THINK YOU'RE DUMB
AND YOU KIND OF SMELL.
OKAY, THAT WAS
SUPPOSED TO BE A JOKE.
I SHOULD GET BACK
TO MY HOMEWORK.
SPINNER'S LOADED ME UP
WITH MORE WORK
FOR PAIGE'S SURPRISE PARTY.
ASH, LOOK, OF COURSE I FEEL
LIKE YOU DO.
IT'S JUST-
HOLY, MAKEOUT HAIR.
I BETTER, UH-
ASH.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Hear what I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
CRAIG:
SO WHAT'S WITH ALL
THE UH, FLOWER POWER?
MARCO:
I DON'T KNOW,
SOME FUNDRAISER.
IT'S LOVE DAY.
CRAIG:
OF COURSE IT IS.
PAIGE:
SO ARE YOU SURE YOU DON'T
MIND HELPING MANNY AND I
MOVE THE NEW CHEER SUPPLIES,
HONEYBEE?
NO, I'LL BE RIGHT THERE,
PUMPKINBUNNY!
I THINK I NEED AN INSULIN SHOT.
DUDE, SHUT UP.
SHE LIKES IT.
SPINNER, WHEN YOU AND PAIGE
ARE LIKE...
LIKE IN THE MOMENT,
DOES SHE STOP YOU?
OR-
DUDE, WHAT DO YOU WANT,
A VIDEO?
THANKS, BUT NO.
MORE LIKE HELP.
OKAY. WELL, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO.
MARCO:
IT'S OKAY, CRAIG.
LOOKS LIKE SOMEBODY HERE
HASN'T MADE IT PAST
THIRD BASE HIMSELF.
LIKE YOU KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT
GETTING TO HOME PLATE.
YOU'RE TOO BUSY CHECKING OUT
THE BAT BOY.
SPIKE:
HONEY, WHY DON'T I JUST
DROP YOU BACK OFF AT HOME.
TAKE THE DAY OFF.
IT'S TOO LATE.
NO TIME TO FOR A SUB.
I'M SURE THE SCHOOL
CAN WORK SOMETHING OUT.
AT LEAST EAT SOMETHING TODAY,
OKAY?
WELL THERE'S AN ACTIVITY
WITH A POINT.
LUNCH, MEET THE TOILET.
TOILET, MEET MY LUNCH.
I KNOW THAT CHEMO IS REALLY
HARD, BUT-
SO DO YOU LOVE HER?
THAT'S A REALLY
BIG WORD.
MANNY:
HI, CRAIG!
UH, HI.
(WHISTLES)
MANNY'S JUST PUTTING IT
ALL OUT THERE, HUH?
NEVER NOTICED.
LIBERTY:
LAST CHANCE TO SEND
A ROSE-A-GRAM!
HEY PERFECT.
LOOK, SEND ASH ONE,
OKAY?
SHOW HER HOW YOU
REALLY FEEL.
OH COME ON, MAN,
A LITTLE ROMANCE...
IT'S NOT GOING
TO KILL YOU.
CHRIS:
TO MY BABYGIRL, MELANDA,
LOVE CHRIS.
HOMEROOM 9F.
ON ITS WAY. THANKS.
NEXT?
UH, ONE PLEASE?
OH, I DON'T NEED A CARD.
LIBERTY:
IF IT'S FOR A GIRL,
YOU NEED ONE.
CRAIG:
YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET'S MAKE IT A DOZEN.
SPINNER:
OKAY. SO WE'RE ALL SET
FOR PAIGE'S PARTY?
ASHLEY:
DON'T WORRY, SECRET AGENT PARTY
PLANNER BOYFRIEND.
I'M ON IT.
SPINNER:
OKAY. PARENTS STILL
LEAVING DODGE?
CHECK.
CURFEW EXTENDED?
I TRIED, OKAY?
BUT 1:00 IS THE BEST
I COULD GET.
MY MOM IS IN OVER-PROTECTIVE
MODE SINCE MY LAST PARTY.
GOOD MORNING, OLDEST FRIEND
IN THE WORLD
AND FABULOUS BOYFRIEND!
WHAT ON EARTH
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
NOTHING.
SIMPSON:
KENDRA, YOU HAVE THIRTY SECONDS
TO FINISH UP WITH THOSE.
YOU GUYS THINK YOU'RE GONNA
GET A ROSE?
AND CAN WE PLEASE BRING
THE DECIBEL LEVEL
A BIT LOWER IN HERE?
WHAT'S HIS DAMAGE?
HE HASN'T LOOKED GOOD LATELY.
OH.
OKAY UM, HOW CAN YOU LOOK SAD
WITH A DOZEN ROSES
IN YOUR GREEDY LAP?
"ASH, YOU ROCK.
X O CRAIG."
HEY.
SWEETIE,
DID YOU LIKE THE ROSE?
OH YEAH.
GREAT. THANKS.
DID YOU SEND ONE?
BECAUSE I THOUGHT MAYBE
KENDRA MADE A MISTAKE.
HERE.
PRETEND IT'S FROM ME.
YOU KNOW, CRAIG SENT
HIS GIRLFRIEND TWELVE.
SO HE'S A SUCKER.
OH YEAH, AND IT TURNS OUT
I CAN'T GO TO THAT PARTY
TOMORROW.
BOB'S HAVING GUYS OVER.
SO YOU KNOW...
BUT I THOUGHT WE COULD
GO TOGETHER-
JUST THE WAY IT IS,
BOO.
(SLAPS HER BUTTOCKS)
NICE.
HEY.
AND HOW IS MY FAVOURITE
PASTRY CHEF?
DON'T, OKAY.
I ASKED YOU HERE BECAUSE
I THINK WE SHOULD TALK.
EVERY GUYS FAVOURITE
WORDS.
SOMETIMES I DON'T THINK YOU
FEEL THE SAME WAY I DO -
ABOUT US.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I SENT YOU-
ROSES, I KNOW.
AND THEY WERE BEAUTIFUL,
THEY REALLY WERE, BUT-
WHAT? BUT WHAT?
LOOK, IT'S HARD FOR ME, ASH.
I KNOW.
AND THAT'S WHY I THINK WE
SHOULD TAKE A BIT OF A BREAK.
GO PRACTICE, OKAY?
I'LL SEE YOU AT SCHOOL.
(TRYING TO PLAY SOMETHING
RESEMBLING MUSIC)
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY, RINGO!
ONE STEADY BEAT THROUGHOUT
THE WHOLE SONG, OKAY?
OKAY.
HARDEST WORKING BAND
IN SHOW BUSINESS, FOLKS.
NO, DUDE, DUDE.
WE'VE BEEN JAMMING.
LISTEN. LISTEN.
ONE, TWO, THREE...
(PLAYING OUT OF TUNE)
CRAIG:
THAT'S THE WORST THING
I'VE EVER HEARD.
DUDE, IT WASN'T THAT BAD.
CRAIG:
BAD?
YOU GUYS SUCK.
JIMMY:
OKAY UM, HOW ABOUT WE GO
GRAB A BURGER,
WHILE CRAIGY HERE
HAS A LITTLE TIME OUT?
CRAIG:
SO SHE WANTS TO TAKE A BREAK.
MARCO:
OUCH.
CRAIG:
I DON'T GET IT, MAN.
I GOT HER ROSES,
LIKE YOU SAID...
MARCO:
NO, CASANOVA,
I SAID EXPRESS YOUR FEELINGS.
A DOZEN ROSES, MARCO.
MARCO:
SO?
LOOK, OKAY,
WHAT DID YOU WRITE HER
IN THE CARD?
OKAY, YOU ARE A GIRL.
LOOK, CRAIG,
YOU OBVIOUSLY LOVE ASH, OKAY?
SO JUST TELL HER ALREADY.
I MEAN IT'S STUPID IF-
IT'S NOT.
LOOK...
I DON'T WANT TO LOSE HER,
I JUST,
I CAN'T JUST TELL HER.
MARCO:
WELL, IF YOU DON'T THEN...
YOU'VE LOST HER ALREADY.
(STRUMS GUITAR)
CRAIG?
CRAIG:
NO LAUGHING, OKAY?
♪ SOMETHING 'BOUT
THE WAY YOU SHINE ♪
♪ WHEN THE LIGHTS GO OUT ♪
♪ I WANNA MAKE YOU MINE ♪
♪ SOMETHING ABOUT THE WAY
IT SEEMS ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALWAYS HERE ♪
♪ IN MY DREAMS ♪
♪ WHEN THERE IS NO ONE THERE ♪
♪ NO I'M NOT SCARED ♪
♪ BUT I'M IN LOVE ♪
♪ WITH YOU. ♪
THESE ARE SWEET.
YOU HAVE, YOU HAVE
VERY GOOD TASTE.
OH! WHAT DID I DO?
DO YOU WANT TO STAY OVER?
WHAT?
TONIGHT.
AFTER EVERYBODY LEAVES.
US, SOME MUSIC, MY BED.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
COMPLETELY.
LOOK OUT!
IT'S THE RETURN OF SNAKE'S
WICKED NACHO EXTRAVAGANZA!
HEAVY ON THE GUAC.
HONEY, COME ON,
YOU LOVE NACHOS.
ARE YOU INSANE,
CHRISTINE?
NACHOS?
YOU KNOW I'M NAUSEOUS.
I THOUGHT THEY
MIGHT BE TEMPTING.
YOU NEED TO KEEP UP
YOUR STRENGTH.
WHAT I NEED
IS PEACE AND QUIET.
(DOORBELL)
WHAT IS THIS,
GRAND CENTRAL STATION?
I'LL GET IT.
HEY, JOEY JEREMIAH,
THE ONE MAN CHEER-UP MACHINE
HAS ARRIVED.
PUT THIS ON, BUDDY.
NICE TRY, JOEY.
COME ON, EVERYBODY KNOWS
THAT SNAKE "STRIKE" SIMPSON
CAN'T RESIST A FEW FRAMES
OF BOWLING.
FILTHY BOWLING BALLS,
USED SHOES...
CAN'T YOU JUST SMELL IT?
IT'S NOT GOOD FOR MY CHEMO
COMPROMISED IMMUNITY
AND I DON'T FEEL LIKE-
SPIKE (ANGRY):
PUT THE SHIRT ON, ARCHIE!
YOU ARE NOT DEAD YET!
PUT THE DAMN SHIRT ON,
AND GO!
JOEY:
HEY, HE'S STILL GOT IT, FOLKS!
NEXT UP?
GUTTER BALL FOR SURE.
WHEELS:
SNAKE?
NEVER GUTTERS OUT.
JOEY?
HERE.
THANKS.
JIMMY:
SHE'S COMING!
SORRY, AM I KEEPING YOU
FROM SOMETHING?
TONIGHT...
AFTER EVERYBODY LEAVES?
GUESS WHO'S STAYING OVER.
SHUT UP.
YEAH, BELIEVE IT.
JUST A FEW HOURS...
EVERYBODY:
SURPRISE!
HOLY-
PAIGE:
A SURPRISE PARTY FOR ME?
YOU GUYS!
OH, THANK YOU.
SPINNER:
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
HEY!
WHAT ARE THEY DOING?
WHEELS
WOO! ALL RIGHT!
I HEARD YOU WERE SICK.
YOU DON'T LOOK IT.
NO.
I JUST LIKE SHAVING MY HEAD
AND EYEBROWS FOR KICKS.
I'VE SEEN STRANGER.
YOU DOIN' OKAY?
NO.
I'M STARTING TO WISH
IT WAS ALL JUST... OVER.
YEAH, I KNOW
HOW THAT FEELS.
NO YOU DON'T.
I'M SORRY
BUT THERE'S NO WAY YOU DO.
SNAKE, I WAS DRUNK,
I DROVE,
I KILLED A KID.
I THINK I KNOW WHAT WANTING
TO DIE FEELS LIKE.
WHAT DID YOU DO?
BECAUSE I HAVE NO IDEA
WHERE TO GO FROM HERE.
JUST FOUND SOMETHING
INSIDE ME
THAT WANTED TO KEEP GOING.
I'M REALLY SCARED,
WHEELS.
I CAN'T EVEN TELL MY WIFE.
BUT I'M REALLY SCARED.
YOU HAVE TO KEEP FIGHTING,
BUDDY.
JOEY:
OKAY, WE GOT
THREE SHIRLEY TEMPLES.
NO, I'M KIDDING.
HERE.
TO HEADS THAT MATCH
OUR BOWLING BALLS,
AND TO OLD FRIENDS.
WHEELS:
CHEERS
SIMPSON:
CHEERS.
(CHEERING)
ASHLEY:
YOU TOLD HIM?
IT'S JUST SPIN
BEING AN IDIOT.
WE HAVEN'T
EVEN HAD SEX YET,
AND YOU'RE GOING
AROUND BRAGGING.
WHOA, I TOLD ONE FRIEND.
THAT'S NOT EXACTLY
GOING AROUND.
I THOUGHT THIS MEANT
SOMETHING TO YOU.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
THIS WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
A PRIVATE THING -
BETWEEN US.
WELL I ONLY TOLD SPINNER
BECAUSE I WAS HAPPY.
I BET YOU WERE.
YOU CONNED ME INTO THINKING
I WANTED TO HAVE SEX WITH YOU
AND NOW YOU'RE-
WAIT. WAIT.
I CONNED YOU INTO IT?
WITH THAT STUPID LIE
OF A SONG.
THAT WASN'T A LIE.
WRONG.
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW TO SAY IT,
CRAIG,
BECAUSE YOU DON'T
REALLY LOVE ME.
JIMMY:
YO MAN, YOU OKAY?
(SLAMS DOOR)
MANNY:
CRAIG! HEY!
NOT NOW, MANNY.
OKAY?
WHAT HAPPENED?
I MESSED UP.
AGAIN AND AGAIN
AND AGAIN-
I'M SURE,
I'M SURE YOU DIDN'T.
TELL ASHLEY THAT.
YOU KNOW THAT SONG
YOU SANG TODAY?
YOU HEARD THAT?
IT WAS AMAZING.
AND IF IT WAS FOR ME?
I'D BE HAPPY
FOR MONTHS.
FOREVER.
ALL:
♪ EVERYBODY WANTS SOMETHING
THEY'LL NEVER GIVE UP ♪
♪ EVERYBODY WANTS SOMETHING ♪
♪ THEY'LL TAKE YOUR MONEY
AND NEVER GIVE UP ♪
♪ EVERYBODY WANTS SOMETHING
THEY'LL NEVER GIVE UP ♪
♪ EVERYBODY WANTS SOMETHING ♪
♪ THEY'LL TAKE YOUR MONEY
AND NEVER GIVE UP ♪
MANNY:
THIS IS SUPER COOL!
IT'S LIKE A VIDEO
OR SOMETHING!
IT'S NOT BAD.
YOU WROTE THAT SONG
RIGHT HERE?
WILL YOU PLAY IT
FOR ME?
PLEASE?
YEAH.
CRAIG,
YOU'RE THE BEST
AND-
AND WHAT?
AND IF ASH
DOESN'T SEE THAT,
THEN SHE DOESN'T
DESERVE YOU.
IT'S OKAY.
IT WAS THE BEST NIGHT
OF MY LIFE.
JUST TELL ME
WHAT HAPPENED ALREADY!
NO, I CAN'T, NOT YET.
BUT SOON.
HEY CRAIG!
I LEFT YOU, LIKE,
A ZILLION MESSAGES.
YOU MUST'VE BEEN
REALLY BUSY.
I MISSED YOU!
LOOK MANNY, I'M NOT
REALLY SURE WHAT HAPPENED-
ASHLEY:
HEY.
UM, MANNY, CAN I TALK
TO CRAIG FOR A MINUTE?
PAIGE AND I HAD A LONG TALK
AFTER YOU LEFT,
AND I'M SO SORRY.
I COMPLETELY OVER-REACTED.
ASHLEY-
ASHLEY:
LOOK, I KNOW WHAT YOU MEANT
ABOUT THIS NOT BEING EASY?
IF YOU'D BE WILLING TO GIVE ME
ONE MORE CHANCE...
YOU WANT ME BACK?
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I LOVE YOU.
(CRYING)
I LOVE YOU TOO.