SEAN:
HAVE YOU SEEN THIS?
THIS IS MC TERMINAL.
HE DRIVES UP ON STAGE
IN A HUMVEE.
IT'S SICK.
WE NEED THIS DISC.
IT'S FIFTY BUCKS.
IT'S AN IMPORT.
HOLD ON...
I'VE GOT DISCOUNT CARDS.
YOU'VE GOT DISCOUNT CARDS?
YEAH, TWO.
THEY GET ME 100% OFF
EVERYWHERE.
SECURITY GUARD 1:
YOU BOYS FORGET TO PAY
FOR SOMETHING?
WELL, WE WERE JUST ABOUT-
JAY:
GO!
SECURITY GUARD 1:
HEY! GET BACK HERE!
SECURITY GUARD 2:
HEY! HEY!
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Hear what I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
SEAN:
SO SOME STUPID RENT-A-COP
BANNED ME FROM THE MALL.
BIG DEAL.
TRACKER:
IT IS A BIG DEAL, SEAN,
BECAUSE THEY COULD'VE CALLED
THE REAL COPS.
SEAN:
I KNOW. I WAS LUCKY.
TRACKER:
YOU'VE BEEN OFF PROBATION FOR,
WHAT, LIKE A MONTH NOW?
THIS HOW YOU CELEBRATE?
BY PULLING A STUNT LIKE THIS?
THAT GUY UM, JAY.
HE TALKED YOU INTO DOING THIS?
WHAT?
NO. NO.
I KNOW GUYS LIKE HIM, SEAN,
ALL RIGHT?
HE'S BAD NEWS AND YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE TO CUT HIM LOOSE.
HE'S MY BEST FRIEND, OKAY? DAD.
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
TRACKER:
YEAH, HELLO?
HOLD ON ONE SECOND.
WHAT KIND OF BREAKFAST
IS THAT, HUH?
YEAH, GO AHEAD. I'M SORRY.
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
THE JOB WAS FILLED.
AND HOW MUCH IS IT?
ABSOLUTELY.
SO, JT...
GOT A DATE FOR
THE SEMI-FORMAL?
WHY?
ARE YOU PROPOSITIONING ME,
LIBERTY?
NO SUCH LUCK.
I'M VERY TAKEN.
JT:
OH WOW. THAT'S GOOD.
HE'S GETTING SOME PRACTICE
FOR THE MUG SHOT.
AS A MORE
EXPERIENCED DATER
I'D LIKE TO OFFER YOU
SOME WORDS OF ADVICE.
OH, THIS SHOULD BE GOOD.
LIBERTY:
(WHISPERING) ASK MANNY
TO THE SEMI-FORMAL.
JT:
YEAH, RIGHT.
SHE DOESN'T LIKE ME "THAT WAY".
WANNA BET?
INCREDIBLE.
REALLY, YOU'VE REWRITTEN
THE BOOK ON...
WHAT IS IT, AGAIN?
AN INTAKE MANIFOLD?
SORRY.
WHAT I KNOW ABOUT CARS
CAN BE WRITTEN
ON THE HEAD OF A PIN.
IF ONLY MR. EHL
AGREES WITH YOU.
ABOUT THE PROJECT, I MEAN.
IT'S WORTH 50%.
NO WONDER YOU SPEND
SO MUCH TIME ON IT.
HEY.
OTHER STUDENTS:
(MOCKING OOHS AND AHS)
WHAT'S HE SEE IN THAT
BLOODLESS FREAKBAG?
AMY, YOU BROKE UP WITH HIM.
P.A. ANNOUNCER:
WILL CAROL SIMONS PLEASE REPORT
OT THE OFFICE?
CAROL SIMONS,
PLEASE REPORT TO THE OFFICE.
JT:
TWO PLEASE.
TWO?
WELL, JT FINALLY GETS
A GIRL OF HIS OWN.
UNLESS THE OTHER
TICKET'S FOR TOBY.
NO. CLOSE THOUGH.
RADITCH, ACTUALLY.
WE REALLY HIT IT OFF.
JT THAT'S NOT RADITCH,
BUT A WAY BETTER CHOICE
IF YOU'RE LOOKING TO GET SOME.
WHAT?
WELL, YOU GOTTA FIGURE,
MANNY, WITH HER HISTORY.
SPINNER, HOW WOULD YOU LIKE IT
IF PEOPLE TALKED ABOUT
PAIGE LIKE THAT?
THEY DON'T.
'CAUSE PAIGE ISN'T A SLUT,
AND SHE DOESN'T GO AT IT
WITH OTHER PEOPLE'S BOYFRIENDS.
LOOK JT, I DIDN'T MEAN
TO GET ALL UP IN YOUR FRIES.
JUST...
DON'T FALL TOO HARD
FOR A GIRL LIKE MANNY.
SHE'S GOT A REPUTATION
FOR A REASON.
TRACKER:
THAT'S AWESOME.
HEY, I'M SEAN. I LIVE HERE.
TRACKER:
HEY BRO, COME HERE!
(ENTHUSIASTIC BEAR HUG)
CRAZY DAY, BRO.
DO REMEMBER THE OIL DRILLING
JOB OUT IN ALBERTA?
YEAH?
WELL, THE FIRST GUY,
HE LIKE BAILED
AT THE LAST SECOND.
WENDY:
SO TRACKER GOT IT!
ISN'T THAT AWESOME?
TRACKER:
PAYS BIG!
WE'RE GONNA BE LIVIN'
LIKE KINGS.
THEY ONLY PROBLEM IS,
WE GOTTA BE THERE
LIKE, YESTERDAY.
SO WE GOTTA GO.
EXAMS ARE STARTING.
I'D LOSE MY YEAR.
TRACKER:
YEAH, I KNOW.
I'M SORRY.
I WISH THERE WAS SOMETHING ELSE
WE COULD DO.
TRACKER,
I REPEATED GRADE SEVEN.
I'M NOT REPEATING GRADE NINE.
AND I CAN'T LEAVE YOU
HERE ALONE.
YOU EITHER COME
WITH US TO ALBERTA,
OR I COULD DROP YOU IN WASAGA.
SEAN:
NO! NO, I'M NOT LIVING
WITH MOM AND DAD!
TRACKER:
AND I'M NOT SITTIN' AROUND
WATCHING YOU END UP IN PRISON
WITH YOUR STUPID FRIEND,
ALL RIGHT?
SO THAT'S IT, END OF STORY.
ALBERTA, HERE WE COME!
TWO WEEKS WORTH.
HEY SEAN, WHAT'S UP?
NOTHIN'.
HEY. WHAT'S WRONG?
I'M MOVING TOMORROW TO ALBERTA.
ELLIE:
WHAT?
WE HAVE TO BREAK UP.
WHAT'S UP, DAWG?
YOU EVER GONNA FINISH
THAT THING?
LOOK WHAT YOU MADE ME DO!
MAYBE IF YOU WEREN'T
SUCH A GOOF.
HEY MAN, I WAS JOKING!
PSYCHO.
(SMASH)
SEAN!
ALL RIGHT,
TELL ME WHAT'S GOING ON.
MY BROTHER GOT A JOB
IN ALBERTA AND I'M MOVING...
TOMORROW.
THAT THREATENS THE SCHOOL YEAR.
SO? YOU THINK I CARE?
EHL:
YEAH.
YOU TOLD ME YOU WERE GONNA BE
THE FIRST PERSON IN YOUR FAMILY
TO GRADUATE HIGH SCHOOL.
YEAH, WELL, WHATEVER.
IT'S POINTLESS.
WHAT ABOUT STUDENT WELFARE?
YEAH, RIGHT.
'CAUSE THEY'RE LINING UP
TO GIVE GUYS LIKE ME MONEY.
EHL:
IF YOU KEEP DECENT GRADES
AND GET A TRUSTEE TO SIGN
ALL YOUR PAPERWORK.
MY OWN PARENTS AREN'T THERE
FOR ME, MAN.
THEN I WILL BE.
MR. EHL, YOU BARELY KNOW ME.
EHL:
SEAN.
I WAS THE FIRST PERSON
IN MY FAMILY TO GRADUATE.
I KNOW MORE THAN YOU THINK.
TRACKER:
COME ON, BRO,
GIVE ME A HAND HERE.
OKAY, I KNOW,
YOU DON'T WANT TO GO.
YOU DON'T WANT TO LEAVE
EVERYBODY.
THIS IS A GREAT OPPORTUNITY,
MAN.
I'M DOING YOU A FAVOUR.
IT'S A FRESH START.
I DON'T WANT A FRESH START.
I WANT TO STAY HERE,
RIGHT WHERE I AM.
I'M SORRY BUT YOU CAN'T.
SEAN:
ACTUALLY, I CAN.
I CAN COLLECT STUDENT WELFARE.
LIVE HERE.
I DON'T NEED YOU.
TRACKER:
OKAY.
RENT'S BEEN PAID TO THE END
OF THE MONTH ANYWAY.
FINISH YOUR YEAR.
BUT I'LL TELL YOU THIS,
YOU'RE GONNA BE BANGING ON MY
DOOR BEFORE YOU KNOW IT, BRO.
P.A. ANNOUNCER:
ATTENTION STUDENTS.
THE EXAM SCHEDULE WILL
BE POSTED NEXT WEEK.
PLEASE BE SURE TO CHECK
THE TIMES OF ALL YOUR...
ELLIE!
GUESS THIS IS IT.
I WAS THINKING...
LONG DISTANCE RELATIONSHIPS
ARE BRUTAL BUT-
WE DON'T HAVE
TO WORRY ABOUT THAT.
I LOVE HOW YOU
FIND THIS FUNNY.
YOU'RE STAYING?
YEAH!
ELLIE:
WOO!
(MUSIC BLARES FROM RADIO)
SO, MANNY.
THE SEMI-FORMAL DRAWS NIGH.
GOT A SARI PICKED OUT?
NO.
I'VE GOT MY SWEAT PANTS
AND ICE CREAM PICKED OUT
'CAUSE I'M NOT GOING.
I DISAGREE.
YOU CAN'T DISAGREE.
I'M NOT GOING.
BESIDES IT'S NOT LIKE
ANYONE WANTS ME THERE.
I KNOW SOMEONE WHO DOES.
OKAY, IT BETTER NOT JUST
BE YOU.
NEGATIVE.
IT'S A CERTAIN, SHALL WE SAY,
"FRIEND" OF YOURS.
YOU MEAN JT?
WELL, IS HE GONNA ASK ME?
YOU DIDN'T HEAR IT FROM ME.
SO THE GOVERNMENT PAYS YOU
FOR NOTHING?
I GOTTA GO TO SCHOOL,
GET GOOD GRADES,
AND I GOTTA GET BY ON WELFARE.
DOES THAT SOUND LIKE NOTHING?
JAY:
AW, POOR SEAN.
HE HAS IT SO HARD.
(LAUGHTER)
AMY:
SO, CAN I COME OVER SOMETIME?
YEAH. YEAH. YOU ALL CAN.
IT'S NOT JUST MY HOUSE,
IT'S OUR HOUSE.
♪♪♪
MR. CAMERON.
YOU SEEM TO BE MAKING LATENESS
A REGULAR HABIT.
I'M SORRY, MR. EHL.
IF IT'S ABOUT YOUR EXAM
I CAN DO IT IN MY SLEEP.
EHL:
IT'S NOT ABOUT MY EXAM.
IT'S ABOUT YOUR OTHER EXAMS.
AND YOUR PROJECT...
WORTH 50%, REMEMBER?
I'LL GET IT DONE.
I PROMISE.
DO YOU GIVE REFUNDS ON THESE?
TICKET SELLER:
NO. I DON'T THINK SO.
JT.
CAN I TALK TO YOU
FOR A SECOND?
NOW ISN'T A VERY
GOOD TIME.
UM, I HEARD YOU WERE
GOING TO ASK ME...
AND I WAS WAITING.
JT.
I SAW YOU WITH CRAIG.
AND?
WE HADN'T TALKED SINCE...
HE WAS JUST MAKING SURE
I WAS OKAY.
YEAH, RIGHT.
WHAT?
YOU THINK I WAS ABOUT TO GO OFF
AND HAVE SEX WITH HIM
BECAUSE I'M THAT EASY?
MANNY...
HE WAS THE ONE WHO WAS CHEATING
ON HIS GIRLFRIEND, OKAY?
BUT NO ONE EVER TALKS
ABOUT THAT, DO THEY?
AND SO THAT'S
OVER THERE.
JAY:
YO, SEAN.
MEET THE MONTREAL CREW.
BOY:
WHAT'S UP, MAN?
ARE YOU GONNA BE ABLE
TO WORK?
HAVE TO.
(MUSIC IS TURNED UP LOUDER)
(LAUGHTER)
TAKE IT EASY!
HEY, SEANNIE,
WANNA SEE MY WORLD-FAMOUS
AVRIL LAVIGNE IMPRESSION?
SURE.
YOU DON'T LIKE ME
ANYMORE.
AMY, YOU DUMPED ME.
ELLIE:
AND HE HAS A GIRLFRIEND.
RIGHT. AND WHAT ARE YOU?
SOME KIND OF BLOOD-SUCKING
VAMPIRE?
KEEP LEANING ON MY BOYFRIEND
AND YOU'LL FIND OUT.
ALEX:
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
KID 1:
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM, MAN?
KID 2:
NO MAN, WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
SEAN:
HEY!
OUTSIDE!
JAY!
JAY:
HEY, HEY, YOU HEARD HIM.
SEAN:
THANKS A LOT, JAY.
INVITING THE MONTREAL CREW.
I AM GONNA KICK HIS-
ALEX:
(SCREAMS)
KIDS:
OH MY GOD! WHAT WAS THAT?
IT'S AMY! SOMETHING'S REALLY,
REALLY WRONG!
I CAN'T WAKE HER UP.
OKAY, SOMEBODY CALL
AN AMBULANCE!
KID:
I'M ON IT.
THERE GOES YOUR
STUDENT WELFARE.
IT MIGHT BE ALCOHOL
POISONING.
JAY:
LOOK, MAYBE YOU'VE NEVER BEEN
TO A PARTY,
BUT THIS HAPPENS.
SHE'S GONNA BE FINE.
SEAN:
MAN, LOOK AT HER!
SHE IS NOT GONNA BE FINE!
HEY, IT WAS A GOOD JOB
CALLING US.
WELL, I HOPE YOU'RE HAPPY,
'CAUSE YOU GROUND THAT PARTY
RIGHT TO A HALT.
WHATEVER.
THE MONTREAL BOYS ARE BORED.
WHERE ARE WE MOVING THE PARTY?
NOWHERE.
IT'S OVER.
DID YOUR GIRLFRIEND
DECIDE THAT?
NO, SHE DIDN'T.
I DID.
PARTY'S OVER.
Y'KNOW, I THOUGHT YOU
WERE COOL.
YOU HAD ME FOOLED.
I KNOW THE FEELING.
JT:
MANNY!
LOOK I JUST WANTED
TO APOLOGIZE, OKAY?
I NEVER THOUGHT ANYTHING
BAD ABOUT YOU.
JT, SAVE IT.
JT:
WHEN I SAW YOU WITH CRAIG,
I THOUGHT YOU STILL LIKED HIM.
LOOK.
WHEN I ASKED YOU OUT
THE FIRST TIME
YOU BLEW ME OFF.
I JUST, I WAS AFRAID THAT
WAS GONNA HAPPEN AGAIN.
I WAS AN IDIOT, OKAY?
I ADMIT THAT.
BUT I'M ONLY GONNA
ASK YOU THIS ONCE.
I'VE GOT TWO TICKETS
TO THE SEMI-FORMAL.
WILL YOU GO WITH ME?
ALL RIGHT, I LIED.
I'M GONNA ASK YOU TWICE.
WILL YOU GO WITH ME?
I'M WARNING YOU,
I'M PREPARED TO WAIT.
MONTHS IF I HAVE TO.
WELL, MAYBE NOT MONTHS.
WE'LL MISS THE DANCE.
WAS THAT A YES?
I HEARD A YES.
CAN WE GET A RULING ON THAT?
JT, YOU'RE SUCH A JERK.
JT:
BUT YOU MEAN THAT IN THE BEST
POSSIBLE WAY, RIGHT?
P.A. ANNOUNCER:
ALL RIGHT, JUNIORS,
IT'S THAT TIME
YOU'VE BEEN WAITING FOR.
THIS YEAR'S SENIOR AUCTION
WILL BE HELD...
JAY:
AMY OKAY?
SHE WILL BE.
MR. EHL?
I HAVE THESE FORMS.
BRING IT HERE.
BEFORE YOU SIGN...
THERE'S SOMETHING
I SHOULD TELL YOU.
I HAD A PARTY.
AND...
IT SORTA GOT OUT OF HAND.
THE COPS WERE CALLED.
NO CHARGES OR ANYTHING BUT...
WELL, IF YOU DON'T WANT
TO BE MY TRUSTEE ANYMORE
I UNDERSTAND.
I HAVE A FEELING A LOT
OF PEOPLE
HAVE LET YOU DOWN,
SEAN.
I'M NOT GONNA ADD
MY NAME TO THAT LIST.
BUT I'M NOT GONNA SIGN...
UNTIL YOU CAN CONVINCE ME
THAT THE PARTYING IS OVER
AND THAT YOU'RE READY.
I AM.
I AM, MR. EHL.
THANK YOU.
DO YOU MIND IF I STICK AROUND?
I HAVE TO FINISH MY PROJECT.