SEAN:
I DON'T EVEN CARE.
(BELL RINGS)
KWAN:
TODAY WE START TO DISCUSS
ONE OF SHAKESPEARE'S
MOST QUOTABLE PLAYS,
JULIUS CAESAR.
WHO CAN SPEAK TO HIS THEMES?
SEAN?
HUH?
CAN YOU SPEAK TO THE PLAY'S
THEMES?
I MEAN, ARE THEY
STILL RELEVANT?
RELEVANT?
SHAKESPEARE'S SOME DEAD
OLD WHITE GUY
FROM 500 YEARS AGO.
WHAT DOES HE KNOW ABOUT
MY LIFE?
NOTHING.
KWAN:
OKAY.
ANYONE ELSE?
CHRIS.
CHRIS:
I LOVED IT.
IT WAS ALL ABOUT BETRAYAL,
LOYALTY, POWER, JEALOUSY.
KWAN:
HEAVY THEMES.
CHRIS:
YEAH.
I'M GLAD TO SEE YOU GOT
SOMETHING OUT OF THE PLAY.
WELL, UNLIKE MY MAN SLIM SHADY
OVER THERE,
I ACTUALLY READ IT.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Hear what I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
I'M GONNA MISS YOU
THIS WEEKEND.
NO FLIRTING WITH, YOU KNOW,
MONTREAL BOYS, OKAY?
I'M TAKING ELLIE
FOR SOME R'N'R.
SHE'S HAD A HARD TIME
AND SHE IS DEFINITELY NOT
SHOPPING FOR GUYS,
AND NEITHER AM I.
CAUSE I'VE GOT
THE CUTEST ONE THERE IS.
ELLIE:
I PACKED TOO MUCH.
I ALWAYS PACK TOO MUCH.
YOU NEED SOME HELP?
I'LL SEE YOU IN HOMEROOM.
CRAIG:
YEP.
MANNY:
CRAIG.
HEY, HOW ARE YOU?
UH, I'M GOOD. HOW ARE YOU?
I MISS YOU.
THERE'S REALLY NOT MUCH
TO MISS, MANNY.
I MEAN, WE ONLY HOOKED UP
ONCE.
THERE'S A RAVE TONIGHT,
SOUNDS SLAM.
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT WANNA...
JUST COME.
NO STRINGS, OKAY?
CHRIS: (ROBOTIC VOICE)
LADIES AND GENTLEMAN...
CHRIS SHARPE,
FOR THE BEAUTIFUL LADIES
AND THE BOYS.
(RAPS)
I GRADED YOUR TESTS.
SOME RESULTS WERE
DISAPPOINTING.
SOME WERE APPALLING.
AND SOME WERE QUITE IMPRESSIVE.
OKAY, YOU'VE GOT ANOTHER TEST
MONDAY.
SO PLEASE SOME OF YOU TAKE
THE TIME TO STUDY THIS WEEKEND.
WANNA SLEEP OVER TONIGHT?
HIT THE BOOKS?
YEAH.
MARCO, YOU IN?
HELP US STUDY?
MARCO:
UH, YEAH, SURE.
ANYTHING FOR MY TWO
FAVORITE GUYS.
WHAT?
HE CAN TOTALLY HELP US.
NO,
MARCO'S NOT THAT SMART.
WHAT?
HE'S QUITE SURPRISINGLY
STUPID.
AN IDIOT.
A MORON IF YOU WILL.
YOU'RE A MORON, OKAY,
AND HE'S COMING.
OKAY, MARCO MAY BE SMART.
BUT I MEAN, STUDYING ALL NIGHT?
SLEEPING OVER?
JIMMY:
YOUR FRIEND'S GAY.
STOP HATING AND JUST DEAL.
HEY, I DON'T HATE.
I DO DEAL.
OKAY, I'M TOTALLY FINE
WITH MARCO'S GAY-OSITY.
GOOD.
OKAY, CAUSE I FORGOT
TO TELL YOU?
YOU TWO ARE SHARING A ROOM,
LOVER BOY.
CHRIS:
EMMA, WHAT'S UP?
HEY, MANNY.
CHRIS, I REALLY LIKED
WHAT YOU SAID IN CLASS TODAY.
I NEVER THOUGHT OF
JULIUS CAESAR THAT WAY.
IT WAS SMART.
THANKS.
UH, LATER!
OH CHRIS SHARPE,
I DO DECLARE
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU!
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I COULD'VE SWORN I READ
SOMEONE'S NAME ON HERE.
WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT?
DJ JACOB SHARPE.
JACOB SHARPE?
CHRIS' COUSIN.
AND I HEAR HE ALWAYS LETS
CHRIS SPIN A SET.
EMMA:
I HAVE NO CHANCE WITH CHRIS.
IT'S LIKE HE'S ON A DIFFERENT
PLANET OR SOMETHING.
A COOL PLANET.
I'M ON PLANET
WHITE DORK.
HM. NOT TONIGHT.
YOU LOOK HOT.
EMMA:
I CAN'T WEAR THIS.
EVERYONE IS GOING TO
STARE AT ME.
MANNY:
INCLUDING HIM,
AND THAT'S GOOD.
SEE YOU GOT TO DO WHATEVER
IT TAKES.
WHEN DID YOU BECOME
AN EXPERT ON ALL THIS?
MANNY:
I'M NOT AN EXPERT.
I JUST KNOW.
WHATEVER IT TAKES?
MANNY:
YES.
NOW STOP TALKING BEFORE
I PUT LIP-GLOSS ON YOUR TEETH.
OKAY, RUB.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY. LET'S GO.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
EXPLAINING THE BOOTYLICIOUS
MAKEOVER TO MY MOM
IS SO NOT WORTH IT.
FINE BY ME.
SPINNER:
JIMMY.
NEXT TIME,
REGULAR SPRAY CHEESE -
NOT 5-ALARM JALAPENO.
UH, DUDE, YOU TOOK MY SPOT.
MARCO:
UH, SPIN, THE MIDDLE CUSHION
DOESN'T HAVE TEETH, BUD.
IT'S NOT GONNA BITE.
SPINNER:
YEAH.
MARCO:
OKAY, SO WHERE WERE WE?
POLYNOMIALS, RIGHT?
JIMMY:
YOU GUYS MIND
IF I PUT ON THE TUBE?
I LIKE A LITTLE BACKGROUND
NOISE.
AH, THE WONDERS OF SATELLITE.
WHOA!
DIDN'T KNOW YOU COULD FIT THAT
MANY PEOPLE ON A POOL TABLE.
HEY!
NO, SPIN.
NOT EVERYONE HERE WANTS
TO WATCH THAT.
KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
MARCO:
NO, NO.
SEEING NAKED LADIES
DOESN'T BURN MY EYES OUT, NO.
BESIDES, I WASN'T LOOKING
AT THEM.
THEN WHAT WERE YOU LOOKING AT?
THE DRAPES.
SPIN, THE DRAPES.
HE WAS LOOKING AT THE DUDES,
YOU IDIOT.
UGH.
OKAY, CAN WE
GET BACK TO WORK?
I KIND OF CARE ABOUT
MY STUDIES.
♪♪♪
OKAY, ONE MORE THING...
NO TALKING ABOUT
THE ENVIRONMENT.
THE ENVIRONMENT
IS NOT SEXY.
DO NOT TALK ABOUT IT.
OKAY, I GOT IT.
MANNY:
HE'S HERE
AND HE'S WATCHING YOU.
GO! DON'T BE CHICKEN.
JOEY:
CRAIG.
HELLO? CRAIG MANNING?
HM? SORRY?
SYDNEY:
IF THIS MOVIE IS BORING YOU,
WE CAN CHANGE IT.
NAH, NO, IT'S FINE.
IT'S FINE. IT'S GOOD.
HEY LOOK, CRAIG I'M NOT TRYING
TO BE NOSEY OR ANYTHING,
AND BOY, WE SURE DO ENJOY
YOUR COMPANY,
BUT WHAT ARE YOU DOING HOME
ON A FRIDAY NIGHT?
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE I SHOULD,
MAYBE I SHOULD GO TO JIMMY'S.
IF YOU WANT.
OKAY, OKAY.
JIMMY'S.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
AND NOW WE HAVE THE PLACE
TO OURSELVES.
OKAY,
SO X IS THE VARIABLE?
FOR THE TENTH TIME,
SPINNER, YES.
OKAY?
JAMES?
I'M TRYING TO STUDY.
SO AM I.
I'M STUDYING HER.
MARCO:
OKAY, LOOK.
SPIN, YOU'VE WORKED HARD,
OKAY? SO JUST RELAX.
SPINNER:
UH, SPRAY CHEESE ANYONE?
JIMMY:
GENTLEMEN,
YOU'RE LOOKING AT THE FUTURE
MRS. JIMMY BROOKS.
WHAT? HER, MAN?
SHE'S COMPLETELY FAKE.
OKAY, NOW LOOK AT HIM
RIGHT OVER THERE.
HE'S VERY REAL.
(COUGHS)
SPIN,
ARE YOU OKAY?
I THINK HE'S CHOKING.
MARCO:
MAN, OKAY.
OKAY, I'LL HELP YOU.
COME HERE.
OKAY, HOLD STILL.
LOOK, I KNOW THE HEIM-
I KNOW THE HEIMLICH,
SPINNER!
I LEARNED IT IN FIRST AID.
WHAT ARE YOU-
HOLD STILL.
JUST HOLD STILL.
COME HERE. OKAY.
I GOTCHA...
(GRUNTS WITH EFFORT)
OKAY.
SPINNER:
(SPITS AND COUGHS)
THAT WAS NEW CARPET.
CHRIS:
EMMA, I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE COMING.
ME MISS A RAVE?
SO I HEARD YOU MIGHT
BE SPINNING TONIGHT?
YEAH, IF JACOB WOULD
STOP BEING SO GREEDY.
JACOB:
GREEDY?
WHO'RE YOU CALLING GREEDY?
GET OVER HERE.
COME UP, EMMA.
AH YEAH, IT'S YOUR BOY
C-DAWG IN THE HOUSE!
(CHEERING)
♪♪♪
(CROWD IS UPSET)
EMMA.
YOU TURNED OFF THE POWER!
CHRIS, I AM SO SORRY.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
MELANDA:
CHRIS!
MELANDA.
THIS IS EMMA,
MY FRIEND.
EMMA, THIS IS MELANDA.
MY GIRLFRIEND.
EMMA:
MANNY, I WANT TO GO NOW!
MANNY:
WHAT?
EMMA:
LOOK!
MANNY:
I DIDN'T KNOW
HE HAD A GIRLFRIEND.
ME NEITHER.
SO CAN WE PLEASE GO?
IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
THEY'RE GONNA LAST LONG.
SO HERE'S YOUR CHANCE.
YOU WAIT FOR
THE FIGHT TO END.
CHRIS IS HURT AND HE NEEDS
A SHOULDER TO CRY ON...
THERE YOU ARE.
OKAY, THAT'S TOTALLY EVIL.
IT MAY BE EVIL
BUT IT'S EFFECTIVE.
I CAN'T DO THAT,
IT'S NOT RIGHT.
YES, IT IS.
AND YES, YOU CAN.
WHATEVER IT TAKES,
RIGHT?
I'LL GO GET US
SOME WATER.
HEY!
HEY! YOU CAME!
SURE.
UH... YOU WANT TO DANCE MAYBE?
WHY NOT?
MARCO:
ALL RIGHT, GUYS, I'M WIPED.
I'M GONNA GO BRUSH MY TEETH.
JIMMY:
I GUESS I'LL GO GET
THE SLEEPING BAGS.
I NEED TO SLEEP
IN YOUR BED TONIGHT.
SPIN, I LIKE YOU,
BUT NOT THAT WAY.
STOP, I'M NOT JOKING, OKAY?
I CAN'T SLEEP OUT HERE
WITH HIM.
MARCO DOESN'T LIKE YOU.
YOU SAW HIM CHASING ME
AROUND BEFORE.
HE JUST WANTED TO WRAP
HIS HANDS AROUND ME.
LOOK, SERIOUSLY,
WHAT YOU NEED IS SOME SLEEP.
CAUSE IT'S OBVIOUS YOU'RE
NOT GETTING ENOUGH OXYGEN
TO YOUR BRAIN.
JIMMY.
THOUGHT YOU MIGHT BE
THIRSTY.
I WAS. I AM.
THANK YOU.
CHRIS, I'M SORRY.
FOR WHAT?
FOR UNPLUGGING
THE SOUND SYSTEM.
GETTING YOU IN TROUBLE
WITH MELANDA.
IT'S OKAY.
I'M ALWAYS IN TROUBLE.
DO YOU WANT TO TALK?
LET'S FIND SOMEWHERE QUIET.
YEAH.
SO HOW'S THE ENVIRONMENTAL
CLUB GOING?
YEAH, IT'S...
LET'S NOT TALK ABOUT THAT.
LET'S TALK ABOUT YOU.
DJING,
IT'S ALL ABOUT THE BEAT.
LET ME SHOW YOU.
CLOSE YOUR EYES.
BOP BOP K-K, BOP BOP K-K,
BOP BOP K-K...
KINDA LIKE THE BEATING
OF THE HEART.
I SHOULD GO.
DON'T.
PLEASE.
I HAVE A GIRLFRIEND.
MANNY:
IT'S OKAY.
I CAN KEEP A SECRET.
I CAN'T.
I'M SORRY,
I SHOULDN'T HAVE.
IT'S NOT YOU.
IT'S ME.
I'M SORRY, I WISH THINGS
WERE DIFFERENT BUT-
SPINNER:
I KNEW IT!
I KNEW YOU
WERE GONNA TOUCH ME.
WHAT?
MAN, IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
OH YEAH, AND WHAT ABOUT BEFORE,
WHEN YOU CHASED ME AROUND
AND TRIED-
I WAS TRYING TO SAVE YOU
FROM CHOKING.
IT'S CALLED THE HEIMLICH?
SPINNER:
NO, IT'S CALLED YOU TRYING
TO GET A CHEAP FEEL.
DUDE, ADMIT IT.
YOU HAVE A MAN-CRUSH.
ON YOU?
YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
I MEAN, YOUR HAIR?
IT'S SO LAST YEAR, BUDDY.
YOUR SHOES, THEY NEVER MATCH
ANYTHING,
AND THEY SMELL.
AND TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
YOU'RE NOT EVEN THAT CUTE.
I'LL TAKE THE BATHTUB.
EMMA!
I'M, I'M SORRY, I THOUGHT YOU
WOULDN'T BE BACK TILL LATE.
CHRIS HAS A GIRLFRIEND,
REMEMBER?
CRAIG:
I GOTTA GO.
EMMA:
YEAH, I THINK YOU'D BETTER.
YOU ABANDONED ME AT THE RAVE,
SO YOU COULD COME HERE
WITH CRAIG AND-
I'M SORRY, OKAY?
EMMA-
I SAID I WAS SORRY, OKAY?
QUIET. YOU'LL WAKE UP
MY PARENTS.
SPINNER:
HEY.
MARCO:
SO UH...
YOU READY FOR THAT TEST?
UH YEAH.
I KNOW IT PRETTY GOOD.
THANKS FOR YOUR HELP.
YEAH, YOU'RE WELCOME.
OKAY SPIN, LOOK...
JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE
A GUY,
IT DOESN'T AUTOMATICALLY MEAN
I'M ATTRACTED TO YOU.
I MEAN, DO YOU LIKE
EVERY GIRL THAT COMES ALONG?
IF THEY'RE HOT.
WELL, YOU'RE NOT.
YEAH, YEAH, BUT
YOU'RE OFF BASE THERE.
SEE LOOK, LET'S AGREE
TO DISAGREE.
ARMSTRONG:
GENTLEMEN. TEST STARTS
IN A FEW MINUTES...
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
YOU'RE UPSET ABOUT THIS.
DUDE, I'M NOT UPSET.
COME ON, IT'S JUST REALLY
OBVIOUS YOU HAVE BAD TASTE.
I FEEL SORRY FOR YOU.
I REALLY DO.
MANNY:
EMMA.
ARE YOU GONNA
TALK TO ME? EVER?
I EXPLAINED ALREADY,
I THOUGHT YOU WEREN'T COMING
HOME TILL LATE.
DON'T YOU FEEL BAD
ABOUT WHAT YOU DID?
OR FEEL FOR ASHLEY?
IF CRAIG REALLY
LOVES HER...
THEN WHY DOES HE KEEP
COMING BACK TO ME?
KEEP COMING BACK-
MANNY, DON'T TELL ME.
YOU KNOW, YOU KNEW CHRIS
HAD A GIRLFRIEND.
WHICH IS WHY I CAME HOME.
I THINK YOU CHICKENED OUT.
I MADE THE RIGHT CHOICE
AND IT'S SOMETHING YOU
SHOULD THINK ABOUT.
YOU WANT ME TO MAKE A CHOICE?
FINE. I CHOOSE TO STOP HANGING
OUT WITH YOU.
YOU DON'T WANT TO BE FRIENDS?
NOT WITH A STUCK-UP,
PRUDE PRINCESS.
GOOD.
'CAUSE I DON'T WANT TO BE
FRIENDS WITH THE SCHOOL SLUT.