HATZILAKOS:
SO YOUR EXAM WILL MAINLY FOCUS
ON SECOND TERM.
BUT MUCH OF WHAT YOU LEARNED
LAST FALL
HAS INFLUENCED WHAT
WE'VE COVERED SINCE AND-
WAIT.
SO WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
WE HAVE TO STUDY BOTH TERMS?
HATZILAKOS:
THAT'S USUALLY HOW IT WORKS,
GAVIN.
SO WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO-
MORE WORK?
HATZILAKOS:
IT'S A COMPREHENSION
ASSIGNMENT.
USING MOLECULAR MODELS,
I'D LIKE YOU TO ILLUSTRATE
THE STRUCTURE OF THREE SIMPLE
MOLECULES BY NEXT WEEK.
(MURMURS FROM THE CLASS)
HATZILAKOS:
WELCOME TO THE REAL WORLD,
GUYS.
OH AND PAIGE, CAN YOU MAKE SURE
THAT ASHLEY GETS THIS?
SEEMS LIKE SHE'S SICK AGAIN.
OKAY, I CAN'T HANDLE THIS.
IT'S SO UNFAIR.
HATZILAKOS WANTS US TO LIVE
IN THE REAL WORLD?
THEN I SAY WE DO JUST THAT.
TOMORROW...
WE'RE TAKING THE DAY OFF.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Hear what I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
DYLAN:
OKAY, YOU KNOW THIS CAR MEANS
EVERYTHING TO ME, RIGHT?
PAIGE:
YES, DYLAN.
THIS CAR MEANS MORE
TO YOU THAN I DO.
OKAY, NOW THIS GOES
TO MISS SMITH,
EXCUSING ME FROM ALL CLASSES
TODAY.
OOH, THE OLD "FORGING YOUR
MOM'S SIGNATURE", HUH?
NICE.
JUST MAKE SURE SHE GETS IT.
AND YOU MAKE SURE YOU RETURN
THIS CAR, OKAY?
UNDAMAGED...
WITH A FULL TANK.
BUT IT'S ONLY AT A QUARTER-
HAVE FUN.
MRS. MASON:
HERE.
NOW I KNOW HAVING A THERMOMETER
IN YOUR MOUTH IS UNCOMFORTABLE,
BUT YOU GOTTA LEAVE IT THERE,
OKAY?
OKAY, MOM. I LOVE YOU.
OH.
JUST WAIT TILL I TELL MOM.
OH YEAH, GO RIGHT AHEAD,
MISS I-DON'T-HAVE-ANY-EVIDENCE.
KENDRA:
MOM, HE'S FAKING!
WITH A TEMPERATURE OF 101?
I DON'T THINK SO.
OH THE PAIN.
KENDRA:
PAIN?
I'M THE ONE IN PAIN.
MY ARM!
MRS. MASON:
KENDRA, THIS ISN'T
A COMPETITION.
NOW I'LL BE HOME BY FIVE.
YOU BE SURE TO DRINK
LOTS OF FLUIDS
AND CALL ME AT WORK
IF YOU NEED ANYTHING.
KENDRA:
BUT...
PAIGE?
THE HEN HAS FLOWN THE COUPE.
NICE.
SIMPSON:
IN CONSTRUCTING
THIS SEQUEL QUERY
WE NEED TO USE A FILTER AS IN...
"WHERE AMOUNT IS GREATER
THAN 100."
NO, THAT'S NOT RIGHT.
SO, THE SEMI-FORMAL COMING UP...
JT, CAN WE TALK LATER?
UH, THAT'D BE A NO.
I WAS THINKING ABOUT
ASKING MANNY,
BUT, I MEAN, I KNOW SHE'S BEEN
THROUGH SOME TOUGH TIMES LATELY-
SIMPSON:
TIME'S GONNA GET A WHOLE
LOT TOUGHER
IF YOU DON'T STOP TALKING.
FOR AGGREGATE FUNCTIONS
YOU NEED TO USE
THE... HAVING CLAUSE.
ACTUALLY...
WE COULD JUST GO
AS FRIENDS.
JT! LATER!
HI. WHAT ARE YOU DOING
AT LUNCH?
DEFRAGGING THE M.I. LAB?
THANKS.
AND EMMA, SO GLAD YOU CAN
HELP OUT.
ASHLEY: (DEPRESSED)
♪ I'M LOST IN A VOID
OF ETERNITY, ♪
♪ THE EYE OF THE STORM,
THE DEPTH OF THE SEA. ♪
♪ A BLACK HOLE RIPS
ME FROM INSIDE OUT, ♪
♪ GRAVITY, ENDING ME. ♪
KATE:
YOU DON'T LOOK SICK TO ME,
KIDDO.
YOU KNOW, I'VE BEEN REALLY
PATIENT,
BUT THE END OF THE YEAR'S
COMING UP AND YOU GOT EXAMS.
AND I'LL DO FINE.
I'VE BEEN DOING
ALL THE HOMEWORK.
I'LL GO TO SCHOOL MONDAY, OKAY?
BUT NOT TODAY. PLEASE.
KATE:
I'M GONNA BE SHOWING HOUSES
ALL DAY
BUT I'LL BE HOME FOR DINNER,
OKAY?
WHAT WE TALKED ABOUT
THE OTHER DAY?
I THINK IT MIGHT BE A GOOD
THING.
SPINNER:
HERE WE ARE.
FRESH AIR, HOT-ROD CONVERTIBLE,
THE WORLD IS OUR OYSTER.
WHAT DO YOU WANNA DO?
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
ANYTHING! BOWLING, THE MALL.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
MINI GOLF!
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
PAIGE MEE-HAIL-SHOOK'S
TELEPHONE. (USING HEAVY ACCENT)
WHAT'S WITH THE WEIRD ACCENT?
PAIGE:
JUST PRETENDING TO BE MY MOM.
WHY? WHERE ARE YOU?
DYLAN'S CAR.
SKIPPING WITH SPIN.
IN CASE YOU WERE AT THE SCHOOL.
WELL, I'M NOT.
AND I'M ACTUALLY I WAS
JUST CALLING
FOR YESTERDAY'S HOMEWORK.
PAIGE:
YEAH, I WAS JUST ABOUT
TO DROP IT BY.
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING TODAY?
ASHLEY:
JUST FEELING SORRY FOR MYSELF,
WHY?
(WHISPERS) NO, NO.
WELL MISERY LOVES COMPANY, HON.
SO GET DRESSED.
WE'LL BE THERE IN FIVE.
HON, WE HAVE A MAJOR
METROPOLITAN AREA
AT OUR DISPOSAL HERE.
YEAH, WITH AT LEAST 20
MINI-PUTT COURSES TO EXPLORE.
ASHLEY:
GO AWAY.
PAIGE:
SPIN, NOT HELPING.
ASH? GET UP.
OKAY. LET'S THINK OF DYLAN'S
CAR AS A GENIE,
ONE THAT CAN GRANT US
THREE WISHES.
SPIN.
I WISH WE COULD GO EAT LUNCH
AT A NICE RESTAURANT
WITH MY HONEY
AND MY OLDEST FRIEND.
I WISH WE COULD
GO PLAY MINI-GOLF.
FINE.
ASH, ONE WISH TO GO.
(SIGHS)
I WISH WE COULD GO VISIT TERRI.
ASHLEY!
I'M SO GLAD YOU COULD COME.
YEAH, FINALLY, HUH?
WELL, YOU LOOK GREAT.
I'M FEELING SO MUCH BETTER,
OTHER THAN THE OCCASIONAL
HEADACHE
FROM HITTING THE ROCK
AND THE SURGERY.
HERE TO CHANGE YOUR BANDAGE.
I UM, I NEED SOME AIR.
ASHLEY?
ANNOUNCER ON P.A.:
A REMINDER TO THE DANCE
COMMITTEE
THAT WE WILL MEET AFTER
SCHOOL TODAY-
ALEX, I NEED SOME TIME
WITH THAT MACHINE NOW.
THE ROW OVER THERE IS FINISHED
IF YOU COULD JUST...
CAN YOU PLEASE MOVE?
GO AWAY, LITTLE GIRL.
YOU'RE ANNOYING ME.
WELL, I'M DONE LIKE DINNER.
ME TOO.
NOW THERE'S JUST MY DAD'S
AND ONE THAT I'LL APPARENTLY
BE DOING AFTER SCHOOL.
OH MAMA.
CAN'T BLAME YOU THERE.
HEY, EM,
I CAN'T DEFRAG THIS
IF HE'S WORKING
ON SOMETHING, RIGHT?
UM NO. JUST SAVE IT
AND QUIT THE PROGRAM.
OH.
WHAT'S WRONG?
UH, I DON'T THINK I WAS
SUPPOSED TO SEE THIS.
WHAT?
HIS WILL.
SPINNER:
ORAZ CUN PALO?
RIZOTTO WITH PORKINE
AND SHITAK- WHAT?
PAIGE:
SPIN HAS TROUBLE WITH FOODS
HE CAN'T PRONOUNCE.
SPINNER:
(CHUCKLES)
PAIGE:
STOP!
SPIN, THIS IS A RESTAURANT,
NOT THE SCHOOL CAFETERIA.
CAN I TAKE YOUR BEVERAGE ORDER?
GINGER ALE FOR ME, PLEASE.
FINE.
UM, I'LL HAVE WHATEVER'S
ON TAP...
ANDREW.
WHAT? IF I WERE UNDERAGE,
WOULDN'T I BE IN SCHOOL
RIGHT NOW?
INSTEAD OF YOUR FINE DINING
ESTABLISHMENT?
THREE GINGER ALES
COMING RIGHT UP.
(LAUGHS)
SO UM, ASH,
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA HAVE?
NOTHING. I'M NOT HUNGRY.
I'M SORRY, OKAY?
BUT SEEING TERRI
IN THE HOSPITAL
SORT OF DID THAT TO ME.
YEAH, ME TOO,
BUT GETTING ALL DOWN AND SUCKY
DOESN'T HELP ANYONE.
YOU JUST DON'T GET IT, DO YOU?
ASH...
ASHLEY:
THESE ARE SUPPOSED TO BE
THE BEST YEARS OF OUR LIVES
AND IT'S JUST BEEN ONE DISASTER
AFTER ANOTHER AFTER ANOTHER.
THAT SCHOOL IS CURSED.
THEN JUST TRANSFER ALREADY.
SPINNER.
ASHLEY:
NO, HE'S RIGHT.
NEXT YEAR,
I'M LEAVING DEGRASSI.
OH, IF ONLY THIS WAS CHAMPAGNE,
NOT JUST THE CHAMPAGNE
OF GINGER ALES.
YOU'RE ECSTATIC THAT ASHLEY'S
TRANSFERRING, AREN'T YOU?
SHE IS MY FRIEND
WHO HAD A REALLY TOUGH YEAR
AND SHE'S PROBABLY CRYING
HER EYES OUT
IN THE BATHROOM RIGHT NOW.
SO LET'S TAKE HER HOME TO CRY,
SO WE CAN ENJOY THE REST
OF OUR AFTERNOON.
OR WE COULD SHOW HER
A GOOD TIME
AND MAYBE MAKE HER CHANGE
HER MIND?
GUYS, SEE THAT BLONDE
WOMAN OVER THERE?
LOOK WHO SHE'S WITH.
PAIGE:
RADITCH?
SO MAYBE WE SHOULD, UH...
SPIN YOU DID LEAVE MONEY
FOR LUNCH
LIKE YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO,
RIGHT?
NO.
SO WHAT? WE DIDN'T PAY?
COOL. COME ON.
NOT COOL!
JUST GIVE ME THE MONEY
I'LL GO PAY AND-
WHAT? AND GET CAUGHT SKIPPING
BY RADITCH?
SO WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
(YELLING) YEAH! WOO!
♪♪♪
OH! OH!
UH HUH!
OKAY, LET'S GO.
PAIGE:
ENJOYING THE ART, HONEY BEE?
ART?
THAT'S WHAT THEY CALL THIS.
ASHLEY:
SPIN, SOMEONE POURED THEIR SOUL
INTO THESE PAINTINGS.
REALLY?
I DON'T SEE IT.
OH WAIT.
YEAH, THERE IT IS.
WHAT?
I WASN'T DOING ANYTHING.
YOU WERE BEING A SEXIST JERK.
NO, I WAS TRYING
TO MAKE YOU LAUGH.
YEAH, WELL, IT WASN'T FUNNY.
IT WAS EMBARRASSING.
SPINNER:
SO WHAT? BEING AN IDIOT
IS OKAY SOMETIMES.
YEAH, AND SO IS GROWING UP.
SPINNER:
I'LL BE IN THE SCULPTURE
GARDEN.
OKAY, UM, I'M SORRY
YOU HAD A CRAPPY YEAR.
I'M SORRY CRAIG TREATED
YOU LIKE DIRT,
BUT GET OVER IT.
PAIGE YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
YOU TAKE EVERYTHING
SO SERIOUSLY.
JUST LIGHTEN UP.
YEAH, I'LL JUST DO THAT,
PAIGE.
YOU SHOULD.
I'M SORRY TO BE
BRUTALLY BLUNT,
BUT CRAIG DIDN'T CHEAT ON YOU
JUST BECAUSE OF HORMONES.
PAIGE-
PAIGE:
SO RUNAWAY NEXT YEAR
BUT IT WON'T HELP,
'CAUSE THE REAL PROBLEM
IS YOU.
EMMA:
UH, MR. PERINO,
IS MY DAD IN THERE?
PERINO:
MMM, NO.
LIBERTY:
SO THAT CANADIAN GEOGRAPHY
CLASS WAS GREAT, WASN'T IT?
THE CANADIAN SHIELD,
THE GREAT LAKES-
LIBERTY,
SHUT UP FOR ONCE.
I'M LOOKING
FOR MR. SIMPSON.
ALEX:
PLEASANT AS ALWAYS, EMMA.
DON'T START WITH ME.
ALEX, WHAT IS YOUR PROBLEM?
ALEX:
LET ME SEE.
YOUR CLOTHES, YOUR VOICE,
YOUR HOLIER-THAN-THOU ATTITUDE.
YOU.
KIDS:
(EXCITED SHOUTING)
(KNEE KICK)
(SLAP)
PERINO:
HEY! HEY!
HEY, THAT'S ENOUGH!
ALEX! EMMA!
SIMMER DOWN.
RONNY: (SINGING)
♪ HOW GREAT THOU ART, ♪
♪ THAT CHANGED MY SOUL,
MY SOUL, MY SAVIOUR, ♪
♪ MY GOD TO THEE. ♪
SPINNER:
OKAY, THE KING IS COOL
BUT THAT FREAK-SHOW ON STAGE
IS NOT.
A PERFECTLY LAME END
TO A LAME DAY.
SPIN, WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
LOOK, THAT GUY IS COOL
AND I HAD FUN TODAY.
YEAH, CAN'T WAIT TO TELL
EVERYONE WE SKIPPED
AND MOPED ALL DAY
WITH THE QUEEN OF DOOM.
PAIGE:
HE DIDN'T MEAN THAT.
IT'S COOL.
UM, SO WHY DON'T YOU GUYS
JUST SIT.
I'LL GET US A SNACK.
(SLAP)
RONNY: (SINGING)
♪ HOW GREAT THOU ART! ♪
THANK YOU.
WHERE'S A GOOD T-BONE STEAK
WHEN YOU NEED ONE, HUH?
I THOUGHT WE WERE DONE
WITH SECRETS, DAD.
I FOUND YOUR WILL.
WHEN WERE YOU GONNA TELL
ME THE CHEMO FAILED?
SIMPSON:
NO, NO, NO, NO.
EMMA, YOU GOT IT ALL WRONG.
THE DOCTOR JUST TOLD
ME TO BE PREPARED.
PREPARED FOR WHAT?
WHAT IS GOING ON?
THIS AFTERNOON I GET
THE RESULTS
FROM MY LAST ROUND OF CHEMO.
YOUR MOM AND I JUST WANTED
TO PROTECT YOU.
WELL STOP, OKAY?
SIMPSON:
OKAY, BUT...
THIS IS BIG, EM.
IT'S LIFE OR DEATH BIG
BECAUSE IF THE CHEMO
DIDN'T WORK...
BUT I WANT TO KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON.
I NEED TO KNOW.
OKAY.
SO COME WITH US TODAY
TO THE DOCTOR'S.
THERE'S NO MORE SECRETS.
MINI-E:
(SINGING) ♪ AMEN! ♪
♪ AMEN! ♪
♪ AMEN! AMEN! AMEN! ♪
SPINNER:
OKAY, THAT'S JUST BIZARRE.
PAIGE:
OKAY, WHERE IS ASH?
SHE'S BEEN GONE FOR LIKE,
20 MINUTES.
SPINNER:
AND THAT'S A PROBLEM?
MINI-E:
(SINGING) ♪ AMEN... ♪
♪ AMEN! ♪
(CHEERS)
HOWARD:
NICE JOB! MINI-E,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
MINI-E!
NOW UP, A LATE ADDITION.
NEXT UP ELVIRA, QUEEN OF DOOM!
ELVIRA!
THANK YOU, HOWARD.
(ELVIS VOICE)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THIS LITTLE NUMBER GOES OUT
TO MY DEAR OL' FRIEND RONNY,
WHO LEANT ME THIS OUTFIT
AND TO MY GOOD FRIENDS
SPINNER AND PAIGE.
THIS ONE'S FOR YOU.
WHAT IS SHE DOING?
(UP BEAT)
♪ I'M LOST IN A VOID
OF ETERNITY, ♪
♪ THE EYE OF THE STORM,
THE DEPTH OF THE SEA. ♪
♪ A BLACK HOLE RIPS ME
FROM INSIDE OUT, ♪
♪ GRAVITY, ENDING ME.
I WANT TO SHOUT! ♪
AUDIENCE:
(CHEERS AND CLAPS WILDLY)
DR. MORAGODA:
AH, THE WHOLE FAMILY'S
HERE TODAY.
SO...
BONE MARROW TESTS ARE IN.
YOUR PERIPHERAL BLOOD CELL
COUNT COULD BE BETTER,
BUT YOUR NORMOCELLULAR MARROW
HAS JUST 3.2% BLASTS.
PLEASE. IN ENGLISH.
YOU'RE IN REMISSION.
(RELIEVED SIGH)
(DEEP SIGH)
DR. MORAGODA:
NURSE GRANT WILL SET UP
YOUR FOLLOW-UPS.
CONGRATULATIONS.
UH, TAKE AS MUCH TIME
AS YOU NEED IN HERE.
GOOD, 'CAUSE I THINK
WE'RE GONNA BE AWHILE.
KATE:
I WORRY ABOUT YOU ALL DAY
SO I CANCEL A HOUSE SHOWING
SO I CAN BE WITH YOU
AND THEN I FIND YOU
PULLING UP IN PAIGE'S CAR
WITH THE WORLD'S WEIRDEST
TROPHY.
(ELVIS VOICE) I'M SORRY,
LITTLE LADY. (GIGGLES)
ASHLEY, THIS IS NOT FUNNY!
(LAUGHS)
ASHLEY'S SANITY HAS LEFT
THE BUILDING.
(LAUGHS)
SPINNER:
(ELVIS VOICE)
THANK YOU. THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
PAIGE:
OKAY, THAT WAS A WORSE
IMPERSONATION
THAN THAT MINI-E KID.
(LAUGHTER)
OH, TIME TO PICK UP DYLAN.
HE'S GOING TO KILL ME
IF I'M LATE.
SPINNER:
YEAH, NOT TO MENTION...
FOR THIS.
WHICH HE WILL NEVER
KNOW ABOUT.
SMALL PRICE TO PAY
FOR A DAY OFF, RIGHT?