MARCO:
GUYS! GUYS!
CHECK IT OUT, OKAY?
IT'S THE POSTER
FOR THE SEMI-FORMAL.
WATCH.
HUH? COME ON.
IT'S THEMED ON THOSE MOVIE
MUSICALS FROM INDIA?
SO HOT RIGHT NOW.
SPINNER:
YEAH, IF YOU'RE A BIG FLAMING-
MR. DEL ROSSI!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING AT OUR
SCHOOL ON THIS FINE MORNING?
MR. DEL ROSSI:
MY COMPANY MAKE THE POSTERS
FOR YOUR DANCE.
MARCO:
YEAH,
AND THE TICKETS.
I'LL NEED TWO...
FOR THE SOON-TO-BE CROWNED
KING AND QUEEN OF DEGRASSI.
EXCUSE ME?
THAT'S ME AND JIMMY.
MR. DEL ROSSI:
OH, NO, NO, NO, NO.
THIS YEAR THE KING
IS GONNA BE MARCO DEL ROSSI!
BUT WHO'S GOING TO BESIDE
HIM TO SHARE THE GLORY?
MARCO:
PAP, I'M CHAIR OF THE COMMITTEE
THIS YEAR.
I'M NOT GONNA HAVE TIME
FOR A DATE.
MR. DEL ROSSI:
MARCO.
ALL THESE BEAUTIFUL GIRLS
OVER HERE,
AND NOT ONE YOU LIKE?
MR. DEL ROSSI:
YOU'RE TOO SHY, MARCO. HUH?
HEY SPINNER?
HELP YOUR FRIEND, PLEASE?
(LAUGHS POLITELY)
(BELL RINGS)
PAP, WE'RE GONNA BE LATE.
THANK YOU.
YES. OKAY.
CIAO EVERYONE.
BYE, PAP.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Hear what I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
MARCO:
(IMITATING HIS DAD)
OH MARCO, ALL THESE BEAUTIFUL
GIRLS
AND THERE IS NOT ONE YOU LIKE.
DYLAN:
SOUNDS BEYOND EMBARRASSING.
YEAH, AND JUST
TO SHUT HIM UP
I WANTED TO SAY,
PAPA, THERE IS SOMEBODY
I LIKE - A GUY!
ANYONE I KNOW?
UH...YEAH.
WELL, JUST SOMEONE.
SO UH, YOU SEEN THAT
NEW ZOMBIE MOVIE YET -
"KILLER RAGE"?
UH, ELLIE DID.
SHE SAID IT WAS A CLEVER
CRITIQUE ON CONSUMERISM.
AND SCARY TOO.
I'VE JUST BEEN WAITING FOREVER
FOR IT TO COME OUT,
BUT... YOU KNOW,
NO ONE WILL GO.
IT SOUNDS COOL,
BUT ZOMBIE FLICKS,
THEY SORT OF FREAK ME OUT...
LIKE BAD.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, TOM SAID
HE WANTED TO GO SO...
GOTTA GO.
JT:
WHASSUP, DAWG?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
HERE I AM, THERE I AM,
HERE I AM, THERE I AM.
PRETTY WEIRD, HUH?
THAT'S ONE WORD FOR IT.
MAN:
OKAY, JT,
TIME TO GIVE IT BACK.
THANKS FOR LETTING ME...
BORROW ME.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT CUT-OUT'S
GONNA BE IN THE CAF.
OUR CAF.
I KNOW.
AND SCHOOLS ACROSS
OUR FAIR LAND.
JUST WHAT THE COUNTRY
NEEDS - MORE JT.
TAKE YOUR CHEAP SHOTS NOW,
MY FRIEND,
CAUSE TONIGHT...
THE COMMERCIAL HITS
THE AIRWAVES!
MORNING, MANNY.
HEY!
WE COULD HAVE
A LAUNCH PARTY!
INVITE PEOPLE OVER
TO WATCH MY BIG DEBUT?
YEAH, TOO BAD
YOUR APARTMENT'S SO SMALL.
YEAH.
IF ONLY I KNEW SOMEONE
WITH A BIG LIVING ROOM
AND A BIG TV.
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
WE CAN HAVE IT
AT MY PLACE.
JUST DON'T INVITE
TOO MANY PEOPLE.
NO, NO, NO.
THE INVITE LIST WILL BE
HANDPICKED.
VERY EXCLUSIVE.
JT YORKE COMMERCIAL
LAUNCH PARTY...
CASA KERWIN-ISAACS.
SEE YOU THERE.
HERE YOU GO, GUYS.
SEE YOU GUYS THERE.
DO YOU LIKE DYLAN
OR WHAT?
A LITTLE LOUDER, SPIN.
I THINK A FEW OF THE KIDS
IN THE BACK DIDN'T HEAR YOU.
JUST ANSWER THE QUESTION.
YEAH.
I MEAN, HE'S THE FIRST GUY
I CAN ACTUALLY SEE MYSELF
HOOKING UP WITH, YOU KNOW.
WAIT, WHY AM I TELLING
YOU THIS?
WHAT DIFFERENCE DOES
IT MAKE?
I'M YOUR FRIEND.
I WANNA HELP.
OKAY.
YEAH, I LIKE HIM,
BUT I'M SCARED.
OKAY.
BUT YOU NEED TO GET OVER THAT.
JUST ASK THE DUDE OUT.
MARCO:
HOW DO I START?
SPINNER:
DUDE, IT'S NOT GRADE 9
PUBLIC SPEAKING.
JUST GO UP TO HIM AND SAY,
"DUDE, I LIKE YOU.
YOU LIKE ME. LET'S HOOK UP."
OKAY, MAYBE NOT THOSE
EXACT WORDS.
JUST GO. COME ON.
TOM:
HERE'S THAT CD I MADE YOU.
DYLAN:
OH, THANKS, TOM.
MARCO. HEY.
HEY.
I GOTTA JET.
HATZILAKOS:
SO FROM AN EVOLUTIONARY
STANDPOINT,
BEES ARE ALMOST PERFECT
AND THAT'S WHY IN MILLENIA,
THEY'VE BARELY CHANGED.
MARCO:
SPIN. SPIN!
I HATE BEES, OKAY?
THEY'RE LIKE FLYING
DEATH MONKEYS.
DUDE,
BEES ARE SMALL.
YOU JUST SMACK 'EM.
OH, AND SPEAKING OF BUGS
THAT NEED A SMACK?
WHAT'S WITH TOM?
I DON'T EVEN WANT TO HEAR
HIS NAME, OKAY?
HE STOLE MY CRUSH.
C'MON...
MARCO:
NO.
IT'S A LOST CAUSE ANYWAY.
I MEAN...
I'M TOO YOUNG FOR DYLAN.
AND WHAT DO I KNOW
ABOUT SORTS, MAN? NOTHING.
I'M TOO GIRLY.
DUDE, DO NOT PUT YOURSELF DOWN,
OKAY?
DATING IS WAR. YOU HAVE TO BE
READY TO FIGHT DIRTY.
LOOK, ALL I KNOW...
IS THAT DYLAN'S MOVED ON.
SO MAYBE I SHOULD TOO.
(BELL RINGS)
SPINNER:
DYLAN, MY MAN.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
SPINNER?
YEAH UH, LISTEN...
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT YOUR LITTLE FRIEND
TOMMY BOY.
OKAY, ON THE DOWN-LOW?
DUDE'S GOT SCABIES.
WHAT?
I SAW HIM IN THE SHOWER?
IT'S SICK.
IT'S DISGUST-
DYLAN:
WHAT IS THIS?
HUG THE HOMO DAY?
SPINNER:
I JUST CARE ABOUT YOU,
MAN,
SHOWING YOU LOVE.
SPINNER, I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU,
MAN.
I'M JUST ONLY TRYING TO HELP
OUT MARCO.
YOU LIKE HIM, RIGHT?
THEN ASK HIM OUT.
I DON'T THINK
HE'S READY.
WHAT'S THE WORST
THAT COULD HAPPEN?
LISTEN, I WASN'T READY
FOR MY FIRST DATE, OKAY,
AND IT WAS A DISASTER.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO PUT MARCO
THROUGH THAT.
IT WON'T HAPPEN.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT BEING GAY?
WELL, I KNOW MARCO.
AND I KNOW HE LIKES YOU
A LOT.
JUST THINK ABOUT IT,
OKAY?
♪♪♪
GREAT SLIDE,
SWEET POTATO.
SO I HEAR
YOU'RE HAVING A-
SORRY,
BUT I CAN'T TALK RIGHT NOW.
MANNY.
SORRY. NO POCKETS.
JUST READ IT.
EVERYONE'S GONNA BE THERE.
EMMA, LIBERTY.
BUT THIS IS
AT ASHLEY'S HOUSE.
YEAH, BUT TOBY SAID
SHE'S OUT TONIGHT.
I'D REALLY LIKE IT
IF YOU CAME.
ME TOO,
BUT I CAN'T.
WHY?
JUST TELL ME.
AT SCHOOL,
WHEN PEOPLE TALK ABOUT ME?
I WALK.
AT A PARTY,
I'M STUCK.
WELL, WHAT IF I TOLD YOU
I WON'T LET ANYONE
SAY A WORD ABOUT YOU?
THAT'S REALLY SWEET,
BUT...
MANNY PLEASE.
THE COMMERCIAL MIGHT SEEM
DUMB BUT...
IT'S A DREAM COME TRUE.
OKAY.
I'LL BE THERE.
♪♪♪
DYLAN:
HEY.
WE NEED TO TALK.
UH... OKAY.
I JUST THOUGHT
YOU SHOULD KNOW
THAT THERE'S SOMEONE
I LIKE.
OH, YEAH.
I MEAN, I UNDERSTAND.
I'M TOO SHORT,
TOO YOUNG, TOO GIRLY-
AND WAY TOO HARD ON YOURSELF.
ARE YOU MESSING WITH ME?
GUILTY AS CHARGED.
YOU'RE SUCH A JERK!
HEY TAKE IT EASY!
I HAVEN'T EVEN
ASKED YOU OUT YET.
SO TONIGHT,
YOU WANT TO GO SEE
THAT ZOMBIE MOVIE
OR WILL IT FREAK YOU OUT?
YEAH, A LITTLE,
BUT I WANT TO.
GOOD.
SO, IT'S A DATE?
YOU BET.
KENDRA:
SPINNER, MARCO'S HERE!
MARCO:
SPIN, I'M DYING!
HERE. OKAY,
FASHION CRISIS.
COWBOY,
VINTAGE,
OR CLUBBY?
I DON'T KNOW.
UH DUDE, MAYBE YOU
DIDN'T GET THE MEMO -
I'M STRAIGHT.
MARCO:
YEAH,
BUT YOUR TASTE IS WAY CLOSER
TO DYLAN'S THAN MINE IS.
SO HELP ME, PLEASE.
SPINNER:
OKAY. IT'S LIKE "STRAIGHT EYE
FOR THE GAY GUY".
OKAY, THIS?
ENRIQUE CALLED,
WANTS HIS SHIRT BACK.
AND THIS WHOLE OLIVER TWIST
THING?
PLEASE SIR, DON'T WEAR THIS.
YOU'LL LOOK LIKE AN IDIOT.
SPIN, WHAT?
PLANNING ON RUSTLING CATTLE,
DUDE?
DON'T THROW THAT.
NOW THIS?
CLASSY, SPORTY,
VERY DAVID BECKHAM...
AND VERY DEL ROSSI.
COOL.
SPIN?
I JUST WANT TO SAY
THANKS FOR...
WELL, I GUESS
FOR EVERYTHING.
YEAH, DON'T GET MUSHY.
SPINNER:
MARCO!
MARCO:
YEAH.
EVENING, MR. MASON.
MARCO READY?
YOU BET.
MARCO:
YOU LOOK NICE.
DYLAN:
THANKS. SO DO YOU.
EXCEPT FOR THIS.
WELL, I MEAN, IT'S GREAT...
FOR A CLUB.
YEAH.
SPIN TRIED TO WARN ME.
I'M SO STUPID.
MARCO, IT'S FINE.
IT'S JUST A HAT.
OKAY.
OH MY GOD! OH MY GOD!
BEE IN THE CAR!
BEE! BEE! BEE!
SORRY.
I HAVE A BIT
OF A BEE PHOBIA.
MARCO:
SO YOU DON'T THINK
I'M COMPLETELY LAME?
DYLAN:
YOUR BEE PHOBIA?
PALES IN COMPARISON
TO MY FEAR OF KILLER WHALES.
MY MOM TOOK ME TO A MARINE PARK
FOR MY TENTH BIRTHDAY,
AND I VOLUNTEERED
TO BE KISSED BY THE WHALE.
BUT WHEN IT LEAPT
FROM THE WATER
IT JUST HAD THIS LOOK
IN ITS EYE,
LIKE "I'M GONNA KILL YOU".
I JUST, I RAN FROM THE PARK
SCREAMING.
GUESS I'M A FREAK, HUH?
NO.
ACTUALLY...
YOU'RE PRETTY GREAT.
I THINK YOU'RE PRETTY
GREAT TOO.
(SOUND OF TV)
TOBY:
HANDPICKED INVITE LIST?
EXCLUSIVE?
BOY:
CHIPS!
JT:
(NOTICES THE TV)
THIS IS IT! THIS IS IT!
JT:
YO DAWG, THESE FRIES
ARE WHICKY-WHICKY-WHACK!
WHAT THEY NEED?
IS SOME STUPID SUPAFLY FLAVOUR.
(DOG BARKS)
JT:
FIRST WE GIVE 'EM THE MAD CURL.
THEN WE DUNK 'EM
IN THE DOPE BATTER.
THEN IT'S TIME TO KICK
THE SUPAFLY FRY FLAVOUR...
A CRAZY COMBO OF SEVEN
SLAMMIN' SPICES!
THAT SUPAFLY TASTE
IS OFF THE CHAIN, YO!
HEY, DON'T GET ALL UP
IN MY FRIES, DAWG!
GET YOUR FRY ON,
WITH SUPAFLY FRIES!
UH, GUESS IT WASN'T REALLY
OFF THE CHAIN THEN?
JIMMY
LOOK, IF PEOPLE DO MAKE FUN
OF YOU TOMORROW,
YOU JUST TELL 'EM...
(IMITATES HIM)
DON'T GET ALL UP IN MY FRIES,
DAWG!
(EVERYONE LAUGHS)
(SOUND OF THE HORROR MOVIE)
IT'S OKAY.
DYLAN:
WHAT ABOUT THAT PRIEST,
AND THAT ZOMBIE PRIEST
JUST CAME RUNNING
AFTER HIM LIKE THAT.
MARCO:
NO, NO, NO, NO.
THE PART WHEN THE ZOMBIE
JUST TORE OFF HIS ARM?
GOD, I NEARLY...
DYLAN:
I KNOW.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
THEY'RE HERE.
WHO?
FLESH-EATING ZOMBIES?
WORSE.
MY PARENTS. OKAY?
MRS. DEL ROSSI:
MARCO!
HEY MA.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
STUDYING WITH SPINNER?
MARCO:
UH, SPINNER GOT SICK.
ACTUALLY, I BUMPED INTO
PAIGE'S BROTHER, DYLAN.
MR. DEL ROSSI:
YOU ARE DYLAN?
MY SON, HE TALKS ABOUT YOU
ALL THE TIME.
HE DOES?
MR. DEL ROSSI:
YES. HE SAYS YOU ARE
A GREAT HOCKEY PLAYER...
AND I LOVE HOCKEY.
WHY DON'T YOU COME
TO DINNER WITH US!
MA, WE ALREADY ATE.
YOU KNOW HOW
YOUR FATHER GETS.
MR. DEL ROSSI:
SO YOU PLAY FORWARD.
WHICH LINE?
DYLAN:
FIRST. I'M A PRETTY
HIGH SCORER.
MR. DEL ROSSI:
YEAH. ON THE ICE.
HOW ABOUT WITH THE GIRLS?
NOT LIKE MARCO...
MARCO:
PA?
I'M JUST SAYING,
YOU GUYS ARE YOUNG.
RIGHT NOW IT SHOULD BE GIRLS,
GIRLS, GIRLS.
LIKE GABRIELLA...
FROM CHURCH?
MA, SHE'S 300 POUNDS.
SHE'S BIG, BUT NICE.
MAYBE DYLAN WOULD LIKE HER?
MARCO:
NO.
HE WOULDN'T.
GAY WAITER:
HOW ARE YOU ALL DOING?
CAN I GET YOU ANYTHING?
NO, WE'RE OKAY.
THANK YOU.
HOW CAN A FRUITY-BOY
CARRY THOSE PLATES
WITH THOSE LIMP WRISTS?
PA...
MR. DEL ROSSI:
I NEVER UNDERSTAND THAT KIND?
TWO MEN. TOGETHER...
IS DISGUSTING.
MARCO:
PA...
IT'S SICKENING.
PA, STOP!
THE TIME -
UH, I'VE GOT EARLY PRACTICE
TOMORROW SO...
NICE MEETING YOU BOTH.
MR. DEL ROSSI:
NICE TO MEET YOU TOO.
THAT'S A NICE BOY.
MRS. DEL ROSSI:
HOW CAN YOU SAY THAT?
MR. DEL ROSSI:
SAY WHAT?
MRS. DEL ROSSI:
YOU GOT A BIG MOUTH.
MR. DEL ROSSI:
I GOT A BIG MOUTH?
JUST PUT THE PASTA IN YOUR BIG
MOUTH AND LEAVE ME ALONE.
I DON'T MAKE NO COMMOTIONS,
YOU MAKE...
JAY:
HEY, WHERE'S YOUR DOG, DAWG?
SEAN:
HAS HE BEEN GETTING UP
IN YOUR FRIES?
IT'S A FUN WAY TO START
TO THE DAY, HUH?
JT, YOUR COMMERCIAL SUCKED.
THANKS.
BUT YOU DIDN'T.
YOU WERE GREAT.
WELL, YOU MIND TELLING
EVERYONE IN THE SCHOOL THAT?
COMING FROM THE SCHOOL TRAMP,
I DON'T THINK THEY'D LISTEN.
I DO NOT WANT TO GO
IN THERE.
MANNY:
I KNOW,
BUT WE'VE GOT ARMSTRONG'S TEST
AND WE HAVE TO GET OUR MATH ON.
I AM SO GOING TO KILL YOU!
MARCO:
LOOK SPIN, I'M TELLING YOU,
OKAY?
IT WAS THE DATE FROM HELL.
AND I DON'T KNOW HOW I'M GOING
TO FACE DYLAN TODAY, NOW.
WELL, YOU'RE ABOUT
TO FIND OUT.
DYLAN:
HEY.
TALK TO YOU A SEC?
OKAY.
MARCO:
LOOK, YOU DON'T HAVE TO EXPLAIN
ABOUT WHAT MY DAD SAID.
DYLAN:
NO, IT WAS STUPID AND OFFENSIVE,
BUT YOU KNOW,
WE'VE BOTH HEARD WORSE.
YEAH, BUT THE WAY
YOU JUST RUN OFF LIKE THAT...
YOU LOOKED LIKE YOU WERE
GOING INTO CARDIAC ARREST.
I WAS SPARING YOU.
(BOTH LAUGH)
MAN, AFTER THAT PIMP HAT,
AND THE BEE INCIDENT,
AND THEN
WHAT MY DAD SAID?
I JUST...
I THOUGHT YOU WERE NEVER
GOING TO TALK TO ME AGAIN.
WELL, IT CROSSED MY MIND,
BUT UH...
I DO THINK
YOU'RE PRETTY CUTE.
SO THEN, DOES THAT MEAN
I GET ANOTHER SHOT?
A CHANCE TO REDEEM MYSELF?
THAT DEPENDS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
THIS FRIDAY?
(BREATHY CHUCKLE)