♪♪♪
RILEY:
HEY, BUDDY.
HEY, GUYS.
ALL SET FOR THE EARLY PRACTICE?
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
RILEY:
THOUGHT WE'D WELCOME YOU
TO THE TEAM FIRST, DREW,
AND GIVE THE WHOLE SCHOOL
A CHANCE TO MEET YOU, TOO.
DREW:
I KNOW,
THE FLAGPOLE THING.
I EXPECTED BETTER HAZING
THAN THIS.
RILEY:
HAZING? WHO SAID ANYTHING
ABOUT HAZING?
(STRUGGLING)
GUYS!
GUYS,
COME ON!
NO MORE TALKING.
YOU'RE LUCKY.
I USED TO HAVE
A VIOLENT STREAK!
(LAUGHS)
(BUZZ OF EXCITED CHATTER)
DREW:
(STRUGGLING GRUNTS)
MMM!
(STUDENTS LAUGHING)
DREW:
(STRUGGLING GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
OKAY, WHO DID IT?
MM-MM-MMPH!
OH... SORRY, SON.
THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
TO DO THIS,
I'M AFRAID.
AHHHHHH!
(STUDENTS LAUGH AND CALL OUT)
SO, I ASSUME YOU DIDN'T
PLASTIC WRAP YOURSELF
TO THE POLE?
CAN YOU FIND
MY CLOTHES?
OKAY,
I'LL GET SOME SCISSORS.
JUST...DON'T GO ANYWHERE.
VERY FUNNY.
GIRL:
WELCOME TO DEGRASSI!
COACH ARMSTRONG:
HEY, COME ON.
GET TO CLASS.
NOTHING TO SEE HERE.
LET'S GO!
(STUDENTS LAUGHING
AND TALKING)
(WHISPERING)
LOOKING GOOD!
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
WANNA HAVE THE BEST TIME
OF YOUR LIFE?
IF YOU'RE INTERESTED IN US,
WE'RE INTERESTED IN YOU!
(CHUCKLES)
HERE, TAKE ONE.
DO YOU DANCE?
NOT FOR SOMETHING CALLED
THE "BIG D DANCE CRUE."
OH, OKAY. SO THE NAME
COULD USE A LITTLE HELP.
BUT THIS LITTLE
DANCE CREW
IS ABOUT TO BECOME
THE COOLEST CLUB IN SCHOOL.
YEAH, WHAT COLOUR
ARE YOUR POMPOMS?
THERE ARE NO POMPOMS,
OR UNIFORMS,
OR STUPID TRYOUTS.
WE'RE THE CLUB FOR PEOPLE
WHO CAN'T STAND CLUBS.
(SIGHS)
SO WHAT'S THE POINT?
TO DANCE,
HAVE FUN.
MAYBE MAKE
A FEW NEW FRIENDS?
I HAVE ALL THE FRIENDS
I NEED.
PLUS, YOU GET TO CUT CLASS
EARLY FOR PRACTICE!
HMM...
MR. SIMPSON:
(OVER PA) ALL MEMBERS
OF THE FOOTBALL TEAM,
PLEASE REPORT TO THE GYM
IMMEDIATELY.
COACH ARMSTRONG:
(CLEARS THROAT)
MR. SIMPSON:
THERE'S BEEN AN INCIDENT
AND I HOPE THAT NONE OF YOU
WERE INVOLVED.
MY SON WAS HAZED!
OBVIOUSLY SOMEONE WAS INVOLVED!
WELL, POSSIBLY,
BUT-
NO! THERE'S NO ACCEPTABLE
"BUT" AFTER THAT.
UNLESS YOU'RE DEFENDING HAZING?
COACH ARMSTRONG:
NO ONE WOULD DO THAT.
WELL, BY TACITLY ACCEPTING IT,
YOU'RE ENDORSING THE BEHAVIOUR.
COACH ARMSTRONG:
DOES ANYONE KNOW
HOW DREW GOT WRAPPED
TO THE FLAGPOLE?
AHEM! DOESN'T DREW
KNOW WHO DID IT?
THEY HAD MASKS.
I-I DIDN'T GET A GOOD LOOK.
OH! IT WAS SOMEONE
IN THIS ROOM!
AND IF NOBODY OWNS UP,
I'LL GO TO THE SCHOOL BOARD.
I DON'T NEED
TO REMIND YOU
OF THE SERIOUS CONSEQUENCES
TO THE TEAM.
ANYONE?
RILEY, DID YOU HEAR
ANYTHING?
UH... NO, SIR.
AUDRA:
OH, NO?
SO YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHO TRIED TO HUMILIATE
THE YOUNG MAN
WHO ALSO JUST HAPPENS TO BE
TRYING OUT FOR QUARTERBACK?
I KNOW RILEY.
MOM, HE'D TELL YOU.
WE'LL KEEP LOOKING INTO THIS.
OH,
I'M SURE YOU WILL.
COACH ARMSTRONG:
ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
GET TO CLASS.
LET'S GO!
♪ One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven ♪
♪ Eight, nine, ten, eleven,
jack, king, queen ♪
♪ I like it ♪
♪ I like it I do ♪
♪ Hi-fi, low-fi ♪
♪ Put your hand to the sky ♪
♪ Do-da-dit-dat-do-da-da ♪
♪ I like it ♪
♪ I like it, I do ♪
(WHISTLES LOUDLY)
GIRL:
OH!
GIRL 1: WHAT'S SHE DOING HERE?
GIRL 2: I DON'T KNOW!
♪ One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven ♪
♪ Say it again ♪
♪ I like it ♪
♪ I like it, I do ♪
♪ Just like you ♪
GIRL:
WHOO! YEAH!
♪ Just like you ♪
WELL,
WHATEVER YOU JUST DID,
IS EXACTLY WHAT
WE'RE LOOKING FOR.
(LAUGHS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
SORRY I'M LATE.
(SIGHS) IF YOU FORGOT
WHERE THE NEW CAF WAS AGAIN,
I'LL DRAW YOU
A MAP.
MARISOL BROUGHT HER BROTHER'S
OLD FOOTBALL PLAYBOOK FOR ME.
ONLY SHE COULDN'T FIND IT,
AND HER EARRING GOT STUCK IN
THIS FLUFFY SCARF SHE HAD ON,
SO THAT TOOK A WHILE.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT IT MEANS
WHEN A GIRL STARTS
"BRINGING THINGS IN" FOR YOU?
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
IS THAT HER NOW?
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
NO.
MARISOL:
KC! FOUND IT!
MARISOL. GREAT.
I'LL GET RID OF HER.
(LOW HUM OF STUDENT CHATTER)
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
(PHONE RINGS)
WOMAN: HELLO?
JENNA: WHO IS THIS?
WOMAN:
YOU CALLED ME.
DO YOU GO TO DEGRASSI?
WOMAN:
M-MY SON DOES.
YOUR SON?
WOMAN:
KC. DO YOU KNOW HIM?
I-I'VE BEEN TRYING TO GET
MESSAGES TO HIM ALL WEEK.
UM...
SORRY, WRONG NUMBER!
(PHONE BEEPS)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
RILEY:
HEY. THANKS, MAN.
REALLY,
IT WAS COOL OF YOU.
I MEAN,
NOBODY LIKES A SNITCH,
BUT I FEEL KINDA BAD.
YOU FEEL "KINDA" BAD
THAT THE SCHOOL SAW ME
WRAPPED UP LIKE A SANDWICH?
I REALLY APPRECIATE
YOU BAILING ME OUT.
I DIDN'T DO IT FOR YOU,
DUMBASS.
ZERO TOLERANCE.
IF I TOLD, WE MIGHT FORFEIT
THE ENTIRE SEASON.
THERE'S NOT MUCH POINT
OF MAKING STARTING QB1
IF THERE'S NO SEASON.
RILEY:
YOU MAKING IT?
YOU MEAN, BY THREATENING
TO TELL THE WORLD
THAT SOME GUY'S GAY.
THAT'S HEROIC.
I DON'T CARE HOW GAY,
OR NOT GAY YOU ARE.
I JUST DID YOU A HUGE FAVOUR
BACK THERE,
AND NOW YOU OWE ME.
AND I'M JUST SUPPOSED
TO STEP ASIDE?
YOU DO NOT WANT ME
TO FORCE YOU.
♪♪♪
♪ Come on, come on, come on,
Come on, come on, come on ♪
♪ Come on, come on ♪
♪ Shake your booty
booty booty booty now ♪
♪ You're a cutie cutie ♪
♪ Shake your body booty now... ♪
FRONT, FRONT,
AND POSE!
POSE HARD!
ALLI:
(LAUGHS)
OH MY GOD, BIANCA.
THAT WAS AMAZING!
DOES "AMAZING" MEAN "GARBAGE"
TO YOU?
JESS FELL TWICE,
AND JANIE LOOKS LIKE
SHE'S IN THE BALLET.
O-KAY,
SO MAYBE WE HAVE A LITTLE BIT
OF WORK TO DO
BEFORE WE GET BOOKED
FOR ANY HIP HOP VIDEOS.
WE HAVE A LOT OF WORK
TO DO
BEFORE WE GET BOOKED
FOR INDECENT EXPOSURE.
(SIGHS DISGUSTEDLY)
OKAY, BACK IN THE LINE!
UM, ACTUALLY,
WHY DON'T WE TAKE A BREAK.
MAYBE DISCUSS WARDROBE OPTIONS?
OR WE COULD PUT OUR EFFORT
INTO THINGS THAT MATTER!
SAV: (OVER PA)
PRESIDENT SAV HERE
WITH A REMINDER
THAT BUSES WILL TAKE
PANTHERS FANS TO BARDELL.
GET THERE EARLY
TO GET A SEAT!
GO PANTHERS!
ALLI:
UM, OKAY, EVERYONE MEET OUTSIDE
AT 3 P.M. SHARP!
AND WHY EXACTLY
WOULD WE DO THAT?
SO WE CAN ALL GO
TO THE GAME TOGETHER.
YOU KNOW,
LIKE THE POWER SQUAD.
GIRL, CHEERLEADERS CHEER
AT GAMES.
DANCE CREW'S DON'T.
THAT DOESN'T MEAN
WE CAN'T SIT IN THE STANDS.
WE'RE A CLUB,
AREN'T WE SUPPOSED
TO DO STUFF TOGETHER?
YEAH.
LIKE DANCE.
♪ Shake your booty, baby
booty, baby ♪
♪ Booty now ♪
♪ You're a thug with the hoodie
hoodie hoodie down ♪
♪ Shake your booty booty booty
booty now ♪
♪ You're a cutie cutie
Shake your body, booty now ♪
♪ Shake your booty booty booty
booty now ♪
COACH ARMSTRONG:
NOW I KNOW THIS STUFF
CAN BE TOUGH,
BUT IF YOU APPLY YOURSELF,
I KNOW YOU CAN GET IT.
(BELL RINGS)
COACH ARSTRONG:
OKAY, GOOD WORK, EVERYONE.
NO HOMEWORK TONIGHT.
SO THERE'S NO EXCUSE FOR MISSING
THE FIRST GAME, OKAY?
(STUDENTS MURMUR QUIETLY)
RILEY:
HEY, COACH?
CAN I TALK TO YOU?
YEAH. EVERYTHING OKAY?
YEAH. I WAS JUST WONDERING
ABOUT TRYOUTS
AND IF YOU'VE MADE
ANY DECISIONS?
WELL, YOU KNOW
WE ONLY MAKE CUTS
IF WE RUN OUT OF UNIFORMS.
SO...
WHAT ABOUT QUARTERBACK?
WELL, I ASSUMED YOU'D PICK UP
WHERE YOU LEFT OFF LAST SEASON.
ONLY THIS TIME,
AS CAPTAIN.
(SIGHS) I THINK DREW MIGHT BE
A BETTER CAPTAIN.
WELL, DREW'S A GOOD QB
WITH GREAT POTENTIAL,
BUT EVERYONE KNOWS
THIS IS YOUR TEAM, RILEY.
I NEED YOU TO SHOW ME THAT,
STARTING TODAY.
I DON'T KNOW
IF I'M UP FOR IT, COACH.
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
NO, IT'S...
IT'S JUST PRE-GAME JITTERS.
YOU'RE ALWAYS NERVOUS
BEFORE A GAME.
THEN YOU GET OUT THERE
AND TEAR THE OTHER TEAM APART.
I'VE SEEN IT.
I GUESS IT'S JUST BEEN
SO INTENSE,
FIGHTING FOR MY JOB.
DON'T WORRY.
DREW'S GOT NOTHING ON YOU.
STUDENTS:
(LAUGHTER AND CHATTER)
♪♪♪
♪ Avenues ♪
♪ There's a chance
taking too many times ♪
♪ So cut the brake lines ♪
♪ Pretend you don't see
the signs ♪
♪ You try to see the stars ♪
♪ But there's far too many
clouds in the sky ♪
♪ The solution to the problem ♪
♪ Is to paint whitest of lines ♪
♪ You are the stars ♪
♪ So don't let it slip away ♪
♪ The ghost of all
those memories ♪
♪ Become the sun today ♪
JENNA:
HEY. HOW WAS FRENCH?
KC:
PAS MAL.
I WAS GONNA TEXT YOU,
BUT I CAN'T FIND MY PHONE.
(NERVOUSLY)
REALLY?
DON'T WORRY,
I DIDN'T LEAVE IT
AT MARISOL'S HOUSE
OR ANYTHING.
IT'S OKAY,
I'M DONE BEING JEALOUS.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
DID YOU CHANGE
YOUR MESSAGE SOUND?
UM...
'CAUSE THAT SOUNDS
LIKE MINE.
(SIGHS)
I KINDA BORROWED IT,
AND THEN,
I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU SINCE LUNCH,
SO I HAD NO CHANCE
TO GIVE IT BACK.
YOU BORROWED IT.
(PHONE BEEPS)
FIND ANYTHING INTERESTING?
I WAS BEING PARANOID.
ALL THESE TEXTS
FROM THE SAME NUMBER, SO..
OH, GOD!
YOU CALLED IT.
I DIDN'T SAY WHO I WAS.
I FREAKED OUT AND HUNG UP.
MS. OH:
I KNOW YOUR MINDS
ARE ALREADY AT THE BIG GAME,
BUT I'LL NEED 50 MINUTES
OF YOUR ATTENTION.
MY FAMILY'S OFF LIMITS,
JENNA.
SO IS MY STUFF.
(DISGUSTED) NO WONDER
I CAN'T TRUST ANYONE.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
BIG ANNOUNCEMENT!
BIANCA:
YOU BROUGHT US ALL BROWNIES?
ALLI:
HMM... BETTER.
REMEMBER HOW YOU THOUGHT
IT WAS POINTLESS FOR US
TO ALL GO
TO THE GAME TOGETHER.
I STILL DO.
WELL, EVEN IF BIG D
DANCE CRUE'S...
PERFORMING THERE?
GIRLS:
(GASPS) OH!
IS THERE ANOTHER
BIG D DANCE CRUE?
WELL, I PULLED SOME MAJOR
STRINGS WITH MY BROTHER,
BUT IT'S GONNA BE AMAZING.
ALLI, WE'RE NOT READY!
READY, SHMREADY.
I JUST WANT PEOPLE TO SEE
THAT I HAVE MY OWN GROUP
AND THAT IT'S AWESOME.
SO, WAIT.
THIS IS ALL ABOUT POPULARITY?
UH, HELLO?
WHAT ELSE IS IT ABOUT?
(SCOFFS) DANCING?
DANCING EQUALS CONFIDENCE,
WHICH EQUALS COOLNESS,
WHICH EQUALS GETTING INVITED
TO ALL THE BEST PARTIES,
AND GETTING DREW -
OR SOMEONE LIKE DREW -
AS MY BOYFRIEND.
WOW.
YOU'VE REALLY GOT THIS
LITTLE PLAN ALL FIGURED OUT.
AND IT SEEMS LIKE
YOUR LITTLE PLAN
IS TO ARGUE
WITH EVERYTHING I SAY.
I'M NOT PERFORMING
AT ANY GAME TODAY.
THEN YOU'RE CUT!
(LAUGHS DERISIVELY)
LATER.
HAVE FUN BEING POPULAR.
OKAY, EVERYONE.
WE HAVE GOT
A LOT OF MOVES
TO CRAM INTO THOSE LITTLE
TINY BRAINS,
SO LET'S GET...STARTED.
UH...
WHERE ARE YOU GUYS GOING?
BIANCA'S RIGHT.
WE'RE A TEAM...
AND YOU'RE NOT ON IT.
ALLI:
(LAUGHS) YOU CAN'T KICK ME OFF
MY OWN... TEAM.
GUYS. GUYS, WAIT!
(SCOFFS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
COACH ARMSTRONG:
LET'S GIVE IT UP
FOR OUR NEWEST WIDE RECEIVER...
KC GUTHRIE!
PLAYERS:
YEAH, KC!
(APPLAUSE)
PLAYERS:
YEAH!
CONGRATULATIONS!
WHOO! IN THE HOUSE!
COACH ARMSTRONG:
OUR NEW STARTING KICKER...
ZANE PARK!
DREW:
AW, YEAH!
(APPLAUSE)
WHOO!
(LAUGHS)
COACH ARMSTRONG:
AND FINALLY,
STARTING QUARTERBACK
REQUIRES A LEADER.
A MAN OF SKILL, STRENGTH,
AND INTEGRITY.
AND THAT MAN...
IS RILEY STAVROS!
TEAMMATES:
YEAH! YEAH, RILEY!
(APPLAUSE)
I THOUGHT WE HAD A DEAL.
I CHANGED MY MIND.
TEAMMATES:
COME'RE, BUD!
YEAH, MAN!
COACH ARMSTRONG:
OKAY, PANTHERS!
BIG FIRST GAME TODAY!
FULLY DRESSED,
AND ON THE BUS IN 20!
LET'S GO!
PLAYER:
LET'S GO, PANTHERS!
LET'S GO, BOYS!
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
JENNA:
SO?
STARTING WIDE RECEIVER.
THAT'S AMAZING!
(SIGHS)
AND YOU'RE STILL MAD AT ME.
KC:
I'VE GOTTA GET TO THE BUS.
TALK TO ME.
PLEASE.
(SIGHS)
I SHOULD'VE NEVER
SNOOPED AROUND ON YOUR CELL.
I'M REALLY SORRY!
BUT IF WHATEVER'S GOING ON
WITH YOUR MOM
IS SUCH A BIG DEAL,
YOU CAN'T KEEP IT
ALL BOTTLED UP.
SHE'S OUT OF JAIL.
UH... OH MY GOSH!
WHEN DID SHE GET OUT?
EIGHT MONTHS AGO.
AND YOU STILL HAVEN'T
SEEN HER?
(HALF LAUGHS)
BEEN TRYING NOT TO
FOR EIGHT MONTHS.
BUT WHERE'S SHE LIVING?
CLOSE BY? FAR AWAY?
I THINK WE'VE TALKED ENOUGH.
(FRUSTRATED SIGH)
OKAY.
AUDRA:
AH! COACH ARMSTRONG!
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
MY SON IS HAZED
AND NOTHING HAPPENS?
COACH ARMSTRONG:
THE INVESTIGATION IS ONGOING,
MRS. TORRES.
DREW WAS CLEARLY TARGETED.
AND WHEN HE TRANSFERRED
TO THIS SCHOOL,
HE EXPECTED A FAIR CHANCE
AT STARTING QUARTERBACK!
HE WAS GIVEN A CHANCE
IN TRYOUTS,
LIKE EVERYBODY ELSE.
OH...
BUT ONLY ONE PLAYER WAS TIED
TO THE FLAGPOLE THIS MORNING.
WELL, YOU LEAVE ME
NO OTHER CHOICE.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO HAVE
ANOTHER CHAT
WITH YOUR PRINCIPAL.
(SIGHS)
RILEY:
DUDE, WHAT'S YOUR MOM DOING?
IF I CAN'T PLAY,
NOBODY CAN.
ARE YOU GONNA RAT ON ME?
I DON'T HAVE TO.
COACH ARMSTRONG:
EVERYBODY ON THE BUS!
LET'S GO.
SAV: (ON PA)
PRESIDENT SAV HERE
WITH A REMINDER
THAT BUSES WILL TAKE
PANTHER FANS TO BARDELL.
GO PANTHERS!
ALLI:
ARE YOU GOING TO THE GAME?
UH, THE FOOTBALL GAME?
NOT IF I CAN HELP IT.
YEAH, ME NEITHER.
WELL, WHAT ABOUT
YOUR DANCE CREW?
(SCOFFS)
THEY'RE NOT MY "CRUE"
ANYMORE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
THEY DIDN'T CARE ABOUT
FOOTBALL GAMES OR PARTIES.
ALL THEY WANTED TO DO
WAS DANCE, DANCE, DANCE.
HMM, WHAT KIND
OF A DUMMY
THINKS A DANCE CREW
IS ABOUT DANCING?
(SIGHS)
THIS ISN'T FUNNY, CLARE.
EVEN MY OWN CREW
DOESN'T WANT ME.
I MEAN, IS THIS IT?
WILL I MISS EVERY FOOTBALL GAME
'CAUSE I HAVE NO ONE
TO GO WITH?
(SIGHS)
NOT THIS ONE.
REALLY?
YOU'RE THE BEST!
JUST REMEMBER THAT
WHEN I DRAG YOU
TO THE SCIENCE CENTRE
THIS WEEKEND.
(STUDENTS TALKING AND CHEERING)
(DRUM BEATS)
RILEY:
ZANE, CONGRATULATIONS ON KICKER.
YOU EARNED IT.
SAME TO YOU,
I GUESS.
I HOPE IT WAS WORTH IT.
EXCUSE ME?
COACH ARMSTRONG:
HOLD UP, GUYS!
YEAH.
OKAY.
I JUST GOT AN ORDER
FROM THE SCHOOL BOARD.
UNTIL THEY INVESTIGATE
TODAY'S INCIDENT,
THE PANTHERS WON'T BE
PLAYING FOOTBALL.
TEAM MEMBERS:
WHAT? COME ON!
YOU'RE KIDDING ME!
ALL THIS DRAMA
BECAUSE YOU THINK GAY GUYS
CAN'T PLAY FOOTBALL.
I HAVE SOMETHING
TO TELL EVERYONE.
ALL OF THIS HAPPENED
BECAUSE I'M...
I'M...
I SHOULDN'T BE
THE STARTING QUARTERBACK
OF THIS TEAM.
BOY:
COME ON, MAN!
THE FLAGPOLE THING?
IT WAS ME.
(SIGHS) I WAS SCARED
I COULDN'T BEAT DREW.
DREW?
LOOKS LIKE YOU HAVE
THE START, SON.
(LAUGHS)
COME WITH ME.
(TEAMMATES MURMUR)
YOU WIN.
(PLAYERS CHATTING)
SAV:
ALL RIGHT!
HEY, EVERYONE.
OKAY, SO BEFORE WE START
OUR GAME,
WE HAVE A VERY SPECIAL
PERFORMANCE
FROM DEGRASSI'S VERY OWN...
BIG D DANCE CRUE!
BOY IN CROWD:
(LAUGHS) WHOO!
OH NO.
CROWD:
ALL RIGHT! LET'S SEE BIG D!
ALLI?
WHAT?
(CROWD LAUGHING AND TALKING)
HI...
I'M ALLI BHANDARI,
AND THIS IS... WELL,
I AM...
DEGRASSI'S BIG D DANCE CRUE!
WHOO!
(CROWD LAUGHS)
I'M A BAD FRIEND,
I'M A KIND OF BAD DANCER,
AND A MEGA-BAD CLUB ORGANIZER.
BUT I LOVE MY SCHOOL,
AND THE PANTHERS.
AND IF YOU DO TOO,
FEEL FREE TO JOIN!
PEOPLE IN CROWD:
(LAUGHING) ALL RIGHT!
HEY!
♪♪♪
PEOPLE IN CROWD:
WHOO! WHOO!
COME ON!
♪ There you go,
you're back again, babe ♪
AW, SHOULD WE GO RESCUE HER?
I THINK SHE MIGHT BE
BEYOND THAT POINT.
♪ You're still so sleepy
when you're struggling ♪
WHAT KIND OF FRIENDS
WOULD WE BE
IF WE DIDN'T TRY?
OH, I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M DOING THIS.
♪ That you're dying here ♪
♪ You make my friends all sad ♪
♪ I know that you're harmless ♪
♪ And you're not so bad ♪
♪ Well I can be your friend ♪
♪ Will you feel
the lovin', baby ♪
♪ Will you bend down? ♪
(HORN BLATTS)
WHOO!
(CROWD CLAPPING)
(CROWD CHEERS LOUDLY)
♪ Will you bend down? ♪
♪ You got his ghost
to disappear ♪
♪ But I'll soon forget ♪
STARTING QUARTERBACK
HAS TO BE PROPERLY HYDRATED.
ARMSTRONG LET YOU STAY?
TO WATCH,
NOT TO PLAY.
AND I GOT A FIVE GAME
SUSPENSION.
YOU KNOW, I'M SORRY THE WAY
THINGS TURNED OUT.
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
ANY CHANCES, UH,
YOU CAN HELP ME RUN SOME PLAYS?
ARE YOU DREAMING?
WHAT ELSE ARE YOU GONNA DO,
SITTING ON THE SIDELINES
FOR THE NEXT FIVE GAMES?
I'M COUNTING DOWN
EVERY MINUTE
UNTIL I COME BACK.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(CROWD CHEERS)
THAT SHOULD BE YOU OUT THERE.
OR, AT LEAST,
THE FOOTBALL YOU.
HOPE SOMEDAY
IT CAN BE ALL OF ME.
(CROWD CHEERS)
OKAY, GUYS, LET'S GO!
I WANNA SEE SOME HUSTLE!