ALLI:
(FRUSTRATED SIGH)
COME ON, MALIKA,
ANSWER THE PHONE!
(SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
(PHONE BEEPS)
ARE MOM AND DAD UP?
NOT YET, BUT I THINK
I HEARD THE BATHROOM.
ALLI:
(SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
WHERE'S MALIKA?
SHE HAD TO...
CATCH AN EARLY BUS.
(DOOR OPENS)
ACTUALLY,
SHE'S RIGHT HERE!
MORNING, SAV.
I HOPE YOU HAD A GREAT TIME
WITH YOUR BOYFRIEND,
SO MUCH FOR BEING HOME
BY SUNRISE!
I LOST TRACK OF TIME.
YOU COULD'VE GOT ME
IN SO MUCH TROUBLE!
I'M SORRY,
BUT YOU KNOW HOW IT IS.
MY PARENTS DON'T LET ME
DO ANYTHING!
AND NEXT TIME,
I'LL COVER FOR YOU.
MALIKA,
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
MY PARENTS THINK
THAT I'M TROUBLE,
AND THAT YOU'RE PERFECT!
THEY'RE HOPING
THAT YOU'LL CHANGE ME.
TRUST ME!
I'LL HAVE YOU BACK
IN YOUR PARENTS GOOD BOOKS
IN NO TIME.
AS LONG AS YOU DON'T MIND
COVERING FOR ME
ONCE IN A WHILE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
THAT THIS MIGHT BE
THE BEGINNING
OF AN AMAZING FRIENDSHIP.
(FAKE LAUGH)
(LAUGHS)
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever, Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
WE NEED TO TALK.
OH, DO WE NOW?
YEAH. YESTERDAY,
I WON THAT GAME.
I PROVED THAT BIANCA
ISN'T A DISTRACTION
AND YET, YOU GUYS STILL
TREAT HER LIKE TRASH!
WE DIDN'T TREAT HER
LIKE TRASH.
OUR GIRLFRIENDS
JUST DON'T LIKE HER,
ALL RIGHT?
WE DIDN'T WANT THINGS
TO GET WEIRD.
ARE YOU THAT WORRIED ABOUT
WHAT YOUR GIRLFRIENDS THINK?
YOU GUYS HAVE SOMETHING
PERSONAL AGAINST HER?
NO. I MEAN,
I BARELY KNOW HER.
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
ALL YOU KNOW
IS HER REPUTATION.
AND SHE'S NOT LIKE THAT
AT ALL!
SO, WHAT DO YOU SAY?
COFFEES AT THE DOT,
AFTER SCHOOL?
(SCOFFS)
PLEASE? FOR ME?
OKAY, BUT IT'S GONNA BE
A TOUGH SELL.
LET'S GO PRACTICE!
♪♪♪
(SIGHS)
♪ Hey hey hey ♪
♪ Oh hey hey hey ♪
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
MA?
(TEARFUL SIGH)
PIPE DOWN, SWEETHEART.
I'VE GOT YOUR BREAKFAST
RIGHT HERE.
THANKS, BUT...
BUT I'M NOT HUNGRY.
ARE YOU FEELING ALL RIGHT?
YOU LOOK A LITTLE PALE.
(SIGHS)
I WAS HOPING WE COULD TALK
ABOUT YESTERDAY.
WHEN ZANE WAS HERE,
AND YOU WALKED IN?
DID YOU TWO GET
ANY STUDYING DONE?
STUDYING? NO!
ZANE LEFT IN A HURRY.
YOU SAW US, RIGHT?
YEAH,
YOU TWO GOOFING OFF.
MA, WE WEREN'T GOOFING OFF!
IT SURE LOOKED LIKE
YOU WEREN'T DOING HOMEWORK.
NOW, EAT!
YOU'RE GOING TO BE
LATE FOR SCHOOL.
RILEY: BUT MA!
MRS. STAVROS: NO BUTS, MISTER!
EAT!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(SIGHS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
MORNING, TINY DANCER.
YOU STILL GOT THOSE MOVES?
YOU TELL ME.
SO, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
AFTER SCHOOL?
I WAS GONNA GO
BLOW OFF SOME STEAM.
YOU SHOULD COME!
GONNA BE A HUGE JAM.
CAN'T.
BASKETBALL FINALS.
BUT WHEN WE WIN,
WE'RE GOING TO CELEBRATE
AND I WANT YOU
TO BE THERE.
YOU GET HIT IN THE HEAD
LAST NIGHT?
THE TEAM DOESN'T
WANT ME THERE.
I'VE GOT A PLAN:
THE DOT,
AFTER SCHOOL -
A LITTLE ICE BREAKER.
YOU WANT TO KEEP
HANGING OUT, RIGHT?
YEAH.
WELL, IT WOULD BE A LOT EASIER
IF YOU AND MY FRIENDS
DIDN'T HATE
EACH OTHER'S GUTS.
SO, CAN WE TRY
AND GET ALONG?
(SIGHS)
YOU'RE LUCKY YOU'RE HOT.
(LAUGHS)
PHEW!
GIRL:
BYE, GUYS!
(STUDENTS LAUGH AND CHATTER)
OH! I HOPE THERE'S
NO GARLIC
IN THAT TZATZIKI.
HEY.
I'M, UH, I'M SORRY
YOU HAD TO COME OUT
TO YOUR MOM LIKE THAT.
WHAT DID SHE SAY?
NOTHING.
WAIT...
YOUR MOM CATCHES YOU
MAKING OUT WITH A GUY,
AND SHE SAYS NOTHING?
IT'S LIKE NOTHING HAPPENED.
SO I GUESS YOU HAVE
AN OUT.
I MEAN, IF YOUR MOM
WANTS TO PRETEND
LIKE SHE SAW NOTHING,
LET HER.
COME OUT
WHEN YOU'RE READY.
(SIGHS)
I DON'T WANT
TO PRETEND ANYMORE.
WELL,
THEN YOU'VE GOTTA
FIND A WAY
TO HELP YOUR MOM
FACE THE FACTS.
ALLI:
SO AFTER BOILERGATE
I DUMPED DREW,
WHICH REALLY SUCKED.
GOD, HE'S SO BEAUTIFUL!
STUPID,
BUT BEAUTIFUL.
MALIKA:
WHY IS IT THE CUTE ONES
ALWAYS ARE?
ALLI:
(LAUGHS)
I KNOW, RIGHT?
IT FEELS SO GOOD TO VENT.
SO, ARE WE REALLY
GONNA PRAY?
HILARIOUS.
IT'S JUST THE PERFECT EXCUSE
FOR THE SCHOOL'S
TWO MUSLIM STUDENTS
TO GET A LITTLE FRESH AIR.
(LAUGHS)
(SIGHS)
(LIGHTER CLICKS)
ALLI:
SMOKING ON SCHOOL PROPERTY?
UH...
DO YOU WANT?
NO, I'M GOOD.
OOH! HOLD THIS FOR A SEC?
(SIGHS)
HEY, SMOKING IS BAD ENOUGH.
BUT SMOKING DURING
PRAYER BREAK?
THAT'S LIKE HARAAM PLUS!
THROW IT AWAY!
WHAT? HERE.
MRS. BHANDARI:
ALLIA?
ARE YOU SMOKING?
WHAT? MOM,
IT-IT'S NOT MINE,
I SWEAR!
MALIKA:
ALLI, DON'T LIE TO YOUR MOM.
MRS. BHANDARI:
I COME TO MEET
YOUR NEW PRINCIPAL
AND I FIND YOU SMOKING!
ALLI:
BUT IT'S NOT MINE!
HERE, TAKE IT!
YOU'RE GOING TO APOLOGIZE
TO YOUR PRINCIPAL
AND THEN WE'RE GOING HOME.
ALLI:
BUT, MOM...
COME WITH ME.
NOW!
(SIGHS)
♪♪♪
MA?
I'M GOING FOR A RUN.
♪♪♪
♪ Shut down the trains ♪
♪ No fuel for the planes ♪
♪ It's all right
'cause we like it here ♪
(DOOR SLAMS)
(DISHES CLINK)
SO, YOU GONNA SHOOT
ANOTHER THREE TONIGHT?
THAT'S THE PLAN.
JENNA, YOU KNOW BIANCA,
RIGHT?
SO, HOW'S THE PREGNANCY?
UM...
SO FAR, SO GOOD.
WELL, YOU LOOK GREAT.
BARELY BIGGER
THAN BEFORE.
WHAT BIANCA MEANT TO SAY,
IS THAT YOU'RE PERFECT.
NOW AND THEN.
TOTALLY.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
AN IDIOT
FOR BUYING
THOSE DIET PILLS.
JENNA:
GREAT, SO I'M FAT
AND STUPID?
BIANCA DIDN'T MEAN THAT.
I-I SWEAR,
I DIDN'T.
I TOLD YOU THIS
WAS A BAD IDEA.
COME ON, JENNA,
CHILL OUT!
DUDE, DON'T TALK
TO MY GIRLFRIEND LIKE THAT!
SHE'S BEING UNREASONABLE!
WELL, BETTER THAT
THAN A SKANK
WHO TAKES BOYS
TO THE BOILER ROOM.
(LAUGHS)
I TRIED.
BUT I'M NOT GONNA LISTEN
TO THESE GUYS
TALK CRAP ABOUT ME.
DREW:
WAY TO MAKE HER FEEL WELCOME.
SHE SAID
ONE THING WRONG,
AND YOU GUYS
JUMPED ON HER!
SHE CALLED ME FAT!
SHE WASN'T WRONG!
I'M PREGNANT!
(SIGHS)
YOU GUYS THINK YOU'RE
SO MUCH BETTER THAN HER.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE
PARENTS AT FIFTEEN.
REAL WINNERS.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
BIANCA'S GREAT.
YOU GUYS ARE THE PROBLEM.
(SCOFFS INDIGNANTLY)
(DOOR SLAMS)
♪♪♪
♪ I'm the fool ♪
♪ I've always been ♪
♪ But you are the girl ♪
♪ You're the girl ♪
MA?
THANKS FOR CLEANING
MY ROOM.
MRS. STAVROS:
I SWEAR,
IF IT WASN'T FOR ME,
YOU'D NEVER SEE
THE FLOOR IN HERE.
IS THERE ANYTHING
YOU WANNA TALK ABOUT?
ONLY HOW LUCKY YOU ARE
TO HAVE A MOM
WHO STILL CLEANS YOUR ROOM.
ANYTHING ELSE?
MRS. STAVROS:
NOTHING COMES TO MIND.
YOU GONNA SHOWER
BEFORE DINNER?
(SIGHS)
(GIRL LAUGHS)
♪♪♪
BIANCA:
I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO INSULT JENNA.
I REALLY TRIED.
YEAH,
BUT MY FRIENDS DIDN'T.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE I HAVE
TO PLAY BASKETBALL WITH THEM,
INSTEAD OF HANG OUT
WITH YOU.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO GO.
DITCH THE TEAM?
THEY'D TOTALLY LOSE
WITHOUT YOU.
YOU'RE FREE?
BIANCA:
AS A BIRD.
I WAS JUST GOING
TO CHILL OUT HERE.
RON-RON:
MAYBE DO SOME MAGIC MUSHROOMS?
DRUGS?
NOT NOW, RON-RON.
MY BOY HERE DOESN'T
RIDE THAT TRAIN.
HMM.
HE'S MISSING OUT.
BIANCA:
BESIDES, DON'T YOU HAVE
THAT BIG GAME TO PLAY?
RON-RON:
I GUESS IT'S JUST YOU AND ME, B.
IT'D SERVE THOSE GUYS RIGHT
IF I DIDN'T SHOW.
OKAY.
LET'S DO THIS!
♪♪♪
♪ Oh oh oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh-oh-oh ♪
(LAUGHS)
WHAT ARE THESE?
RILEY:
EVIDENCE.
MISSION FAILED, ZANE.
MISSION FAILED
BIG TIME.
YOUR MOM FOUND THESE?
AND SHE STILL DIDN'T
SAY ANYTHING?
IF MY MOM WANTS TO LIVE
IN A FANTASY WORLD
WHERE HER STRAIGHT SON
READS...
"HUNKZ" MAGAZINE,
MAYBE THAT'S OKAY.
REALLY?
SO NEXT FALL,
WHEN YOU ENROLL
AT EASTERN
AS AN OPENLY GAY
QUARTERBACK...
I'LL BE FAR AWAY
FROM HOME.
MY MOM CAN PRETEND
WHATEVER SHE WANTS.
EVER THOUGHT ABOUT
TELLING YOUR DAD?
WHAT'S THE POINT?
I MIGHT AS WELL RIDE IT OUT
FOR THE NEXT SIX MONTHS.
SO, DATE NIGHT TONIGHT?
OH, I CAN'T.
DAD AND I ARE HITTING UP
THE BASEBALL GAME.
FATHER SON TRADITION.
UM...RAIN CHECK?
SURE.
ALL RIGHT.
ALLI:
MOM, THE CIGARETTE WAS MALIKA'S,
NOT MINE.
YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE ME!
YOU PROMISED
YOU WOULD CHANGE.
WE GAVE YOU
A SECOND CHANCE,
AND YOU THREW IT
IN OUR FACES!
I HAVE CHANGED!
BUT ALL THIS BAD STUFF
JUST KEEPS HAPPENING TO ME!
YES, IT'S ALWAYS
SOMEONE ELSE'S FAULT,
ISN'T IT?
THIS TIME IT WAS!
HOW CAN I BELIEVE YOU?
BECAUSE EVERYTHING I'VE DONE
SINCE LEAVING DEGRASSI
WAS TO EARN YOUR RESPECT!
I NEED YOU TO LISTEN!
YOU'VE MALIGNED MALIKA,
YOU'VE EARNED
A SUSPENSION!
WHEN DOES IT END?
IT NEVER STARTED!
BUT YOU AND DAD
ARE SO CONVINCED
THAT I'M SUCH
A TERRIBLE PERSON
THAT THERE'S NOTHING
I CAN DO!
MRS. BHANDARI:
CLEARLY THIS SCHOOL
ISN'T GOING
TO STRAIGHTEN YOU OUT
LIKE WE'D HOPED.
THE CIGARETTE WASN'T MINE.
YOUR FATHER'S GONNA BE
SO DISAPPOINTED.
JUST GO TO YOUR ROOM,
PLEASE.
I CAN'T LISTEN
TO ANY MORE OF YOUR LIES.
(SIGHS)
♪♪♪
♪ If it's a dream ♪
♪ It's all it seems ♪
♪ You could be a baseball star ♪
♪ On a beautiful team ♪
OKAY.
SO THERE'S THIS
INVISIBLE BOX, RIGHT?
IT'S GOT FOUR SIDES,
AND A TOP.
AND NOW I'M GONNA PUT IT
ON TOP OF YOUR HEAD.
(LAUGHS)
THAT'S AMAZING!
(BOTH LAUGH)
I KNOW, RIGHT?
MY MOUTH IS REALLY DRY.
LIKE REALLY,
REALLY DRY.
IS MY MOUTH SUPPOSED
TO GET THIS DRY?
HMM!
ALMOST GAME TIME.
G-GAME TIME?
WON'T IT BE AWESOME?
TOMORROW THEY'LL ALL
BE CRYING,
"WHERE WERE YOU, DREW,
WE LOST!"
"WHY DIDN'T YOU SAVE US?"
"COACH WAS SO LET DOWN."
(GIGGLES)
(HALF LAUGHS)
NO.
NO, NO, I'VE-
I'VE-I'VE GOTTA GET
OUT OF HERE!
WHAT, NOW?
EVERYTHING'S FINE!
NO, I-I CAN'T MISS
THE GAME,
I-I CAN'T LET THE TEAM DOWN!
BIANCA:
OKAY, YOU CAN'T BE PLAYING
ANYTHING,
RIGHT NOW.
SHROOMS ARE JUST STARTING
TO KICK IN.
THIS GETS WORSE?
I'M SO STUPID FOR LETTING YOU
TALK ME INTO THIS!
BIANCA:
JUST CALM DOWN!
CALM DOWN?
MY MOM IS GOING TO BE
AT THAT GAME.
IF I MISS IT,
SHE'S GOING TO KILL ME.
I'M SO STUPID FOR LETTING YOU
TALK ME INTO THIS.
EVERYONE WAS RIGHT ABOUT YOU!
RILEY:
HEY, MA.
WHERE'S DAD?
WE'RE GONNA BE LATE
FOR THE GAME.
HE WENT WITH UNCLE PAUL.
OH. WHY?
I TOLD HIM TO GO
WITHOUT YOU.
I THOUGHT YOU WOULDN'T
BE INTERESTED,
ON ACCOUNT OF...
YOU KNOW.
ON ACCOUNT OF WHAT?
THAT YOU'RE GOING
THROUGH SOMETHING.
RILEY:
BUT I STILL LOVE SPORTS!
BEING GAY DOESN'T CHANGE
WHO I AM!
MRS. STAVROS:
YOU'RE NOT GAY!
YOU SAW ME MAKING OUT
WITH MY BOYFRIEND!
I'M GAY!
MRS. STAVROS:
IT'S A PHASE!
YOU'RE YOUNG,
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU ARE!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
MOM, JUST LISTEN.
I'M DONE DISCUSSING IT!
RILEY:
WHEN DAD COMES HOME,
WE'RE ALL GONNA SIT DOWN
AND TALK ABOUT THIS.
DON'T BOTHER YOUR FATHER
WITH THIS!
MOM...
DON'T!
♪♪♪
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(SPECTATORS CHATTER)
(SNICKERS)
(GIGGLES STRANGELY)
OH!
OH HEY, GUYS.
WHERE WERE YOU?
DOESN'T MATTER,
I'M HERE NOW, RIGHT?
(GIGGLES)
HEY, IS IT...
IS IT THIRSTY IN HERE,
OR IS IT JUST ME?
GIRL:
COME ON, DEGRASSI!
YOU SURE YOU'RE OKAY
TO PLAY, BRO?
SURE.
I JUST CAN'T LOOK
AT MY HANDS,
THAT'S ALL.
AAAAH...
STOP IT!
KC:
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
ARE YOU ON SOMETHING?
HUH? WHAT?
NO!
DAVE:
YOU'RE ACTING KINDA FUNNY, BRO.
ARE YOU HIGH?
(GIGGLES)
NOPE, I'M FINE.
I DON'T BELIEVE YOU.
SSSHHH!
I TOOK SOME SHROOMS.
(LAUGHS WILDLY)
BEFORE THE BIGGEST GAME
OF THE YEAR?
AUDRA:
HEY, YOU BOYS READY
TO KNOCK 'EM DEAD?
DAVE:
YEAH.
JUST CAME BY
TO WISH YOU LUCK.
MAKE US PROUD!
THANKS.
UH...
EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, GREAT.
WHOA!
OKAY.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD COME WITH ME.
OKAY!
LET'S GO.
(DREW GIGGLES)
(TRAFFIC RUMBLES)
RILEY:
HEY.
HEY!
THANKS FOR MEETING ME HERE.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE BASEBALL GAME?
MY DAD WENT WITHOUT ME.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
I TOLD MY MOM
I WAS GAY,
AND SHE REFUSED TO TALK.
EVEN FORBADE ME
TO TELL MY DAD.
THAT SUCKS.
YEAH.
WHAT ELSE CAN I DO?
GIVE HER TIME?
THIS IS ALL NEW
TO YOUR MOM.
I MEAN HOW LONG DID IT TAKE
YOU TO ACCEPT YOURSELF?
FOREVER.
MM-HMM.
BUT YOU GOT THERE.
(LAUGHS)
WHERE WOULD I BE WITHOUT YOU?
YOU'VE COME A LONG WAY,
AND SO WILL YOUR PARENTS.
EVENTUALLY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
TOMORROW NIGHT?
YOU WANNA CATCH
A GAME WITH ME?
JUST TRY AND STOP ME.
(LAUGHS)
(SPECTATORS CHATTER)
(DREW GIGGLES)
(GASPS)
AUDRA:
ARE YOU ON DRUGS?
(GIGGLES)
DREW,
ANSWER THE QUESTION!
SORRY, WHAT QUESTION?
ARE YOU HIGH?
YES, MA'AM.
VERY.
(FRUSTRATED SIGH)
(GIGGLES)
WHAT DID YOU TAKE?
WOULD YOU STOP
STARING AT MY SHIRT?
(BUZZER SOUNDS)
I'M GONNA GO TELL THE COACH
YOU'RE NOT FEELING WELL,
YOU STAY HERE!
WHA-
AM-AM I IN TROUBLE?
HUH!
BIG, BIG TROUBLE.
(ALLI SOBS)
SAV:
DON'T WORRY.
THIS'LL ALL BLOW OVER
IN NO TIME.
HEY, THEY CAN'T STAY
MAD FOREVER, RIGHT?
I THINK I COULD
SOLVE WORLD HUNGER,
AND THEY'D STILL THINK
I'M A TERRIBLE PERSON.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
THEY STILL LOVE YOU.
IN THEIR OWN WAY.
YOU BELIEVE ME, RIGHT?
THE CIGARETTE WASN'T MINE!
DO YOU REMEMBER OUR...
"SMOKING IS STUPID" LECTURES?
YOU WERE ONLY TEN,
BUT I KNEW I GOT
THROUGH TO YOU.
(SOBS)
THANKS, SAV.
YOU'RE ALL I HAVE.
I DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH LONGER
I CAN TAKE THIS.
(CRYING)
IT'LL LOOK BETTER
IN THE MORNING.
I PROMISE.
(SIGHS)
(CRYING)
SAV: (ON P.A.)
DESPITE THEIR BEST EFFORTS,
OUR B-BALL BOYS
CAME UP JUST SHORT
OF WINNING FINALS
LAST NIGHT.
BETTER LUCK NEXT TIME, BOYS.
DREW:
DUDE, I'M SORRY.
REALLY SORRY.
YEAH, ME TOO.
SO, YOU GROUNDED?
OH, YES.
AND I HAVE TO SEE
A COUNSELOR
FOR THE NEXT MONTH
ABOUT DRUG ABUSE,
AND I'LL BE LUCKY
IF I GET TO LEAVE MY HOUSE
BEFORE I'M THIRTY.
BUT I'M-I'M SORRY.
REALLY.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
UH WE BOTH HAVE
SPARE NOW,
IF YOU UH WANNA GO
SHOOT SOME HOOPS?
I'M SORRY,
I'VE GOT PLANS.
SURE.
UM...MAYBE LATER.
(SIGHS)
(SCOFFS)
(DREW SIGHS)
UM...
I'M SORRY FOR THAT STUFF
I SAID YESTERDAY,
IT WAS MY DECISION
TO TAKE THE SHROOMS,
AND SKIP THE GAME.
NOT YOURS.
YOU DONE?
YEAH.
GOOD.
LET'S HANG OUT.
WAIT, YOU DON'T CARE
ABOUT THAT?
THAT YOU SAID A FEW
STUPID THINGS
WHILE YOU WERE HIGH?
I'M NOT YOUR JUDGEY FRIENDS.
SO...
ARE YOU COMING?
UNLESS YOU HAVE
A BETTER OFFER?
(SIGHS)
I DON'T.
♪♪♪