MR. BHANDARI:
WHERE'S YOUR SISTER?
IS SHE UP?
I DON'T KNOW,
I HAVEN'T SEEN HER.
MRS. BHANDARI:
SHE'S SUSPENDED FROM SCHOOL
AND SHE'S SLEEPING IN?
UNACCEPTABLE.
MM...
SHE'S PROBABLY SULKING.
WE HAD A FIGHT
LAST NIGHT.
MR. BHANDARI:
WHAT ABOUT?
OH, I NEED A DRUMMER
FOR MY UNIVERSITY MUSIC DEMO,
AND THE ONLY GOOD DRUMMER
I COULD FIND
IS SOMEONE SHE HATES.
SO SHE WANTS ME
TO GET RID OF HIM.
AND JEOPARDIZE YOUR CHANCES
OF GETTING ACCEPTED
INTO UNIVERSITY?
HAH!
DAD, SHE'S IN ENOUGH TROUBLE
AS IT IS.
MR. BHANDARI:
ALLIA!
WHY DOES SHE HATE
THIS DRUMMER?
DAD, IT'S FINE.
SHE JUST NEEDS SOME TIME
TO GET OVER IT.
SHE'S GONE,
AND HER BED HASN'T BEEN
SLEPT IN.
DO YOU KNOW
WHERE SHE IS?
I'M SURE SHE HASN'T GONE FAR.
UH, SHE'S... SHE'S...
JUST TRYING TO FREAK
YOU GUYS OUT
AND GET YOU TO PANIC.
MR. BHANDARI:
WELL, IT'S NOT GOING TO WORK.
AND IF SHE THINKS
SHE WAS IN TROUBLE BEFORE,
SHE HAS NO IDEA.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever, Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(LOW HUM OF STUDENT CHATTER)
♪ You had such a lovely
crooked smile ♪
♪ And blue eyes
that were grey ♪
♪ When it was raining ♪
♪ And I still have
the bracelet ♪
♪ With the gold
and ivory clovers ♪
♪ That you made me ♪
ABOUT LAST NIGHT...
ME TALKING TO FITZ,
I KNOW IT FREAKED YOU OUT
AND I'M SORRY.
ELI:
IT'S OKAY.
(SIGHS)
WELL...
THEN WHAT IS IT?
DO YOU NOT LIKE MY EDIT
ON "STALKER/ANGEL?"
SHHH!
I'M READING.
DID I ADD TOO MUCH?
OH, I DID ADD TOO MUCH!
YOU HATE IT.
I WRECKED
YOUR HORROR STORY!
(SIGHS)
HONESTLY?
IT'S WAY BETTER.
I'M SUPER IMPRESSED,
CLARE!
REALLY?
(SIGHS HAPPILY)
I AM SO GLAD
TO HEAR YOU SAY THAT!
AND YOU KNOW,
YOU HAVE NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
NO ONE IS GOING
TO COME BETWEEN US,
I PROMISE.
LET'S PROMISE...
TO NOT FIGHT AGAIN.
(LAUGHS)
(BELL RINGS)
TWO HOURS
OF MATH HOMEWORK?
WE'RE MORE THAN HALFWAY
THROUGH SENIOR YEAR!
HAVEN'T WE PROVEN
OURSELVES?
I'M EXHAUSTED,
I NEED A BREAK.
MY SISTER HEATHER SAYS DAYTONA
IS TOTALLY THE PLACE
FOR SPRING BREAK.
TONS OF HOT GIRLS,
WORKING THEIR BIKINIS
ON THE BEACH.
YEAH, IT REALLY
MAKES ME WONDER
IF I SHOULD
TAKE UP LESBIANISM,
YOU KNOW,
JUST FOR KICKS.
SAV!
HELLO.
WHERE ARE YOU?
I'M LISTENING.
I'M JUST CAUGHT UP
IN THE DRAMA
OF THE ALLI BHANDARI SHOW.
SPOILER ALERT:
ALLI'S GONE!
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
"GONE"?
I DON'T KNOW,
SHE JUST TOOK OFF
SOMETIME LAST NIGHT.
LOOK, YOU DON'T THINK
SHE RAN AWAY FOR REAL?
NO, NO, SHE'S JUST TRYING
TO STIR UP DRAMA.
SAV? YOUR MOM CALLED.
SHE NEEDS YOU AT HOME.
DID SHE SAY
WHAT IT WAS ABOUT?
SHE JUST SAID
IT WAS URGENT.
HEY.
(KEYS CLACK)
♪♪♪
♪ I'm a stranger ♪
♪ These words are foreign ♪
♪ On my tongue ♪
♪ You'd hate yourself ♪
♪ If you knew what I was doing ♪
♪ In your name ♪
♪ Well maybe not ♪
♪ If it's all the same ♪
♪ It's all the same ♪
♪ And we're all the same ♪
YES.
THANK YOU, OFFICER.
THE POLICE HAVE NOTHING
SO FAR.
THEN WHAT'S THE EMERGENCY?
I CALLED ALLI'S FRIENDS;
NO ONE HAS SEEN
OR HEARD FROM HER.
THEN I HAD A GOOD LOOK
THROUGH ALLI'S ROOM.
SHE TOOK A BAG
AND SOME CLOTHES!
WELL, SHE'S A DRAMA QUEEN,
REMEMBER?
SHE'S TRYING
TO MAKE IT LOOK GOOD.
JUST CHILL.
SHE'S MY DAUGHTER,
SAVTAJ!
I WORRY;
THAT'S WHAT PARENTS DO.
WELL, YOU ALREADY
CALLED THE POLICE,
WHICH IS POINTLESS
BECAUSE SHE'S GONNA COME
WALTZING THROUGH THAT DOOR
ANY SECOND.
THERE'S NOTHING WE CAN DO NOW
BUT WAIT.
THERE IS SOMETHING
WE CAN DO.
YOU'RE GOOD
AT COMPUTERS.
YOU WANT ME TO HACK
ALLI'S LAPTOP?
WOULD YOU?
WE'LL GO THROUGH HER EMAILS.
MOM, THAT IS SO WRONG!
MRS. BHANDARI:
WE NEED TO KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON
WITH HER, SAVTAJ.
DO IT FOR ME.
MAN, IF ALLI KNEW I WAS TRYING
TO CRACK HER PASSWORD...
(BELL RINGS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
WHAT IS GOING ON,
FITZ?
YOU GOT MY EMAILS.
GOOD.
LOOK, I'M CONCERNED
ABOUT YOU AND ELI.
STOP IT.
ELI AND I ARE GREAT.
AND BESIDES,
IT'S NOT YOUR PLACE
TO BE CONCERNED.
I'M JUST LOOKING OUT
FOR A FRIEND.
WHERE DID YOU GET THE IDEA
THAT WE'RE FRIENDS?
AND WHY ARE YOU SENDING ME
EMAILS AT 3 A.M.?
ARE YOU CYBER-STALKING ME
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT?
NO, I WASN'T.
I WAS IN AN INTERNET CAFE
AND I WAS TOTALLY BORED.
WHAT WERE YOU DOING
IN AN INTERNET CAFE
AT 3 A.M.?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
IT'S OPEN ALL NIGHT.
I WAS TRYING TO SLEEP.
AND YOU CAN'T SLEEP
AT HOME?
NOPE.
BUT WHAT DO YOU CARE?
WHAT ABOUT FATHER GREG?
JUST DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME,
OKAY?
I'M JUST TRYING TO HELP.
LIKE YOU SAID BEFORE,
WE'RE NOT FRIENDS.
BLAIR BONGARD:
I'M NOT ONE OF THESE STRICT
HELICOPTER PARENTS.
I'M FINE WITH YOU DOING ANYTHING
WITH CALEB.
AS LONG AS THERE'S NO RUNNING,
PLAYING IN THE SUN,
OR TOUCHING ANY TOYS
MADE FROM SYNTHETIC MATERIALS.
OTHER THAN THAT,
HAVE FUN!
JENNA:
GOT IT.
AND WE ARE GONNA HAVE FUN,
RIGHT, CALEB?
CALEB IS WHAT WE CALL
"CONVERSATIONALLY SELECTIVE."
JENNA:
OH! YOU MEAN
HE'S A LITTLE BIT SHY?
BLAIR BONGARD:
I WOULD PREFER...
IF YOU DIDN'T USE THE "S" WORD
AROUND HIM!
MY CHOICE.
CALEB, YOU HAVE FUN
WITH KC AND JENNA,
AND I'LL SEE YOU LATER,
OKAY?
(LAUGHS AWKWARDLY)
DO YOU LIKE MUSIC,
CALEB?
OH WELL,
YOU'RE IN LUCK,
'CAUSE I'VE WRITTEN A SONG
JUST FOR YOU!
(KEYS CLACK)
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
(COMPUTER CHIMES)
SAV: ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
MRS. BHANDARI: WHAT?
THE LAST FILE SHE ACCESSED
WAS AN E-JOURNAL ENTRY
AT 9:52 LAST NIGHT.
"BIG FIGHT WITH SAV.
I'VE BEEN CRYING FOR HOURS."
SHE WAS CRYING.
"I CAN'T EVEN LOOK MOM AND DAD
IN THE EYE,
BECAUSE I SEE
THEIR DISAPPOINTMENT.
ALL I DO IS HURT
THE PEOPLE I LOVE.
MAYBE THEY'D ALL BE BETTER OFF
IF I WAS GONE."
OKAY.
WE NEED TO FIND HER.
MRS. BHANDARI:
I'M CALLING YOUR FATHER
AT WORK.
YEAH, WE'LL UH...
WE'LL CHECK THE NEIGHBOURHOOD,
AND-AND WE'LL GO FROM THERE.
JENNA:
(SINGING AND PLAYING)
♪ CALEB IS A LITTLE BOY ♪
♪ WHO IS FILLED UP
WITH SO MUCH JOY ♪
♪ HE LIKES TO RUN AND PLAY ♪
♪ AND IF YOU ASK HIM
HE WILL SAY... ♪
I WANNA GO TO THE ZOO!
PARDON ME?
KC:
I'M SORRY, DUDE.
A TRIP TO THE ZOO
AIN'T ON THE ITINERARY.
OW!
OH, NO!
CALEB,
WE DO NOT KICK PEOPLE!
CALEB:
(SCREAMS LOUDLY)
KC:
OKAY, BUBBLE BOY'S
GONE DEMONIC!
OKAY, NO, NO, NO.
MAYBE UH...
MAYBE HE'S JUST HUNGRY.
UM, CALEB, WOULD YOU LIKE SOME
DELICIOUS ORGANIC FRUIT SNACKS?
(CALEB CONTINUES SCREAMING)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
OH! OH, GREAT.
RAIN GEAR'S THE ONE THING
WE DIDN'T BRING.
BECAUSE THEY DON'T MAKE
HEMP UMBRELLAS!
(CALEB GRUNTS AND GROWLS)
OH, THIS IS A DISASTER!
WE CAN'T BE PARENTS;
WE CAN'T EVEN WATCH
A SIX-YEAR-OLD!
(CALEB HOWLS)
KC:
THERE'S OUR ANSWER.
KIDS LOVE HOT DOGS.
UH, NO WAY!
BLAIR WOULD SKIN US ALIVE!
HOT DOG?
YOU GOT IT,
LITTLE DUDE!
HUH.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
I KNOW.
ALL OF THE SUDDEN
THE SKIES OPENED UP.
IT SHOULD PUT YOU IN THE MOOD
TO FINISH YOUR HORROR STORY.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
IF YOU FINISH,
YOU CAN COME OVER.
(RAIN POURS DOWN)
(PANTING QUIETLY)
I'LL CALL YOU BACK,
OKAY?
BYE.
(PHONE BEEPS OFF)
(PANTING)
FITZ?
I HAVE NOWHERE ELSE TO GO.
(DOOR CLOSES)
FITZ:
I FELL OFF MY BIKE.
THE ROAD'S SLICK
WITH ALL THIS RAIN.
AND YOU JUST HAPPENED
TO FALL OFF YOUR BIKE
RIGHT OUTSIDE MY HOUSE?
I GUESS SO.
CAN I STAY HERE
FOR A BIT?
MY MOM'S NOT HOME
AND SHE WOULDN'T LIKE IT.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
PLEASE,
IT'S RAINING HARD.
I WON'T BUG YOU AT ALL,
I PROMISE.
(SIGHS)
LET ME THROW THAT
IN THE DRYER.
THAT LOOKS BAD!
IT WAS A BAD FALL.
(FITZ SIGHS)
OKAY IF I WATCH
SOME TV?
JUST UNTIL
THE RAIN STOPS.
DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING
TO EAT?
(HALF LAUGHS)
(TV CLICKS ON)
♪♪♪
♪ Think of a place
I would go ♪
♪ I'm daydreaming ♪
♪ And oh if you knew ♪
♪ What it meant to me ♪
♪ Beware the end ♪
♪ So clear ♪
♪ Oh if you knew
what it meant to me ♪
WHEN WE FIND YOUR SISTER,
SHE'S GONNA BE VERY,
VERY SORRY.
YOU'RE GONNA-
YOU'RE GONNA PUNISH HER?
YOU WANT ME
TO REWARD HER
FOR PUTTING YOUR MOTHER
THROUGH THIS?
HOW WOULD YOU SUGGEST
WE DEAL WITH IT?
I DON'T KNOW,
YOU COULD TRY TALKING TO HER.
WE TALK ALL THE TIME
TO ALLIA.
YEAH,
BUT DO YOU EVER LISTEN?
SHE WROTE IN HER JOURNAL
THAT SHE CAN'T EVEN
LOOK YOU IN THE EYE!
THAT'S ENOUGH,
SAVTAJ.
W-WELL MAYBE SHE RAN AWAY
BECAUSE OF WHAT YOU AND MOM
ARE DOING TO HER!
I SAID ENOUGH!
FINE.
TURN RIGHT.
♪ Oh, if you knew ♪
♪ What it meant to me ♪
♪ Anywhere but here ♪
(CAR CHASE SOUNDS ON TV)
THE RAIN STOPPED.
AS SOON AS MY STUFF'S DRY,
I'LL GO.
(TV CLICKS OFF)
CLARE:
LOOK...
IF YOU'RE GONNA SIT HERE,
YOU'RE GONNA TELL ME
WHAT REALLY HAPPENED.
MY BIKE...
THE TRUTH, FITZ.
(SIGHS)
MY STEPBROTHER'S NEVER
REALLY LIKED ME.
BUT SINCE I GOT OUT
FROM JUVIE,
IT'S FULL-ON HATE!
STEVE HATES EVERYTHING
BUT THE DRUGS
HE PUTS IN HIS PIPE.
THIS IS SERIOUS.
I'M TRYING TO HELP HIM!
BUT THE MORE I TRY,
THE MORE HE HATES ME.
TODAY, HE LOST IT;
BEAT ME UP.
I'M REALLY SORRY,
BUT YOU CAN'T STAY HERE.
WHAT ABOUT YOUR PARENTS?
I'M THE LEAST OF THEIR WORRIES.
BESIDES, I'M GONNA GET THROUGH
TO STEVE.
ONCE HE FINDS
THE PATH TO THE LORD,
HE'LL BE OKAY.
I CHANGED, SO CAN HE.
(DRIER BUZZES)
LET ME GO CHECK
THE DRYER.
FITZ:
CLARE?
WHAT DID ELI DO TO GET TO BE
WITH SUCH AN AMAZING GIRL?
FITZ, YOU REALLY DO
NEED TO GO NOW.
OH! UH, MAMA'S COMING.
COME ON.
KC:
OKAY, NOW REMEMBER,
LITTLE DUDE,
THE HOT DOG
IS A BIG SECRET.
OKAY,
AND NOBODY CAN KNOW,
EXCEPT FOR PEOPLE
IN A SPECIAL HOT DOG CLUB.
JENNA:
SHH!
KC:
GOT IT?
ALL RIGHT.
BLAIR BONGARD:
SO? HOW WAS BABYSITTING?
KC AND JENNA:
AWESOME!
BLAIR BONGARD:
AND HOW'S MY LITTLE ANGEL?
I ATE A HOT DOG,
MOMMY!
I'M GOING TO ASSUME
THIS WASN'T AN ORGANIC HOT DOG?
I DON'T THINK SO,
NO.
KC:
FULL ON STREET MEAT,
AND HE LOVED IT.
BLAIR BONGARD:
OH! SOME SAY HOT DOGS
ARE HARMLESS,
BUT I WOULD PREFER
NOT TO POISON
A CHILD'S BODY WITH NITRATES.
MY CHOICE.
JENNA:
WE'RE REALLY SORRY,
BLAIR.
LOOK,
HE-HE ASKED FOR IT.
WELL, THEN YOU NEED
TO LEARN
NOT TO LET A CHILD
PUSH YOU AROUND.
NOW, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I NEED TO PERFORM
A HOLISTIC CLEANSE
ON MY SON.
COME ON, CALEB,
LET'S GO!
BYE!
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(BOTH BURST OUT LAUGHING)
I WANNA BE A GOOD PARENT,
BUT I CAN'T BE LIKE HER.
WELL, WHATEVER WE HAVE
TO DEAL WITH,
YOU'RE A COOL CO-PILOT,
BIG DADDY.
(BOTH LAUGH)
WANNA GRAB A HOT DOG?
MY CHOICE.
(BOTH LAUGH)
(SIGHS)
YOU HAVE EVERYTHING
YOU NEED?
YES, THANK YOU.
ACTUALLY,
THERE IS ONE THING.
WHEN I WAS IN JUVIE,
I HAD A SPECIAL PLACE
TO GO IN MY MIND.
YOU.
OF COURSE!
PEOPLE WARNED ME.
THEY SAID
THIS WAS ALL AN ACT.
WHAT'S AN ACT?
FINDING GOD,
WANTING ME TO FORGIVE YOU.
IS ANY OF THIS REAL?
IT'S ALL REAL!
JUST LIKE MY FEELINGS
FOR YOU, CLARE.
OKAY, BUT I LOVE ELI
AND ELI LOVES ME.
ELI DOESN'T LOVE
ANYONE.
HE'S A SERIOUSLY
MESSED UP DUDE!
EXCUSE ME?
THIS COMING FROM THE GUY
WHO CAME AT HIM
WITH A KNIFE?!
WHAT I DID WAS WRONG
AND I ADMIT IT,
BUT I'VE CHANGED!
ELI NEVER WILL
AND YOU KNOW THAT.
ME AND YOU?
WE HAVE
A SPIRITUAL CONNECTION.
WHOA!
OKAY, ENOUGH, FITZ.
ELI:
(KNOCKING)
CLARE? IT'S ME!
ELI,
JUST ONE SECOND!
YOU NEED TO GO OUT THE BACK,
RIGHT NOW!
ELI:
YOU ARE LOOKING
AT A LITERARY MASTER.
HEY, ELI.
(PEOPLE LAUGH AND CHATTER)
SAV:
WELL, THAT WAS A BUST.
THIS IS USELESS!
WE HAVE NO IDEA
WHERE SHE IS.
(TEARFUL SIGH)
DAD?
YOUR MOTHER AND I LOVE YOU
AND ALLIA,
BUT IT'S NOT EASY
RAISING CHILDREN.
I HOPE ONE DAY...
YOU ARE LUCKY ENOUGH
TO KNOW THAT.
LET'S GO HOME.
FITZ JUST SHOWED UP
ON MY DOORSTEP,
ALL BEATEN UP.
HE'S HAVING PROBLEMS
AT HOME!
SURE. MORE LIES.
WHY DO YOU CARE?
BECAUSE ANYONE WITH A HEART
TRIES TO HELP PEOPLE
WHEN THEY'RE IN TROUBLE!
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
THAT I'M SOME
HEARTLESS MONSTER?
SOMETIMES!
FITZ:
ELI, WE NEED TO TALK.
I HAVE NOTHING TO SAY
TO YOU.
ME AND CLARE HAVE
A SPECIAL CONNECTION!
CALL FATHER GREG
TO COME PICK YOU UP.
I HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO CLEAN UP THIS MESS.
♪♪♪
♪ The sky is breaking up, Jim ♪
♪ Inform my next of kin ♪
♪ There's a storm
on my horizon ♪
♪ And I think I'm walking in ♪
(CAR DOOR SLAMS)
I KNOW YOU'RE MAD,
BUT JUST LET ME EXPLAIN.
I DIDN'T MEAN IT
WHEN I SAID YOU WERE HEARTLESS.
ELI:
IT'S OKAY.
I DESERVE IT.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
I DON'T WANNA LOSE YOU,
CLARE.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO.
I JUST FEEL LIKE
YOU'RE SLIPPING AWAY
AND I CAN'T STOP IT.
DON'T LEAVE ME,
OKAY?
PLEASE.
PROMISE ME, OKAY?
JUST PROMISE ME.
OKAY.
(CRYING)
YOU NEED TO GET
SOME SLEEP.
LOOK, I'M FINE.
MAYBE I'LL DRIVE AROUND
THE NEIGHBORHOOD
UH, BY THE PRIVATE SCHOOL.
DAD, YOU'VE ALREADY
BEEN THERE
A MILLION TIMES!
JUST TRY AND CHILL.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
OFFICER COSTA:
HI, I'M OFFICER COSTA.
I'M WORKING THE CASE
ON YOUR DAUGHTER.
AH, YES,
WE SPOKE ON THE PHONE.
PLEASE, COME IN.
HAVE YOU FOUND HER YET?
NO.
BUT THE OWNER OF A TEA SHOP
ACROSS FROM ALLI'S SCHOOL
LET ME REVIEW
THE SECURITY TAPES.
I WANT YOU TO SEE THIS.
MRS. BHANDARI:
IT LOOKS LIKE...
IS SHE BEING ABDUCTED?
THE LICENCE PLATE
ISN'T VISIBLE ON THE CAR.
CAN YOU IDENTIFY IT?
I'VE NEVER SEEN
THIS CAR BEFORE.
SAV:
ME NEITHER.
Y-YOU DON'T THINK
SHE'S ACTUALLY-
LET'S NOT JUMP
TO THAT CONCLUSION JUST YET.
BUT I WOULD BE LYING
IF I SAID
I'D NEVER SEEN IT
HAPPEN BEFORE.
ELI:
(SIGHS)
GOT SOMETHING FOR YOU.
CLARE:
"STALKER/ANGEL?"
YOU NEVER GOT A CHANCE
TO READ IT LAST NIGHT,
SO I THOUGHT
YOU'D WANNA GO OVER IT
BEFORE WE SUBMIT IT.
I'D LOVE TO.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE
HOW IT ALL TURNS OUT!
WELL, WITH ALL THE DRAMA
LAST NIGHT
WITH YOU-KNOW-WHO,
THE RAIN AND THE THUNDER,
IT...
REALLY GOT ME THINKING
ABOUT THE ENDING.
YOU CHANGED
THE ENDING AGAIN?
I REALLY THINK
I NAILED IT THIS TIME.
THE HERO, MALCOLM,
REALIZES HE CAN NEVER
PROTECT HIS HEROINE RACHEL
FROM STALKER/ANGEL,
SO HE HAS NO CHOICE
BUT TO...
KILL STALKER/ANGEL!
NO!
HE KILLS RACHEL.
HE GRABS HIS KNIFE,
CUTS HER THROAT,
DRINKS HER BLOOD,
AND FOREVER THEY ARE ONE.
THAT'S...DISTURBING.
IT'S BRILLIANT!
WOULDN'T BE MUCH
OF A HORROR STORY OTHERWISE.
RIGHT. OF COURSE.
IT'S MY MASTERPIECE,
AND I COULDN'TVE WRITTEN IT
WITHOUT YOU.
IT'S ALL ABOUT YOU,
CLARE.
GREAT. UH, JUST...
TRY NOT TO KILL ME,
'KAY?
FUNNY!
DON'T I OWE YOU
A DRIVING LESSON?
THE HEARSE AWAITS!
YOU SURE
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA?
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS!
I'LL BE WITH YOU
EVERY STEP OF THE WAY.
MILADY...
♪ There's a storm
on my horizon ♪
I LOVE CLARE EDWARDS!
(LAUGHS)
♪ And I think I'm walking in ♪