(CELL PHONE RINGS)
FITZ:
(GROANING)
SOMEONE ANSWER THE PHONE.
(CELL PHONE RINGS,
THEN BEEPS ON)
KC:
YEAH?
I STAYED AT MY MOM'S
LAST NIGHT.
SORRY I DIDN'T CHECK IN.
OKAY, SORRY.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS OFF)
BIANCA:
EVER HEARD THE WORD VIBRATE?
KC:
I SHOULD GO.
(DOOR OPENING)
BIANCA:
TAKE THESE.
IT'S ASPIRIN, MORON.
I'D EXPECT A JUNKIE'S KID
TO BE A LITTLE MORE
STREET-SMART.
HOW'D YOU KNOW ABOUT MY MOM?
BIANCA:
YOU SUFFERED AN EXTREME CASE
OF GIN-INDUCED VERBAL DIARRHEA.
DID YOUR BASKETBALL COACH
REALLY HIRE A HOOKER?
'CAUSE I WANT ON THAT TEAM.
BIANCA:
BARBIE AT 12 O'CLOCK.
GLAD TO SEE YOU'RE STILL ALIVE.
UGH! YOU REEK!
AND YOU'RE STUPID ENOUGH
TO THINK GIN
WOULD SOLVE ALL YOUR PROBLEMS?
NO, MOM.
MOM.
SHE'S THE ONE CRYING
'CAUSE HER SON DOESN'T WANT
TO LIVE WITH HER.
WHY DON'T YOU GO GIVE HER
A TISSUE
SINCE YOU'RE HER NEW BFF?
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
EVERYONE TELLING ME
WHAT TO DO.
'CAUSE CARING'S A CRIME
IN YOUR WORLD.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT MY WORLD?
I KNOW THAT
IF YOU DON'T WATCH OUT
YOU COULD END UP
LIKE THOSE LOSERS.
BIANCA:
(CHUCKLING WEAKLY)
(CHUCKLING)
I AM NOT LIKE THEM.
REALLY? 'CAUSE FROM WHERE
I'M STANDING
IT SURE DOESN'T LOOK
THAT WAY.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-ooh! ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be! ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make through ♪
MRS. EDWARDS:
THAT RED DRESS MRS. SALINGER
WORE TO THE FUNDRAISER?
CLARE:
REVEREND DUNCAN NEARLY HAD
A HEART ATTACK.
(LAUGHING)
OH.
SO WHY COULDN'T DAD
GO AGAIN?
I TOLD YOU,
HE HAD TO WORK.
HE'S BEEN WORKING
A LOT LATELY.
WHAT'RE YOU GETTING AT,
CLARE?
IF SOMETHING WAS WRONG...
YOU'D TELL ME, RIGHT?
YOU'RE SUCH A WORRY WART.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME
TO TELL YOU?
THE TRUTH.
NOTHING'S WRONG.
YOU'RE SURE?
POSITIVE.
NOW GO.
(CHUCKLES)
(HESITANT INHALE)
MS. OH:
AND EVERYONE THOUGHT
NOT ONLY WAS THE INTERNET
COOL AND USEFUL,
IT WOULD ALSO BE A CASH COW.
THEN CAME THE DOT-COM BUST.
I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT WASN'T A BUST,
YOUR PARTY.
WELL, I COULDN'T HAVE
DONE IT WITHOUT YA.
WE DO MAKE
AN AWESOME TEAM.
AGREED.
SO WHY DON'T WE HAVE
A TEAM HANGOUT?
COFFEES AT THE DOT?
THE DOT?
UM, I WAS I WAS HOPING
TO SPEND SOME QUIET TIME
WITH MY BOYFRIEND.
BOYFRIEND?
OH.
(CHUCKLES)
DIDN'T KNOW IT WAS OFFICIAL.
DO YOU THINK
IT'S TOO SOON?
NO, NO, NO,
NOT AT ALL.
BOTH:
(CHUCKLE)
I CAN'T WAIT
TO TELL DREW.
DREW?
WHY WOULD YOU TELL DREW?
MMM, BECAUSE...
HE'S MY BOYFRIEND.
DAVE,
YOU DIDN'T THINK...
THAT'S SO SWEET.
(CHUCKLES)
(ANNOYED HUFF)
PLAYER 1:
SET HUT!
OKAY, TAKE IT WIDE.
PLAYERS:
(GRUNT)
(OVERLAPPING SHOUTS)
PLAYER 2:
GOOD EYE! YEAH!
OWEN:
(GRUNTS HEAVILY)
DUDE,
IT'S JUST A PRACTICE!
KC:
YEAH, WHAT'S WRONG?
LINEBACKER CAN'T TAKE A HIT?!
OWEN:
NO, THE QUESTION IS CAN YOU?!
ARMSTRONG:
(BLOWS WHISTLE)
KC, OVER HERE!
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
YOU COULD'VE HURT SOMEBODY.
SORRY, COACH,
I UH... FORGOT
THERE WAS NO TACKLING.
WHAT, LACK OF PADS
DIDN'T CLUE YOU IN?
YOU KNOW,
THESE LAST FEW DAYS
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN YOURSELF.
YOU WANNA TELL ME
WHAT'S WRONG?
IT'S NOTHING.
WELL, IF IT TURNS OUT
TO BE MORE THAN NOTHING,
YOU KNOW WHERE TO FIND ME,
RIGHT?
YES, SIR.
OKAY, ONE MORE BALL.
STUDENTS:
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
MISSED YOU LAST NIGHT.
WAS "TWILIGHT" ON TV?
CLARE:
SHE THINKS SHE'S PROTECTING ME
BY LYING,
BUT SHE'S JUST MAKING IT WORSE.
STOP.
REWIND AND...
PLAY.
ACCORDING TO MY MOM,
EVERYTHING'S FINE
BETWEEN HER AND MY DAD,
BUT ANYONE CAN SEE
THAT IT'S NOT.
DO YOU THINK
THEY'RE GETTING DIVORCED?
DIVORCED?!
MY PARENTS WOULD NEVER
GET DIVORCED!
MY MOM'S JUST SAD
BECAUSE MY DAD'S
ALWAYS IN A BAD MOOD.
WELL, HAVE YOU TOLD THEM
HOW YOU FEEL?
I'VE BEEN TRYING,
BUT THEY DON'T WANT TO TALK.
YOU COULD WRITE
HOW YOU FEEL
IN THAT LETTER
FOR ENGLISH CLASS.
KILL TWO BIRDS
WITH ONE STONE.
(SIREN WAILS IN THE DISTANCE)
(RAPID KNOCK ON DOOR)
(RAPID KNOCK)
(DOOR LATCH RATTLES)
WHY ARE YOU TRYING
TO FORCE ME
TO LEAVE THE GROUP HOME?
BECAUSE A SON SHOULD BE
WITH HIS MOTHER.
COME IN.
WHICH MOM WILL I GET?
THE ONE THAT MAKES ME DINNER
OR THE ONE THAT DOESN'T
COME HOME FOR THREE DAYS?
IT'S GONNA BE DIFFERENT
THIS TIME, I POMISE.
THEN WHY DID I FIND
GIN HERE?
OH, I CAN HAVE
A DRINK OR TWO.
THAT WAS NEVER MY PROBLEM.
BUT LAST NIGHT IT WAS MINE.
I DRANK IT.
A LOT OF IT.
DO YOU WANT ME
TO END UP LIKE YOU?!
(GASPS) NO.
IS THAT WHAT
YOU WANT?!
OF COURSE NOT.
THEN PLEASE MAKE IT
EASY FOR ME.
LET ME STAY
IN THE GROUP HOME!
I CAN'T DO THAT, KC.
YOU SHOULD BE WITH ME!
LET'S SEE
IF THE COURTS AGREE.
ELI:
WOW.
HOW DID IT FEEL
TO WRITE THIS?
GOOD. REALLY GOOD.
IT'S EVERYTHING
I WANTED TO SAY.
MS. DAWES:
MISS EDWARDS,
MR. GOLDSWORTHY.
IT'S NICE OF YOU
TO JOIN US TODAY.
ACTUALLY,
I'M EXCITED TO HEAR
YOUR EXCUSES
FOR SKIPPING LAST CLASS.
LET ME GUESS...
VIOLENT FOOD POISONING?
ACTUALLY, WE WERE BOTH WORKING
ON OUR ASSIGNMENTS.
ORIGINAL,
BUT IT'S NOT GONNA SAVE YOU
FROM DETENTION.
NOW, I'D LIKE TO HEAR
THOSE ASSIGNMENTS.
MISS EDWARDS,
WHY DON'T YOU GO FIRST?
ME?
MS. DAWES:
YEAH. COME ON.
WE'LL SEE IF THE ASSIGNMENT
HELPED WITH
YOUR WRITER'S BLOCK.
"'WE NEED TO TALK'
IS A LINE THAT
EVERY KID DREADS.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT'S WORSE?
WAITING FOR IT,
EVERY MINUTE OF EVERY HOUR
OF EVERY DAY.
BECAUSE I KNOW IT'S COMING,
THE REASON WHY YOU'RE FIGHTING
ALL THE TIME,
AND I KNOW I WON'T LIKE
THE ANSWER.
BUT WHATEVER YOU TELL ME
CAN'T BE WORSE
THAN THE WAITING.
SO PLEASE,
DON'T MAKE ME WAIT ANY LONGER."
(EMOTIONAL EXHALE)
I'M SORRY.
(BREATHING EMOTIONALLY)
T-THERE'S MORE.
NO, THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S A GOOD START.
WHAT SAY YOU, ELI?
I THINK IT DESERVES
A LARGER AUDIENCE,
LIKE AT THE STUDENT SHOWCASE
TOMORROW.
THAT'S A FANTASTIC IDEA.
CLARE?
UH, WELL,
IT'S KIND OF PERSONAL.
MS. DAWES:
YEAH, BUT ALL GREAT ART
IS PERSONAL,
AND THIS IS HEAD AND SHOULDERS
ABOVE YOUR LAST WORK.
I AM SIGNING YOU UP
AFTER CLASS.
(WHISPERING)
MY MOM'S GONNA BE
AT THE SHOWCASE!
WHICH MEANS SHE'LL BE FORCED
TO LISTEN TO YOU.
ISN'T THIS
WHAT YOU WANTED?
KC:
THOSE ARE LAST YEARS GRADES.
BUT MY MARKS THIS YEAR
ARE WAY HIGHER.
I CAN SEE THAT.
THANK YOU.
AND I'M THE ONLY SOPHOMORE
ON THE SENIOR FOOTBALL TEAM.
THAT MUST MEAN I'M MATURE
FOR MY AGE, RIGHT?
LET THE LAWYER REVIEW
YOUR FILE.
DOES HE KNOW ABOUT HOW SHE-?
I'VE GOT A COMPLETE PICTURE
OF THE SITUATION.
YOU'RE SURE YOU'D RATHER
STAY IN THE HOME
THAN WITH YOUR MOTHER?
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
WE'LL NEED REFERENCES.
I'M HAPPY TO SPEAK
FOR KC.
THAT WON'T BE ENOUGH.
KC, DO YOU HAVE ANY TEACHERS
THAT COULD TESTIFY
THAT YOU'D BE BETTER OFF
WITHOUT YOUR MOM?
MY FOOTBALL COACH
OFFERED TO HELP.
THE PROCESS COULD
TAKE MONTHS,
AND IN THE END
IT'S UP TO THE JUDGE.
BUT YOU THINK I HAVE A CHANCE?
IF EVERYTHING CHECKS OUT...
POSSIBLY.
TALK TO YOUR COACH
AND GET BACK TO ME.
(LOW HUM OF STUDEN CHATTER
FROM THE HALLWAY)
(KNOCKING)
KC.
WHAT CAN I DO YOU FOR?
REMEMBER HOW YOU SAID
IF I NEEDED SOMETHING
I COULD COME TO YOU?
I DO.
THE THING IS,
I COULD USE YOUR HELP.
I NEED A REFERENCE.
WELL, NO PROBLEM.
WHAT TYPE OF JOB
ARE YOU APPLYING FOR?
WELL,
IT'S NOT EXACTLY A JOB.
I NEED SOMEONE TO TESTIFY THAT
I'M BETTER OFF WITHOUT MY MOM.
SORRY?
IT'S THE ONLY WAY I'LL GET
TO STAY IN THE GROUP HOME.
WELL, WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
I'M QUALIFIED
TO MAKE THAT TYPE
OF DECISION?
YOU SAID YOU'D HELP.
WHAT ABOUT
YOUR SOCIAL WORKER?
I NEED MORE THAN THAT.
WELL, MAYBE YOU SHOULD TALK
TO MS. SAUVE
OR PRINCIPAL SIMPSON.
BUT THEY'RE JUST
MY TEACHERS.
AND I'M JUST YOUR COACH.
THERE MUST BE
SOMEONE ELSE.
KC, I'M SORRY.
(DOOR BANGS OPEN)
(FENCE RATTLES VIOLENTLY)
♪♪♪
(CAR DOOR SHUTS)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
DREW:
SO AFTER YOU PLUG IT
INTO YOUR COMPUTER,
IT'LL SAY "UPDATE?"
AND YOU JUST TAKE YOUR GUITAR,
AFTER YOU PLUG IT IN,
AND YOU JUST HIT
EVERY SINGLE NOTE.
IT MAKES IT
SO MUCH EASIER.
IT'S SO MUCH FUN TOO.
YOU JUST-
ALLI:
HEY.
I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU WANTED TO SEE
"GHOSTBUSTERS" TONIGHT?
IT'S RETRO NIGHT
AT THE VARSITY.
UH, YEAH,
I'VE ALREADY SEEN IT.
(CHUCKLES)
YEAH, THAT'S KINDA THE POINT
OF RETRO NIGHT.
OR WE COULD GRAB DESSERT.
THE DOT MAKES A MEAN
CHOCOLATE CHEESECAKE.
I ALREADY HAVE PLANS.
SO YOU'RE BLOWING ME OFF?
NO, NO.
I GET IT.
IT'S INTENSE SEEING ME
AFTER OUR MAKE-OUT SESSION
AT MY PARTY.
IT WAS PRETTY AWESOME.
WASN'T IT?
SO LET'S MAKE THIS
OFFICIAL.
WOW, I'M FLATTERED.
YOU ARE?
YEAH, YOU'RE A SMART
AND BEAUTIFUL GIRL.
WELL, THEN EVERYTHING'S PERFECT,
RIGHT?
NEARLY.
IT'S FOOTBALL SEASON
AND I'M QB ONE.
WHICH MEANS GAMES,
PRACTICES, WORKOUTS.
I'M GONNA BE REALLY BUSY.
I DON'T MIND.
YOU WILL.
I WISH THINGS WERE DIFFERENT.
YEAH, ME TOO.
GIRLS:
(GIGGLING)
SAV:
LADIES AND GENTS OF THE PTA,
SAV, YOUR STUDENT COUNCIL
PRESIDENT HERE.
ARE YOU READY TO SEE
SOME OF DEGRASSI'S
BEST AND BRIGHTEST?
PARENTS:
(CLAPPING)
YES!
OKAY, YOU WANTED TO TALK
TO YOUR MOM
AND THIS IS YOUR CHANCE.
MAYBE I AM A WORRY WART.
MAYBE THERE'S NOTHING
WRONG AT HOME.
OR MAYBE YOU'RE SCARED.
OF WHAT?!
FINDING OUT WHAT'S REALLY
GOING ON WITH YOUR PARENTS.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
THEN PROVE IT.
DAWES ASSIGNED US
AS ENGLISH PARTNERS
BECAUSE SHE THOUGHT
YOU NEEDED TO TAKE RISKS.
WITH MY WRITING!
NOT MY LIFE.
THIS ISN'T ME SHOUTING
IN A PARK
IN FRONT OF A BUNCH
OF STRANGERS.
THIS IS MY FAMILY.
IT'S PERSONAL.
SAV:
OKAY, UP FIRST WE HAVE
A TALENTED SCRIBE.
ONLY IN GRADE TEN,
SHE'S TAKING GRADE ELEVEN
ADVANCED ENGLISH.
PLEASE PUT YOUR HANDS TOGETHER
FOR CLARE EDWARDS!
PARENTS:
(CLAPPING)
CLARE:
I CAN'T.
SAV:
UH, OKAY...
PARENTS:
(CLAPPING)
(LOCKER DOOR CLANKS SHUT)
KC:
HEY, I NEED TO GET OUT OF HERE,
FAST!
DON'T WORRY,
I WON'T STOP YOU.
COME WITH ME.
WE CAN HITCHHIKE TO NASHVILLE
AND FIND YOUR MOM.
MY MOM'S IN MEMPHIS.
WELL,
THEN WE'LL GO THERE TOO.
I DID SOMETHING BAD.
REALLY BAD.
I WAS MAD.
IT WAS DUMB.
PLEASE,
CAN WE GO?
(SIGHING HEAVILY)
FINE.
OKAY, SO MEMPHIS?
LET'S START WITH COFFEE.
SIMPSON:
KC?
CAN WE HAVE A LITTLE CHAT
IN MY OFFICE?
SO, I SPENT ALL AFTERNOON
THINKING ABOUT YOU.
GREAT. WHAT AMAZING IDEA
DID YOU COME UP WITH?
I STILL WANT TO SPEND TIME
WITH YOU,
IF YOU WANT.
WE COULD CATCH THAT MOVIE.
(WHISPERING)
OR WE COULD GO MAKE OUT
SOMEWHERE.
(HESITANT EXHALE)
UM, WELL,
MY PARENTS WON'T BE HOME
FOR ANOTHER HOUR.
PERFECT.
(DOOR SHUTS)
MRS. EDWARDS:
THERE YOU ARE.
WHAT HAPPENED?!
I THOUGHT YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO READ SOMETHING
AT THE SHOWCASE.
I GOT COLD FEET.
STAGE FRIGHT'S NOT LIKE YOU.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
YOU TELL ME.
WHAT'S THIS?
THE PIECE I WAS SUPPOSED
TO READ TODAY.
WHAT'S GOING ON
WITH YOU AND DAD?
ARE YOU...
ARE YOU GETTING
A DIVORCE?
I WISH I COULD TELL YOU.
YOU CAN.
I'M NOT A KID.
BUT YOU ARE A KID,
CLARE,
AND YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT YOUR FATHER AND ME.
BUT I CAN'T JUST IGNORE
THE FACT
THAT SOMETHING'S WRONG!
WHAT IS IT?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOUR FATHER DOESN'T WANT
TO SPEND TIME WITH ME,
AND NOTHING I DO
SEEMS TO CHANGE THAT.
SO ASK HIM WHY.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT WHAT
THE ANSWER WILL BE.
I NEED TO KNOW, MOM.
DON'T YOU?
I'LL TALK TO HIM TONIGHT.
MR. SIMPSON:
(SIGHING)
WHAT'S GOING ON?
COACH ARMSTRONG ASKED ME
TO CALL THIS MEETING
BECAUSE HE'S CONCERNED
ABOUT YOU.
THAT'S CRAP.
EXCUSE ME?
IF HE CARED ABOUT ME,
HE WOULD HAVE HELPED.
KC, I'M JUST YOUR COACH.
KC:
SO, IS THIS AN INTERVENTION?
SIMPSON:
NO, IT'S NOT.
SIT DOWN.
(TELEPHONE RINGS
IN DISTANCE)
WE'LL WAIT.
NOW, WE WANT TO DISCUSS
WHAT'S BEEN GOING ON
WITH YOU LATELY.
WE KNOW YOU DIDN'T SLEEP
AT YOUR MOM'S LAST NIGHT.
AND YOU'VE BEEN ACTING OUT
AT PRACTICE.
AND THERE'S ALSO
THE, UH,
LITTLE INCIDENT WITH
COACH ARMSTRONG'S CAR.
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT THAT.
ARE YOU SURE?
LISA:
(SNORTS)
IS THIS WHAT YOU DO
AT THIS SCHOOL?
YOU ACCUSE THE POOR KID
OF EVERY CRIME?
WELL...
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
THEN I ASSUME YOU HAVE
SOME PROOF THAT KC'S GUILTY?
LOOK, WE JUST WANT TO GET
TO THE BOTTOM OF THIS THING.
BUT YOU FIGURE
THE MOM DID JAIL TIME
SO THE KID'S A BAD SEED!
SIMPSON:
MISS GUTHRIE,
WE WOULD NOT JUMP
TO CONCLUSIONS LIKE THAT.
(SLAPS HAND ON DESK)
GOOD!
THEN I GUESS WE'RE DONE!
(CLEARS HER THROAT)
IS THERE SOMEWHERE
I CAN TALK TO MY KID?
TAKE YOUR TIME.
WHY'D YOU COVER FOR ME?
'CAUSE YOU'RE MY SON.
I NOT GONNA LET ANYBODY
MESS WITH YOU.
EVEN ME.
I KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO NOT HAVE CONTROL
OVER YOUR LIFE,
AND I WOULDN'T WISH IT
ON ANYBODY.
SO, IF YOU WANT TO STAY
IN THE GROUP HOME,
I NOT GONNA FIGHT YA.
(CAR DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
HI, ELI, HOW ARE YOU?
FINE, CLARE,
THANKS FOR ASKING.
HI.
IF YOU DON'T WANNA TELL YOUR MOM
HOW YOU'RE FEELING,
I RESPECT THAT.
TOO LATE.
YOU READ HER THE LETTER?
AND SHE WANTS TO KNOW
WHAT'S WRONG AS MUCH AS I DO.
SHE AND MY DAD
ARE TALKING RIGHT NOW.
SO WHAT YOU'RE SAYING IS...
MY PLAN WORKED?
(SMALL LAUGH)
COULD YOU BE MORE SMUG?
ABSOLUTELY.
(LAUGHS)
HERE.
YOU MIGHT WANT
TO BORROW THESE.
THEY'RE NOISE
CANCELLATION.
MIGHT COME IN HANDY
IF THINGS GET WORSE
WITH YOUR FOLKS.
OR IF YOU NEED TO IGNORE
AN ENGLISH PARTNER.
THANKS.
AND I'M SORRY
FOR INTERFERING.
I PROMISE
NOT TO DO IT AGAIN.
UM...
YOU CAN INTERFERE
EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE,
BUT I'M STILL GONNA DO
WHATEVER I WANT.
WOULDN'T EXPECT
ANYTHING LESS.
♪ So tell me
where did I go wrong ♪
♪ Before you... ♪
♪ Before you came along? ♪
♪ Well, it's seems like
I was lost...
(KNOCKING)
♪ You showed me
how to do things right... ♪
HI.
(EMOTIONAL INHALE)
ARE YOU HERE TO STAY?
I'M SCARED, MOM.
(TEARFUL)
ME TOO.
IT'S GOING TO BE BETTER
THIS TIME.
SO MUCH BETTER.
(EMOTIONAL LAUGH)
YOU'RE PROBABLY HUNGRY.
I HAVE CHICKEN WINGS
AND PIZZA.
I WANTED TO MAKE SURE
I HAD ALL YOUR FAVOURITES
JUST IN CASE, SO...
(EMOTIONAL EXHALE)
DID I DO
SOMETHING WRONG?
NO?
WELL, THEN LET'S GET
OUT OF THE HALLWAY
AND HAVE DINNER!
THEN, MAYBE AFTER,
WE CAN DISCUSS
THE DRINKING
AND WHY IT'S NOT OKAY
TO KEY A TEACHER'S CAR.
NOT GONNA LET ME OFF EASY,
ARE YOU?
(LAUGHS RUEFULLY)
WHAT KINDA MOM WOULD I BE?
MOM?
♪ So use me,
don't let me screw it up ♪
♪ I believe you,
oh, and I need your touch... ♪
I REALLY MISSED YOU.
ME TOO.
♪ I believe you,
oh, and I need you now ♪
♪ To make it better
all somehow ♪