(WHISTLE BLOWS,
POWER SQUAD CHEERS)
♪ Do you know ♪
♪ It's a waste of time ♪
(FOOTBALL WHOOSHES)
♪ Though it's all gone ♪
♪ But still it's in your mind ♪
(FANS CHEERING)
♪ They all love you ♪
♪ They all need you ♪
♪ And you might never find
another way ♪
(FANS CHEERING)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(AIR HORN BLARES)
(POWER SQUAD CHEERS LOUDLY)
DREW:
YEAH!
(DEGRASSI PLAYERS CHEERING)
(CHEERING AND CLAPPING)
(HORN BLOWS)
JENNA:
GREAT GAME.
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT
STILL MAD AT ME.
I'LL CALL YOU TONIGHT?
CAN'T WAIT.
LISA:
GREAT CATCH
IN THAT LAST DRIVE.
MOM?!
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
WOW.
ALMOST THREE YEARS!
LOOK AT YOU!
UH...
WE SHOULD TALK.
COACH ARMSTRONG:
EVERYBODY ON THE BUS,
LET'S GO!
YEAH, I HAVE TO GO.
YOUR COACH OKAYED IT.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
HOW LONG YOU BEEN
PLAYING FOOTBALL?
JUST THIS YEAR.
YEAH?
YOUR DAD PLAYED FOOTBALL
ON HIS HIGH SCHOOL TEAM.
HE WAS TERRIBLE.
(LAUGHS)
YOU CAN'T JUST SHOW UP
LIKE THIS.
WELL, HOW ELSE AM I SUPPOSED
TO TALK TO YOU?
YOU DON'T TAKE MY CALLS,
YOU DON'T ANSWER MY EMAILS.
I'VE BEEN BUSY.
THERE'S...
SCHOOL, SPORTS,
THE CURFEW
AT THE GROUP HOME.
NOT FOR LONG.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I UH...
FILED PAPERS
TO REGAIN CUSTODY.
SO...
SOON, YOU AND ME COULD BE
LIVING TOGETHER.
I GOT AN APARTMENT
A FEW BLOCKS AWAY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I HAVE A HOME...
AND A LIFE.
YOU-YOU CAN'T COME BACK
AND MESS IT UP!
BELIEVE ME,
THAT'S THE LAST THING
I WANNA DO, OKAY?
SO I SET UP A MEETING
WITH YOUR SOCIAL WORKER.
AWESOME.
SEE YOU THEN.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
MS. DAWES:
SOME OF THE GREATEST WORKS
OF ALL TIME?
LETTERS.
THEY REVEAL THE HEARTS
AND SOULS
OF WORLD LEADERS,
OF GREAT ARTISTS,
AND NOW, OF YOU.
MS. DAWES?
THERE MUST BE SOME SORT
OF MISTAKE.
I'VE NEVER GOTTEN
A "C."
HOW DID THIS HAPPEN?
WELL, YOUR EARLY ASSIGNMENTS
WERE DIVINE,
BUT RECENTLY YOUR WRITING
HAS BECOME...
DISTANT.
IMPERSONAL.
I USED COMPLEX
SENTENCE STRUCTURE,
AND ADVANCED VOCABULARY.
MS. DAWES:
YES, BUT YOUR ASSIGNMENT
DIDN'T TELL ME ANYTHING
ABOUT WHO YOU ARE.
WHAT YOU WANT.
YOU CAN'T HIDE BEHIND
VAMPIRE FICTION FOREVER.
I'M NOT HIDING.
THEN PROVE IT...
TO YOUR WRITING PARTNER.
ELI: ME?!
MS. DAWES: YEAH, YOU.
YOU WRITE WELL,
BUT YOU'RE A... LITTLE WORDY.
YOU AND CLARE WILL BE
EDITING EACH OTHER'S WORK
THIS SEMESTER.
GREAT.
THAT'LL BE FUN.
MS. DAWES:
WE MAY HAVE
A VERY SPECIAL PARTNERSHIP
ON OUR HANDS, PEOPLE.
(GASPS) LIKE SYLVIA PLATH
AND TED HUGHES!
SYLVIA PLATH KILLED HERSELF.
(SCOFFS)
HE'S JUST SO... UGH!
YOU KNOW?
I GET IT, CLARE.
YOU'RE IN LOVE WITH ELI.
BUT CAN WE TALK ABOUT SOMETHING
MORE IMPORTANT HERE,
LIKE HOW I CAN GET
DREW'S ATTENTION?
EVER SINCE I LAID EYES
ON HIM,
I KNEW WE WERE MEANT TO BE.
UH, HAVE YOU EVER EVEN
TALKED TO HIM?
YOU CAN'T JUST TALK
TO A GUY LIKE THAT, CLARE,
YOU HAVE TO HAVE
A STRATEGY.
GIRL:
BYE! THANKS!
WELL, BETTER COME UP
WITH IT FAST.
ALLI:
OH!
(GIGGLES)
HI, DREW.
UM...
GREAT GAME YESTERDAY.
YOU'RE SAV'S LITTLE SISTER,
RIGHT?
YEAH.
(BELL RINGS)
CATCH YOU LATER.
(UNDER HER BREATH)
YEAH.
HAS ANYONE EVER DIED
OF HUMILIATION?
MMM...NO,
JUST PERMANENTLY SCARRED.
(EXASPERATED SIGH)
(GIGGLES)
(SHARPENER GRINDS)
GUESS YOU WERE TOO BUSY
TO CALL LAST NIGHT?
NONE OF MY BUSINESS,
I KNOW.
JUST...WANTED TO MAKE SURE
YOU WERE OKAY.
MY MOM WANTS ME
TO LIVE WITH HER.
THAT'S GOOD, RIGHT?
I MEAN, IT'S GOTTA BE BETTER
THAN THE GROUP HOME.
NO, IT'S WORSE.
(SHARPENER GRINDS)
WAY WORSE.
BUT... SHE'S YOUR MOM.
(SIGHS) YEAH,
WHEN SHE WASN'T TWEAKED OUT.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
I THOUGHT SHE WAS BETTER.
IT DOESN'T MATTER,
'CAUSE I'M NOT LIVING WITH HER.
YOU CAN'T JUST IGNORE
YOUR MOM.
MS. OH:
LET'S GET STARTED, THEN!
(CAR RUMBLES PAST)
MRS. EDWARDS:
CLARE,
DO YOU THINK
THIS IS TOO MUCH
FOR TOMORROW'S
CHURCH FUNDRAISER?
YOU LOOK PRETTY.
OH! WELL,
NOT TOO PRETTY, I HOPE.
HEY!
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WHAT?
OH, THE DRESS?
IT'S FINE.
(SCOFFS)
RANDALL!
MR. EDWARDS:
HERE WE GO WITH THAT LOOK
AGAIN.
I DIDN'T GIVE YOU
A LOOK!
FINE.
I DON'T WANNA ARGUE.
OH, THEN I GUESS
YOUR FATHER AND I
JUST WON'T TALK
AT ALL!
YOU GUYS ARE FIGHTING AGAIN.
WE'RE NOT FIGHTING,
WE'RE DISAGREEING.
DON'T WORRY, SWEETIE.
♪ I'm just sittin' here ♪
♪ Waitin' for the change
to come ♪
HEH.
♪ But oh I think ♪
♪ I may have got it wrong ♪
SEE 'YA.
♪ Where... ♪
♪ Where did the good times go ♪
TODD:
SO, LET'S DISCUSS
YOUR TRANSITION
FROM THE GROUP HOME
TO YOUR MOM'S.
KC:
I CAN SAVE EVERYONE'S TIME
'CAUSE I'M STAYING HERE.
THE SPACES
IN THE GROUP HOME
ARE FOR KIDS WHO DON'T HAVE
SUITABLE ALTERNATIVES.
SHE'S A JUNKIE
WITH A RECORD.
HOW IS THAT SUITABLE?
I'VE BEEN CLEAN FOR TWO YEARS.
'CAUSE IT'S HARD TO GET
CRACK IN PRISON.
TODD:
YOUR MOTHER'S BEEN WORKING
VERY HARD
TO TURN HER LIFE AROUND.
SHE'S FOUND A JOB
AND A PLACE TO LIVE.
SO SHE WON'T LOCK ME
IN THE CLOSET
WHILE SHE GETS HIGH AGAIN?
I DON'T WANNA BE AROUND
TO SEE THE NEXT STUNT
SHE PULLS, OKAY?
(SIGHS)
I THINK IT'S BEST
IF KC AND I...
COULD HAVE A CHAT ALONE.
(TAKES A DEEP BREATH)
SURE.
CALL ME ANY TIME.
OKAY.
BYE, KC.
(DOOR SHUTS)
HOW COULD YOU DO THIS
TO ME?
A MOTHER HAS A RIGHT
AND A DUTY
TO RAISE HER CHILD.
THERE MUST BE SOMETHING
I CAN DO.
WELL, THERE ARE LEGAL ROUTES,
BUT THAT COULD TAKE MONTHS,
EVEN YEARS.
AND THERE'S NO GUARANTEE
THE COURT WILL FIND
IN YOUR FAVOUR.
SO THAT'S IT.
I'M JUST SUPPOSED
TO ACCEPT
THAT SHE'S GONNA TURN
MY LIFE UPSIDE DOWN?!
OR YOU COULD TRY
AND BE PROUD OF YOUR MOM.
IT'S HARD TO TURN
YOUR LIFE AROUND,
AND SHE'S DOING IT.
WHY DON'T YOU SPEND
SOME TIME WITH HER,
SEE IF THINGS HAVE CHANGED.
KC:
AND IF I SEE THEY HAVEN'T?
CAN I STAY
AT THE GROUP HOME?
LET'S DEAL WITH THAT
WHEN AND IF IT HAPPENS.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
SEE THIS?
THIS IS A PHONE.
BEST FRIENDS ANSWER IT.
CAN WE SAVE THE LECTURE
UNTIL AFTER I FINISH
MY ENGLISH ASSIGNMENT?
SO WHO'S GONNA GIVE ME
GUY ADVICE?
I DON'T KNOW,
TRY A GUY.
(SIGHS)
DAVE'S KIND OF A GUY,
RIGHT?
DAVE:
YOU SEE THAT?
ALLI JUST SMILED AT ME.
I THOUGHT YOU MOVED ON.
NO! THAT'S WHAT
I WANTED HER TO THINK.
SOON AS THE QUEEN BEE
RUNS OUT OF HONEY,
SHE'LL COME FLYING BACK
TO THE HIVE.
ALLI:
HI, DAVE.
CAN I TALK TO YOU,
PRIVATELY?
HE SHOULD WRITE A BOOK.
ALLI:
SO, THERE'S THIS GUY
I LIKE.
AND YOU DON'T KNOW
IF HE'S INTO YOU.
EXACTLY.
HOW DO I FIND OUT?
WELL, YOU SHOULD
SPEND TIME WITH HIM.
LOTS OF TIME.
I JUST UH...
I NEED SOME SORT OF EXCUSE,
YOU KNOW?
WELL,
EVERYONE LOVES A PARTY.
WELL, MY PARENTS
ARE AWAY TONIGHT!
DO YOU REALLY THINK
A PARTY WILL WORK?
I GUARANTEE IT.
AH!
THANKS, DAVE.
MUAH!
YOU'RE THE BEST!
MS. OH:
GOOD MORNING, CLASS.
CLARE:
SO?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
IT'S UM...
(SIGHS)
AWKWARDLY CONSTRUCTED,
FILLED WITH HYPERBOLE,
AND GENERALLY SLOPPY.
THE TITLE'S CENTERED.
OH!
DAWES IS RIGHT!
I HAVE WRITER'S BLOCK.
SO DON'T HAND IT IN.
CLARE:
AND WHAT, TELL HER THE DOG
ATE MY HOMEWORK?
OR YOU COULD TAKE OFF.
YOU MEAN SKIP?
IF YOU WANNA GET OFFICIAL.
IT WOULD GIVE ME TIME TO WRITE
A WAY BETTER ASSIGNMENT.
(BELL RINGS)
DECISION TIME.
STAY OR GO?
♪♪♪
WELL,
ARE YOU COMING?
♪ Big cheer
for what you do ♪
♪ Got everyone dreamin'
about you ♪
♪ Star of the team
with A grades ♪
MR. SIMPSON:
WELL, THANK YOU FOR THE NEWS,
SIR.
BIG PROBLEMS!
DEGRASSI TEST SCORES
DROPPED A LOT,
SO THE PTA WANTS
TO TAKE AWAY THEIR FUNDING,
AND PUT IT TOWARDS ACADEMICS.
WHICH MEANS NO SPORTS,
NO CLUBS.
NO FUN.
MR. SIMPSON:
WHICH IS WHY I WANT TO PUT ON
A STUDENT SHOWCASE
TO SHOW PARENTS
DEGRASSI'S BRIGHTEST.
SOUNDS LIKE A LOT OF WORK.
MR. SIMPSON: IT WILL BE.
I'LL MEET YOU HERE AFTER SCHOOL
TO START PLANNING.
GUESS YOU WON'T MAKE THAT
BIG BHANDARI BASH TONIGHT.
WHAT BIG BHANDARI BASH?
IT'S MORE OF A SMALL
GET TOGETHER REALLY.
YEAH. IF MOM AND DAD
FIND OUT,
I'M DEAD.
LISTEN, YOU HAVE STUDENT
COUNCIL STUFF TONIGHT,
RIGHT?
SO YOU NEVER HEARD OF IT.
TOTALLY NOT
YOUR RESPONSIBILITY.
FINE.
DON'T GO IN MY ROOM.
DREW:
SO, DID I JUST HEAR
YOU'RE HOSTING
A THROW-DOWN TONIGHT?
(LAUGHS SHYLY)
ACTUALLY,
IT'S MORE OF A SMALL
GET-TOGETHER.
WANNA COME?
HMM.
(LAUGHS SHYLY)
WOW,
THIS IS A FIRST -
SKIPPING SCHOOL TO DO WORK.
OKAY, I DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW YOU GOT AN "A"
AND I GOT A "C."
SIMPLE.
I'M DATING MS. DAWES.
YOU'RE A GOOD WRITER,
BUT ANYONE COULD'VE PENNED
THIS PIECE.
THERE'S NO POINT OF VIEW.
I WROTE ABOUT GUN CONTROL.
I SAY IT'S GOOD.
(SARCASTICALLY)
WOW! CONTROVERSIAL!
OKAY, FINE.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED
TO WRITE ABOUT?
SOMETHING THAT PISSES
YOU OFF.
BESIDES MY ENGLISH PARTNER?
OUCH!
IF YOU COULD CHANGE
ONE THING IN THE WORLD,
WHAT WOULD IT BE?
MY MOM AND DAD.
THEY'RE NOT EXACTLY
GETTING ALONG.
SO WRITE ABOUT THAT.
I CAN'T.
IT'S PERSONAL.
YOU CARE TOO MUCH
WHAT PEOPLE THINK.
THAT IS NOT TRUE.
THEN PROVE IT.
SCREAM.
AT THE TOP OF YOUR LUNGS.
(QUIETLY)
AAHHH...
(SNORTS)
THAT'S THE BEST
YOU COULD DO?
(SIGHS)
(SCREAMS REALLY LOUDLY)
AAHHHHHHHHHH!
(MAN GASPS,
WOMEN CHUCKLE)
OKAY, YOUR TURN.
YEAH, NOT MY STYLE.
WHA-?
NO, YOU HAVE TO!
IT'S NOT,
SO YOU CAN'T MAKE ME.
IT'S NOT MY STYLE.
YOU HAVE TO DO IT.
I HAVE TO...
(AWKWARD CHUCKLE)
♪♪♪
DRINKS ARE ON ICE,
THE CHIPS ARE NEXT TO THE DIP.
WHAT ELSE CAN I DO?
OKAY,
HYPOTHETICAL QUESTION HERE.
IF I SAID I HAD
THE BIGGEST CRUSH ON YOU,
WHAT WOULD YOU SAY?
I'D SAY I'M THE LUCKIEST GUY
ON EARTH.
EVEN IF THERE WERE A MILLION
OTHER GIRLS AFTER YOU?
THEN I'D TELL THEM
TO TAKE A HIKE.
THEN I GUESS IT'S TIME
TO KICK THIS PARTY
INTO HIGH GEAR.
DAVE:
WHY, WHAT-WHAT DID YOU,
WHAT DID YOU HAVE IN MIND?
"I NEVER."
NEVER WHAT?
NO, IT'S A GAME.
YOU SAY SOMETHING
YOU HAVEN'T DONE,
LIKE, I'VE NEVER DRIVEN
A CAR.
AND IF YOU HAVE,
YOU REMOVE AN ARTICLE
OF CLOTHING.
WELL,
IT-IT SOUNDS AWESOME,
BUT...WHAT'S THE POINT?
WATCH AND SEE.
♪♪♪
(SIREN WAILS)
(JENNA LAUGHS)
LISA:
WELL, I HOPE THE MAC & CHEESE
WAS OKAY.
JENNA:
OKAY? TRY AMAZING, MRS...
LISA:
IT'S LISA.
YOU KNOW, BETWEEN THE AGES
FIVE AND SEVEN,
THIS WAS ALL KC WOULD EAT,
I THOUGHT HE WOULD DIE
OF MALNUTRITION.
HE'S EXPANDED HIS TASTES.
OH, REALLY?
WHAT, PIZZA?
JENNA:
AND WINGS!
NICE.
LISA:
I HOPE YOU HAVE ROOM FOR
GRANDMA GUTHRIE'S APPLE PIE,
JUST LIKE YOU ASKED.
I'LL HAVE MINE
WITH ICE CREAM.
AH, NUTS!
I'M ALL OUT.
KC:
OH.
BUMMER.
BUT THERE'S A STORE
AROUND THE CORNER.
WHY DON'T I JUST GO
GET US SOME?
OKAY?
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
(DOOR SHUTS)
JENNA:
HOW BADLY DO YOU NEED
ICE CREAM?
KC:
I DON'T.
I NEED TO SEARCH THE APARTMENT.
FOR WHAT?
ANYTHING THAT PROVES
I SHOULDN'T LIVE HERE.
(RUMMAGING NOISES)
♪♪♪
SO I'M SUPPOSED TO SAY
SOMETHING I HAVEN'T DONE.
AND ANYONE
WHO HAS DONE IT,
REMOVES AN ITEM OF CLOTHING.
(LAUGHS)
OKAY, WELL UH...
NEVER HAVE I EVER LIED
TO MY FOLKS.
OH, GOD.
DREW:
WITH QUESTIONS LIKE THAT,
AND I'LL BE NAKED IN TEN.
GIRL:
OH! (LAUGHS)
ALLI, YOUR TURN.
WHAT?
YOUR TURN.
OH, RIGHT.
UM...
WHY DON'T WE LET DREW SHOW US
HOW IT'S DONE?
IF YOU INSIST.
NEVER HAVE I EVER...
SEXTED.
(LAUGHS)
HMM.
LONG STORY.
IT ALWAYS IS.
IT'S YOUR TURN,
LONG STORY.
NEVER HAVE I EVER...
LIKED ANYONE IN THIS ROOM.
ALLI, YOU'RE ONLY SUPPOSED
TO TAKE SOMETHING OFF
IF YOU HAVE DONE IT.
GUESS I'M STILL GETTING
THE HANG OF THIS GAME.
♪♪♪
(DOG BARKS,
CRICKETS CHIRP)
(KEYS CLACK)
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
MRS. EDWARDS:
NO, I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU HAVE TO GO
BACK TO WORK TONIGHT!
MR. EDWARDS:
BECAUSE THE WORLD
DOESN'T REVOLVE AROUND YOU
AND YOUR FUNDRAISERS,
HELEN.
SOMEONE'S GOTTA DO A LITTLE
FUNDRAISING FOR THIS FAMILY!
MRS. EDWARDS:
WE MADE THESE PLANS WEEKS AGO.
MR. EDWARDS:
YOU MADE THE PLANS, HELEN.
GOOD NIGHT.
(DOOR CLOSES)
EVERYTHING OKAY?
OH, CLARE.
ANY CHANCE YOU WANT
TO SUB IN TONIGHT?
CLARE:
TONIGHT?
MRS. EDWARDS:
NEVER MIND.
NEVER MIND, I'LL BE FINE.
UM...
I COULD WEAR MY NAVY DRESS.
OKAY.
I'LL GO IRON IT.
♪♪♪
NEVER HAVE I EVER
WANTED TO...
MAKE OUT WITH SOMEONE
IN THIS ROOM.
OH, WOW.
HOW DID IT GET TO BE...
EIGHT O'CLOCK.
DREW:
YEAH, WE SHOULD PROBABLY JET.
LET YOU GET
YOUR BEAUTY SLEEP.
NO, NO!
THE PARTY'S JUST ABOUT
TO GET AWESOME!
ALLI:
WELL, ALL THE MORE REASON
TO END IT.
LEAVE IT ON A HIGH.
THANKS FOR COMING,
EVERYONE!
I-I COULD STICK AROUND
AND HELP CLEAN UP.
UH, NO NEED.
UM, BUT-BUT THANK YOU.
TONIGHT WAS PERFECT.
(LAUGHS)
WOW.
KC, THIS ISN'T RIGHT.
YOUR MOM'S GONNA BE HOME
ANY MINUTE.
BINGO.
TOLD YOU MY MOM WAS GUILTY.
JENNA:
OF TRYING TO STOP A HEADACHE?
THIS IS IBUPROFEN.
AND THOSE ARE PRESCRIPTIONS.
YOU'VE GOTTA ACCEPT,
YOUR MOM'S CHANGED.
NO, SHE HASN'T.
(SIGHS)
NEWSFLASH!
ALCOHOL, NOT ILLEGAL.
BUT AN EX-ADDICT
SHOULDN'T HAVE IT.
AND SHE DEFINITELY SHOULDN'T
GIVE IT TO HER SON.
BUT SHE DIDN'T.
THAT'S NOT WHAT WE'LL TELL
MY SOCIAL WORKER.
JENNA:
WHAT DID SHE DO
THAT WAS SO BAD?
SORRY I TOOK SO LONG.
THE FIRST STORE
WAS ALL OUT.
I HOPE VANILLA BEAN
IS OKAY.
I THINK THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
DON'T YOU, KC?
THREE...
TWO...
ONE.
(KNOCKING)
I SEEM TO BE MISSING A WATCH.
OOPS!
SO...
DO YOU WANNA HANG OUT MORE
OR SOMETHING?
OR SOMETHING.
♪ ...real life ♪
♪ Time to face facts ♪
KC:
SECOND HELPINGS OF PIE.
I THOUGHT MY MOM
WOULD NEVER LET US LEAVE.
YEAH,
SHE'S A REAL MONSTER.
KC:
OKAY.
SO, HERE'S THE PLAN.
YOU COME BACK
TO THE GROUP HOME WITH ME...
AND UH...
TELL TODD MY MOM
OFFERED US BOOZE.
(SCOFFS)
I CAN'T LIE.
THEN IT'S JUST MY WORD
AGAINST HERS.
NO ONE WILL BELIEVE ME.
BECAUSE YOU WON'T BE
TELLING THE TRUTH.
YOUR MOM'S NICE.
WHAT MAKES YOU THE EXPERT
ON MOTHERS?
YOURS LEFT YOU.
(DISGUSTED SIGH)
REAL NICE, KC.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
HOME.
JENNA:
I'M TIRED.
WHY ARE YOU TAKING
MY MOM'S SIDE?
BECAUSE MAYBE
IT'S THE RIGHT ONE.
DO YOU HAVE A PLAN
FOR THAT BOTTLE?
NOT ANYMORE.
I MIGHT BE ABLE TO HELP YOU
WITH THAT.
♪♪♪
♪ I'm gonna take you down ♪