JENNA:
WHY DIDN'T ANYONE TELL ME
MY TOP WAS GAPING LIKE THAT?
ALLI:
I AM SURE IT WASN'T A PROBLEM
FOR AT LEAST HALF THE SCHOOL.
UM...
DIDN'T THAT SHIRT
USED TO FIT?
IT STILL FITS.
JENNA, DENIAL ISN'T JUST
A RIVER DOWN YOU KNOW WHERE!
WHERE?
MAYBE I SHOULD'VE CHECKED OUT
AN ATLAS INSTEAD.
OOH, VERY FUNNY.
(BATHROOM DOOR CLOSES)
OKAY...
LET'S SEE HERE...
"SIGNS OF PREGNANCY
CAN INCLUDE
ANY OR ALL OF THESE SYMPTOMS:
FREQUENT URINATION,
INTERMITTENT NAUSEA,
SENSITIVITY TO SMELLS,
WEIGHT GAIN!"
ALLI,
I'M NOT PREGNANT!
"BREAST TENDERNESS!"
OW!
HAVE YOU AND KC BEEN
SEXUALLY ACTIVE?
YEAH.
AND HAVE YOU ALWAYS
BEEN SAFE?
JUST TAKE A TEST, JENNA.
RULE IT OUT.
I DON'T NEED TO.
ESPECIALLY BEFORE THE MOST
IMPORTANT AUDITION OF MY LIFE.
FINE.
THEN TAKE THIS.
SOME READING
WHILE YOU'RE IN LINE.
YOU'RE NOT COMING
TO THE AUDITIONS?
OH, I'D LOVE TO,
BUT I HAVE DETENTION.
BECAUSE OF YOU.
ME?
GOT CAUGHT TRYING TO SNEAK
THESE BOOKS
OUT OF THE LIBRARY.
IN OTHER NEWS, THE LIBRARIAN
THINKS I'M PREGNANT.
THE THINGS I DO FOR YOU.
(LAUGHS)
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, whatever ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
SO?
OOH! HEY, HOT STUFF!
WHAT'S THE OCCASION?
UM, HELLO?
NEXT TEEN STAR AUDITIONS?
DON'T TELL ME YOU FORGOT!
I DIDN'T "FORGET" FORGET.
WE'VE JUST GOT THAT
BIG GAME AFTER SCHOOL.
YOU'RE NOT COMING WITH ME?
TO THE MOST IMPORTANT
AUDITION OF MY LIFE?
THE TEAM NEEDS ME.
AND HAVEN'T I ALWAYS BEEN
THERE TO SUPPORT YOU?
(SCOFFS) BECAUSE YOU'RE
ON POWER SQUAD!
YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE THERE TOO!
NOT TODAY!
I KNOW YOU'LL DO GREAT.
BUT I'M JUST NOT SURE
WHY I HAVE TO BE THERE.
BECAUSE IT'S A HUGE,
ONCE IN A LIFETIME CHANCE.
BUT IT'S ALSO KIND OF A ONE
IN A MILLION CHANCE, RIGHT?
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
NOTHING!
JUST THINK YOU NEED
TO BE REALISTIC.
(SARCASTIC)
THANKS!
(VIDEO GAME MUSIC PLAYS)
(SWORD THUNKS)
LOVEQUEEN16:
EXCELLENT KILL, CONNOR!
I HAVE TO GO. BYE.
DAVE:
YOU'RE NOT STILL TALKING
TO THAT LADY CREEP, ARE YOU?
SHE'S NOT A CREEP,
AND WHY DO YOU CARE?
UM, BECAUSE:
A) SHE IS A LADY CREEP,
AND B) SHE'S LIKE,
42 YEARS OLD!
BRO, WHEN SHE WAS OUR AGE,
YOU WERE, LIKE...
WESLEY AND CONNOR:
NEGATIVE 12.
REALLY?
YEAH.
IT'S JUST WEIRD.
SHE'S JUST MY FRIEND AND WE'RE
BOTH INTO "REALM OF DOOM".
WELL, "REALM OF DOOM"
DOES RULE.
BUT YOU KNOW,
WE'RE YOUR FRIENDS, CONNOR!
DAVE:
EXACTLY,
WHY MESS WITH THE REST,
WHEN YOU ALREADY HAVE
THE BEST, HUH?
SHE CARES ABOUT ME,
SHE THINKS I'M INTERESTING,
AND SHE TAKES ME SERIOUSLY.
WE TAKE YOU SERIOUSLY.
YEAH, WE JUST...
THINK YOU'RE TOO SERIOUS.
LET US JUST HELP YOU
GET OVER IT.
THERE'S NOTHING TO GET OVER!
WESLEY:
LET'S JUST GO.
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
OWEN:
BRO, HOLD UP!
BREAK ROOM WITH THE GUYS
AFTER THE GAME?
SHOOT SOME POOL,
SCOPE SOME CHICKS?
I'D LOVE TO.
BUT I HAVE OTHER PLANS.
AW DUDE,
YOU'RE BAILING AGAIN?
YOU'RE NEVER GONNA GET
ANY ACTION THAT WAY!
BIG GAME TODAY, ROCKETTE!
(LAUGHS)
DUDE.
ROCKETTE?
I'M THE TEAM KICKER.
IT'S A GAY JOKE.
OH, HUH!
ANOTHER ONE.
DON'T THEY BOTHER YOU?
OR AT LEAST THE GAY VERSION
OF YOU?
WELL, I DON'T EVEN GET IT.
SO DO YOU WANT TO HANG OUT
SOMEWHERE AFTER THE GAME?
UNTIL FOOTBALL RILEY
AND GAY RILEY COME TOGETHER,
YOU'RE BETTER OFF
HANGING OUT WITH THE TEAM.
DON'T WANNA CRAMP
YOUR STYLE.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
ONE HAZELNUT MACCHIATO,
YOUR FAVOURITE!
(SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
I DON'T THINK
I CAN STOMACH IT.
YOU STILL FEELING LIKE CRAP?
I'M JUST... TIRED,
AND LIKE, ICK.
YEAH,
NOT TO BE A BIG BROTHER?
BUT GO SEE A DOCTOR!
OKAY, OKAY. I WILL.
JUST NOT TODAY.
ALLS I'M SAYING IS YOU'RE NOT
GONNA BE OF ANY USE TO ANYONE
IF YOU'RE YAKKING
IN THE AUDITION.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO ALWAYS SAYS,
"YOU GOTTA PLAY
THROUGH THE PAIN."
(SIGHS)
I'VE COME THIS FAR,
NO WAY AM I GIVING UP NOW.
NOTHING IS GETTING IN THE WAY
OF ME AND MY DEST...
(GAGS)
ARE YOU OKAY?
(CLEARS THROAT)
UH, I'M FINE.
(SIGHS QUEASILY)
CONNOR:
CHATSOFAST?
UH, I DON'T GET IT.
HERE, YOU CLICK HERE
AND IT SEARCHES
FOR HOTTIES
WITH THEIR WEBCAMS ON.
PRETTY COOL, HUH?
WHY WOULD I WANT
TO TALK TO STRANGERS?
STRANGERS?
NO, THEY'RE JUST FRIENDS
YOU HAVEN'T MET YET!
DAVE:
GUYS, FOCUS.
OKAY?
IT'S NOT ABOUT STRANGERS,
IT'S NOT ABOUT YOUR FRIENDS.
IT'S ABOUT HOT GIRLS.
ALL RIGHT?
GO AHEAD, PRESS IT.
DAVE: OOH!
WESLEY: (LAUGHS)
WESLEY:
OH NO, NEXT.
CONNOR:
OKAY.
UH... NO.
NEXT.
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
CONNOR: OH, NO!
WESLEY: NO, NEXT.
WESLEY:
(LAUGHS AWKWARDLY)
OH! THERE, THERE, THERE!
BABE-ALERT!
DAVE: TYPE SOMETHING.
CONNOR: LIKE WHAT?
DAVE: TRY "HELLO", DUMMY.
CONNOR: I'M NOT A DUMMY.
WESLEY:
QUICK! BEFORE THEY CLICK AWAY!
(KEYS CLICK)
WESLEY: (READING)
"DO YOU GUYS PLAY
REALM OF DOOM?"
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
DAVE:
CON MAN!
CONNOR: HUH?
DAVE: THAT'S YOUR OPENING LINE?
CONNOR: YEAH.
DAVE: MOVE, LET ME DO IT.
OKAY UH,
MOVE OVER.
OKAY...
NO, NEXT.
WESLEY:
OH NICE, MAN.
(KEYS CLICK,
COMPUTER BEEPS)
DAVE:
OH! WAIT, WAIT...
RILEY:
HEY ANYA,
I WAS THINKING IT'S BEEN
AGES SINCE WE HUNG OUT.
WANNA DO SOMETHING
AFTER THE GAME?
SORRY RILEY, I'VE GOT A LOT
ON MY PLATE RIGHT NOW.
MAYBE I CAN HELP.
DOUBT IT.
WHAT IS IT?
SCHOOL?
GUY TROUBLES?
YOU CAN TELL ME.
I DON'T THINK SO.
WHATEVER IT IS,
IT CAN'T BE THAT BAD.
MY MOM HAS CANCER.
OH.
I'M SORRY.
I'M GOING STRAIGHT
TO THE ONCOLOGY WARD
AFTER THE GAME.
AND I'M SURE YOU HAVE
BETTER THINGS TO DO.
BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
I, I DON'T.
IT DOES GET BORING
IN THE WAITING ROOM.
MEET ME OUT FRONT,
WE'LL GO TOGETHER.
ARE YOU SURE?
THAT'S WHAT FRIENDS DO,
RIGHT?
♪♪♪
♪ I don't know about you ♪
♪ But I'm ready to go ♪
(CONTESTANTS CHATTER, WARM UP)
♪ They're tryin'
to straighten us up ♪
♪ So let's get on
with the show ♪
♪ Oh oh ♪
♪ Everyone is gonna know
our name ♪
♪ Shake it up ♪
♪ And blast off
with a bang ♪
♪ Are you ready
for a good time ♪
HEY, KC.
UH, I'M SORRY WE HAD A FIGHT.
CAN YOU CALL ME SOON
AS THE GAME'S DONE?
I'M HERE WAITING
FOR MY AUDITION, AND...
I REALLY, REALLY,
NEED YOU HERE.
(SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
PLEASE COME?
(COMPUTER KEYS CLICK)
CONNOR!
DIDN'T WE TALK ABOUT YOU
SPENDING TOO MUCH TIME GAMING?
I DID EVERYTHING YOU TOLD ME
TO DO AT HOME.
I FINISHED MY HOMEWORK,
CLEANED MY ROOM,
SORTED THE RECYCLING?
EVEN PUT OUT THE COMPOST.
FINE, I WANT YOU HOME
AT A DECENT HOUR, OKAY?
(KEYS CLICK)
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
LOVEQUEEN16:
HEY STRANGER,
WHERE WERE YOU?
I MISSED YOU YESTERDAY.
CONNOR:
MY FRIENDS WON'T LET ME
TALK TO YOU.
LOVEQUEEN16:
BUT YOU WANT TO TALK TO ME?
CONNOR:
WELL, YEAH.
LOVEQUEEN16:
GOOD. I WANNA TALK TO YOU, TOO.
I THINK WE'RE A LOT ALIKE.
HOW ARE WE ALIKE?
LOVEQUEEN16:
WELL, WE'RE BOTH ON A QUEST
TO FIND SOMEONE
WHO UNDERSTANDS US.
WHO ACCEPTS US AS WHO WE ARE.
YOU'RE THE FIRST FRIEND
I'VE EVER HAD WHO DOES.
LOVEQUEEN16:
WE CAN TALK SOME MORE
IF YOU WANT.
OH! THE "REALM OF DOOM"
EXPANSION PACK COMES OUT TODAY!
I KNOW, I'M GONNA GO
GET IT AFTER THIS.
LOVEQUEEN16:
WE COULD GO TOGETHER.
MESSAGE ME WHERE YOU'LL BE,
AND I'LL MAP IT.
YEAH, FOR SURE,
I'LL MEET YOU THERE!
(BUTTON CLICKS)
(HEARTBEAT ECHOES)
(HEARTBEATS GROW LOUDER)
YOUR NAME, SWEETHEART.
UM, JENNA MIDDLETON.
VAUGHN:
WELL, IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU,
JENNA MIDDLETON.
DO YOU HAVE WHAT IT TAKES
TO BE THE NEXT TEEN STAR?
UH... (CLEARS THROAT)
YES, SIR.
WHY'S THAT?
UM...
I-I WANT IT REALLY BAD.
YEAH WELL,
WANTING IT'S NOT ENOUGH.
YOU NEED THE TALENT.
I-I THINK I HAVE IT.
WELL, LET'S SEE, WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA PLAY FOR US TODAY?
JENNA:
UM... I-IT'S SOMETHING I WROTE.
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
GREAT.
(SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
YOU CAN BEGIN ANY TIME.
OKAY. UM, SORRY.
(SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
1, 2...
(PLAYING GUITAR)
(HITS DISCORDANT NOTE)
JENNA:
OH! (LAUGHS AWKWARDLY)
OH, SORRY. UM, 1...
(STRUMS OUT OF TUNE CHORD)
YOU KNOW YOU'RE WASTING
OUR TIME HERE,
MS. MIDDLETON.
UH, SORRY.
(SIGHS QUEASILY)
(GASPS)
UM, I THINK...
I THINK I'M GONNA PUKE!
(VOMITING)
VAUGHN:
NEXT!
(SIGHS HEAVIILY)
VAUGHAN:
OKAY, GO AHEAD.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
ANYA:
HEY RILEY,
GREAT GAME!
ALL SET!
ACTUALLY, I'M-I'M KINDA
SURPRISED YOU'RE HERE.
WHY?
I GUESS I JUST DON'T GET
WHY THE WINNING QB
WOULD RATHER HANG OUT
WITH ME AT THE HOSPITAL,
THAN WITH THE TEAM.
OR WITH ZANE.
HE'S STILL MAD
BECAUSE I CAN'T BE MYSELF
WITH THE TEAM.
I DON'T FIT IN ANYWHERE
AT SCHOOL.
MAYBE YOU NEED TO FIND SOMEONE
YOU CAN BE YOURSELF WITH
OUTSIDE OF SCHOOL?
MAYBE I'LL FIND AN OPENLY GAY
FOOTBALL PLAYER
IN THE CANCER WARD!
(LAUGHS)
OH SORRY,
THAT DIDN'T COME OUT RIGHT.
AH, IT'S OKAY.
SOME THINGS YOU NEED
A SENSE OF HUMOUR ABOUT.
YOU KNOW MY MOM'S ONLY GOT ONE
MORE WEEK OF TREATMENT LEFT,
SO IF YOU'RE GONNA FIND
THAT GUY,
YOU BETTER HURRY!
(CONTESTANTS CHATTER)
GIRL:
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU GOT IT!
KC:
JENNA!
I'M SORRY,
I GOT YOUR MESSAGE LATE!
JENNA:
KC, OH!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I KNOW.
BUT FROM NOW ON,
I PROMISE,
I'M SUPPORTIVE
IN EVERYTHING YOU DO.
NO!
I-I TOTALLY MESSED IT UP.
CONTESTANT:
I GOT IT! I GOT IT!
THANK YOU, THANK YOU,
THANK YOU!
WHOOOO! HA HA!
GIRL:
YES!
HEY!
IT'S NOT OVER
TILL IT'S OVER.
I'M PRETTY SURE IT'S OVER.
YOU CAN'T GIVE UP
ON YOUR DREAM.
MARCH BACK IN THERE
AND DON'T TAKE "NO"
FOR AN ANSWER!
(LAUGHS)
I'LL SHOW THEM
WHO'S THEIR NEXT TEEN STAR.
WE SAID MEET AT THE SCHOOL
STEPS, RIGHT?
WESLEY:
YEAH, AT 1600 HOURS.
AKA FOUR O'CLOCK.
YEAH, THAT WAS ALMOST
AN HOUR AGO.
I'VE CALLED HIM LIKE,
10 TIMES.
WHERE THE HELL IS HE?
HE CAN'T BE THAT MAD AT US.
DID YOU CSI THE GAME?
I TRIED,
BUT THERE'S NO ONE ONLINE.
IT'S LIKE A GHOST TOWN
OUT THERE.
SO THERE'S NO CLUES
TO WHERE HE IS RIGHT NOW?
I COULDN'T FIND ANYTHING.
ZIP ZAP ZERO.
YOU DON'T THINK HE'S OVER
LOVEQUEEN16, DO YOU?
WHAT ABOUT THAT BANNER
RIGHT THERE?
WESLEY:
WHAT ABOUT IT?
DAVE:
WELL, HE MIGHT BE IN LINE
FOR IT WITH HER RIGHT NOW!
IT'S POSSIBLE, I GUESS.
WELL, IT'S THE BEST WE'VE GOT.
BUT WHERE?
WELL, HE PRACTICALLY LIVES
AT GAMER WORLD.
OKAY, GOOD.
ALL RIGHT, GOOD.
LET'S ROLL.
WELL, SHOULD WE TELL
MR. SIMPSON?
YEAH,
SHOOT HIM AN EMAIL.
(KEYS CLICK)
DONE.
GOOD SLEUTHING, DAVE!
(GAMERS CHATTER)
LOVEQUEEN16:
(LAUGHS)
YOU'RE REALLY FUNNY, CONNOR.
YOU REALLY MAKE ME LAUGH.
CONNOR:
INTENTIONALLY?
YES, INTENTIONALLY!
NO ONE'S EVER TOLD YOU
THAT BEFORE?
NO.
COME ON,
I DON'T BELIEVE IT!
THE GIRLS AT YOUR SCHOOL
MUST BE ALL OVER YOU!
THEY DON'T EVEN KNOW
I'M ALIVE.
OH, THEY KNOW YOU'RE ALIVE.
YOU'RE TOO HANDSOME
NOT TO NOTICE.
IT'S PROBABLY BECAUSE...
THEY JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND YOU
THE WAY I DO.
YOU'RE REALLY MATURE
FOR YOUR AGE.
YEAH, MAYBE THAT'S IT.
(LAUGHS)
SO, WHAT'RE YOU DOING
AFTER THIS?
DO YOU WANNA COME BACK
TO MY PLACE,
AND WE'LL LIKE,
TEST OUT THE EXPANSION PACK?
SURE, YEAH.
IT'D BETTER LIVE UP
TO THE REVIEWS.
(LAUGHS)
I'M REALLY GLAD WE MET.
ME TOO.
(DOOR LOCK CLICKS)
THANKS.
(GAMERS CHATTER EXCITEDLY)
JENNA:
UH, EXCUSE ME?
UH, HELLO?
I'M UH, JENNA MIDDLETON.
FROM BEFORE?
YEAH, YOU...
YOU HAD YOUR CHANCE, DARLING.
I KNOW, BUT...
I KNOW I CAN DO THIS.
I'M SORRY ABOUT BEFORE,
I HAVEN'T BEEN FEELING WELL.
VAUGHN:
YEAH WELL, SORRY,
THAT'S THE NAME OF THE GAME.
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT
ISN'T GONNA HAPPEN
IN THE REAL WORLD, RIGHT?
SURE, BUT SOMETIMES
THE REAL WORLD
GIVES YOU A SECOND CHANCE?
LOOK,
I'M SORRY SWEETHEART,
WE'VE GOTTA KEEP THINGS
MOVING HERE, SO...
(PLAYING GUITAR)
♪ OH MR. PERFECT
YOU GAVE EVERYTHING TO ME ♪
♪ IT FELT LIKE DESTINY ♪
♪ AND YOU CALL ME
RIGHT ON TIME ♪
♪ YOU'D HOLD MY HAND ♪
♪ DRIVE AROUND IN YOUR CAR ♪
♪ HE LIKES TO PLAY GUITAR
WITH THE RADIO ♪
♪ HAS A TATTOO ♪
♪ AND MY PARENTS
LOVE HIM TOO ♪
♪ NEVER PUT UP A FIGHT ♪
♪ YOU'D SAY IT'S ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ BUT MR. PERFECT
YOU CAN CALL ME CRAZY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I FEEL LIKE
SOMETHING'S MISSING... ♪
WHAT DID YOU GET FOR X?
UH... Y MINUS FIVE?
REALLY?
I GUESSED.
YOU MUST GET A LOT
OF HOMEWORK DONE
WAITING FOR YOUR MOM.
MY MOM'S DAILY RADIOTHERAPY
WAS THE BEST THING
THAT COULD'VE HAPPENED
TO MY MARKS.
YOU REALLY CAN LAUGH
ABOUT IT.
IT'S NICE TO HAVE SOMEBODY
TO LAUGH WITH.
I MEAN, SHE TOLD ME
I DON'T HAVE TO COME,
BUT SHE'S NORMALLY PRETTY TIRED
AFTER HER TREATMENT.
YOU'RE A GOOD DAUGHTER.
AND YOU'RE A GOOD STUDY BUDDY.
(LAUGHS)
YOU KNOW, I'M ACTUALLY
STARTING TO HOPE
THAT YOU DON'T FIND
THAT BOY
THAT YOU CAN BE YOURSELF WITH.
(LAUGHS)
DR. CHRIS:
ANYA,
YOUR MOM'S DOING GREAT.
AH THANKS, DR. CHRIS.
AND I CHECKED OUT THAT BOOK
THAT YOU RECOMMENDED,
AND I LOVED IT.
WELL, I'M GLAD.
RILEY: (CLEARS THROAT)
ANYA: UM...
THIS IS MY FRIEND RILEY.
HI, RILEY.
UH, HI.
YOUR MOM WILL BE RIGHT OUT.
THANKS.
SO, SAME TIME TOMORROW?
AND THE DAY AFTER THAT,
AND THE DAY AFTER THAT.
OH, NO.
I-NOT...
MY MOM'S DOCTOR?
WHAT, YOU TOLD ME
TO LOOK FOR SOMEONE
OUTSIDE OF DEGRASSI...
WELL, HANDS OFF.
DR. CHRIS IS MINE.
YOU HAVE A CRUSH?
KINDA.
TOO BAD HE'S GAY.
HE IS NOT!
MY GAYDAR NEVER
FAILS ME.
UNTIL NOW.
HMPH!
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
TO SETTLE THIS.
HE'S NOT GAY.
♪ HEY MR. PERFECT ♪
♪ I MISS THE SILLY GAMES ♪
♪ TALKIN' ON THE PHONE ♪
♪ YOU'RE DRIVIN' ME INSANE ♪
♪ OH MR. PERFECT ♪
♪ WHERE IS THE ATTITUDE ♪
♪ DANCIN' IN THE RAIN ♪
♪ IT'S A BATTLE EVERY DAY ♪
♪ OH MR. PERFECT ♪
♪ YEAH, MR. PERFECT ♪
♪ MR. PERFECT ♪
♪ OH MR. PERFECT ♪
(SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
(PEN CLATTERS)
VAUGHAN: (WHISPERING)
UM, IT WAS KIND OF UPLIFTING,
DON'T YOU THINK?
SO IT'S OBVIOUS TO ME,
THAT I THINK IT'S-
(WHISPERING)
IT'S A YES FOR ME.
SO, UH... JENNA, RIGHT?
JENNA:
YES.
IT WAS QUITE A RISK
SINGING YOUR OWN SONG.
UH, I CAN PLAY SOMETHING ELSE
IF YOU LIKE, UM...
NO, THAT WON'T BE NECESSARY.
YOU HAD YOUR CHANCE.
I'M JUST GONNA,
I'M GONNA TELL HER.
WE UNANIMOUSLY AGREE
ON THIS ONE.
I'M SORRY...
...THAT WE EVER DOUBTED YOU!
JENNA:
(GASPS)
I-I-I DID IT?
YOU ARE A, A NATURAL.
YOU'RE A,
YOU'RE A TOTAL NATURAL.
AAAH! (LAUGHS)
OH!
VAUGHN:
COME ON, GET YOUR TICKET!
YOU COULD BE THE NEXT
TEEN STAR!
OH, THANK YOU, BABY!
AAAAH!
AAAAAH!
I DID IT! I DID IT!
I DID IT!
AAAH!
JENNA: I GOT IT!
KC: THAT'S AMAZING!
OH!
I KNEW YOU COULD DO IT.
OH! SORRY.
YOU OKAY?
YEAH UH,
JUST A LITTE DIZZY,
I DIDN'T EAT MUCH.
(LAUGHS)
OKAY WELL, LET'S GET
THIS NEXT TEEN STAR SOME FOOD!
KC: STAT!
JENNA: YEP...
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
WHAT IF WE MISS HIM?
WHAT IF HE'S IN COSTUME?
JUST KEEP YOUR EYES OPEN.
CONNOR:
THIS IS SO AWESOME.
DAVE:
THERE!
WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
WE'VE GOTTA GET HIM
AWAY FROM THAT WOMAN.
CONNOR:
IT GOT A 9.1 ON REVIEWS.
LOVEQUEEN16: REALLY?
CONNOR: YEAH.
CONNOR.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
UM, BOUGHT THE EXPANSION PACK.
WE JUST RAN INTO EACH OTHER.
ARE THESE YOUR FRIENDS?
YEAH. SORT OF.
I'M WESLEY,
AND THIS IS DAVE.
WESLEY!
WELL...
YOU GUYS PROBABLY HAVE
STUFF TO DO.
UH, I'LL...
CATCH UP WITH YOU ONLINE.
OKAY?
CONNOR: OKAY.
LOVEQUEEN16: SEE 'YA.
EXCUSE ME.
(SIGHS)
(CAR HONKS)
I'M SO EXCITED,
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
UGH, STUPID DETENTION!
SO, WHAT'D I MISS?
JUST CELEBRATION HUMMUS!
AAAAH! EE!
I KNEW IT!
CONGRATULATIONS!
OH, THANK YOU!
(LAUGHS)
ALLI NEEDS A CELEBRATION
DRINK.
KC, WOULD YOU MIND?
THE DIVA DEMANDS BEGIN ALREADY.
(ALL LAUGH)
(SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
QUICK,
DO SOMETHING WITH THIS.
YOUR CELEBRATION HUMMUS?
WHY?
I CAN'T STAND THE SMELL,
BUT...
I DON'T WANT KC TO GET
SUSPICIOUS.
SUSPICIOUS OF WHAT?
ARE YOU GONNA TAKE
THE PREGNANCY TEST, OR WHAT?
YEAH.
JUST TO RULE IT OUT.
(SIGHS WORRIEDLY)
WESLEY:
WHY WERE YOU HANGING OUT
WITH THAT OLD LADY?
DAVE:
YEAH. WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOU, MAN?
CONNOR:
SHE'S MY FRIEND.
BUT SHE'S OLD!
REALLY, REALLY OLD.
YEAH WELL, SIMPSON'S OLD,
AND HE HANGS OUT WITH ME.
THAT'S 'CAUSE
HE'S YOUR GUARDIAN.
IT'S LIKE HIS JOB.
WHY DOES SHE WANNA SPEND
TIME WITH YOU?
DOESN'T SHE KNOW PEOPLE
HER OWN AGE?
I KEEP TELLING YOU,
SHE'S JUST MY FRIEND!
NOTHING BAD IS HAPPENING!
WHY CAN'T YOU BELIEVE ME?
SHE DID SEEM PRETTY NICE.
SO SHE'S REALLY YOUR FRIEND,
HUH?
YEAH, WE JUST LIKE
THE SAME RPG.
THAT'S ALL.
I'M NOT STUPID!
WESLEY:
SHE'S KIND OF LIKE AN OLD,
FEMALE CONNOR,
IN A, IN A WEIRD WAY.
DAVE:
OKAY, OKAY,
HOW 'BOUT WE JUST YOU KNOW,
BACK OFF A BIT,
AND GIVE YOU SOME SPACE.
DAVE: SOUND GOOD?
CONNOR: YEAH, THANKS.
SORRY WE SCARED HER AWAY.
WHAT ABOUT SIMPSON?
OH, CRAP!
NO, CALL HIM!
WHAT'S SIMPSON'S CELL?
(TIRES SQUEAL)
(ENGINE CUTS OFF)
(DOOR SLAMS)
WAS SHE THERE?
YEAH,
SHE JUST DROVE AWAY.
YOU KNOW BETTER
THAN THIS CONNOR, COME ON.
CONNOR:
YOU TOLD HIM?
MR. SIMPSON:
YOU SHOULD BE THANKING THEM.
GET IN THE CAR.
SHEESH!
♪♪♪
NOTHING'S HAPPENING.
ARE YOU SURE
WE DID IT RIGHT?
(SIGHS)
LET'S SEE.
"PLACE ON DRY SURFACE,
RESULT SIDE UP,
AND WAIT FOR THREE MINUTES."
♪ No we are not new ♪
♪ In our tiny glass houses ♪
(SIGHS)
♪ With the beautiful views ♪
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(SIGHS)
KC AND I SHOULD HAVE BEEN
MORE CAREFUL.
IT'S A BIT LATE TO BE THINKING
ABOUT BIRTH CONTROL.
(SIGHS EMOTIONALLY)
(EXHALES NOISILY)
UGH,
HOW LONG IS THREE MINUTES?!
(SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
(BOTH SIGH)
♪♪♪
♪ And tiny glass houses ♪
♪ Are all tumblin' down ♪
♪ And tiny glass houses
are all tumblin' down ♪
OH, CRAP.