SAV:
DON'T FORGET THE LOVERS LUNCH
IN THE CAF.
IT'S GREAT GRUB,
GREAT SERVICE,
AND IT'S WALKING DISTANCE.
AND WE HAVE ADAM.
SORRY, I'M LATE.
ANY CHANCE YOU BROUGHT
YOUR LEADING LADY?
UH, FIONA PROBABLY
SLEPT IN.
WE WERE UP LATE.
REHEARSING?
IF THAT'S WHAT THE KIDS
ARE CALLING IT.
OFFICIALLY,
I DON'T SUPPORT THIS
DIVA-LIKE BEHAVIOUR.
UNOFFICIALLY...
UP HERE!
YOU WERE RIGHT,
DUDE.
FIONA'S TOTALLY INTO ME.
NO CHAMPAGNE REQUIRED.
SHE'S DRINKING AGAIN?
SHE LIKES CHAMPAGNE AND ME -
SEPARATELY.
IF YOU SPENT TIME
WITH US, YOU'D SEE THAT.
WELL, THEN LET'S SPEND
TIME WITH YOU.
I'M DRAGGING ELI
TO THE LOVERS LUNCH
IN THE CAF TODAY.
YOU AND FIONA SHOULD
COME WITH.
TO-TODAY?
UNLESS YOU HAVE
OTHER PLANS?
NO, NO,
THAT SHOULD BE FINE.
GREAT.
THEN WE'LL SEE YOU
AT NOON.
OKAY.
COME ON.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever! Woo-hoo!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
ANYA:
(GIGGLING)
PAM:
SOMEONE'S GIDDY.
JUST TEXTING HOLLY J.
ABOUT A BOY?
THE SWEETEST!
LIKE AMAZING!
SO WHEN DO I GET TO MEET
MY FUTURE SON-IN-LAW?
IT'S DR. CHRIS.
MY WAY-TOO-OLD-FOR-YOU-
CANCER DOCTOR?
HE'S ONLY TWENTY-FIVE.
THAT'S EIGHT YEARS OLDER
THAN YOU ARE.
HONEY, NOTHING IS GOING
TO HAPPEN.
THEN WHY DID WE GO
ON A DATE?!
WHEN?!
LAST NIGHT.
AND I THINK WE'RE GONNA
DO IT AGAIN.
OH, NO YOU'RE NOT.
MOM, I'M SEVENTEEN.
YOU CAN'T TELL ME
WHAT TO DO.
ANYA MARIE MACPHERSON,
WE ARE NOT FINISHED
WITH THIS DISCUSSION.
ARE YOU GONNA CHANGE
YOUR MIND?
(BELL RINGS)
THEN WE ARE.
WOW.
SO ARE YOU AND ADAM
A THING?
YOU KNOW, A COUPLE.
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT YOU LIKE HIM?
THEN WHY WERE YOU
MAKING OUT?
I DON'T KNOW,
HOLLY J.
CAN WE STOP WITH
THE INTERROGATION?!
OKAY, OKAY...
I'VE JUST NEVER SEEN YOU WITH
SOMEONE LIKE THAT BEFORE.
I FEEL COMFORTABLE
AROUND HIM.
SAFE.
HE LIKES ME
THE WAY I AM.
THOSE ARE ALL
REALLY GOOD THINGS.
SO WHY THROW DRINKING
INTO THE MIX?
DID I TELL YOU
ADAM SENT ME ROSES?
WHITE.
MY FAVOURITE.
FIONA...
DRINKING MAKES ME
FEEL GOOD, HOLLY J.
WHY WOULD I STOP?
(SCOFFS)
SADIE:
HEY. LET ME GET THAT
FOR YOU.
THANKS.
SO WE STILL ON
FOR BASKETBALL LATER?
UH, I WAS THINKING
WE COULD DO
SOMETHING A LITTLE BIT
MORE SEDENTARY,
LIKE A, LIKE A MOVIE?
ARE YOU AFRAID TO PLAY
A GIRL?
YEAH.
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
LOOK, I'LL, UH, TALL YOU.
UH, CALL YOU.
CALL YOU LATER.
SO, I HEARD WIZARD OF OZ
IS PLAYING AT THE REP.
BET SADIE LOVES
MUNCHKINS.
BETTER BUY HER DINNER FIRST.
YOU DON'T WANT HER
TO FEEL... SHORT CHANGED.
(LAUGHING)
YEAH, WELL,
AT LEAST I'M NOT A GEEK.
CONNOR:
GOOD ONE, DAVE.
YEAH, YOU'RE DEFINITELY
NOT SHORT ON MATERIAL.
(LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY)
OVER HERE.
ANYA:
MY MOM IS BEING
SO UNREASONABLE.
EVERYONE KNOWS THE RULES
FOR DATING
IS HALF YOUR AGE
PLUS SEVEN.
SO HALF OF TWENTY-FIVE,
PLUS SEVEN...
HOLLY J:
IS NINETEEN AND A HALF.
AND YOU ARE...
ANYA:
ALMOST EIGHTEEN.
BUT WHO NEEDS STUPID RULES
WHEN YOU HAVE A CONNECTION
LIKE WE DO?
WELL, YOU HAVE TO TELL HIM
THE TRUTH.
I'M GOING TO.
HOLLY J:
AFTER YOU'RE HAPPILY MARRIED
AND HAVE TWO CHILDREN?
(SIGHS) OR THREE.
I'M STILL HAVEN'T
DECIDED YET.
HOLLY J:
WHAT IF HE WANTS TO GO
TO A BAR?
I'LL GET A FAKE ID.
HOLLY J:
OR RENT A CAR?
I DON'T DRIVE.
OR TAKES YOU TO
A WORK EVENT
WHERE YOU BUMP INTO ONE
OF YOUR PARENTS' FRIENDS
AND THEY KNOW
HOW OLD YOU ARE?
(BLOWS) I'D...
DO YOU THINK HE'D GET
IN TROUBLE?
MAYBE.
THE LONGER YOU WAIT
TO TELL HIM,
THE HARDER IT'S GONNA BE.
WE'RE HAVING LUNCH
AT HIS OFFICE.
SEE? SOUNDS LIKE
THE PERFECT OPPORTUNITY
TO SPILL THE BEANS.
IF HE LIKES ME AT TWENTY,
HE'LL LIKE ME AT SEVENTEEN,
RIGHT?
(EXHALES)
(CHATTER)
HOLLY J:
BON APPETIT!
AND DON'T FORGET TO SAVE
SOME ROOM FOR DESSERT.
ADAM:
TWELVE-TEN.
GUESS SHE'S NOT COMING.
FIONA:
HELLOOOOOO.
YOU MADE IT.
HOW COULD I RESIST
SPENDING TIME
WITH YOU, ELI
AND CLARE.
YOU HAVE PRETTY EYES.
UM, THANKS.
THE COLOUR OF THAT SHIRT
DOES NOTHING FOR THEM.
ELI:
DUDE, YOU NEED TO GET HER
OUTTA HERE; SHE'S WASTED.
IT'S NOT VERY NICE
TO WHISPER.
IS IT?
COME ON.
LET'S GO FOR A WALK?
BUT WE JUST GOT HERE.
BESIDES, CLARE AND I...
ARE REALLY
HITTING IT OFF.
CLARE:
(FAKE CHUCKLE)
NO, I WANT TO BE
ALONE WITH YOU.
OH...
THAT TYPE OF WALK.
YEAH.
COME ON.
WE SHOULD GO SHOPPING.
CALL ME.
A WALK WAS
A GOOD IDEA.
ADAM:
FIONA... FIONA, STOP.
FIONA:
I THOUGHT YOU LIKED ME?
YOU'RE DRUNK.
DID HOLLY J TALK
TO YOU?
WHAT?
SHE THINKS I DRINK
TOO MUCH.
SHE DOESN'T UNDERSTAND ME
LIKE YOU DO.
SHE DOESN'T GET THAT
DRINKING MAKES IT EASIER.
MAKES WHAT EASIER?
BEING WITH YOU.
YOU'RE DRINKING
BECAUSE OF ME?
SEE?
YOU DO UNDERSTAND.
NO...
I DON'T.
FIONA:
ADAM!
DR. CHRIS:
UH, WHEN YOU CALLED EARLIER,
IT SOUNDED SERIOUS.
MM, IT'S JUST THIS
LITTLE THING.
WHEN I TELL YOU,
YOU'LL PROBABLY LAUGH.
ARE THOSE TICKETS
TO A RENAISSANCE FAIR?
THERE'S ONE IN ITHACA
THIS WEEKEND.
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT
LIKE TO GO.
UH...
IT'S TOO SOON,
ISN'T IT?
I'LL RETURN THEM.
UM, NO,
DON'T YOU DARE!
THERE'S THIS AMAZING
BED AND BREAKFAST THERE.
WE'D STAY OVERNIGHT?
NO, I'D BOOK TWO ROOMS.
THERE'S NO PRESSURE.
UM, UH...
(NERVOUS CHUCKLE)
THEN I GUESS I JUST HAVE
TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT TO TELL MY MOM.
(GIGGLES)
UH, BECAUSE WE WERE SUPPOSED
TO DO SOMETHING TOGETHER
THIS WEEKEND.
SO WHAT DID YOU WANT
TO TELL ME?
OH THAT...
UM, IT'S... IT'S...
NOT IMPORTANT.
COMEDY OR HORROR?
I CAN'T DECIDE.
YEAH, I, UH...
I DON'T THINK I'M GONNA
BE ABLE TO MAKE IT.
SOMETHING CAME UP.
OH.
MAYBE TOMORROW?
YEAH, YEAH, MAYBE.
(BELL RINGS)
COOL.
SO, READY FOR YOUR
BIG DATE TONIGHT?
YEAH, I DON'T THINK
IT'S GONNA WORK OUT.
ME AND SADIE,
WE HAVE NOTHING IN COMMON.
BUT SHE PLAYS BASKETBALL.
AND YOU PLAY BASKETBALL.
SHE LIKES HIP HOP.
YOU LIKE HIP HOP.
AND SHE LIKES YOU.
AND YOU LIKE YOU -
A LOT.
(BOTH LAUGH)
SO WHAT'S
THE PROBLEM?
DAVE:
LOOK, MAN,
SHE'S A GIRAFFE, ALL RIGHT?
SHE'S A BEAN POLE...
A FREAK OF NATURE.
AND YOU'RE A JERK.
ELI:
WE WERE LOOKING FOR YOU.
WE CANCELLED
REHEARSAL.
ADAM:
SORRY ABOUT FIONA.
CLARE:
DON'T BE.
WOMEN ARE TROUBLE.
EVEN ME?
ESPECIALLY YOU.
I WANT THAT -
WHAT YOU TWO HAVE.
AND GET IT YOU WILL.
BUT FOR RIGHT NOW,
LET'S BLOW THIS JOINT.
FIONA:
DID I MISS REHEARSAL?
THOUGHT IT STARTED AT FOUR.
CAN YOU GUYS GIVE US
A MINUTE?
WE'LL BE OUT THERE
IF YOU NEED US.
GUESS CLARE AND I WON'T BE
SHOPPING ANYTIME SOON.
I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD
HANG OUT ANYMORE.
BECAUSE OF WHAT
I SAID?
I WAS STRESSED.
CONFUSED.
ARE YOU DRINKING
BECAUSE OF ME?
I CAN STOP.
JUST, PLEASE,
DON'T LEAVE.
GIVE ME ONE GOOD REASON.
I'M FALLING IN LOVE
WITH YOU.
YOU'RE WHAT?
I LOVE YOU, ADAM.
I THOUGHT YOU FELT
THE SAME WAY.
I DO.
WALK ME HOME?
ANYA:
MOM! UM... (NERVOUS LAUGH)
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HOME?!
I LEFT SOME FILES
ON THE COUNTER.
WHY AREN'T YOU
AT SCHOOL?
I WAS JUST HEADING BACK.
WITHOUT YOUR UNIFORM?
ANYA, WOULD YOU LIKE
TO TELL ME
WHERE YOU'RE GOING
AND WITH WHOM?
(EXHALES)
UH, DR. CHRIS.
WE'RE GOING TO THE RENAISSANCE
FAIR IN ITHACA.
OH NO, YOU'RE NOT.
BUT MOM-
NO BUTS ABOUT IT.
WHAT KIND OF GUY
SKIPS TOWN
WITH A SEVENTEEN-YEAR-OLD
GIRL?
HOW OLD DOES HE THINK
YOU ARE?
(SIGHS) TWENTY...
OH...
AND A HALF.
ANYA!
YOU HAVE TO TELL HIM
THE TRUTH.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
♪♪♪
MISSED YOU.
FIONA:
SO, I WAS THINKING,
FOR OUR FIRST OFFICIAL DATE,
A LATTE IN PARIS?
PARIS?
YOU'RE RIGHT. TOO CROWDED
IN THE SPRING.
WHAT ABOUT A MACCHIATO
IN ROME.
(CHUCKLES)
LET ME COME UP
WITH SOMETHING.
IT'LL BE A SURPRISE.
FIONA:
PERFETTO.
I GOTTA GO.
I'LL SEE YOU AFTER CLASS.
FIONA PULLS YOU IN.
YOU WANNA BELIEVE
WHAT SHE SAYS;
THAT SHE DOESN'T
HAVE A PROBLEM.
UM, HAD A PROBLEM.
SHE WAS ONLY DRINKING
'CAUSE SHE WAS STRESSED.
I THINK FIONA'S
AN ALCOHOLIC
AND YOU'RE ENABLING HER.
NO. (LAUGHS)
NO, YOU'RE WRONG.
SHE NEEDS HELP -
REHAB.
HER MOM AND I ARE ORGANIZING
AN INTERVENTION FOR TONIGHT,
AND I THINK
YOU SHOULD BE THERE.
SO YOU'RE TAKING HER
AWAY?
WE'VE TRIED
EVERYTHING ELSE.
LET'S TAKE OFF.
WHERE TO?
FAR AWAY FROM HERE.
OKAY. I JUST NEED
TO GO HOME FIRST,
PACK SOME ESSENTIALS.
THIS IS NOT THE RIGHT OUTFIT
FOR AN ADVENTURE.
OKAY. WHATEVER.
LET'S JUST GO.
GIRL:
DOWN LOW!
DOWN HERE!
GREAT!
WESLEY:
YOU STILL LIKE HER.
YOU KNOW, THERE'S A LOT
OF ADVANTAGES
TO DATING A TALLER GIRL.
SHE LOOKS OLDER
FOR STARTERS.
CONNOR:
AND SHE CAN REACH THINGS
YOU CAN'T.
WESLEY:
GOOD ONE, CONNOR.
AND TALLER PEOPLE TEND TO BE
MORE SUCCESSFUL IN LIFE.
LOOK, KNOCK IT OFF,
GUYS, ALL RIGHT?
I CAN'T DATE SADIE.
SHE'S FREAKISH.
WESLEY:
DAVE, I DON'T THINK SADIE'S
HEIGHT'S THE PROBLEM.
THEN WHAT IS?
YOURS.
LOOK, EVERYONE WHO SEES ME
WITH HER
IS GONNA THINK
I'M A SHRIMP.
BUT YOU ARE
A SHRIMP.
YEAH, AND A SHORTER GIRLFRIEND
WON'T CHANGE THAT.
I MEAN, WE DO HAVE
A LOT IN COMMON.
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T THINK
SHE'LL NEVER FORGIVE ME.
WESLEY:
OH, COME ON.
DON'T SELL YOURSELF SHORT.
(LAUGHING)
(KNOCKING)
DR. CHRIS:
YOU'RE RIGHT ON TIME,
AND YOU'RE A LIGHT PACKER.
PAM, UH...
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
DID I DO
SOMETHING WRONG?
(SIGHS) I HAVEN'T BEEN
COMPLETELY HONEST WITH YOU.
I'M A LITTLE YOUNGER
THAN I SAID I WAS.
NINETEEN?
CLOSE.
EIGHTEEN?
ALMOST.
YOU'RE SEVENTEEN.
OH MY GOD!
PAM, I HAD NO IDEA.
I WAS GOING AWAY
WITH YOU.
COME ON, ANYA.
IT'S TIME TO GO HOME.
UH... PAM, IT WAS, UH,
NICE SEEING YOU.
AND ANYA, I REALLY
ENJOYED DINNER.
YEAH, ME TOO.
PAM:
IT'S GONNA BE OKAY,
HONEY.
ANYA:
NO, IT'S NOT.
YOU RUINED EVERYTHING!
ADAM:
HEY, FIONA, BACK FROM
THE BANK MACHINE.
YOU ALL PACKED?
FIONA?
ARE YOU OKAY?
MMM...
I ONLY HAD A LITTLE.
OH, EVERYTHING'S
SPINNING.
'KAY, I'LL GET YOU
SOME WATER.
(FIONA VOMITS AND COUGHS)
(DIALING BEEPS, PHONE RINGS)
HOLLY J'S VOICEMAIL:
HI, YOU'VE REACHED
HOLLY J SINCLAIR.
PLEASE LEAVE A MESSAGE.
HEY, IT'S ADAM.
I WANT TO HELP.
(HUM OF STUDENT CHATTER)
(BASKETBALL BOUNCES)
(NET AND RIM RATTLE)
DAVE:
YOU'RE NOT SQUARE
TO THE BASKET.
(CHAIN JINGLES)
ALL RIGHT, LOOK,
I WAS A JERK EARLIER.
SADIE:
YOU CALLED ME A GIRAFFE.
THEY'RE BEAUTIFUL
CREATURES:
THEY'RE TALL, GRACEFUL.
THEY CAN, YOU KNOW,
REACH ALL THE HIGH LEAVES.
SOUNDED BETTER
IN MY HEAD.
HMM.
LOOK, I WANT TO
MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
HOW ABOUT NACHOS
AT LITTLE MISS STEAKS?
ALL RIGHT,
I'LL MAKE IT EASY.
FIRST ONE TO TEN WINS.
I WIN, WE GO OUT;
YOU WIN, SAYONARA.
YOUR BALL.
♪ She high!
You're quite a guy ♪
Back at the line ♪
♪ She high!
I'm out to play ♪
♪ Watch my body
Get out the way ♪
♪ She high!
You're quite a guy ♪
Back at the line ♪
♪ She high!
I'll rock the shot ♪
♪ She looks like
she never stops! ♪
♪ She high! ♪
♪ That's right! ♪
♪ She hotter than the fire
in the room ♪
♪ Let's try! ♪
♪ She got the booty,
make your pants go woo! ♪
(GIGGLES)
WHY WON'T YOU TELL ME
WHERE WE'RE GOING?
BECAUSE THEN IT WOULDN'T
BE A SURPRISE.
DOES IT INVOLVE
A PLANE?
NO.
A TRAIN?
FIONA.
WELL, WHAT IF I'M NOT
APPROPRIATELY ATTIRED?
YOU LOOK PERFECT.
ADAM:
OKAY, YOU CAN TAKE
THE BLIND-FOLD OFF.
WHAT ARE THEY
DOING HERE?
MRS. COYNE:
HONEY, WE'RE WORRIED
ABOUT YOUR DRINKING
AND WE WANT YOU TO CONSIDER
SOME IN-PATIENT THERAPY.
REHAB?!
OH, THIS IS SO
NOT HAPPENING.
GET OUT OF MY WAY!
SWEETIE,
ADAM DID A GOOD THING.
MAKE HIM LEAVE!
I NEVER WANT
TO SEE HIM AGAIN.
I'LL LEAVE.
HOLLY J:
LOOK, WE JUST WANNA
TALK TO YOU.
FIONA:
I TOLD YOU, I'M FINE.
ANYA:
(SIGHS)
THANK YOU
FOR MEETING ME HERE.
UM...
I LIED, BUT...
WE HAD A CONNECTION
AND I REALLY DON'T THINK
MY AGE CHANGES THAT.
YOU KNOW, JAY-Z IS LIKE
12 YEARS OLDER THAN BEYONCE.
YEAH, BEYONCE'S
NOT SEVENTEEN.
IN TWO MONTHS,
I WON'T BE EITHER.
TWO MONTHS?
SIXTY DAYS.
(SIGHS)
YOUR MOM HAS TO BE
ON BOARD.
WELL, YOU DID HELP
SAVE HER LIFE.
'KAY, LET'S TALK
IN TWO MONTHS.
SERIOUSLY?!
SERIOUSLY.
BUT UNTIL THEN,
WE'RE JUST FRIENDS.
YEAH.
(CHUCKLES)
WELL, HOW ABOUT A KISS
TO TIDE ME OVER?
OKAY.
WELL, YOU BETTER BE
WORTH THE WAIT.
(LAUGHING)
ELI:
PIE?
COME ON, IT'LL MAKE YOU
FEEL BETTER.
FIONA SAID SHE NEVER
WANTS TO SEE ME AGAIN.
ELI:
SHE WASN'T THINKING STRAIGHT.
CLARE:
SHE'LL CHANGE HER MIND.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
TO WALLOW IN SELF-PITY.
HEY.
I CALLED YOUR HOUSE.
YOUR BROTHER SAID
YOU WERE HERE.
ADAM:
HOW IS SHE?
HOLLY J:
SHE'S MAD - AT ALL OF US.
YEAH, BUT MOSTLY ME.
LISTEN, I'VE BEEN IN
THE DOGHOUSE
WITH MISS COYNE BEFORE.
SHE'LL GET OVER IT.
MAYBE.
DEFINITELY.
WHEN I WENT
TO HER CONDO
TO PACK HER A BAG
FOR REHAB,
I FOUND THIS.
I THINK IT'S A PAGE
FROM HER JOURNAL.
SHE'D KILL ME
FOR GIVING THIS TO YOU,
BUT AFTER ALL
YOU'VE DONE...
(SIGHS)
FIONA:
YOU'VE JUST LEFT...
AND I CAN'T STOP
THINKING ABOUT YOU -
YOUR FACE, YOUR VOICE,
YOUR TOUCH;
HOW YOU LISTEN TO ME
THE WAY NO ONE ELSE DOES;
HOW IT'S EASIER
TO BE WITH YOU THAN NOT;
HOW WHEN WE'RE TOGETHER,
I NEVER WANT IT TO END.
I'D BE EASIER
IF I DIDN'T FEEL THIS WAY
CUZ THERE ARE A MILLION REASONS
WHY WE SHOULDN'T WORK.
BUT EVEN THOUGH I KNOW THAT,
I REALLY, REALLY HOPE
THAT WE WILL.