♪♪♪
IS SHE OKAY?
SHE'S BREATHING,
RIGHT?
IS SHE SLEEPING?
PROBABLY JUST UP
ALL NIGHT GAMING.
CHANTAY:
WAKEY, WAKEY!
TOUGH NIGHT
AT THE OFFICE?
I JUST WANTED TO GET UH...
A HEAD START ON
OUR WORK STUDY PRESENTATION.
I GUESS I MUST HAVE DOSED OFF.
(BELL RINGS)
WHY ARE WE SURROUNDED
BY GRADE TENS?
THIS IS OUR CLASS.
WE HAVE HISTORY.
RIGHT, I KNEW THAT.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever, Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
MS. OH:
AND AS SOCIETY MOVES FROM
THE HOW OF MEDIA CONSUMPTION,
CRITICAL ANALYSIS
OF THE INFORMATION
IS MOST IMPORTANT.
IS IT OBJECTIVE
OR IS THERE AN AGENDA?
AND HOW DO WE SNIFF OUT
AN AGENDA?
HOLLY J?
HI. I THOUGHT THAT WOULD BE
A SOFTIE FOR YOU.
I'M SORRY.
(BELL RINGS)
SAVED BY THE BELL.
OKAY, SOCIAL MEDIA SITES
CAN BE UNBLOCKED
FOR STUDENTS WHO NEED THEM
FOR WORK-STUDY RESEARCH.
I'LL HAVE THE CODES TOMORROW.
HEY...
WE GOT A LEAD
ON MY SISTER.
ALLI? WH-WHAT IS IT?
SURVEILLANCE FOOTAGE
OF HER GETTING INTO A CAR.
THE POLICE ARE GONNA
COME OVER TONIGHT
TO MAKE A PLAN.
I'LL JUST KEEP YOU POSTED.
WELL, GOOD LUCK.
THANKS.
MS. OH:
HOLLY J, CHANTAY...
HOW ARE THINGS
WITH COUNCILLOR GREYSON?
CHANTAY:
OUR WORK-STUDY?
THREE WEEKS IN
AND IT'S GOING GREAT!
WELL, YOUR INITIAL EVALUATIONS
ARE IN
AND, CHANTAY, MS. GREYSON'S
VERY IMPRESSED WITH YOU.
I'M JUST SOAKING IT UP
LIKE A SPONGE.
IT'S A GREAT EVALUATION.
KEEP IT UP.
WHAT ABOUT MINE?
CHANTAY, YOU MIND IF I HAVE
A WORD WITH HOLLY J?
SURE. BYE.
BYE.
SOMETHING WRONG?
COUNCILLOR GREYSON
SEES POTENTIAL,
BUT SHE THINKS
YOU'RE DISTRACTED,
UNFOCUSED.
MAYBE I'M A TAD STRESSED.
THIS ISN'T LIKE YOU,
HOLLY J.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
YOU PRIORITIZE
WHAT'S IMPORTANT,
OKAY?
THANKS, MS. OH.
I'LL DO BETTER.
MR. BHANDARI:
MY 15-YEAR-OLD DAUGHTER
HAS BEEN MISSING FOR 24 HOURS
AND ALL THE POLICE CAN SAY
IS "CONTACT THE SHELTERS."
THERE MUST BE SOMETHING ELSE!
SAV, SHOW ME THE PHOTO AGAIN.
THE POLICE SAID THERE'S
NO IDENTIFYING INFORMATION,
BUT SHE'S SMILING.
MR. BHANDARI:
WHO DOES SHE KNOW WITH A CAR?
THE OFFICER SAYS THREE-QUARTERS
OF RUNAWAYS COME HOME IN A WEEK.
SAV:
SO, WHAT?
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO WAIT THEN?
THAT'S THE PLAN?
WHAT ABOUT THE OTHER QUARTER?
SAV!
(SHAKY BREATH)
I'M SURE
THEY'LL FIND HER, MOM.
I SHOULD GET STARTED
ON THE LAUNDRY.
IT'S PILING UP.
I'VE ALREADY CANVASSED
ALL HER FRIENDS AT SCHOOL.
THEY HAVEN'T SEEN HER.
WHERE WOULD SHE GO?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
PERINO:
AH-HA!
(GRUNTS)
HISTORY IS THE STUDY OF CHANGE
OVER TIME!
HOW MANY OF YOU REMEMBER
BURYING THIS BAD BOY
BACK IN GRADE SEVEN?
YOU WROTE LETTERS TO YOURSELVES!
HOW MUCH DID YOUR TWEEN SELVES
THINK YOU'D CHANGE BY NOW?
I WAS SUCH A GEEK
BACK THEN.
UN-HUH.
"HEY, WESLEY,
WHAT'S UP, DUDE?
REMEMBER WHEN WE USED TO LIST
THE ATMOSPHERIC LAYERS?
BET WE'RE SAYING SOMETHING
COOLER NOW, RIGHT?"
(SCOFFS)
"AND YOU'RE SAYING IT
WHILE DRIVING YOUR HOT CAR,
WITH YOUR GIRLFRIEND,
CELEBRATING YOUR WORLD RECORD!"
WORLD RECORD?
I WAS REALLY INTO
THE GUINNESS BOOK.
SO?
I'LL BE SIXTEEN IN A WEEK
AND I'VE DONE NOTHING!
I STRIKE OUT WITH THE LADIES,
I HAVE NO CAR...
(SIGHS)
I'VE LET MYSELF DOWN.
(GROANS)
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
(SIGHS)
(CHURCH BELL RINGS)
(KNOCKS)
SAV BHANDARI!
TO WHAT DO I OWE
THE PLEASURE?
HAVE YOU SEEN MY SISTER?
ALLI?
YEAH.
YOUR EX-GIRLFRIEND.
WHY? SHE ON THE LAM
OR SOMETHING?
SHE RAN AWAY
AND WE'RE REALLY WORRIED
ABOUT HER.
UH, NO. SORRY,
BUT I HAVEN'T SEEN HER.
WELL,
IF YOU HEAR FROM HER,
COULD YOU GIVE ME
A CALL PLEASE?
WILL DO.
I CAN EXPLAIN.
I THOUGHT YOUR PARENTS
KICKED YOU OUT.
THEY DIDN'T WANT ME
AT HOME ANYMORE;
SAME DIFFERENCE.
PEOPLE ARE LOOKING FOR YOU,
THEY'RE WORRIED.
YOU GOTTA BE HEADING HOME.
I CAN'T.
MY PARENTS HATE ME.
THERE ARE DISGUSTING RUMOURS
ABOUT ME AT DEGRASSI.
I GOT INTO A FIGHT
WITH THIS GIRL...
SO RUMOURS AND A FIGHT -
NO BIG DEAL.
AFTER THE FIGHT,
MY PARENTS GOT CALLED
INTO THE SCHOOL.
JOHNNY,
THEY SAW MY FILE.
THEY FOUND OUT
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
EVERYTHING?
ALLI:
ABOUT THE NAKED PHOTOS
I SENT YOU;
THAT WE HAD SEX.
THEY FOUND OUT
ABOUT MY STD TESTS.
THEY TREATED ME
LIKE I WAS DIRT.
I TRIED EVERYTHING I COULD
TO MAKE IT BETTER,
BUT NOTHING WORKED.
I HAVE NOWHERE ELSE TO GO.
(EXHALES)
OKAY,
ALL RIGHT, YOU CAN...
YOU CAN STAY HERE FOR A WHILE.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU,
THANK YOU!
JUST UNTIL I FIGURE
EVERYTHING OUT.
(RELIEVED SIGH)
HOLLY J:
(SIGHS) JUST LOOK AT EVERYONE
DOING REAL STUFF,
WHILE WE SIT HERE
STUFFING ENVELOPES.
CHANTAY:
NOBODY SAID A WORK-STUDY
WOULD BE GLAMOROUS.
YOU KNOW,
IF I LICK ONE MORE OF THESE,
I'M GONNA BE SICK.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE NOT?
I MEAN, I KINDA TOOK
THIS WORK-STUDY
BECAUSE YOU'RE THIS TYPE-A
WONDER WOMAN
AND I THOUGHT
WE'D MAKE A GREAT TEAM.
(COUGHS)
BUT NO OFFENCE,
YOU'VE KIND OF BEEN
A DRAG.
HOW COULD I POSSIBLY
BE OFFENDED BY THAT?
OKAY,
YOU TELL ME SOMETHING.
HOW ARE YOU NOT COMPLETELY
STRESSED OUT AND TIRED
ALL THE TIME?
I DON'T HAVE
50 GAZILLION THINGS GOING ON.
BUT I GUESS THAT'S WHY
YOU'RE MS. YALE
AND I'M NOT.
BEV GREYSON:
HOW ARE THOSE ENVELOPES COMING?
UH, GREAT, MS. GREYSON.
CALL ME BEV.
YOU MIGHT BE STUDENTS,
BUT HERE YOU'RE PART
OF MY TEAM.
OKAY, BEV.
UM, CAN I ASK YOU
SOMETHING?
SURE.
HOLLY, RIGHT?
I'M STILL TRYING TO LEARN
ALL THE NAMES!
IT'S HOLLY J, ACTUALLY,
BUT IT DOESN'T EVEN MATTER.
CAN I PITCH YOU
MY IDEAS
FOR MOBILIZING THE YOUTH VOTE
THROUGH SOCIAL MEDIA?
BEV:
SURE. BUT FIRST WE HAVE
TO MOBILIZE
A WHOLE BUNCH OF FEET
FOR THE MINDS IN MOVEMENT
10K CHARITY FUN RUN.
THOSE SUMMER CAMPS
DON'T PAY FOR THEMSELVES.
10K?
YOU'RE LUCKY YOU'RE BOTH
YOUNG AND ENERGETIC.
(STUNNED LAUGH)
A 10K RUN?
MIGHT BE A CHANCE TO MAKE
A GOOD SECOND IMPRESSION.
YEAH.
(SIGHS)
♪♪♪
♪ Take the feelings
that you felt ♪
♪ Toss them down
a wishing well ♪
♪ Shut your eyes
and dream your dreams ♪
♪ Where it's lonely
and serene ♪
♪ Are you lonely and serene? ♪
♪♪♪
(SIGHS)
♪ 'Cause your love
will be revealed  ♪
(DOOR OPENS)
EVER BEEN TO VANCOUVER?
YEAH. RAINY AS HELL.
GOOD THING
I PACKED MY JACKET,
'CAUSE I THINK
IT'S GONNA BE MY NEW HOME.
WHAT?
YOU GONNA LIVE IN A PARK?
I'LL GET A JOB.
MAYBE I COULD BE A NANNY.
YOU KNOW, FREE ROOM AND BOARD.
(EXHALES)
WHAT? YOU SAID I'D HAVE
TO LEAVE EVENTUALLY.
NOT ACROSS THE COUNTRY -
HOME.
FINE.
I'LL WALK MYSELF
TO THE BUS STATION.
(EXHALES)
WAIT.
YOU'RE NEVER GONNA MAKE IT
ACROSS THE COUNTRY
WITH EVERYONE LOOKING
FOR YOU.
YOU NEED...
YOU NEED A DISGUISE.
WHERE AM I GOING
TO GET THAT?
JUST STAY ONE
MORE NIGHT.
WE'LL WORK ON IT
IN THE MORNING.
FINE,
BUT THEN I'M GONE.
♪ Hide yourself
from all this consequence ♪
♪ 'cause it seems much greater
than defense ♪
FEMALE SERVER:
ARE YOU DONE?
(BREATHING HARD)
HELLO?
PUNCH IN YOUR ORDER!
JEEZ! WHAT'S WRONG?
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S MY HEAD.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD GO HOME.
YEAH.
♪ So forward on... ♪
(BELL RINGS)
THERE'S GOTTA BE A WORLD RECORD
I CAN BREAK.
HOT-DOG EATING?
MM. YOU GET THE STOMACH CRAMPS
AFTER LIKE TWO.
OH, YEAH.
OH,
LONGEST FINGERNAILS?
YEAH, YEAH, SURE...
UNLESS YOU GET NERVOUS.
'CAUSE...
SLEEPING WITH
THE MOST SCORPIONS!
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WHERE WOULD I FIND
THAT MANY SCORPIONS?
YOU KNOW, YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO
CRAZY THINGS
TO IMPRESS PEOPLE.
BUT UNCLE MIKE,
THIS ISN'T CRAZY.
SO SLEEPING WITH...
OH, 57 SCORPIONS ISN'T CRAZY?
I PROMISED MYSELF
I'D SET A WORLD RECORD
BY SIXTEEN.
THIS IS MY RITE OF PASSAGE.
MY... MY VISION QUEST.
MY TRIP UP THE MOUNTAIN
TO FIGHT THE WOLF!
OKAY. OKAY.
WOW! OKAY, OKAY.
GIVE ME THIS.
HEY, WHAT ABOUT THIS?
HEY, YOU WERE PRETTY GOOD
AS A KID.
RIGHT?
ONE HUNDRED SEVENTY EIGHT
THOUSAND.
YEAH, YEAH.
I CAN TRY!
BUT I'M GONNA NEED
SURGICAL TAPE, RUBBER HOSING,
AN IV, CRASH MATS,
AN EMPTY ROOM AND...
AND TIME OFF SCHOOL.
I'LL TALK TO SIMPSON.
WE'LL-WE'LL TELL HIM
IT'S A PHYSICS PROJECT!
SAV: HEY, HOLLY J.
HOLLY J: HEY.
(COUGHING)
JEEZ, YOU OKAY?
DO I NEED
A SURGICAL MASK?
SORE THROAT -
COULD BE STREP.
WHICH COULD EXPLAIN
WHY I'VE BEEN SO TIRED
AND COMPLETELY OUT OF IT
LATELY.
HEY, ENOUGH ABOUT ME.
ANY NEWS?
NOPE. BUT UH...
I'M PUTTING THESE UP
AFTER SCHOOL.
GREAT! I'LL HELP!
ARE YOU KIDDING?
NO.
HOLLY J, YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU'VE BEEN HIT BY A TRUCK!
OKAY, I JUST NEED A QUICK NAP
IN THE STUDENT COUNCIL LOUNGE
SO I CAN DO THIS 10K RUN
THIS AFTERNOON, AND THEN-
YOU'RE DOING A 10K RUN
THIS AFTERNOON?
AS PART OF MY WORK-STUDY.
I HAVE TO MAKE A GOOD IMPRESSION
ON BEV GREYSON.
YEAH... NO. SHE TAKES ONE
LOOK AT YOU
AND SHE'S GONNA
SEND YOU HOME.
AS IF I'D PLAY
THE SICK CARD.
WHY NOT?
YOU'RE SICK!
GO HOME,
PUT ON SOME SWEAT PANTS-
SAV,
OKAY, WOMEN LIKE BEV GREYSON
DON'T GET SICK,
AND IF THEY DO,
THEY SUCK IT UP
AND THEY GET THE JOB DONE.
OH YEAH, EVEN IF IT
KILLS THEM, RIGHT?
(SIGHS)
I'M JUST WORRIED,
HOLLY J.
DON'T BE WORRIED.
GO FIND YOUR SISTER.
SHE NEEDS YOU.
(PAINED GRUNT,
SIGHS HEAVILY)
KAYLA:
WHAT EXACTLY DO YOU
WANT ME TO DO?
JUST SHOW HER
HOW GREAT UNIVERSITY IS
SO SHE DOESN'T THROW
HER FUTURE AWAY.
CAN'T YOU JUST CALL
HER BROTHER
TO TAKE HER KICKING
AND SCREAMING
BACK TO HER
NUTSO PARENTS?
NO.
NO, GOING HOME MUST BE
HER OWN DECISION.
AND YOU WANT HER
TO GO...?
OF COURSE.
BUT I CAN'T JUST
KICK HER OUT.
I MEAN,
SOME OF THE STUFF...
IT WOULDN'T HAVE HAPPENED
WITHOUT ME.
FINE.
BUT YOU SO OWE ME.
ALLI:
OKAY. YOUR WASHROOMS
ARE SO GROSS.
ANY LUCK WITH
MY NEW IDENTITY?
I DIDN'T KNOW
JOHNNY HAD GUESTS.
HI. ALLI.
KAYLA.
JOHNNY:
KAYLA'S INTO THEATRE;
SHE'S A MASTER OF DISGUISE.
PERFECT.
JOHNNY:
SHE'S ALSO IN NEURO-SCIENCE.
DOES SOME PRETTY COOL
EXPERIMENTS.
YOU'RE IN NEURO-SCIENCE?
I'M WORKING WITH A PROF
TO PROVE THAT RATS
CAN LEARN THINGS
WHILE UNDER ANESTHESIA.
LIKE MIND-CONTROL?!
KAYLA:
PRETTY MUCH.
COME ON, I'LL TELL YOU
MORE ABOUT IT
WHILE WE DISGUISE YOU.
♪ Give me the boogie love ♪
♪ The boogie love ♪
♪ Or give it back to you ♪
♪ Give me the boogie love ♪
DAVE:
NO, NO, NO.
DON'T TELL ME
THIS IS A WORLD RECORD?
YUP. MOST JUMPS ON A POGO STICK
IN TWENTY-FOUR HOURS!
WHAT, ARE YOU SERIOUS?!
WITH PRACTICE,
I CAN BEAT IT!
YEAH. HE'S ALREADY NEARING
RECORD PACE!
IT'S ALL ABOUT ACHIEVING
MY DREAMS!
YEAH, BUT YOU ALSO DREAMT
ABOUT HAVING A GIRLFRIEND.
WHEN THE GIRLS SEE THIS...
YEAH, DREAM? DEAD.
WHEN I SET THIS RECORD,
I'LL BE THE BEST
IN THE WORLD.
WHAT ARE YOU THE BEST
IN THE WORLD AT, DAVE?
PFFFTT! HMPH! PSHA!
YOU KNOW.
I HAVE TO PRACTICE.
SO IF YOU'RE NOT GONNA HELP,
SAYANORA!
♪ Give me the boogie love ♪
♪ The boogie love ♪
♪ Or give it back to you ♪
HOLLY J:
MS. GREYSON? BEV?
HI. LOOK, I'M REALLY SORRY,
BUT-
YOU'RE SORRY?
COME ON!
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SPEND A MINT
ON RUNNING GEAR.
NOT A FASHION SHOW,
RIGHT?
YEAH.
NO, I'M ACTUALLY-
CHANTAY!
HEY, BEV!
ALL SET FOR THE RUN!
I THOUGHT I'D TAKE SOME PHOTOS
FOR THE BLOG.
YOU TWO ARE SUCH
GO-GETTERS!
I'M GONNA NEED PEOPLE LIKE YOU
WITH BOUNDLESS ENERGY
WHEN I...
KEEP A SECRET?
I'M RUNNING FOR MAYOR
THIS SUMMER!
MAYOR? WOW.
THIS WORK-STUDY COULD
TURN INTO A SUMMER JOB
FOR BOTH OF YOU.
(EXHALES)
EVERYTHING OKAY?
IT'S A SORE THROAT.
IT'S NOTHING.
SHIRLEY KEEPS SOME LOZENGES
IN HER DESK.
ASK INSIDE.
GREAT!
I CAN'T WAIT TO DO
THIS RUN!
I HOPE YOU TWO
CAN KEEP UP.
A MINUTE AND...
A HUNDRED AND THREE!
(FRUSTRATED GRUNT)
IS SOMETHING WRONG
WITH MY FORM?
LOOKS NORMAL TO ME.
BUT I NEED TO DO
135 JUMPS A MINUTE
FOR TWENTY-FOUR HOURS!
I SWEAR I USED TO BE
BETTER AT THIS!
YOU'LL JUST HAVE
TO GET FASTER.
I DON'T THINK I CAN.
MY UNCLE ONLY SIGNED ME
OUT OF CLASS FOR TOMORROW!
I MEAN...
(PANTS)
SHOULD I PACK IT IN?
DAVE:
HEY DEGRASSI,
SPARE TIME TOMORROW?
COME SEE
WES "THE ANIMAL" BETENKAMP
SET A WORLD RECORD.
HE'LL POGO INTO
THE RECORD BOOKS
AND INTO YOUR HEARTS!
OH BOY.
ALLI:
CLOTHES, A WIG, A FAKE ID...
EVERYTHING WE NEEDED,
AND WE DIDN'T EVEN HAVE
TO LEAVE YOUR FLOOR.
JOHNNY:
ISN'T IT GREAT HERE?
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
NEXT STOP, THE BUS STATION,
AND A FRESH BEGINNING
FOR ALLI BHANDARI.
YOU DON'T WANT
TO LOOK AROUND CAMPUS
A BIT MORE?
WE GOT THE BEST LIBRARY
IN THE COUNTRY.
NOT GONNA WORK,
JOHNNY.
WHAT WON'T?
YOU TRYING TO KEEP ME HERE
UNTIL I GO HOME.
YOU'VE ONLY GOT TWO YEARS
UNTIL UNIVERSITY.
TWO MORE YEARS OF PARENTS,
AND THEN THOSE NEURO SCIENCE
EXPERIMENTS,
LIVING IN A DORM -
THAT COULD BE YOU!
HERE'S WHAT YOU DON'T GET:
THIS CAN NEVER BE MY REALITY.
MY PARENTS WOULD NEVER
LET ME LIVE IN A REZ.
IF I GO BACK HOME,
I'LL BE UNDER LOCK
AND KEY FOREVER.
RUNNING AWAY
IS MY ONLY ESCAPE.
ALLI, I'VE BEEN THERE.
I STOOD NEXT TO A DUDE
WHO STABBED A GUY
THAT EVERYONE LOVED,
AND THEN I HAD TO GO
TO THAT KID'S SCHOOL.
IT'S NOT THE SAME.
IT WAS HELL WITH MY PARENTS
AFTER THAT,
BUT WE WORKED THROUGH IT.
AND NOW I'M HERE
AND I'M DIFFERENT.
EVERYTHING'S GREAT.
MAYBE I'LL STAY
ONE MORE NIGHT.
THINK I CAN STILL GET THAT
CAMPUS TOUR?
HOLLY J:
(PANTING HARD)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
YOU LOOK GREEN.
SIT.
NO. NO.
I NEED TO FINISH.
I'LL FINISH
FOR BOTH OF US.
YOU'D LIKE THAT,
WOULDN'T YOU?
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED
TO MEAN?
YOU, YOU'RE ALL PERKY
WITH ALL YOUR ENERGY.
YOU'RE MAKING ME
LOOK BAD.
YOU'RE DOING THAT
TO YOURSELF.
YOUR BODY'S
TELLING YOU SOMETHING
AND YOU'RE NOT LISTENING.
OKAY, WHAT IS MY BODY
TRYING TO TELL ME,
IF YOU'RE SO SMART?
YOU AND SAV,
ARE YOU SEXUALLY ACTIVE?
SPARE ME, OKAY?
I'M NOT PREGNANT.
IS THERE ANY CHANCE?
NO!
NOT WITH SAV.
(COUGHING)
WELL, YOU'RE SOMETHING.
AND WHATEVER IT IS,
YOU'D BETTER START DEALING.
WE CAN TALK,
IF YOU WANT.
THANKS, MOM.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(VOMITS AND COUGHS)
(COUGHS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
ALLI:
THANKS FOR THE CAMPUS TOUR.
EVEN THE CAF FOOD
IS NOT THAT BAD.
THINK YOU'LL STICK
AROUND TOWN?
WHO KNOWS,
MAYBE I'LL ENROLL HERE.
GO TO T.U. WITH YOU!
STRAIGHT OUT OF GRADE TEN?
WHAT? DON'T THINK
I'M SMART ENOUGH?
NO, I DIDN'T SAY THAT.
KAYLA:
JOHN, BABE,
DID YOUR LITTLE PROBLEM
RUN ALONG...
HOME?
PROBLEM?
I MEAN...
AND SHE'S YOUR GIRLFRIEND,
I GUESS?
GREAT.
I CAME HERE 'CAUSE I THOUGHT
YOU WERE THE ONE PERSON
THAT ACTUALLY CARED ABOUT ME.
ALLI...
NO, FORGET IT.
YOU DON'T WANT ME HERE.
I'M GOING TO THE STATION!
(KAYLA SIGHS)
CHANTAY:
WHOO! WHAT A RUN!
ARE YOU FEELING
ANY BETTER?
I'M TIRED,
MY BRAIN DOESN'T WORK,
I HAVE NO ENERGY,
AND I'M SO THIRSTY.
WELL, YOU DID JUST RUN
A VERY SMALL PART OF A 10K.
THE GOOD NEWS?
I GOT MY PERIOD.
IT'S GOOD THAT
YOU'RE NOT PREGNANT,
BUT IT MUST BE
SOMETHING ELSE, RIGHT?
CHANTAY, THE LAST THING
I NEED RIGHT NOW
IS FOR IT TO BE SOMETHING.
WELL, MAYBE IT'LL ALL GO AWAY
WITH A GOOD NIGHT'S REST.
HOLLY J?
WHAT IF-
WHAT IF IT IS SOMETHING?
OH, HONEY... WOW.
(TEARFUL EXHALE)
I'M JUST...
I'M REALLY SCARED.