LOVE IS IN THE AIR,
DEGRASSI!
AND WHILE OUR HALLS
ARE STILL PDA-FREE,
YOU CAN SHOW YOUR SWEETHEART
YOU CARE
WITH A ROSE OR TWO,
OR THREE.
HI.
(SIGHS)
UH, A DOZEN YELLOW.
WHO'S THE LUCKY GUY?
MY MOM.
TODAY'S THE BIG DAY.
WE FIND OUT
IF HER RADIATION WORKED.
OOH!
BEST FRIEND SPECIAL.
IF YOU NEED ME...
I'LL CALL.
BUT, UM, I'M REALLY HOPING
THAT I DON'T.
YEAH.
WHAT ABOUT ANYA
FOR THE PLAY?
NO, TOO... CHEERFUL.
WE'VE AUDITIONED
10 GIRLS,
NOT ONE AS GOOD
AS MARISOL.
OFFER TO RESIGN REINSTATED.
AND AGAIN OVERRULED.
WE'LL FIND YOU
A PERFECT LEADING LADY.
THERE SHE IS.
HEY, ADAM.
ADIOS.
I'M STARTING TO GET THE FEELING
THAT YOU'RE IGNORING ME.
SORRY I COULDN'T MAKE IT
TO YOUR PARTY, ADAM.
I HAD TO WASH MY HAIR.
I WANTED TO COME.
SOMETHING BETTER CAME UP.
IT'S OKAY, I GET IT.
MY GREAT AUNT DIED.
I BARELY KNEW HER,
BUT...
MY MOM WAS BEYOND UPSET.
I, UH...
DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
SAY YOU'LL LET ME
MAKE IT UP TO YOU?
WELL, YOU PROBABLY WON'T
BE INTERESTED,
BUT...
WE NEED A NEW LEADING LADY
FOR THE PLAY,
AND...
YOU'D BE PERFECT.
THERE SINGING INVOLVED?
NO,
BUT THERE'S A KISS.
WITH ME.
OKAY,
BUT I GET FINAL WARDROBE
APPROVAL.
(LAUGHS)
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever! Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
LET'S GET THIS STRAIGHT.
I DON'T COOK
AND I DON'T CLEAN.
YOU WILL NOT FIND ME
HOLDING A BROOM
OR SCRUBBING
ON MY HANDS AND KNEES.
I EXPECT MEALS FOR ME
PREPARED THREE TIMES A DAY...
(MOCKINGLY)
YOU LIKE HER!
STOP IT!
YOU LOOOOVE HER!
DO NOT.
SHE LIKES YOU.
WHY ELSE WOULD SHE AGREE
TO DO OUR PLAY?
WELL...
MAYBE SHE DOESN'T KNOW
ABOUT ME.
YOU KNOW,
FIONA KEEPS TO HERSELF.
DOESN'T PAY ATTENTION
TO GOSSIP.
IF I COULD GET HER
TO KNOW THE REAL ME FIRST,
THEN MAYBE THE WHOLE
TRANSGENDER THING
WOULDN'T MATTER
DOWN THE LINE.
THAT'S A PRETTY BIG
"IF."
SO, DO I HAVE THE PART?
THE LEADING MAN APPROVES!
BUT YOU'LL HAVE TO WORK HARD
TO CATCH UP.
UH...YEAH.
I-I CAN HELP.
ARE YOU FREE TONIGHT?
WELL, I'D HAVE TO CANCEL
MY REIKI...
BUT YOSHI WILL DEAL.
MY CONDO AT SEVEN?
IT'S A DATE.
WELL, NOT A-
NOT A DATE.
(LAUGHS)
I'LL SEE YOU AT SEVEN, ADAM.
(FRUSTRATED SIGH)
HEY, YOU GUYS WANNA GET
A ROOM?
HELLO?
GREAT.
GREAT, GREAT, GREAT.
I'M GONNA BE LATE
FOR MATH AGAIN,
'CAUSE THESE TWO HAVE
TURNED MY LOCKER
INTO THEIR PERSONAL
LOVE NEST!
(MOCKING) "LOOK AT ME,
I'M SO IN LOVE."
"AND THE ONLY WAY
TO SHOW IT IS TO SWAP SALIVA
IN FRONT OF EVERYBODY!"
SWEETHEART WEEK BLOWS!
JUST ANOTHER ACTIVITY
TO HIGHLIGHT THE GAP
BETWEEN THE HAVES
AND THE HAVE NOTS.
BUT, YOU KNOW,
I-I COULD BUY YOU A ROSE.
AND THEN I COULD CALL YOU
MY BOYFRIEND!
THEN WE'D BE LOCKING LIPS.
THAT SOUNDS TERRIBLE.
(LAUGHS)
YEAH, TOTALLY.
OH, I'M-I'M DAVE.
SADIE.
OH. UM, UH...
BUT, YOU KNOW,
US SWEETHEART WEEK HATERS
GOTTA-GOTTA STICK TOGETHER.
YEAH, THERE'S STRENGTH
IN NUMBERS.
RIGHT, RIGHT, RIGHT.
SO, UH,
WELL, WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE MEET UP SOMETIME?
SAY, THE DOT?
TOMORROW?
YEAH, I'D LIKE THAT.
(LAUGHS)
OKAY, COOL.
WHOA!
DR. CHRIS:
SO, HERE ARE THE RESULTS
OF YOUR MOST RECENT M.R.I.
ANYA:
I-I DON'T SEE ANYTHING.
DOES THAT MEAN...
IT MEANS THE CANCER'S GONE!
EVERY SINGLE CELL OF IT.
OH MY GOD!
AHH!
YOU SEE?
ANYA:
I TOLD YOU THERE'S NOTHING
TO BE WORRIED ABOUT!
(BOTH LAUGH EXCITEDLY)
DR. CHRIS:
IF YOU'RE LUCKY,
YOU'LL NEVER SEE US AGAIN.
OH! SO... UH, NEVER?
SO THIS IS,
THIS IS GOODBYE, THEN?
I'M AFRAID SO.
WE REALLY OWE YOU ONE,
DR. CHRIS.
YOU AND YOUR TEAM
HAVE BEEN WONDERFUL!
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
YEAH. UH, YEAH,
THANKS FOR EVERYTHING!
(DR. CHRIS AND ANYA LAUGH)
ALL RIGHT.
COME ON,
LET'S GO CALL DAD
WITH THE GOOD NEWS!
YEAH!
PAM: BYE!
DR. CHRIS: BYE.
ANYA:
AHEM!
(LAUGHS AWKWARDLY)
COME ON, THERE'LL BE
OTHER CUTE DOCTORS
IN YOUR FUTURE.
I HOPE SO.
(PAM LAUGHS)
(BELL RINGS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
CINNAMON HEART?
I DON'T DESERVE IT.
MY MOM'S CANCER FREE,
AND ALL I CAN THINK ABOUT
IS NO MORE VISITS
TO THE HOSPITAL.
THERE'S THIS BOY
THAT WORKS THERE.
A VOLUNTEER?
UH, MORE LIKE
A TRAINING PROGRAM.
MED SCHOOL?
WHAT COMES AFTER THAT?
ANYA, HE'S A DOCTOR?
YOU CAN'T DATE A DOCTOR!
HE'S ONLY A FIRST YEAR
RESIDENT.
I KNOW, I KNOW!
I JUST CAN'T STOP
THINKING ABOUT HIM.
WELL, FOCUS ON
HIS ANNOYING HABITS.
LIKE THE CUTE WAY
HE BITES HIS PEN?
YOU HAVE HIM
ON A PEDESTAL.
IF YOU SPENT TIME
WITH HIM,
YOU'D REALIZE
HE'S JUST A REGULAR JOE.
WHO LEAVES HIS SEAT UP
AND SPENDS HOURS
ON PLAYSTATION.
EXACTLY.
SO WHAT YOU'RE SAYING IS...
I NEED TO SPEND MORE TIME
WITH HIM.
ANYA.
COME ON, I'VE HAD
A PRETTY SUCKY YEAR.
DON'T I DESERVE
ONE PERFECT DATE?
OKAY, SO HOW ARE YOU
GOING TO GET IT?
WELL,
ME AND MY BEST FRIEND,
WHO HAPPENS TO BE
DATING MY EX,
WILL BUMP INTO HIM.
HE'LL BE AT PIZZA LESLIE,
AT SEVEN.
(SIGHS)
OKAY.
(CAR RUMBLES)
(DOOR SLAMS)
ADAM:
WHOA, THIS PLACE IS AMAZING!
FIONA:
THANKS!
(BOTTLES CLINK)
FIONA:
YOU DON'T MIND
IF I HAVE A LITTLE CHAMPAGNE
TO GET INTO CHARACTER?
UH...NO,
OF COURSE NOT.
GO AHEAD.
(CORK POPS)
SOME PEOPLE CAN BE
SO WEIRD ABOUT IT.
UH, NOT ME.
(SIGHS)
SO...
WHERE DO WE BEGIN?
UM...
THE FIRST TIME
THE INVENTOR
BRINGS THE WOMAN TO LIFE?
YOU MEAN,
WHERE HE KISSES HER?
OR WE COULD START
SOMEWHERE ELSE.
UM, THERE'S THIS SCENE
AT THE PARK.
IT'S PROBABLY JUST...
BETTER TO GET THE KISS
OUT OF THE WAY.
OKAY, UH, IF THAT'S
WHAT YOU THINK.
SO, I'M FLICKING
THE SWITCH.
NOTHING HAPPENS.
SO I APPROACH.
LOOK, BEFORE...
WE DO THIS,
THERE'S SOMETHING
YOU SHOULD KNOW.
I'M TRANSGENDER.
OKAY.
OKAY?
YOU KNEW?
I'M FROM NEW YORK.
MY MOM'S STYLIST WILMA
USED TO BE WILLIAM.
(RELIEVED SIGH)
YOU THOUGHT
I'D FREAK OUT?
IT'S A PRE-ESTABLISHED
PATTERN.
GIRLS AREN'T EXACTLY
LINING UP TO KISS ME.
WELL, I'D RATHER KISS YOU
THAN ANY OTHER GUY AT SCHOOL.
WAIT, WHAT?
OOPS!
OH!
OH, MY BROTHER KEEPS
A SPARE CHANGE OF CLOTHES.
I'LL GO GET THEM.
(SIGHS)
(HORN HONKS)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYS)
DR. CHRIS:
HI. UH, I HAVE A RESERVATION
FOR TWO FOR...
ANYA:
OKAY, UM, THERE HE IS
AT THE HOSTESS STAND.
DOESN'T HE LOOK SO...
OLD.
AND, AND CUTE.
ARE YOU GONNA GO
TALK TO HIM?
NO, I'D LOOK
TOO DESPERATE.
SO...
YOU'RE GONNA FAKE CHOKING.
WHAT?
I FAKED A PREGNANCY
FOR YOU.
FINE.
PASS ME THOSE OLIVES.
(HOLLY J SIGHS)
(MAKES CHOKING SOUNDS)
ANYA:
OH HELP,
WE NEED A DOCTOR!
SIT!
DR. CHRIS:
ANYA, WHAT'S WRONG?
UH, MY FRIEND,
SHE'S CHOKING!
DR. CHRIS:
OKAY, DO YOU NEED HELP?
OKAY, THIS MIGHT HURT
A LITTLE.
OH!
DR. CHRIS:
CAN I GET YOU SOME WATER?
HOLLY J:
THANKS, I'M-I'M FINE.
DR. CHRIS:
YOU'VE GOTTA WATCH IT
WITH THE OLIVES.
UH, MAJOR CHOKING HAZARD.
AND THAT'S WHAT
I'M ALWAYS TELLING HER!
UM, SO CAN WE BUY YOU
A THANK YOU DESSERT?
I'D LOVE TO,
UH, BUT, UH,
I'M ACTUALLY MEETING SOMEONE.
IT WAS GREAT SEEING YOU, ANYA.
(SIGHS)
HEY!
HOLLY J:
MAYBE SHE'S HIS SISTER.
ANYA:
YEAH, MAYBE THEIR...
FAMILY'S REALLY CLOSE.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
FIONA:
ADAM,
WHAT'S TAKING SO LONG?
(FIONA SIGHS)
LET ME DO IT.
MOLTO BELLO.
(LAUGHS)
TRUTH OR DARE.
TRUTH.
WHY DID YOU SKIP
MY PARTY?
I TOLD YOU,
MY GREAT AUNT...
IS PROBABLY ALIVE
AND WELL.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(TAKES A DEEP BREATH)
YOU LOOK AT ME
LIKE I'M THIS PERFECT PRINCESS,
BUT I'M NOT.
AND ONCE YOU REALIZE THAT,
YOU'LL GET SICK OF ME;
EVERYONE DOES.
THAT'S NEVER GONNA HAPPEN.
COME ON, LET'S GET
ANOTHER DRINK.
YOUR TURN.
DARE.
♪♪♪
(BUS RUMBLES)
(BIRDS CHIRP)
THAT WOMAN DID NOT
SEEM LIKE HIS TYPE!
WHAT'S THAT,
5"5', BROWNISH HAIR,
WAY TOO YOUNG FOR HIM?
I KNOW YOU THINK
I'M CRAZY,
BUT EVERY TIME
I'M AROUND HIM,
I WANNA...PUKE -
IN THE GOOD WAY.
YOU NEED TO FORGET
ABOUT HIM.
(SIGHS) NO!
I-I WENT OUT LAST NIGHT
TO GET A DATE
AND I NEVER EVEN TRIED.
SO... HERE GOES.
(PHONE BEEPS)
(TAPS NERVOUSLY)
AGH!
OH GOD,
OKAY, I CAN'T.
(BOTH LAUGH)
(PHONE RINGS)
ANYA:
IT'S HIM!
IF-IF I LET IT GO THROUGH,
IT'LL GO TO VOICE MAIL
AND HE'LL KNOW I CALLED!
THEN ANSWER IT.
DR. CHRIS!
HI! UM...
I WAS JUST CALLING
TO SAY THANKS
FOR HELPING OUT
MY FRIEND YESTERDAY.
AM I FREE FOR DINNER?
UM, WHAT ABOUT...?
OH!
SHE'S JUST A FRIEND.
OKAY, WELL,
MY, UM, MY COLLEGE SEMINAR
AT... COLLEGE
IS OVER AT FIVE.
UM, MAYBE WE CAN
MEET UP AFTERWARDS?
I-I KNOW THIS GREAT
LITTLE SPOT
CALLED LITTLE MISS STEAKS.
OKAY!
SEE YOU THEN!
(HOLLY J LAUGHS)
WHAT WOULD A COLLEGE STUDENT
WEAR ON HER FIRST DATE?
(LAUGHS EXCITEDLY)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
GIRL:
THAT'S GOOD!
HEY, DID YOU GET THE FLOWERS?
WHITE'S YOUR FAVOURITE,
RIGHT?
(SIGHS)
ABOUT LAST NIGHT...
WE WERE...
JUST...
JUST HAVING FUN.
WE GOT CAUGHT UP
IN THE MOMENT.
IT'S BEST TO PRETEND
IT NEVER HAPPENED.
PRETEND WHAT NEVER HAPPENED?
I KNEW YOU'D UNDERSTAND.
ELI:
OKAY! (CLAPS HANDS)
WE'RE READY TO GET STARTED.
FIONA, TAKE YOUR MARK.
I GUESS THAT'S MY CUE.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
ELI:
HERE.
WESLEY:
SO, WHAT'S THE BIG SURPRISE?
DAVE:
ALL RIGHT, LOOK,
GUESS WHO'S GOT A DATE...
WITH HER?
UH...
ME, YOU MORONS!
I HAVE A DATE WITH HER.
WOW, DAVE.
THAT'S GREAT!
WESLEY:
YEAH, SHE IS FINE!
DAVE:
(LAUGHS) YEAH.
SHE'S ALSO SMART AND FUNNY.
CONNOR:
AND WAY TALLER THAN YOU.
(LAUGHS)
ONLY BY AN INCH
OR TWO.
OKAY, LOOK.
NO ONE'S GONNA NOTICE.
YEAH, IT DOESN'T SOUND
LIKE A STRETCH.
(WESLEY AND CONNOR LAUGH)
ADAM:
LAST NIGHT,
FIONA WAS INTO ME.
LIKE, REALLY INTO ME.
AND NOW SHE CLAIMS
IT WAS SOME BIG MISTAKE.
GIVE ME
THE PLAY-BY-PLAY.
OKAY, WELL,
I TOLD HER ABOUT ME;
SHE ALREADY KNEW.
AND THEN JUST BEFORE
SHE SPILLED HER CHAMPAGNE...
WAIT, WAIT.
SHE WAS DRINKING?
MAYBE A LITTLE.
WHY?
IN VINUM VERITAS.
I DON'T SPEAK GREEK.
LATIN.
WHATEVER.
DOES IT MEAN GIRLS
LIKE FIONA
DON'T FALL FOR GUYS
LIKE ME?
QUITE THE OPPOSITE.
IN WINE,
THERE IS TRUTH.
WHEN PEOPLE DRINK,
THEY SAY OR DO STUFF
THAT THEY'RE TOO SCARED TO
WHEN THEY'RE SOBER.
MAYBE SHE DOES LIKE ME.
(CARS RUMBLE PAST)
ANYA:
SO, UH, DO YOU USUALLY DATE
YOUR PATIENTS' DAUGHTERS?
DR. CHRIS:
THAT'S WHY I GOT INTO MEDICINE.
THE DATING PROSPECTS?
I WAS A GEEK
IN HIGH SCHOOL.
GOT GREAT GRADES,
BUT COULDN'T GET A GIRL
TO SAVE MY LIFE.
(ANYA LAUGHS)
THOSE DOCTORS ON TV
THOUGH,
THEY GOT PLAY.
SO SAVING LIVES...?
MINOR PERK.
YOU KNOW, I'VE WANTED
TO ASK YOU OUT FOR AGES.
I JUST ASSUMED THAT
A COLLEGE GIRL LIKE YOU
WOULDN'T BE INTERESTED
IN AN OLD GUY LIKE ME.
SO, HOW OLD ARE YOU
EXACTLY?
TWENTY-FIVE.
TWENTY-FIVE?
YOU THINK I'M ANCIENT.
NO!
HOW OLD ARE YOU?
UH, TWENTY?
AND A HALF.
(BOTH LAUGH AWKWARDLY)
(SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
(DISHES CLINK)
DAVE:
HEY!
SORRY I'M LATE.
NO NEED TO APOLOGIZE -
FOR ANYTHING
EXCEPT BEING A LAKERS FAN.
WHY,
WHAT'S YOUR TEAM?
NO, WAIT, LET ME GUESS.
MIAMI HEAT.
HOW DID YOU KNOW?
'CAUSE ALL THE GIRLS
LIKE LEBRON.
HE'S ONE OF THE LEAGUE'S
TOP SCORERS.
YEAH? YOU GOT THE STATS
TO BACK THAT UP?
(BOTH LAUGH)
WOW, I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE A BASKETBALL FAN.
FOUR BROTHERS -
DIDN'T HAVE A CHOICE.
WOW. OKAY, WELL,
YOU WANNA GO GET SOME GRUB?
YEAH.
HEY, UH...
UH, YOU SHOULD SIT DOWN.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
YEAH, YEAH.
UM...
WHY DON'T YOU SAVE
OUR SEATS AND, UH,
I'LL-I'LL GO GET THE FOOD.
SADIE: OKAY.
DAVE: COOL.
♪♪♪
(LATCH CLICKS)
YOUR BROTHER'S CLOTHES.
I HAD THEM CLEANED.
YOU COULDN'T WAIT
'TIL REHEARSAL TO SEE ME?
ACTUALLY, I'M UH...
DROPPING OUT OF THE PLAY.
BUT YOU BEGGED ME
TO SIGN UP!
'CAUSE I THOUGHT I HAD
A CHANCE WITH YOU.
BUT NOW THAT I KNOW
IT WAS ALL IN MY HEAD,
IT KINDA BLOWS.
(SIGHS)
WHAT IF IT WASN'T?
THEN YOU'D INVITE ME IN.
WE'D TALK.
WELL, I DID ORDER
ENOUGH DINNER FOR TWO.
DO YOU LIKE FOIE GRAS?
I DO NOW.
(DOOR SLAMS)
(SIGHS)
DR. CHRIS:
SO, HOBBIES.
I LARP.
LIKE ROLE-PLAY.
ARE YOU GONNA ASK
FOR THE BILL?
YOU MIGHT,
WHEN I TELL YOU
I PLAYED DUNGEONS AND DRAGONS.
I BARELY CAME OUT
OF MY BASEMENT IN SENIOR YEAR.
WELL, YOU'VE ADJUSTED
TO THE LIGHT QUITE NICELY.
(BOTH LAUGH)
UH, DO YOU HAVE TIME
FOR DESSERT?
SHE DOESN'T.
I DON'T?
OH! UH, I DON'T.
SHE'S RIGHT, CURFEW.
CURFEW...?
HOLLY J:
IT'S SELF-IMPOSED.
ANYA'S A VERY CONSCIENTIOUS
STUDENT.
GUILTY AS CHARGED!
AS LONG AS YOU'RE NOT
BLOWING ME OFF.
NO, NOT IN
A MILLION YEARS.
(BOTH LAUGH)
WELL,
I'LL DRIVE YOU HOME.
YOUR DORM MUST BE
CLOSE BY.
HOLLY J:
YOU NEED TO PAY
AT THE COUNTER.
(LAUGHS)
WHERE'S MY DORM?
(SIGHS)
FIONA:
YOU'VE GOT TO TRY THIS CHEESE.
I HAD IT SHIPPED
FROM NEW YORK.
GREAT.
I LOVE CHEESE.
(CHAMPAGNE POURS)
(SIGHS)
WHOA, SOMEONE'S THIRSTY.
IT HELPS ME RELAX.
YOU DON'T HAVE A PROBLEM
WITH ME DRINKING, DO YOU?
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
IN FRANCE, EVERYONE HAS
AN APERITIF BEFORE DINNER,
IT'S LIKE THE LAW.
(GIGGLES)
WELL...
MAYBE YOU SHOULD HAVE TWO.
♪♪♪
YOU SURE I CAN'T DRIVE YOU
TO YOUR DORM?
HOLLY J'S HEADED
THAT WAY, ANYWAY.
(GIGGLES FLIRTATIOUSLY)
I HAD A REALLY NICE TIME
TONIGHT.
YEAH, ME TOO.
I WAS AFRAID THAT ONCE
MY MOM GOT BETTER,
THAT I WOULDN'T GET
TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
WELL, I'M SURE WE COULD
COME UP WITH AN EXCUSE
TO GET YOU
INTO THE HOSPITAL.
(LAUGHS)
ANYA:
ACTUALLY,
THERE'S THIS UM...
MOLE THAT I WANTED YOU
TO EXAMINE,
IT'S RIGHT HERE.
I DON'T FEEL
ANYTHING UNUSUAL.
MM.
(LAUGHS)
ARE YOU TRYING TO SEDUCE ME,
MISS MACPHERSON?
ANYA:
IS IT WORKING?
DR. CHRIS:
I'LL CALL YOU TOMORROW?
ANYA:
YOU BETTER!
(SQUEALS EXCITEDLY)
HAH!
(KEYS RATTLE)
FIONA?
I FORGOT MY HISTORY BOOK.
(ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYS SOFTLY)
HOLLY J:
WHOA!
OKAY.
UH...
LOOKS LIKE YOU TWO
HAD QUITE A NIGHT.
ADAM AND I WERE
JUST REHEARSING.
FIONA, YOU'RE DRUNK.
NO, I JUST HAD
A GLASS OR TWO,
RIGHT, ADAM?
RIGHT.
THAT'S VERY CONVINCING.
PARTY'S OVER.
COME ON, FI,
I'LL TUCK YOU IN.
NO, I DON'T WANT TO.
FIONA!
YOU'RE NOT MY MOM!
YOU CAN'T TELL ME
WHAT TO DO.
SHE'S-SHE'S REALLY
NOT THAT DRUNK.
JUST KEEP AN EYE
ON HER, OKAY?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
IF YOU NEED ANYTHING,
MY NUMBER'S IN HER PHONE.
AND SOMETIMES
SHE DOESN'T NOTICE
IF YOU SUBSTITUTE SELTZER
FOR CHAMPAGNE.
(CORK POPS)
(HOLLY J SIGHS ANGRILY)
(CHAMPAGNE POURS)
HOLLY J IS SO UPTIGHT.
(DOOR SLAMS)
EVERYTHING OKAY?
YEAH,
NOW THAT HOLLY J IS GONE.