HOLLY J:
GOOD MORNING, DEGRASSI.
♪♪♪
I'D LIKE TO BEGIN TODAY
WITH A STORY.
ONCE UPON A TIME,
IN A LAND NOT SO FAR AWAY,
THERE WAS A COMMUNITY SCHOOL
CALLED DEGRASSI.
AND AT THIS HIGH SCHOOL,
THERE WERE STUDENTS
WHO KNEW THAT THEY HAD TO MAKE
A DIFFERENCE.
SEE, THESE STUDENTS...
(MELODRAMATICALLY)
YES...
AND ALSO AT THIS
HIGH SCHOOL,
THERE LIVED AN EVIL
PRINCIPAL SIMPSON,
WHO PLAGUED THE SCHOOL
WITH A HORRIBLE CRACKDOWN!
(LAUGHS)
HENCE THE "WISH ON A STAR"
FUNDRAISER?
SAV:
YEAH, YEAH.
IT'S CHANTAY'S EFFORT
TO BREAK THE CURSE.
FIRST SIGN OF LIFE
AROUND HERE IN A WHILE!
I LIKE IT!
WANNA SEND A FRIEND
A POWER SQUAD WISHING STAR?
I'LL JUST MAKE A DONATION.
SAVE THE STAR
FOR SOMEONE ELSE.
HOLLY J:
AND NOW, FOR A SPECIAL
ANNOUNCEMENT.
COME ONE, COME ALL,
TO THE ENCHANTED BALL!
YOUR VERY OWN MAGICAL DANCE
BROUGHT TO YOU
BY THE POWER SQUAD.
(STUDENTS CHEER)
ONE HOUR AFTER SCHOOL,
(SIGHS) THREE TO FOUR,
HEAVILY CHAPERONED,
AND DRESS CODE IN EFFECT.
STUDENTS: AW!
JENNA: WOW!
ORGANIZED, CHAPERONED FUN?
SOUNDS LIKE
AN ENCHANTED BLAST.
HEY, IT WAS THE BEST
I COULD DO!
YEAH, OKAY,
DON'T KNOCK IT.
AND PLUS,
SIMPSON SAYS THAT
DEGRASSI MUSICIANS CAN PLAY.
REALLY?
SAV: YEAH.
DO YOU WANNA LIKE
DO A DUET?
YEAH!
SOUNDS GREAT!
IT'S BETTER
I'LL BE ON STAGE.
NO ONE WOULD HAVE ASKED ME
TO THE DANCE, ANYWAY.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever! Woo-hoo!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
BUY A WISHING STAR
FOR CHARITY?
BUY A WISHING STAR?
JENNA:
I USED TO DATE THE HOTTEST GUY
IN HIGH SCHOOL.
I SANG ON NATIONAL
TELEVISION.
NOW, I'M SUFFERING
FROM PRENATAL VITAMIN
INTESTINAL CRAMPS!
THAT BAD, HUH?
THE CRAMPS,
I CAN DEAL WITH.
THE SUDDEN FALL
FROM GRACE?
NOT SO MUCH.
MY BROTHER CAN'T MAKE IT
TO MY PRENATAL CLASS.
CRAPPY.
I GUESS I'LL HAVE TO FEND OFF
JUDGY MOMS ALONE.
WHAT ABOUT KC?
WELL, YOU'D THINK,
BEING THE FATHER
AND ALL.
SAV:
YOU KNOW,
HE'S PROBABLY TERRIFIED.
AND I'M NOT?
JUST GIVE KC A CHANCE.
I'M SURE HE'S GONNA
MAKE A GREAT DAD.
DREW:
OKAY! GO, KC!
OKAY. EIGHT...
(CLAPS) NINE...
TEN!
(BAT CLATTERS,
BANGS INTO LOCKERS)
(STUDENTS LAUGH AND HOLLER)
GIRL: WHOA!
BLUE 42!
(STUDENTS LAUGH AND HOLLER)
JESS:
OW! AH!
WHOA! (LAUGHS)
JESS:
OW!
(CRYING)
YOU OKAY?
UH, YEAH,
JUST MY SPINE!
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
JESS.
JESS,
I-I APOLOGIZE,
WE WERE ACTING
LIKE IDIOTS.
IDIOTS.
IS THERE ANY CHANCE
YOU WON'T SUE US OVER THIS?
(HALF LAUGHS)
I DON'T KNOW.
I'LL HAVE TO CHECK WITH
MY PERSONAL INJURY LAWYER.
(LAUGHS)
(SIGHS)
SHE'S CUTE.
REALLY CUTE.
YEAH,
I RAN UP TO HER FIRST.
I HIT HER WITH THE BALL.
KNOW WHAT?
TELL YOU WHAT.
FIRT ONE TO GET
ONE OF THOSE STARS FROM HER,
GETS TO ASK HER OUT.
AH, IT'S ON.
SO, UH, DOES THIS MEAN
YOU'RE OVER JENNA?
(SCOFFS)
OF COURSE I'M OVER JENNA.
(DISBELIEVING SIGH)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
ADAM: (IN A DEEP VOICE)
SUSPENDED FOR P.D.A!
KIDDING!
HOLDING HANDS SHOULD BE ALLOWED.
IT IS WISHING STAR WEEK,
OR WHATEVER.
AND WHICH ENCHANTED PRINCESS
DO YOU HAVE YOUR EYE ON?
THE FAIREST OF THEM ALL.
FIONA COYNE.
SO, WHAT'S THE LATEST?
DOES SHE KNOW ABOUT
YOUR SITUATION?
I HAVEN'T TAKEN MY TRANSGENDER
AWARENESS SURVEY LATELY.
WAIT, YOU GUYS DON'T THINK
SHE'S OUT OF MY LEAGUE?
MISSING SOME PARTS
NEVER STOPPED YOU BEFORE.
CHANTAY: (OVER P.A.)
HELP MAKE DREAMS COME TRUE.
DON'T FORGET TO PURCHASE
A WISHING STAR
FOR SOMEONE SPECIAL.
WESLEY, DID...
DID YOU DO THIS?
WELL, YEAH,
THEY'RE WISHING STARS.
MAKE A WISH!
UM, I WISH MY HISTORY TEST
WAS CANCELLED
AND THAT MY NEW DRESS CODE PANTS
DIDN'T CHAFE.
(LAUGHS)
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
WHAT'S UP?
UM... DO YOU WANT TO GO
ON OUR DATE?
THAT'S RIGHT,
I WON YOU FAIR AND SQUARE
AT THE BACHELOR AUCTION,
DIDN'T I?
SO, WHAT'S THE PLAN?
COFFEE?
UH, WELL, I'VE BEEN
SAVING MY ALLOWANCE
AND WAS THINKING OF SOMETHING
A LITTLE MORE SPECIAL.
IT'S A SURPRISE,
ISN'T IT?
YEAH.
OH, BOY!
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
(LAUGHS)
(LOCKER DOOR CLICKS OPEN)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
HEY, JENNA.
HEY.
(MUSIC PLAYS FAINTLY)
OH, HEY...THERE, YOU.
HOW'S EVERYTHING?
GOOD.
THINGS ARE GOOD.
UH... HOW ABOUT YOU?
GOOD.
(SIGHS)
ARE YOU FEELING OKAY?
OH, UH...
YEAH.
GOOD.
(UNSURE)
UH...
(BELL RINGS)
CHANTAY:
WE ARE THE DEGRASSI
POWER SQUAD FAIRIES,
HERE TO MAKE YOUR WISHES
COME TRUE!
JENNA.
JENNA:
UH... WHO'S THIS FROM?
CHANTAY:
I JUST DELIVER THEM!
♪♪♪
THANK YOU!
SIGH.
NOT FEELING IT?
I WAS ACTUALLY LOOKING FORWARD
TO THIS DANCE,
BUT WHAT'S THE POINT
IF I CAN'T PURCHASE A NEW DRESS?
LIFE IS DIFFICULT.
IS THERE ANYTHING LEFT
TO LIVE FOR?
(LAUGHS)
IF I WERE IN NEW YORK
RIGHT NOW,
I'D BE SHOPPING FOR
THE EAST VILLAGE ARTIST'S BALL.
IT'S THE NIGHT
OF THE YEAR.
CRAZY INVITES,
STUNNING COUTURE,
AND THE BEST PART?
CHAMPAGNE FOUNTAINS
EVERYWHERE!
IT SOUNDS AWESOME.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
MS. DAWES:
OKAY, YOUR SKETCH.
REMEMBER,
IT CAN BE SIMPLE,
BUT TRY TO MAKE IT MEANINGFUL.
YOU WANNA...
YOU WANNA FEEL SOMETHING!
ANDIAMO!
SKETCH!
(LAUGHS)
KC:
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
(ALL LAUGH)
DREW:
WHY WOULD WE EVEN COME
THAT CLOSE WITH (UNCLEAR)?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
JENNA:
HEY. UM...
DO YOU MIND IF I SIT?
OF COURSE NOT.
(JENNA CLEARS THROAT)
THANKS FOR THE STAR.
IT MEANT A LOT.
OH.
I'M GLAD.
I UH...
I HAVE MY FIRST
PRENATAL CLASS TODAY.
DO YOU WANNA COME?
SURE.
JENNA:
REALLY?
OH, GOOD,
'CAUSE I WAS A LITTLE SCARED
TO ASK YOU.
I MEAN, EVER SINCE,
YOU KNOW,
YOU SAID YOU DIDN'T WANT
TO BE INVOLVED,
I JUST THOUGHT...
OH, WHATEVER.
I'M JUST... REALLY GLAD
YOU'RE COMING.
KC:
YEAH, ME TOO.
YEAH.
I'LL BE IN THE MUSIC ROOM
AFTER SCHOOL.
KC: COOL.
JENNA: OKAY, GOODBYE.
SEE YA.
BYE.
(LAUGHS)
MM!
YOU DIDN'T SEND HER THAT STAR,
DID YOU?
(LAUGHS)
BUT IF I DIDN'T,
WHO DID?
("Still Believe In Love"
by Jack Soul)
♪♪♪
♪ She left with all
of her clothing on ♪
♪ She walked
with all my cds ♪
♪ She was too small
to take the big screen ♪
♪ So she took all my dvds ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, oh ♪
♪ I swear the woman
went crazy... ♪
(NEEDLE SCRATCHES ON RECORD,
STUDENTS COUGH AND WHISPER)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(KEYS CLICK)
(GASPS NERVOUSLY)
MS. OH, MAY I GO
TO THE BATHROOM, PLEASE?
SURE.
MAKE IT QUICK.
(STUDENTS MURMUR)
DON'T FORGET THE HALL PASS.
(SAV STRUMS GUITAR)
KC WAS SUPPOSED TO BE HERE
20 MINUTES AGO.
YEAH, I'M SURE
HE JUST LOST TRACK OF TIME.
JENNA:
NO, I KNOW KC.
IF HE'S AVOIDING SOMETHING,
IT'S 'CAUSE HE WANTS TO.
WHY WOULD HE SEND ME
A WISHING STAR,
IF HE WAS JUST
GONNA DITCH ME?
I MAY HAVE SENT YOU THAT.
WHAT?
YEAH, YOU WERE SAD
AND I FELT BAD,
SO I WANTED
TO CHEER YOU UP.
WHA-WHA?
OH! HOW COULD I BE
SO STUPID?
YOU'RE NOT STUPID.
YOU'RE RIGHT,
I'M JUST A BIG, FAT,
PITY CASE.
YOU KNOW, I KEEP ON
HOLDING THIS IDEA
THAT KC'S GONNA COME AROUND,
BUT FACE IT, JENNA!
YOU'RE GOING THROUGH
THIS ALONE!
WHOA, WHOA!
NO, YOU'RE NOT!
I'M GONNA BE LATE.
UH, WELL, WAIT.
I'M GONNA COME
WITH YOU THEN, RIGHT?
YOU COULD, YOU COULD USE
A FRIEND THERE.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO DO THAT.
I CAN'T LET
YOU FIGHT OFF
ALL THOSE KNOW-IT-ALL MOMS
BY YOURSELF.
HAI-YAAH!
(SIGHS)
BLAIR BONGARD:
GREAT FIRST CLASS, EVERYONE.
WHAT AN ADVENTURE!
NOW, IN THE COMING WEEKS,
WE'LL CONTINUE TO WORK TOGETHER
TO MAKE SURE THAT YOU STRIVE
IN THE JOURNEY
THAT IS PARENTHOOD.
SINCE WE'RE ALMOST
OUT OF TIME,
I'M GOING TO QUICKLY
OPEN UP THE FLOOR
AND ASK WHAT ARE
YOUR DEEPEST FEARS?
MM-HMM?
NOT BEING A GOOD MOTHER.
OKAY.
QUESTION?
BLAIR BONGARD: MM-HMM?
SAV:
SO, AFTER BIRTH,
DOES STUFF GO BACK
TO NORMAL?
LOSS OF SEX DRIVE.
(INDIGNANT)
SAV!
N-NO, UH...
I MEANT LIKE IN LIFE.
BLAIR BONGARD:
OH, VERY COMMON QUESTION.
IT TAKES SOME TIME, BUT...YES.
(LAUGHS)
FIRST TIME DADDY?
OH, NO,
HE'S NOT THE FATHER.
JUST A FRIEND.
WE LOVE FRIENDS HERE,
OKAY?
OTHER FEARS?
JENNA:
UM...
DOING THIS ALONE.
BLAIR BONGARD:
THESE ARE VERY COMMON FEARS.
BUT LET ME TELL YOU:
WE'RE NOT GONNA
LET THEM HAPPEN, OKAY?
LET THAT HAPPEN!
WE'RE NOT GONNA
OKAY? (LAUGHS)
LET'S GIVE THE PREGNANT MOMS
A BREAK.
PARTNERS?
IT'S BATH TIME!
I GUESS THAT'S ME.
(LAUGHS)
WOMAN:
BYE! HAVE FUN!
HEY, CUTE TOP!
OH, THANKS.
YUYU-LIME, ON SALE.
THAT'S ROMAN.
NOT THE FATHER,
BUT STILL GOING TO BE
AN AWESOME DAD.
YOU KNOW, I WAS ALWAYS WORRIED
PEOPLE WOULD JUDGE ME,
BUT SOMETIMES THE RIGHT GUY
IS THE ONE YOU LEAST SUSPECT.
EVEN IF HE'S NOT
THE BIOLOGICAL DAD?
THAT'S JUST HOW IT WORKS OUT
SOMETIMES.
YOU CAN'T FIGHT FATE.
YEAH.
THAT'S WHAT I ALWAYS SAY.
(LAUGHS)
(BELL RINGS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
(LAUGHS)
WHO'S IT FROM?
STARTS WITH A "J,"
AND ENDS WITH AN "ESS"!
NADA? OH,
WHAT'S THE FUN IN PLAYING,
WHEN YOUR OPPONENT
DOESN'T EVEN CARE?
I CAN'T STOP THINKING
ABOUT JENNA.
OH MAN, I KNEW IT.
SO, UH, DID YOU GO
TO BABY CLASS YESTERDAY?
NO, I BAILED.
OH, I'M SUCH AN ASS!
YOU STILL LIKE HER.
YEAH.
SHE'S STILL JENNA
AND I LIKE HER A LOT.
HAVE YOU TOLD HER THAT?
AGREEING TO BE WITH JENNA
MEANS AGREEING TO BE A DAD.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
WELL, MY ONLY SOLUTION
INVOLVES A TIME MACHINE...
AND A BIG BOX OF CONDOMS.
(LAUGHS)
I'M SORRY,
I CAN'T HELP YOU.
(DREW LAUGHS)
CONDOMS!
(LAUGHS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
I HAD A WET DREAM YESTERDAY...
IN CLASS.
UM...
ISN'T THAT SUPPOSED
TO HAPPEN
IN THE COMFORT
OF YOUR BEDROOM?
YEAH,
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT!
MAYBE YOUR PLUMBING'S
BACKED UP.
I DON'T THINK
IT WORKS THAT WAY.
I WAS-I WAS MERELY
DREAMING ABOUT ANYA
AND HELLO,
VOLCANIC ERUPTION.
OKAY. IN THIS,
IN THIS DREAM,
WAS SHE TOUCHING YOU?
BARELY.
I MEAN, WHAT IF SHE KISSES ME
ON OUR DATE?
(DAVE AND CONNOR LAUGH)
OKAY, OKAY.
YOU DON'T GOTTA WORRY
ABOUT A KISS,
'CAUSE I THINK
AT THIS RATE,
A SIMPLE HANDSHAKE
MIGHT SET YOU OFF!
IT'S NOT FUNNY!
DAVE:
ALL RIGHT, MAN.
I'M SORRY, ALL RIGHT?
RELAX.
I CAN'T!
YOU'RE COOL,
IT'S EASY FOR YOU.
THIS MIGHT BE MY ONLY CHANCE
TO EVER GO ON A DATE!
I'D LIKE TO GET THROUGH IT
ACCIDENT FREE!
I WANT IT TO BE GOOD.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, WES.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK.
LET'S GET REAL HERE.
ANYA, ALL RIGHT,
IS A BEAUTIFUL,
EXPERIENCED WOMAN, RIGHT?
AND WES,
WELL, YOU KNOW, YOU'RE-
NOT EVEN IN CONTROL
OF MY OWN BODILY FUNCTIONS.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD CANCEL.
(DAVE AND CONNOR SNICKER)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
(MATS THUMP)
THANK YOU.
JENNA: FOR SURE.
UM... CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
YOU JUST DID.
I MEAN, SURE,
OF COURSE.
WHAT'S YOUR HONEST OPINION
OF SAV?
YOU KNOW, JUST TRYING
TO GET A SENSE OF HIM,
SINCE WE'RE WORKING TOGETHER
IN THE BAND AND STUFF.
WELL, HE'S...
HE'S A DORK,
BUT IN THE BEST WAY POSSIBLE.
HE'S CUTE,
HE'S CARING,
EVEN WHEN YOU DO
THE WRONG THING.
JENNA:
WOW.
YOU GUYS SOUND CLOSE.
YEAH.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU RUN
A STUDENT GOVERNMENT TOGETHER.
UM...
DO YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENED
WITH ANYA
A-AFTER SHE GOT PREGNANT?
RIGHT, THAT HAPPENED.
UM...
ALL YOU NEED TO KNOW
IS THAT HE WAS...
100 PERCENT SUPPORTIVE.
A SAINT, REALLY.
HE MUST HAVE BEEN
DEVASTATED
AFTER THE MISCARRIAGE.
WELL, IT WAS...
SUCH A TRAGEDY.
HE PROBABLY WOULD HAVE
MADE A GREAT DAD.
GUY:
PERFORMING TOGETHER
FOR THE FIRST TIME,
HERE'S SAV BANDHARI
AND JENNA MIDDLETON!
(APPLAUSE)
(SAV AND JENNA STRUM GUITARS)
♪♪♪
♪ THE LIGHT YOU SHINE
SO BRIGHTLY ♪
♪ LIT THE STAR ♪
♪ IN MY EYES ♪
SAV AND JENNA:
♪ AND NOW THAT STAR IS FALLEN
FROM THE SKY ♪
♪ GOODBYE WHITE HORSE ♪
♪ GOODBYE BRAVE KNIGHT ♪
♪ I'M PULLING THE SWORD ♪
♪ OUT OF THE STONE ♪
♪ TONIGHT ♪
♪♪♪
SAV:
♪ WELL, SINCE YOU CAME
TO SAVE ME ♪
♪ I SEE YOU IN
A DIFFERENT LIGHT ♪
SAV AND JENNA:
♪ BUT NOW MY STAR IS RISING ♪
♪ TONIGHT ♪
♪ GOODBYE WHITE HORSE ♪
♪ GOODBYE BRAVE KNIGHT ♪
♪ I'M PULLING THE SWORD ♪
♪ OUT OF THE STONE ♪
♪ GOODBYE WHITE HORSE ♪
♪ GOODBYE BRAVE KNIGHT ♪
♪ WHEN WILL YOU LEARN ♪
♪ I'M NOT COMING HOME ♪
♪ TONIGHT ♪
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
STUDENTS:
WOO! YEAH!
WOW! (LAUGHS)
WOW.
OH, UH...
UH, THANKS, DEGRASSI.
UM...
ENJOY YOUR REMAINING
TEN MINUTES
OF SCHOOL SANCTIONED FUN.
(STUDENTS APPLAUD)
(MUSIC SWITCHES ON)
♪ I like a punk rock chick ♪
♪ With hair just like Rihanna ♪
♪ Like a go-go girl ♪
SAV:
OKAY, THAT DANCE... WAS LAME.
BUT PLAYING WITH YOU?
THE BEST EVER!
I COULD GET USED
TO THIS!
IT GETS LONELY JUST ME
AND MY GUITAR.
OH, I KNOW WHAT
YOU MEAN.
AND WE MAKE A GOOD TEAM!
Y-YOU THINK SO?
OH, YEAH.
YEAH!
WE DEFINITELY HAVE
A CONNECTION.
OUR HARMONIES
WERE TOTALLY IN SYNC,
WE KILLED IT.
(SIGHS HAPPILY)
WOW.
I KNOW!
HOLLY J:
SAV, YOU BACK THERE?
I NEED A HAND TAKING DOWN
THE TICKET TABLE.
UH, BE RIGHT THERE!
(CAR DOOR SLAMS)
(FENCE RATTLES)
(ADAM GASPS)
(CLARE GIGGLES)
♪♪♪
WHOA!
THIS PLACE IS...
CLARE:
BETTER THAN LUNCH
IN THE CAF?
I HAVE TO BRING FIONA
HERE SOME DAY!
HOW'D YOU GUYS FIND IT?
CLARE:
OH, ELI AND I WERE JUST ON
ONE OF OUR URBAN ADVENTURES
AND WE JUST
STUMBLED UPON IT.
DID YOU JUST SAY
URBAN ADVENTURE?
WHERE YOU'RE STANDING
RIGHT NOW?
THIS IS WHERE
I DEFLOWERED CLARE.
EW! YOU DIDN'T!
HE DID NOT, OKAY?
WE HAD A PICNIC
AND WE KISSED,
C'EST TOUT!
AND IT WAS PARFAIT.
AND WE SHOULDN'T BE
TALKING LIKE THIS
IN A PLACE OF WORSHIP.
ELI:
ABANDONED...PLACE OF WORSHIP.
IMAGINE:
CANDLES HERE,
TWINKLY LIGHTS
ON THIS TREE,
AN ICE BAR!
ELI:
DID YOU JUST SAY
ICE BAR?
WE HAVE TO THROW
A NEW YORK STYLE PARTY!
I HATE TO PIGEON HOLE US,
BUT ARE WE REALLY
THE PARTY-THROWING TYPES?
THE ANTI CRACKDOWN PARTY,
IN A SECRET LOCATION.
BRING YOUR CRUSH!
WOW!
I MEAN, THAT SOUNDS AMAZING,
BUT...
WHY THE SUDDEN NEED
FOR A PARTY?
WELL, FIONA SAYS SHE'S MISSING
THIS EVENT THING BACK AT HOME...
SO...
AND IF THE GIRL YOU LIKE
CAN'T GET TO THE PARTY,
BRING THE PARTY TO HER?
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
AW!
♪♪♪
JENNA: (SINGING)
♪ GOODBYE WHITE HORSE ♪
♪ GOODBYE BRAVE NIGHT ♪
SOMEBODY ENJOYS SWEEPING.
OH! NO, I JUST HAVEN'T HAD
THIS FEELING IN A WHILE.
WHAT FEELING?
JENNA:
THE FEELING IN YOUR TUMMY
WHERE YOU'VE...
FINALLY FOUND THE RIGHT PERSON
AND THAT THEY CAN MAKE
EVERYTHING OKAY.
HOLLY J:
YOU'RE SURE THAT'S NOT
JUST THE BABY KICKING?
(LAUGHS)
HOLLY J,
I'M FALLING FOR SOMEONE!
WELL, THAT SOUNDS
JUST LIKE A FAIRY TALE!
WHO IS THIS PRINCE CHARMING?
SAV BHANDARI.
PARDON?
JENNA:
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
NO.
NO, CONSIDERING WE'RE SEEING
EACH OTHER.
WHAT?
HOLLY J: YEAH.
YOU AND SAV?
HOLLY J: UH-HUH.
YEAH, KIND OF.
WELL, I-I'M SORRY, HOLLY J,
BUT...
HE'S INTO ME.
(ASTONISHED LAUGH)
OKAY, JUST IN CASE
YOU HAVEN'T...
YOU KNOW,
LOOKED DOWN RECENTLY,
YOU'RE WITH CHILD!
I DON'T THINK
IT MATTERS.
WELL, I THINK
YOUR PRENATAL VITAMINS
ARE GETTING TO YOUR HEAD.
OBVIOUSLY, YOU DON'T KNOW ME
VERY WELL.
GETTING RID OF INSIGNIFICANT
TEMPORARY GIRLFRIENDS
IS KINDA MY THING.
HONEY, SAVE YOURSELF
THE EMBARRASSMENT.
SAV WILL NEVER
GO FOR YOU.
NOT IN A MILLION YEARS.
WATCH.