♪♪♪
DECLAN:
SO YOU'RE STILL SHOCKED, HUH?
HOLLY J:
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE HERE!
WHAT ABOUT YOUR ROAD TRIP
TO YALE?
WELL, FIONA SAID THAT
YOU WERE WORRIED ABOUT THAT,
SO I MADE
OTHER ARRANGEMENTS.
YOU KNOW,
I ALMOST FLEW TO NEW YORK!
WHY DO YOU THINK
I TOLD YOU NOT TO?
AND, YOU KNOW, I'M SORRY
I HAD TO BE SO HARSH,
BUT I DIDN'T WANNA RUIN
THE SURPRISE.
YOU HAVEN'T CHECKED
YOUR VOICEMAIL?
NO. GUESS I FORGOT
TO TURN IT BACK ON
AFTER THE FLIGHT.
UGH!
WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU TOLD ME NOT TO COME.
I...KINDA JUMPED
TO CONCLUSIONS.
OH, NO.
JUST IGNORE IT!
WELL,
NOW I'M KINDA CURIOUS!
MM! SKIP IT!
DELETE IT!
HOLLY J:
...IT'S DRIVING ME INSANE!
(LAUGHING)
ARE YOU KIDDING?
THIS IS...
THIS IS CLASSIC!
(LAUGHS)
"IF YOU'RE HOOKING UP
WITH SOME HIGH-CLASS SKANK?"
HOLLY J:
WE'RE DONE.
BYE.
WOW.
(SIGHS) WITH US BEING
SO FAR APART FOR SO LONG,
MY IMAGINATION
JUST RAN WILD.
WELL, I'M HERE NOW.
SO IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I REALLY MISSED YOU.
(SIGHS)
COME HERE.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever! Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(TAXI RUMBLES)
HEY, HOW DOES IT FEEL
TO BE BACK?
I MISS THIS CITY.
(BOTH LAUGH)
YOU KNOW,
I EVEN KIND OF MISS DEGRASSI.
MM!
AND I DEFINITELY MISS
THE SMARTEST GIRL ON EARTH
HELPING ME
WITH MY ASSIGNMENTS.
WHAT, THERE'S NO SMART PEOPLE
AT VANDERBILT?
IT'S VERY COMPETITIVE.
AH. ONLY 200 MORE DAYS
'TIL GRADUATION, THOUGH.
HEY, I'M SORRY
IT'S ALL ON YOU TO COME HERE.
MY MOM WOULD'VE KILLED ME
IF I'D BOUGHT A FLIGHT
TO NEW YORK.
HOW BAD IS IT?
I MEAN,
YOUR SITUATION.
IT'S A LOT WORSE
THAN I EXPECTED.
(SIGHS)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
DECLAN:
WHAT ABOUT DAY TO DAY?
HOLLY J: WHAT?
DECLAN: FUN MONEY.
DECLAN:
A GIRL'S GOTTA LIVE,
RIGHT?
YEAH, I'M UH...
I'M GETTING A JOB
AFTER SCHOOL.
AND KEEP A FOUR-O GPA,
ACE YOUR SATS,
RACK UP EXTRACURRICULARS,
TAKE OVER STUDENT COUNCIL,
WHAT CHOICE DO I HAVE?
WELL, MAYBE I COULD
HELP YOU OUT.
HELP ME OUT?
HOW MUCH DO YOU NEED?
I MEAN, IF I CAN HELP YOU
FOCUS ON SCHOOL...
WHOA!
SO YOU WANT TO PAY ME
NOT TO WORK?
DECLAN:
LOOK, JUST...
JUST THINK ABOUT IT.
SEE YOU TONIGHT?
COME HERE.
♪♪♪
DAVE: (SINGING)
♪ YOU ARE ALWAYS ONLINE ♪
WOO!
GUYS! THE THREE TENNERS
ARE GONNA BLOW THE ROOF
OFF THIS PLACE!
YEAH... WE MIGHT NEED
TO CHANGE THE NAME.
A-AND I WAS THINKING,
MAYBE THE WHOLE THING'S
NOT A GOOD IDEA-
ARE YOU GUYS KIDDING?
ONCE PEOPLE SEE US
ON STAGE,
THEY'LL NEVER CALL US
THAT AGAIN.
AND TO GET OUR SOUND
OUT SOONER,
I BOOKED A RECORDING
SESSION WITH SAV.
(SIGHS)
AWESOME.
I OWE YOU GUYS HUGE.
(BELL RINGS)
WHAT'RE WE GONNA DO?
MR. BETENKAMP:
OKAY!
ALL RIGHT, TODAY WE'LL GET
INTO A NEW COMPONENT
IN OUR STUDY
OF HUMAN/MACHINE SYMBIOSIS:
ARTIFICIAL LIMBS.
THE ABILITY OF TECHNOLOGY
TO COMPENSATE
FOR PHYSICAL DEFICIENCIES
IS TRULY AWE-INSPIRING.
THAT'S IT!
MR. BETENKAMP:
THANK YOU, WESLEY.
IT IS FASCINATING.
(STUDENTS LAUGH)
SAV: (OVER PA)
IT'S PIZZA DAY IN THE CAF!
FIONA: HEY.
HOLLY J: HEY!
THANK YOU FOR THE HEADS UP.
TELL ME YOU'RE NOT MAD AT ME.
DID IT EVER OCCUR TO YOU
THAT HEARING DECLAN
TELL ME THAT
HE DIDN'T WANT TO SEE ME
MIGHT MAKE ME THINK
THAT HE DIDN'T WANT TO SEE ME?
HE MADE ME PROMISE
NOT TO TELL.
I'M A PAWN, HOLLY J!
IT'S OKAY
'CAUSE HE'S HERE,
AND I'M 200 PERCENT HAPPY.
SO YOU LOVEBIRDS
HAVE YOUR DATE TONIGHT?
HOLLY J:
YEAH, AND DECLAN'S ACTUALLY
MADE SURE
THAT I WON'T HAVE TO SPEND
MY EVENINGS WAITING TABLES.
REALLY? HOW?
HE'S GONNA HELP ME OUT,
FINANCIALLY.
OH.
"OH"?
WELL, THAT CAN GET WEIRD.
AND JUST THE OTHER DAY
YOU ACCUSED ME
OF TRYING TO PAY YOU
TO BE MY FRIEND.
THIS IS DIFFERENT!
DECLAN AND I ARE LONG-TERM.
WHAT'S HIS IS MINE,
AND ONCE I'M RICH
AND SUCCESSFUL ON MY OWN,
WHAT'S MINE IS HIS.
WELL, GOOD FOR YOU.
(SCOFFS)
(DICE RATTLE)
FITZ:
AW!
ELI:
HOW WOULD YOU LIKE ACCESS
TO THE FINER THINGS
YOUTH PROHIBITS?
DO YOU HAVE THE ID
OR WHAT?
YOU'LL BE PLEASED.
MY GUY'S AN EXPERT CRAFTSMAN.
LOOKS GOOD.
ELI:
SO, WE'RE GOOD?
NO MORE HASSLES?
LONG AS THIS WORKS.
YOU HAVE MY WORD.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
SO...
WHAT'S THE PLAN?
WHEN THE POLICE CHECK
FITZ'S FAKE ID,
AND MISTAKE HIM
FOR AN ESCAPED ARSONIST?
HILARITY ENSUES.
WHAT DO WE DO UNTIL THEN?
AH, GRASSHOPPER.
THERE ARE WAYS
TO EXPEDITE THE PROCESS.
DAVE:
(OVER DRUMBEATS)
IT'S DIZZLE...
REACHING WIZZLE
AND KIZZLE.
(FLUTE PLAYS)
UH-HUH!
(SINGING OUT OF TUNE)
♪ YOU WERE ALWAYS ONLINE ♪
♪ ALWAYS ON MY MIND ♪
♪ I NEVER EVEN SEEN YOU ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY LOVE IS BLIND ♪
(DRUMBEATS AND FLUTE PLAY)
WHAT'S UP, MY BROTHA?
AND SISTA.
CLARE:
LOOKS LIKE YOU MADE PEACE
WITH YOUR TORMENTOR.
SO HE THINKS.
RIGHT.
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.
CLARE, MY MISSION
IS JUST GETTING STARTED.
THAT NEANDERTHAL
STARTED SOMETHING,
AND I'M GOING TO END IT.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
SHOW HIM THAT MY REPUTATION
IS MORE THAN JUST A RUMOUR.
(SIGHS)
IF ELI'S GONNA DO
SOMETHING BAD,
SOMEONE NEEDS TO STOP HIM.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD STAY
OUT OF IT.
HE HAS A SURPRISE FOR FITZ
AND IT'S GONNA BE BIG.
DAVE: (RAPPING)
♪ I MAY NOT KNOW
WHAT YOU LOOK LIKE ♪
♪ BUT I'D RECOGNIZE YOU
ON SIGHT ♪
♪ WHEN I TALK TO YOU
I THINK, OH! ♪
♪ I SHOULD CALL YOU UP
AND THEN WHOA! ♪
♪ WE'RE GONNA MEET
JUST SAY WHEN ♪
♪ I'LL NEVER FRAG YOU AGAIN ♪
ALL RIGHT!
LET'S HEAR IT.
BUCKLE UP!
("FRAG YOU" PLAYS)
DAVE (IN SONG):
IT'S DIZZLE...
REACHING WIZZLE
AND KIZZLE.
(VOICE DIGITALLY MODULATED)
♪ YOU WERE ALWAYS ONLINE ♪
♪ ALWAYS ON MY MIND ♪
WHOA, HOLD UP.
WHAT DID-WHAT DID YOU DO?
I AUTO-TUNED IT.
DAVE: WHY?
WESLEY: YOUR SINGING,
YOU JUST NEED
A LITTLE HELP.
(LAUGHS)
WHAT'S WRONG WITH MY SINGING?
IT'S TERRIBLE.
NO, IT'S AWESOME.
NO, IT'S-IT'S TERRIBLE.
LIKE, REALLY TERRIBLE.
SO SAV FIXED IT.
WE CAN PUT THIS EFFECT ON
WHEN WE PLAY LIVE!
SAV:
YEAH, IT'S CHOICE!
LIKE T-PAIN STYLES.
YOU KNOW,
YOU GUYS ARE LOSERS.
AND SO AM I
FOR HANGING OUT WITH YOU.
(SCOFFS)
("FRAG YOU" PLAYS)
(BIRDS CHIRP)
OH!
MARY KATE:
I THOUGHT WE AGREED,
NO SHOPPING.
WHERE DID THIS COME FROM?
IT WAS DELIVERED.
"SOMETHING FOR YOU
TO WEAR TONIGHT."
IT'S FROM DECLAN.
(GASPS)
MARY KATE:
WELL, BIBBITI-BOBBITI-BOO!
WHAT, IS THIS HIS ATTEMPT
TO BRIBE HIS WAY BACK?
OH NO,
WE DIDN'T BREAK UP.
HOLLY J,
HE CHEATED ON YOU!
NO, HE DIDN'T.
HE CAME HERE.
TO SEE ME.
IT WAS ALL IN MY HEAD,
I WAS JUST BEING PARANOID.
HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT
WHAT I SAID?
YOU KNOW,
WHAT I DON'T UNDERSTAND
IS WHY YOU THINK I'M EITHER
DOING STUFF FOR MYSELF,
OR TO BE WITH DECLAN.
IT CAN BE BOTH.
AND WHAT ABOUT DOING SOMETHING
FOR YOUR FAMILY?
DID YOU CALL THE RESTAURANT?
I HAVE BETTER THINGS TO DO
THAN DEAL WITH WHINY REQUESTS
FOR FREE REFILLS!
MARY KATE:
WELL, GOOD TO KNOW
YOUR SUPERIORITY COMPLEX
IS ALIVE AND WELL!
AND WHAT'S WRONG WITH THAT?
I HAVE TO WORK 200 TIMES HARDER
TO GET WHAT I WANT
THANKS TO YOUR AND DAD'S
MISTAKES!
WE HAVE GIVEN YOU
EVERY OPPORTUNITY.
AND I'M TRYING
TO TAKE ADVANTAGE OF THEM!
IF DECLAN WANTS TO BUY ME
A NECKLACE,
SO WHAT?
MARY KATE:
YOU'RE NAIVE IF YOU THINK
THIS IS JUST ABOUT A NECKLACE.
NOTHING COMES FOR FREE,
HOLLY J.
NOW WHO'S BEING PARANOID?
ENJOY PLAYING
GROWN-UP TONIGHT.
THEN FINISH PACKING.
WE MOVE TO THE DEPRESSING
APARTMENT ON SUNDAY.
CHANTAY:
THAT'S A ROCK!
DID YOU ROB A BANK?
IT'S A GIFT
FROM MY BOYFRIEND.
NOTHING SAYS LOVE
LIKE A LITTLE BLUE BOX!
MUST BE NICE TO HAVE
A SUGAR DADDY.
EXCUSE ME?
(COUGHS)
GOLD DIGGER!
I'M NOT A GOLD DIGGER!
OH, I'M-I'M JUST TEASING!
FIONA:
YOU WISH YOU HAD SOMEONE
TO BUY YOU NICE THINGS!
HOLLY J:
IT'S OKAY.
SHE WOULDN'T UNDERSTAND.
DO YOU WANNA MEET FOR LUNCH?
FIONA:
NO, I CAN'T.
I'M MEETING MY DECORATOR.
YOU TWO SHOULD
HEAR YOURSELVES.
(CARS RUMBLE BY)
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
911? THERE'S A FIGHT
OUTSIDE MCGRATH VARIETY.
IT LOOKS SERIOUS.
NO, I'LL STAY ON THE LINE.
OH! OH NO! THEY SEE ME!
COME QUICK!
ELI:
HEY, MORON!
THE ID WORKED, EH?
THOSE THINGS'LL KILL YOU.
WHAT THE HELL DO YOU WANT?
♪♪♪
(STUDENTS LAUGHING)
GIRL:
THAT'S GOOD,
I'M GLAD YOU HAD FUN.
GIRL 2:
IT WAS TOTALLY AWESOME.
DECLAN:
LADIES.
ROOM FOR ONE MORE?
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
DECLAN:
WHAT ELSE AM I GONNA DO?
I'M ONLY IN TOWN TO SEE YOU.
MAY I?
WHAT'S MINE IS YOURS.
HOLLY J GETS DIAMONDS;
YOU GET TUNA SALAD.
YOU'RE GETTING RIPPED OFF,
DUDE.
WELL, IF HOLLY J COMES WITH ME
TO YALE THIS WEEKEND,
I'LL CONSIDER US EVEN.
WHAT?!
YEAH,
YOU CAN'T MISS IT.
YOU WERE PREPARED
TO GET ON A FLIGHT YESTERDAY.
WHEN I THOUGHT
YOU WERE CHEATING ON ME!
HEY LOOK,
I ALREADY BOOKED THE FLIGHTS,
AND THE HOTEL ROOM,
SO...
DECLAN,
I HAVE MY SATS!
RESCHEDULE THEM.
I ALSO HAVE TO HELP
MY PARENTS MOVE.
THAT'S BORING.
(SIGHS ANGRILY)
OKAY, FINE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M ALREADY PAYING FOR YOU
NOT TO WORK,
I MIGHT AS WELL PAY
FOR THE MOVERS, TOO.
IT'S NOT THAT EASY.
I THOUGHT THE PLAN
WAS THAT WE'D VISIT
EACH OTHER.
JUST COME FOR A FEW DAYS.
PLEASE.
I JUST CAN'T.
COME ON!
HOW MUCH WILL I HAVE TO SPEND
BEFORE YOU DO WHAT I ASK?
JUST DROP IT,
PREPPY!
HOLLY J:
GO HOME.
JUST GO.
I'LL...CALL YOU LATER.
WELL, WHATEVER.
(GRUNTS)
BYE?
♪♪♪
♪ Come on, yeah ♪
♪ 'cause I'm the big bad wolf ♪
♪ What do you say? ♪
♪ I'm the big bad wolf ♪
♪ Blowin' down
your neighbourhood ♪
FITZ: HAD ENOUGH?
ELI: YOU PUNCH LIKE MY GRANDMA.
OH, REALLY?
(GARBAGE CAN THUDS)
(SIREN WAILS)
(CAR RUMBLES UP)
FITZ:
LET GO!
IT'S THE COPS, MAN!
(ENGINE CUTS OFF ABRUPTLY)
FEMALE COP:
HEY! THIS IS OVER.
NOW!
TURN AROUND.
(CHATTER OVER POLICE RADIO)
YOU TWO STAY RIGHT HERE
WHILE I RUN THESE.
SUCKS TO BE YOU.
WHY'S THAT?
MY FAKE ID.
THEY WON'T EVEN KNOW
WHO I AM.
GUESS IT'S YOUR LUCKY DAY.
HEY DAVE,
WHERE ARE THE GUYS?
OH. THEY WENT TO CONNOR'S HOUSE
TO PLAY X-BOX.
BUT YOU DIDN'T?
DAVE:
I'D RATHER BE HERE ALONE
THAN WITH THOSE LAMEWADS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
("FRAG YOU" PLAYS)
DAVE: (AUTO-TUNED SINGING)
♪ SOMETIMES YOU KNOW I GET
SO BORED ♪
(RAPPING)
♪ WHEN I TALK TO YOU ♪
♪ I THINK, OH! ♪
♪ I SHOULD CALL YOU UP
AND THEN WHOA! ♪
♪ I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT YOU LOOK LIKE ♪
♪ BUT I'D RECOGNIZE YOU... ♪
(TURNS IPOD OFF)
DUDE,
IT SOUNDS REALLY COOL.
SO WHAT?
IT'S NOT ME.
IT'S YOU,
ONLY BETTER!
LISTEN,
I WAS IN A BAND.
IT WAS THE BEST TIME
OF MY LIFE -
HANGING OUT
WITH MY BEST BUDS,
GOOFING OFF,
MAKING TUNES.
BUT THEY ALL MOVED ON,
AND I'M LEFT HERE.
THAT SUCKS, BRO.
BUT WHAT'S YOUR POINT?
WELL...
THOSE GUYS CAME UP
WITH THE BAND IDEA
'CAUSE YOU WERE
IN THE DUMPS,
AND THEY WANTED
TO CHEER YOU UP.
YOU'RE NOT MESSIN' WITH ME?
YOU CAN'T ASK FOR BETTER FRIENDS
THAN THAT.
AUDITIONS ARE STILL OPEN.
(DOOR SLAMS)
FEMALE COP:
THIS ONE'S OKAY.
HANDS BEHIND YOUR BACK.
FITZ:
WHAT'D I DO?
FEMALE COP:
WE'RE GONNA SORT THAT OUT
AT THE STATION.
WHAT ABOUT ME,
OFFICER?
YOU CAN GO.
WE'VE GOT BIGGER
FISH TO FRY TODAY, HUH?
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING!
FEMALE COP:
YEAH? THEN YOU'VE GOT NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
YOU HAVE THE RIGHT
TO REMAIN SILENT-
WHAT DID HE TELL YOU?
I CAN MAKE THAT AN ORDER.
GET IN THE CAR.
(DOOR SLAMS)
(ENGINE STARTS,
COPS RUMBLE AWAY)
SAT INSTRUCTOR:
AND ONCE YOU'VE ALL ACED
YOUR SATS TOMORROW,
WE WILL SEND THE RESULTS
TO THE UNIVERSITIES
OF YOUR CHOICE.
SO, LET'S GO THROUGH
AN APPLICATION.
NOW...
YOU KNOW ABOUT THE ESSAYS,
AND THE SUPPORTING DOCUMENTS,
AND THERE'S THIS SECTION
ON FINANCIAL AID,
AKA YOUR INTRODUCTION
TO YEARS OF STUDENT DEBT.
SO, BE HONEST
WITH YOUR RESPONSES,
BECAUSE NOTHING ON
THIS APPLICATION
WILL BE USED TO DISCRIMINATE
AGAINST YOU...
SHEESH. MAKES YOU WONDER
WHY PEOPLE LIKE US
EVEN GO TO COLLEGE.
PEOPLE LIKE US?
WELL,
I HAVE MY TRUST FUND,
YOU HAVE DECLAN;
WE'RE TAKEN CARE OF.
(SCOFFS)
(SIGHS WORRIEDLY)
(SIGHS)
CLARE:
WHERE WERE YOU THIS AFTERNOON?
CONFLICT RESOLUTION.
CLARE:
SO IT'S RESOLVED?
SO MUCH FOR NON-VIOLENCE.
ELI:
MINOR SKIRMISH,
BUT NOBODY GOT HURT.
WHAT HAPPENED?
COPS HAD TO BREAK UP
A FIGHT.
AND SOMEBODY PUT THE NAME
OF A CONVICTED ARSONIST
ON FITZ'S FAKE ID.
OOPS!
HE'LL BE SPENDING
A FEW HOURS AT THE COP SHOP.
YOU HAD HIM ARRESTED?!
ELI:
HE'LL BE OUT
AS SOON AS THEY CLEAR UP
THE MISTAKEN IDENTITY.
LET'S JUST SAY I'D RATHER BE
FEARED BY FITZ THAN LIKED.
SO THAT'S IT?
ELI:
YEAH. WHAT DID YOU EXPECT?
I DON'T KNOW!
I WAS JUST ON MY WAY
TO SIMPSON'S OFFICE
TO EXPRESS CONCERN
OVER YOUR MENTAL STABILITY!
CLARE,
GIVE ME SOME CREDIT.
WORST THAT HAPPENS,
HE GETS BUSTED
FOR FAKE ID POSSESSION.
MIGHT HAVE TO GO TO COURT.
AND WHAT IF HE TELLS THE COPS
WHERE HE GOT IT?
ELI:
HIS WORDS AGAINST MINE.
HE'S GONNA BE PRETTY MAD.
SPEAK OF THE DEVIL.
GOOD ONE, ELI.
YOU GOT ME.
YOU DO REALIZE THAT
THAT ID
WAS JUST FOR NOVELTY
PURPOSES ONLY.
I'LL HAVE TO TELL THAT
TO THE JUDGE.
HOPE YOU LEARNED YOUR LESSON.
FITZ:
TOO BAD FOR YOU,
I'M A SLOW LEARNER.
SO WHAT NOW?
YOU TWO AT WAR?
I'M IN HIS HEAD,
RIGHT WHERE I WANNA BE.
DECLAN:
I'M REALLY GLAD
YOU CHANGED YOUR MIND.
AND WHEN WE'RE BACK
IN NEW YORK,
I'LL BORROW MY DAD'S CAR
AND WE'LL CATCH UP
WITH THE GUYS AT YALE -
WITH OUR OWN HOTEL ROOM,
OF COURSE.
MAN, I MISS BEING WITH YOU
SO MUCH.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
EXCUSE ME?
I CAN'T TAKE YOUR MONEY.
WHAT?
WHAT-WHAT'S GOING ON?
IT MAKES ME FEEL GROSS.
HOLLY J, MONEY EXISTS
TO SOLVE PROBLEMS.
SO THAT'S WHAT I AM TO YOU?
I'M-I'M A PROBLEM?
NO!
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
HOLLY J:
TURN LEFT AT THE LIGHTS.
'KAY, NO!
WE'RE GOING TO THE AIRPORT.
WE'RE NOT!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
I THOUGHT WE WERE PART
OF EACH OTHER'S DREAMS,
BUT YOU ONLY WANNA MAKE ME
PART OF YOURS.
HOLLY J-
I DON'T NEED
YOUR HELP!
I NEED TIME TO FIGURE
THIS OUT,
AWAY FROM YOU.
YEAH, BUT YOU'VE BEEN
AWAY FROM ME!
AND A RELATIONSHIP ONLINE
AND OVER THE PHONE,
THAT'S THE PROBLEM!
WELL, THEN MAYBE WE SHOULD
GO ON A BREAK.
♪♪♪
♪ I wanna know what you know ♪
GREAT.
THEN WE'RE ON A BREAK.
♪ Take a trip
to the end of time ♪
♪ Kiss your lips,
Grab your hips ♪
♪ And fly away... ♪
HOLLY J:
TURN LEFT.
DAVE HATES US.
WHO'S GONNA LEAD US OUT OF
THE GRADE TEN GHETTO NOW?
WE'LL FIND SOMEONE,
WES.
WE'LL FIND SOMEONE.
("FRAG YOU" PLAYS IN THE DOT)
DAVE: (RAPPING)
♪ IT'S DIZZLE... ♪
♪ REACHING WIZZLE
AND KIZZLE... ♪
♪♪♪
DAVE: (AUTO-TUNED SINGING)
♪ YOU WERE ALWAYS... ♪
WESLEY:
HEY, THAT'S US!
DO YOU GUYS LIKE IT?
WE SOUND LIKE ROBOTS!
LOOK, GUYS,
THE BAND SLAM?
IT'S OUR DESTINY.
ARE WE GONNA RISE
TO THE OCCASION,
OR ARE WE GONNA RUN
LIKE COWARDS?
RISE! RISE!
UM, IS THAT YOU GUYS?
YOU KNOW IT!
THE THREE TENNERS.
IT'S FUNNY.
IT SOUNDS KINDA COOL.
FUNNY AND COOL.
WE COULD DO WORSE, RIGHT?
BAND SLAM -
SEE YOU GUYS THERE?
YEAH, WE'LL BE THERE!
NICE WORK, BOYS.
NICE WORK.
(COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYS)
HOLLY J:
THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR THE SECOND CHANCE.
JUAN:
WITH YOUR RESUME,
WE'RE GLAD YOU COULD MAKE IT OUT
ON SUCH SHORT NOTICE.
AND YOU'RE SURE
I CAN HAVE TOMORROW OFF
FOR MY SATS?
JUST REMEMBER US
WHEN YOU WIN
YOUR FIRST NOBEL PRIZE.
REMEMBER, EYE CONTACT,
ENERGY, SMILES!
CHECK, CHECK, CHECK!
GOOD.
WE'VE ALREADY HAD
A SPECIAL REQUEST
FOR OUR NEW WAITRESS.
(LAUGHS)
(TAKES A DEEP BREATH)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
AND MISS YOUR FIRST SHIFT?
I THINK NOT.
I'M PROUD OF YOU,
SWEETIE.
DID DECLAN TELL YOU
ABOUT OUR FIGHT?
HE CALLED ME FROM THE AIRPORT
IN TEARS.
AND YOU'RE NOT MAD?
I'M YOUR FRIEND,
HOLLY J.
SO,
WHAT ARE YOUR SPECIALS?
WELL, YOU HAVE TO TRY
THE PARMESAN-ARTICHOKE DIP,
AND THE SHRIMP COCKTAIL
IS TO DIE FOR!
HOW AM I DOING?
I'M BUYING IT.
(LAUGHS)