ELI:
WINE TASTING AT SALT LOUNGE?
MY PARENTS
DON'T DRINK.
UH, A FAMILY NIGHT
AT WONDERLAND?
MY PARENTS DON'T
REALLY LIKE FUN.
FREE TAX PREPARATION
AT THE COMMUNITY CENTRE?
THEY'D LOVE IT!
BUT THAT'S - WHAT? -
ONLY AN HOUR?
WE NEED TO GET THEM AWAY
FROM THE TRUCK FOR LIKE FOUR
IF WE'RE GONNA GET TO HAMILTON
AND BACK.
MAYBE THIS CONCERT'S A NO GO.
SAV:
WHAT, AND GIVE UP
BACKSTAGE PASSES?
I DON'T THINK SO.
(FLIPS PAGE)
WHOA.
BOLLYWOOD DOUBLE BILL
SCREENS AT SEVEN.
WITH THE DIRECTOR Q AND A,
THAT'LL BE
AT LEAST FIVE HOURS.
THOSE TICKETS
ARE THIRTY BUCKS!
WELL, WE'LL HAVE
TO POOL OUR MONEY.
SO, I'LL GIVE MY PARENTS
THE TICKETS AFTER SCHOOL,
SNAG MY MOM'S
EXTRA SET OF KEYS.
WE'LL MEET AT THE REVUE
AT 7:15,
"BORROW" THE TRUCK,
WE'LL SEE THE SHOW,
HURRY BACK AND PARK IT
EXACTLY AS WE LEFT IT.
WE CAN DO THIS.
YEAH, WE NEED YOU,
MAN.
YEAH. AND I NEED TO GET
TO THIS CONCERT.
YOU KNOW, DESPITE
WHAT MY DAD THINKS,
I DESERVE TO HAVE
A LITTLE FUN
EVERY NOW AND THEN!
WE'RE DOIN' IT.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
ALLI:
ALL I KEEP HEARING ABOUT
IS THE POWER SQUAD
CALENDAR PHOTO SHOOT!
REALLY?
WHO'S TALKING ABOUT IT?
PEOPLE AT SCHOOL,
PEOPLE AT THE DOT.
EVEN HEARD SOME LADY
MENTION IT
IN LINE AT THE GROCERY STORE!
JENNA:
AND THEY'RE ALL EXCITED
ABOUT IT?
THE LADY AT THE GROCERY STORE
ALMOST DROPPED HER CANTALOUPES!
IT'S REALLY NOT
THAT BIG A DEAL.
EASY FOR YOU TO SAY.
YOU'RE PROBABLY GONNA BE
ON THE COVER!
GREAT.
SHOULD BE FUN.
KC:
MOM TOOK ME
FOR GREASY BREAKFAST.
GOT YOU
YOUR FAVOURITE!
I CAN'T.
IT'S CLASS.
YOU'RE GONNA LET A LITTLE CLASS
COME BETWEEN YOU
AND A EGGY BACON BOY
WITH CHEESE?
(BELL RINGS)
MS. OH:
BETTER SWALLOW IT.
NO FOOD AROUND THE COMPUTERS;
YOU KNOW THE RULES.
TODAY, WE EXPLORE THE WONDERS
OF IMAGE MANIPULATION.
WITH POWERFUL TOOLS
LIKE PHOTOSHOP,
YOU CAN MAKE ANY PICTURE
PERFECT!
TO START, OPEN THE BEFORE
AND AFTER FILE ON YOUR DESKTOP
AND TAKE A MINUTE
TO GO OVER THE IMAGES.
PERINO:
THE AZTECS WERE
A SACRIFICIAL PEOPLE.
AND IN THAT SPIRIT,
I WANT YOU TO SACRIFICE
SOME OF YOUR FREE TIME
AND CREATE A SCULPTURE
THAT, UH,
REFLECTS AN ASPECT
OF AZTEC CULTURE.
YOU DO IT IN GROUPS
OR ON YOUR OWN.
FI?
FIONA,
I'M SORRY I WAS TOO BUSY
TO HANG OUT ON THE WEEKEND.
DO YOU WANNA WORK ON THIS
TOGETHER?
NO. I DON'T NEED YOU
ANYMORE.
WHY ARE YOU ACTING
SO WIGGY?
(SNORTS)
(WHISPERED) IS THAT...
A PIG?
IT'S PORCELINA.
A PIG.
ISN'T SHE PRETTY?
YOU BROUGHT A PIG
TO SCHOOL?
FIONA:
WELL, SHE'D BE SO LONELY
IN THAT BIG CONDO BY HERSELF,
AND I'D NEVER LEAVE
A FRIEND ALL ALONE.
PERINO:
THAT'S GOOD,
BECAUSE YOU PROBABLY SHOULD
GO HOME TOGETHER.
BUT MR. PERINO,
CAN YOU REALLY KICK THIS FACE
OUT OF CLASS?
PERINO:
FINE, THEN STAY.
BUT I'M WARNING YOU,
I'VE GOT A HANKERING FOR BACON.
OKAY,
I'LL TAKE HER HOME.
(SNORTING)
PERINO:
ALL RIGHT, BACK TO THE AZTEC.
FOCUS.
JENNA:
HEY, ANYA, GUESS WHAT!
UM... YOU GOT A PONY?
SORRY, I'M MORE OF
A MULTIPLE CHOICE KINDA GAL.
UH, I LOST THREE POUNDS
ALREADY!
I AM SO GONNA FIT
MY POWER SQUAD UNIFORM
FOR THE CALENDAR SHOOT!
YOU KNOW, THREE POUNDS MIGHT
JUST BE WATER WEIGHT.
IT'S NOT. TRUST ME.
I'VE BEEN TAKING THESE -
BEST SOLUTION EVER!
DIET PILLS?
YEAH.
UM... WERE THESE PRESCRIBED
TO YOU?
NOT EXACTLY.
UH, SO YOU'RE TAKING PILLS
THAT AREN'T EVEN YOURS
THAT CLAIM TO DO SOMETHING
THAT ISN'T EVEN POSSIBLE?
NO, THEY WORK.
THEY MAKE ME LIKE YOU!
HOW IS THAT
ANYTHING LIKE ME?
I CAN EAT WHATEVER I WANT,
AND THEN I TAKE THESE BABIES
AND THEY STOP MY BODY
FROM ABSORBING THE FAT!
AH... AND HAVE YOU SEEN
THESE SIDE EFFECTS? GROSS!
NOTHING BAD'S HAPPENED YET!
AND BESIDES,
SOME THINGS ARE WORTH IT.
SHORT TERM PAIN
FOR LONG TERM GAIN.
FINE,
CHASE YOUR LONG-TERM GAIN,
JUST MAKE SURE
YOU WEAR DIAPERS!
(DOOR CLOSES)
HEY, MOM.
WHATCHA DOIN'?
WHAT DOES IT LOOK LIKE?
SAV:
WELL, I KNOW IT'S SOLITAIRE,
BUT... WHAT KIND OF SOLITAIRE?
IF YOU'RE TRYING
TO SWEET TALK YOUR WAY
INTO SEEING THAT CONCERT,
YOU'LL HAVE TO TALK
TO YOUR FATHER.
MR. BHANDARI:
TALK TO ME ABOUT WHAT?
UH... I...
I HAVE SOMETHING FOR YOU.
UM, V.I.P. PASSES TO...
THE BOLLYWOOD
DOUBLE BILL?
WE WANTED
TO SEE THIS, DEAR!
MR. BHANDARI:
FOR TONIGHT?
WHAT CLEVER RUSE IS THIS?
YOU WANT US OUT OF THE HOUSE?
NO, NO, NO.
IT'S AN APOLOGY.
I WAS ACTING LIKE A JERK.
ARE THERE GIRLS
COMING OVER TONIGHT?
LOOK, I DON'T THINK
WE CAN ACCEPT THESE.
SAV'S BEING SINCERE.
HE'S SORRY.
YEAH, SO SORRY.
AND, AND NO ONE'S COMING OVER;
I'VE GOT TOO MUCH HOMEWORK
ANYWAYS.
OKAY.
WE'LL GO.
BUT ONLY BECAUSE THAT
TAPAS BANERJEE IS SUCH A CARD.
I CAN WEAR
ONE OF MY NEW SHIRTS!
THANK YOU, SAV.
WHAT A GENEROUS GESTURE.
I KNOW YOU AND YOUR FATHER
ARE AT ODDS SOMETIMES,
BUT HE'LL COME AROUND.
WE DO TRUST YOU.
(CAMERA SNAPS PHOTOS)
SAV:
(SIGHS)
OKAY, GUYS,
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THIS.
NAH, IT'S FLAWLESS.
PYLONS TO RESERVE
THE SPACE
AND WE PUT THE WHEELS RIGHT BACK
WHERE THE CHALK IS.
AND WE USE THESE PHOTOS
TO KEEP THE INTERIOR
EXACTLY AS WE LEFT IT!
YEAH, NO.
THE, THE PLAN IS SOUND.
I WAS JUST...
I WAS THINKING ABOUT WHAT...
THINKING ABOUT MY MOM.
AWW... SWEET.
VERY FUNNY.
NO, AT HOME,
SHE WAS ALL LIKE,
(INDIAN ACCENT)
"BUDDY, WE TRUST YOU."
WELL,
THEY SHOULD TRUST YOU.
YEAH, AND I'M TOTALLY
TAKING ADVANTAGE OF THAT.
I KNOW!
IT'S AWESOME!
ARE YOU
CHICKENING OUT?
JUST GET IN THE TRUCK.
REALLY?
BEFORE I CHANGE MY MIND!
GET IN THE TRUCK!
♪ I'm... I'm so popular ♪
♪ La la la la la la ♪
♪ I'm so popular ♪
♪ La la la la la la♪
♪ La la la la la la ♪
♪ I'm so popular
La la la la la la ♪
FIONA:
OH, AREN'T YOU PRETTY?
♪ Yeah, I've got one and two
and three and four ♪
♪ Good guys on my arm ♪
♪ So hot that when I walk in
I set off the alarm ♪
♪ Too much money in my purse ♪
♪ Every dollar I have earned ♪
♪ And I don't need your help ♪
♪ I'm so popular ♪
PROCELINA?
PORCIE?
HERE, PIGGY.
COME HERE.
PORCELINA!
(GASPS)
OH, YUCK!
UGH!
THEY SAID YOU WERE
HOUSE-BROKEN!
♪♪♪
(CROWD SCREAMING AND CHEERING)
♪ SNEAKY CAT
WITH THE NOTCH IN HER BACK ♪
♪ COMES CREEPING MY WAY ♪
♪ SHE'S FAST ON HER FEET,
DANGEROUSLY ♪
♪ AND I LIKE IT THAT WAY ♪
ELI:
MAN, THIS SO RULES!
I OWE YOU HUGE.
SAV:
NO, MAN. I'M SURE YOU DO
THIS KIND OF CRAZY STUFF
ALL THE TIME.
ELI:
THINK I'D TOUCH MY DAD'S MGB?
WHY DO YOU THINK
I HAVE MY OWN CAR?
WHOA, WHOA,
WHOA, WAIT!
SO, YOU MEAN
I RISKED MY ASS
DOING SOMETHING YOU GUYS
WOULDN'T EVEN DO?
THAT'S WHY
YOU'RE THE MAN!
BIANCA:
OH MY GOD, SCHOOL PREZ!
(GIGGLING)
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE HERE.
AT SCHOOL,
YOU'RE ALL...
WHOA. HEY!
BUT YOU'RE HERE,
ROCKIN' OUT!
YEAH,
IT FEELS AWESOME!
♪ TOO LATE, TOO LATE ♪
♪ IT'S TOO LATE,
TOO LATE ♪
♪ FULFILL THE DREAM'S ACHE ♪
♪ BEFORE THE TEACHER SAYS,
"OH YEAH"
CROWD:
♪ OH YEAH! ♪
♪ SECOND CLASS DREAMS
ARE SCATTERED ♪
♪ SAYING OH-OH... ♪
OH, JUNK FOOD,
(SIGHS)
WITH YOUR NACHO-Y GOODNESS.
HOW I HATE YOU.
DON'T MIND ME.
JUST PIGGING OUT.
DON'T WORRY, GIRL.
I'M JEALOUS!
WHY?
CUZ YOU AND ANYA CAN EAT
WHATEVER YOU LIKE
AND NEVER GAIN WEIGHT.
IT IS A BLESSING.
AND A GOOD ONE,
CUZ WE'VE CHOSEN
YOUR CUTE SELF
FOR THE COVER OF
THE POWER SQUAD CALENDAR!
REALLY?
AS SOON AS GERIATRIC BADMINTON
CLEARS OUTTA THE GYM,
WE'RE GONNA BRAINSTORM
SEXY CALENDAR POSES.
OUR LITTLE SECRET?
OUR LITTLE SECRET.
♪ Who wants to tell you off ♪
DEAD HAND SINGER:
GOOD NIGHT, HAMILTON!
WE LOVE YOU!
(CHEERING AND APPLAUDING)
SAV:
GUYS, GREAT CONCERT.
THANKS FOR COMING,
GUYS.
SAV:
WHAT AN AMAZING CONCERT!
THAT WAS RELIGIOUS!
THOSE GUYS ARE MY GODS!
AND SAV, YOU'RE LIKE
THE POPE OR SOMETHING.
YEAH.
LOOKS LIKE WE MIGHT EVEN
MAKE IT HOME IN TIME!
TO THE POPE-MOBILE!
CAN I GET A LIFT?
THERE'S NO WAY
I'LL FIND RON-RON NOW.
(GIGGLES)
UM, YEAH,
YOU CAN RIDE WITH US.
JUST UH, GUYS, COME ON.
WE GOTTA GO. NOW.
I THINK THERE'S GONNA
BE AN ENCORE.
DEAD HAND SINGER:
BETTER STICK AROUND, GUYS!
AUDIENCE:
(CHEERING)
DEAD HAND SINGER:
ALL RIGHT HAMILTON,
THIS IS "YOUR PAISLEY JACKET!"
THAT'S MY FAVOURITE SONG.
GUYS, ARE WE STAYING?
OR-?
WHAT ABOUT THE TRUCK?
♪♪♪
FAN:
WHOO HOO!
♪♪♪
THE DEAD HAND:
♪ I'VE SEEN YOUR PATTERN ♪
♪ AND I CAN MATCH IT ♪
♪ JUST TRACE THE LINES ON... ♪
SAV, ELI, ADAM AND BIANCA:
♪ I'VE SEEN YOUR PATTERN ♪
♪ AND I CAN MATCH IT ♪
♪ JUST TRACE THE LINES ON
YOUR PAISLEY JACKET! ♪
MAN, I CAN'T BELIEVE
WE GOT TO GO BACKSTAGE.
GUY, GUYS.
NOT TO RUIN THE MOOD,
BUT WE'VE ONLY GOT 20 MINUTES
AND WE'RE ONLY
HALFWAY BACK.
BIANCA:
GUN IT, DUDE!
UH, NO.
I'M NOT GONNA SPEED.
WE'RE NOT GONNA MAKE IT.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
EVERYONE JUST BE QUIET, OKAY?
NO DISTRACTIONS.
(SPEEDING UP)
BIANCA:
WOO, SAV!
JUST KNOCK IT OFF!
CHANTAY:
THIS CALENDAR IS GONNA BE
A-MAZING!
LOOKS GOOD.
THINK YOU CAN HOLD IT
LONG ENOUGH
FOR THE PROFESSIONAL
PHOTOGRAPHER NEXT WEEK?
NO, I FEEL KINDA DIZZY.
WELL, DIZZY ISN'T SEXY.
HEY, ANY IDEAS
FOR THE COVER?
JENNA:
UM, I WAS THINKING CLASSIC.
PYRAMID-STYLES,
WITH ME ON TOP!
MMM! LET'S SEE
IF WE CAN GET THE SHOT.
OKAY. SO GIRLS,
WE'RE GONNA DO A PYRAMID.
UH, ANYA SECOND ROW.
HOW ARE WE DOING
FOR TIME?
ELI:
12 MINUTES.
I'M SO DEAD!
(POLICE SIREN WAILS)
COPS!
OKAY, I KNOW!
UM, WHAT DO I DO?
BIANCA:
FLOOR IT!
OKAY, I'M NOT...
I'M NOT GONNA TRY
TO OUTRUN THE COPS!
BIANCA:
GO! I CAN'T GET BUSTED
FOR UNDERAGE DRINKING AGAIN!
ALL RIGHT,
I'M GONNA PULL OVER.
EVERYONE JUST SHUT UP
AND ACT NORMAL.
ALL RIGHT?
GIRL:
OKAY, THERE.
OH YEAH,
THIS IS COOL.
(STOMACH GURGLING)
ACTUALLY,
I THINK I SHOULD GET DOWN.
SERIOUSLY, GUYS.
LOWER ME.
I HAVE TO GET DOWN,
NOW!
UH-OH.
SIDE-EFFECTS.
(FLATULENCE)
GIRLS: EW!
JENNA, THAT'S DISGUSTING!
(FLATULENCE)
GIRLS:
SO AWFUL.
WHAT WAS THAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
I HOPE SHE MAKES IT
TO THE BATHROOM.
(POLICE CHATTER OVER RADIO)
WHAT IS TAKING
SO LONG?
JUST GIVE ME THE STUPID
SPEEDING TICKET, ALREADY.
BIANCA:
WHO CARES?
IF HE FIGURES OUT I'M DRUNK,
I'M GONNA GET A RECORD!
OKAY, UM...
CAN YOU SHUT YOUR DRUNK ASS UP
FOR ONE SECOND, PLEASE?!
HEY,
IT'S GONNA BE OKAY.
NO, ACTUALLY IT WON'T!
YOU'LL GET OUT OF THIS.
NO, I WON'T.
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT THIS COOL GUY
WHO JUST GETS OUTTA STUFF
LIKE YOU GUYS THINK.
I'M A LOSER. I SUCK!
I'M JUST,
I'M SITTING HERE,
I'M WAITING
FOR A SPEEDING TICKET
FOR WHICH MY PARENTS
ARE GONNA KILL ME!
FIVE-OH.
(TAPPING ON THE GLASS)
HEY.
UM, HI, OFFICER.
UH, LISTEN, I AM...
I'M REALLY SORRY.
I'M NEVER GONNA SPEED AGAIN,
UH, BUT WE...
WE NEED TO GET HOME.
OFFICER TURNER:
STEP OUT OF THE CAR, PLEASE.
THIS TRUCK'S BEEN
REPORTED STOLEN.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
MY FRIEND!
PORCELINA:
(OINKING)
(KNOCKING AT THE DOOR)
HOLLY J:
FIONA, ARE YOU HOME?
HEY, UH, I KNOW YOU SAID
YOU DIDN'T WANNA WORK TOGETHER,
I JUST THOUGHT THAT...
WHOA! DID I MISS
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING
OR SOMETHING?
PORCELINA:
(OINKING)
PORCELINA AND I WERE
JUST PLAYING.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
THAT PIG IS A MENACE.
HEY, WE'LL CLEAN IT UP.
IT'S OKAY.
YEAH, UNTIL YOU GET
BUSY AGAIN!
I'M SORRY.
I SHOULD'VE BEEN HERE
FOR YOU,
AND I WILL CLEAR
MY SCHEDULE.
REALLY?
AND ONCE WE'RE DONE
CLEANING UP,
WE CAN RETURN PORCELINA
AND USE THE MONEY TO GO
SHOPPING OR SOMETHING.
MY TREAT!
FIONA, DON'T YOU REALIZE
WHAT YOU'RE DOING?
YOU'RE PAYING ME
TO HANG OUT WITH YOU.
(SIGHS) DR. SANDLER WAS RIGHT.
I CAN'T BE ALONE.
YEAH, YOU REALIZE
I'M NOT JUST YOU'RE FRIEND
BECAUSE OF THE...
THE MONEY, RIGHT?
YEAH, I KNOW,
BUT IT DOESN'T MEAN
YOU HAVE TO BE HERE
ALL THE TIME EITHER.
I NEED TO LEARN
TO BE BY MYSELF
AND TO OPEN UP TO DR. SANDLER
A LITTLE MORE.
SO, IF YOU'RE TOO BUSY,
GO.
RUN FREE.
I'LL BE OKAY.
PORCELINA:
(OINKING)
WELL, HEY,
SOMEBODY'S GOTTA STAY
AND HELP YOU CATCH THAT PIG,
RIGHT?
(PORCELINA SQUEALS)
(SIGHS) YEAH.
(BOTH LAUGH)
♪ And how ♪
♪ Without knowing ♪
THANKS FOR GETTING
THESE FOR ME.
DON'T LAUGH.
MY PANTS LOOK
KINDA HOT ON YOU.
KC!
I'M IN CRISIS MODE HERE!
I STILL DON'T GET
WHAT HAPPENED.
IT WAS DIET-TYPE PILLS
WITH GROSS SIDE EFFECTS
THAT HAPPENED TO ME,
IN FRONT OF THE ENTIRE
POWER SQUAD.
WHY WERE YOU
TAKING PILLS?
I WANTED TO FIT MY UNIFORM
FOR THE CALENDAR.
I DIDN'T WANT TO BE
FAT ANYMORE.
WHO THINKS YOU'RE FAT?
ME. THE GIRLS.
EVERYONE. EVEN YOU.
YOU KEEP JOKING
ABOUT IT.
ME?
I LOVE YOUR BODY.
YOU HAVE TO SAY THAT.
I LOVE YOUR FINGERS.
YOUR PALMS.
I LOVE YOUR ARMS.
YOUR SEXY SHOULDERS,
YOUR NECK...
MR. BHANDARI:
MAKING US TAKE TAXIS
ALL OVER CREATION
TO PICK YOU UP FROM THE POLICE?
THEN I HAD TO SPEND ONE HOUR
TO CLEAN UP YOUR MESS!
OBVIOUSLY, YOU'RE GROUNDED.
TWO MONTHS
AND YOU'LL PAY THE FINE.
BUT... WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
I WASN'T, I GUESS.
I JUST THOUGHT
I DESERVED TO HAVE SOME FUN.
DID WE DESERVE TO COME OUT
OF THAT THEATRE
TO AN EMPTY PARKING SPACE,
THINKING MY BRAND NEW TRUCK
HAD BEEN STOLEN?
NO, SIR.
DID OTHER MOTORISTS DESERVE
TO HAVE THEIR LIVES RISKED
SO THAT YOU COULD SPEED HOME
FROM A CONCERT
YOU WERE NOT EVEN ALLOWED
TO GO TO?
NO, SIR.
THEN WHY DID YOU DO THIS?
BECAUSE YOU MAKE MY LIFE
SO HARD.
IS IT HARD TO LIVE
IN A NICE HOUSE,
WITH NOTHING BUT OPPORTUNITY?
NO, BUT...
YOU HAVE THIS, LIKE,
THIS PERFECT IMAGE OF ME.
WE ARE NOT ASKING YOU
TO BE PERFECT!
YEAH,
NOT IN THAT MANY WORDS!
BUT I HAVE TO SACRIFICE
ALL THESE THINGS -
THE LOVE OF MY LIFE,
MUSIC, FRIENDS -
JUST TO LIVE UP
TO YOUR UNREALISTIC
EXPECTATIONS!
LOOK, I'M SORRY.
SOMETIMES I MESS UP.
BUT I WILL EARN
YOUR TRUST AGAIN.
I HOPE SO.
BECAUSE DEEP DOWN,
I KNOW YOU'RE A GOOD PERSON.
VERY DEEP DOWN.
ALLI:
THE PARENTALS WENT NUCLEAR
ON MY BROTHER LAST NIGHT.
I THINK I COULD GET CAUGHT
WITH DREW IN MY ROOM, NAKED,
AND STILL BE
THE GOOD KID!
(CHUCKLES)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
EATING NORMAL FOOD
AND NOT WORRYING ABOUT IT!
YOU CALL DIPPING YOUR BANANA
IN RANCH DRESSING NORMAL?
IT'S WHAT I FELT LIKE.
SURE YOU DON'T WANNA
EAT WITH THEM?
NO.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
I HEARD ABOUT
YOUR PYRAMID INCIDENT.
JEEZ,
DOES EVERYONE KNOW?
NOT EVERYONE.
WELL, PROBABLY NOT.
I GUESS IT WAS
THE DIET PILLS?
COME ON!
YOU HEARD THAT TOO?
SO YOU REALLY HAD
THE, UM, SIDE EFFECTS?
EVEN...?
ANAL LEAKAGE?
IF YOUR BODY CAN'T ABSORB FAT,
IT HAS TO GO SOMEWHERE.
THEY'RE GONNA CALL ME "SQUIRT"
FOR THE NEXT TWO MONTHS!
OKAY! LA-LA-LA-LA!
I'M EATING.
ON THE BRIGHT SIDE,
I FOUND ANOTHER WAY
TO FIT INTO MY UNIFORM
FOR THE SHOOT NEXT WEEK.
JENNA, COME ON.
DIETS ARE SCARY.
I ASKED ANYA TO ORDER ME
A LARGER SIZE.
REALLY?
WOW, JENNA.
YOU'RE A REAL TRAILBLAZER.
YES, I AM.
AND SPEAKING OF...
YOU SURE YOU DON'T WANNA
TRY SOME?
IT'S DELICIOUS!
I'M GOOD.
♪ All of the traces of dust ♪
♪ Gone,
oh now we're gone ♪
♪ I have been replaced ♪
♪ All of the watch hands
are frozen in place ♪
HEY, DEAD MAN WALKING.
SO HOW GROUNDED
ARE YOU?
TWO MONTHS.
I'M ONLY ALLOWED OUT FOR SCHOOL
AND STUDENT COUNCIL.
ADAM:
SURPRISED IT'S NOT SIX.
SORRY FOR RUINING
YOUR NIGHT.
ELI:
RUINING?
DUDE,
LAST NIGHT WAS EPIC!
THE BAND, THE COPS,
BIANCA GETTING BUSTED...
OH, MAN.
UH, I LEARNED THE BASS PART
FOR "YOUR PAISLEY JACKET."
UH, THOUGHT WE COULD JAM
SOMETIME.
OH, MAN,
WELL THAT'D BE RAD, BUT-
YOU COULD TELL YOUR DAD
YOU'VE GOT AN EMERGENCY
COUNCIL MEETING.
UH.. IT'S TEMPTING,
BUT UH...
I THINK I'M GONNA STICK
TO THE TRUTH FOR A WHILE.
PROBABLY A GOOD IDEA.
HEY, SAV?
YOU'RE, UH, KIND OF OUR HERO.
SHUT UP.
The Dead Hand:
♪ I see your pattern ♪
♪ And I can match it ♪
♪ Just trace the lines on
your paisley jacket ♪