♪♪♪
♪ Little Sally Moore ♪
♪ Sitting on the floor ♪
♪ Fly Sally fly ♪
♪ Wipe out your eye ♪
(CAR DOORS SLAM)
(CLARE SIGHS)
ELI:
GOTHIC TALES SUBMISSION
DEADLINE'S FRIDAY.
THAT GIVES ME LESS
THAN A WEEK
TO TURN MY BRAIN DUMP
INTO A STORY.
CLARE:
CLEAR YOUR SCHEDULE,
ELIMINATE DISTRACTIONS.
LIKE GIVING DRIVING LESSONS?
OKAY, ONE DISTRACTION.
YOUR SERVICES
AS DRIVING INSTRUCTOR
IN EXCHANGE FOR
MY EDITING SKILLS?
FAIR ENOUGH?
WHAT WOULD I DO
WITHOUT MY MUSE?
CLARE:
OH, YOU'D BE SAD
AND LONELY,
AND YOU'D HAVE NO ONE
TO DRIVE YOU TO SCHOOL.
HMM.
ELI:
(LAUGHS)
DON'T GET TOO COCKY.
MORTY'S AN ANTIQUE HEARSE.
REMEMBER WHAT WE TALKED ABOUT:
TIMING, AGILITY,
COORDINATION.
ALL SKILLS I HAPPEN TO HAVE.
YOU DON'T KNOW MORTY,
HE'S SENSITIVE.
(SCOFFS)
(ENGINE COUGHS,
TURNS OVER)
ELI:
EASY ON THE GAS.
THE SLOWER WE GO
THE LESS CHANCE WE HAVE
OF GETTING INTO AN ACCIDENT.
I JUST DON'T WANT YOU
TO GET HURT.
I PROMISE I'LL BE CAREFUL,
GRAMPS.
'KAY,
FOOT ON THE BRAKE,
PUT IT IN DRIVE.
(GEARSHIFT CLICKS)
ELI:
CHECK YOUR BLIND SPOTS
AND GENTLY HIT THE GAS.
(ENGINE REVS)
(BRAKES SCREECH)
CLARE: FITZ?
ELI: WHAT?!
ELI.
BEEN LOOKING FOR YOU GUYS.
ELI:
LET'S GO, LET'S GO!
FITZ:
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU GUYS!
(TIRES SCREECH)
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever! Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(TRUCK RUMBLES)
SAV:
LAST STOP
ON THE LIBRARY SHUTTLE.
THANKS FOR THE LIFT.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
YOU GET THE CAR,
AND I GET LIBRARY LOCKDOWN.
IT COULD BE WORSE.
MOM AND DAD COULD BE
MAKING YOU SPEND
YOUR WEEK OF SUSPENSION
WITH THEM.
YEAH, THAT WOULD BE WORSE.
THEIR COLD, ANGRY EYES
WATCHING MY EVERY MOVE.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
SOMEDAY THEY'LL FORGIVE YOU.
I'LL PROBABLY SCREW UP,
AND YOU'LL BE
GIVING ME RIDES.
IT'S NICE HAVING YOU
IN MY CORNER.
YEAH.
I'LL PICK YOU UP AT FIVE?
NO, SERIOUSLY.
THANK YOU.
THESE PAST FEW WEEKS
HAVE BEEN ROUGH.
I KNOW.
SO, WE'LL MEET
BACK HERE AT FIVE?
EVER SINCE WHAT HAPPENED
WITH DREW...
RIGHT. WELL,
SOMETIMES...
RELATIONSHIPS
DON'T WORK OUT.
ESPECIALLY WHEN
HE CHEATS ON YOU
WITH THE SCHOOL SKANK.
WELL, MAYBE IT WAS
FOR THE BEST.
GOD, WHAT COULD I HAVE SEEN
IN THAT JERK?
(CLEARS THROAT)
ALLI!
UM, MAYBE IT'S TIME TO...
FORGET ABOUT DREW
AND MOVE ON.
UH, AND ALSO,
I'M GONNA BE LATE.
OH, SORRY.
TANGENT.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
SAY "HI" TO DEGRASSI
FOR ME.
(ALLI SIGHS)
(DOOR SLAMS)
CLARE:
HOW IS FITZ
OUT OF JUVIE ALREADY?
YOU DON'T THINK
HE ESCAPED?
THIS IS FITZ,
NOT DAVID BLAINE.
MUST'VE BEEN
LET OUT EARLY.
WHY WAS HE TRYING
TO TALK TO US?
LAST TIME I SAW HIM,
HE PULLED A KNIFE ON ME.
MAYBE HE WANTS
TO SETTLE THE SCORE.
THEY WOULDN'T LET FITZ OUT
IF HE WAS SERIOUSLY DANGEROUS,
RIGHT?
(DRUM MACHINE PLAYS)
(SAV PLAYS FAST ROCK)
IS THAT THE TRACK
YOU'RE SENDING IN
FOR YOUR UNIVERSITY
APPLICATION?
I'M JUST BEING HONEST.
LOOK, I KNOW IT SUCKS,
OKAY?
OKAY,
TAKE A DEEP BREATH.
IT'S NOTHING A LITTLE
PRACTICE CAN'T HELP.
NO, I NEED TO NAIL THIS!
THIS MUSIC SUPPLEMENT IS HEARD
BY A WHOLE PANEL OF PROFESSORS
WHO ARE GOING
TO DECIDE MY FATE!
IF I DON'T GET
INTO THIS PROGRAM,
IT'S OFF TO ENGINEERING
FOR ME.
I'VE GOTTA SHOW MY DAD
THAT A MUSIC MAJOR
IS NOT A WASTE OF TIME.
YOU CAN JUST WRITE
A NEW SONG.
NO!
THE SONG IS GREAT,
IT'S THE TRACK.
IT NEEDS A MOTOR.
I SO NEED A DRUMMER!
WELL, MAYBE NICK JONAS JUST
TRANSFERRED TO DEGRASSI!
SERIOUSLY.
WHAT IF I HOLD
AUDITIONS?
LIKE...
FIVE MINUTES AGO?
I LIKE YOUR HUSTLE, BOY.
YEAH, THIS DEMO
IS MY SHOT
AT GETTING INTO A KICKASS
MUSIC CONSERVATORY.
IT'S MY DREAM.
I NEED THIS!
SAV: (OVER PA)
PRESIDENT SAV HERE,
IN NEED OF A LADY
OR GENT
WHO CAN ROCK THE DRUMS.
AUDITIONS TODAY.
TODAY'S A GOOD DAY!
LUNCH LADY ROSE COOKED UP
HER SPECIAL MAC AND CHEESE!
KC, YOU PROMISED ME
CHICKEN FROM DIPALMA'S.
OH. WELL, I CAN'T MAKE IT
TO DIPALMA'S AND BACK
IN TIME FOR CLASS.
ALL RIGHT, WHAT ELSE
CAN WE GET YOU TO EAT?
WELL, OUR PRENATAL CLASS
TEACHER BLAIR BONGARD
TOLD ME THAT PREGNANT
FOOD CRAVINGS
ARE CAUSED BY
A NUTRITIONAL DEFICIENCY.
I-I THOUGHT YOU
JUST LIKED CHICKEN.
CHICKEN IS RICH
IN NIACIN B3.
SO, HERE ARE SOME
B3 ALTERNATIVES:
CHINOOK SALMON,
VENISON,
CALF'S LIVER,
SARDINES,
CRIMINI MUSHROOMS.
DO YOU THINK ROSE
EVEN KNOWS
WHAT A CRIMINI MUSHROOM
LOOKS LIKE?
THERE'S GOTTA BE
SOME ALTERNATIVES
TO THE ALTERNATIVES.
J!
YOU ARE WAY TOO WOUND UP
RIGHT NOW.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
A HEART ATTACK
BEFORE THE FOURTH
TRIMESTER!
NO, THERE ARE ONLY
THREE TRIMESTERS, KC!
WELL, JEEZ,
WE'D BETTER CRAM IN
AS MUCH PRE-BABY FUN
AS POSSIBLE.
CHECK IT!
HIS AND HERS BOARDS!
WHAT?
I'M GONNA TEACH YOU
HOW TO GRIND RAILS!
NO! I'M LIKE 200 MONTHS
PREGNANT RIGHT NOW!
WHAT IF I FELL?
I JUST THOUGHT YOU NEEDED
TO GET AWAY
FROM THE BABY BOOKS
AND CHILL.
I WAS JUST TRYING TO HELP.
(SIGHS)
YOU KNOW WHAT WOULD HELP?
WE HAVE A BIG PRENATAL
CLASS TOMORROW
AND A TON OF READING
TO DO TONIGHT.
SO... READ UP,
BIG DADDY.
OKAY.
AND AFTER SCHOOL
I'LL GET THAT CHICKEN FOR YOU.
NOW WE'RE TALKING.
(DRUM ROLL)
I'M GONNA ROCK!
YEAH! WHOO!
YEAH! WOO HOO!
YEAH!
WHOOO!
(DRUMS BANG RANDOMLY)
(DRUMSTICK CLATTERS)
(GUY MAKES BEAT-BOX SOUNDS)
S-STOP, PLEASE.
THANKS.
UH, N-NO.
PLEASE DON'T TOUCH ME.
(EXASPERATED SIGH)
DREW:
HEY, DUDE.
HEY, DREW.
YOU CAN HAVE THE ROOM.
I'M DONE FOR TODAY.
AW, YOU CAN'T BE DONE.
YOU STILL HAVE ONE MORE
DRUMMER TO AUDITION.
HAVE STICKS,
WILL ROCK!
U-UNLESS YOU FOUND
SOMEONE ALREADY.
NO, UH...
BUT, MAN, I-I CAN'T.
AND ALLI WOULD KILL ME...
AND THEN YOU.
RIGHT. UH...
YEAH, THAT'S COOL.
IT'S JUST I'M TRYING
TO MOVE ON,
AND I NEED THIS...
AND I THINK YOU NEED ME.
(HALF LAUGHS)
I JUST NEED SOMEONE
WHO CAN CARRY A BEAT.
(SIGHS)
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S HEAR WHAT YOU GOT.
(DRUMS BANG RHYTHMICALLY)
(CYMBAL CRASHES)
CRAP, HE'S GOOD.
(LAUGHS)
FITZ:
DON'T BE SCARED.
CLARE:
YOU SHOULDN'T BE HERE!
I'M GONNA GET MR. SIMPSON!
CLARE, WAIT,
I JUST NEED A SECOND.
YOU'RE GONNA BE IN TROUBLE
FOR EVEN STEPPING
ON SCHOOL GROUNDS.
DON'T YOU REMEMBER
WHAT YOU DID?
TOTALLY!
THAT'S WHY I NEED
TO TALK TO YOU.
I NEED TO MAKE
THIS RIGHT.
I NEED YOU
TO FORGIVE ME.
WHEN I WAS HERE
I WAS MESSED UP, CLARE.
I WAS LOST.
BUT WHILE I WAS AWAY,
I FOUND SOME ANSWERS.
I FOUND THE ANSWER.
I FOUND JESUS.
(CAR RUMBLES)
ELI:
TIME FOR YOUR NEXT LESSON!
(GEARSHIFT CLUNKS,
ENGINE HUMS)
LET'S PRACTICE
GOING BACKWARDS.
FOOT ON THE BRAKE,
PUT IT IN REVERSE.
CLARE?
ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT?
I SAW FITZ.
WHAT? WHEN?
JUST BEFORE
YOU GOT HERE.
I-I TALKED TO HIM.
WHEN HE WAS LOCKED UP...
HE FOUND GOD.
AND YOU BELIEVE
THAT CRAP?
FITZ KNOWS YOU, CLARE;
HE KNOWS YOUR WEAKNESS!
AND WHAT IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
IT'S HIS ANGLE,
THE WHOLE JESUS THING.
THE "FORGIVE ME, LORD,
FOR I HAVE SINNED" THING.
HE'S DANGEROUS,
REMEMBER?
HE PULLED A KNIFE
ON ME!
I THINK THERE'S MORE TO IT
THAN THAT.
DAMMIT, CLARE,
YOU'RE MAKING IT
SO HARD FOR ME
TO DO MY JOB!
YOUR JOB?
AS YOUR BOYFRIEND,
MY JOB IS TO PROTECT YOU!
I NEVER ASKED YOU
TO DO THAT.
WELL, IF NOT ME, WHO?
I'M NOT UP FOR ANOTHER
ONE OF YOUR LESSONS.
CLARE, I DIDN'T MEAN IT
LIKE THAT.
(CAR DOOR SLAMS)
(SIGHS)
WHAT ARE YOU
TYPING ABOUT?
JUST GETTING
MY JOURNAL ON.
A GIRL NEEDS AN OUTLET.
NOT HUNGRY?
AH, MY STOMACH'S ALL
KNOTTED UP.
HMM. BIG TEST
OR SOMETHING?
WELL...
YOU KNOW I'M RECORDING
A DEMO TRACK SOON.
FOR YOUR UNIVERSITY
MUSIC SUPPLEMENT,
I KNOW.
UH, WHAT YOU DON'T KNOW
IS THAT THE TRACK
IS MISSING SOMETHING:
DRUMS.
SO YOU NEED A DRUMMER?
I HAVE...
UH, ACTUALLY,
A REALLY GOOD ONE.
HEY, CONGRATS,
I HEAR THEY'RE HARD TO FIND.
UM, THE THING IS THOUGH,
THAT, UH, IT'S DREW.
(LAUGHS) YEAH,
AND WHO'S ON BASS?
VOLDEMORT?
COME ON, SAV,
YOU CANNOT MAKE JOKES
LIKE THAT.
HE'S REALLY GOOD,
ALLI.
I WOULDN'T EVEN CONSIDER HIM
IF HE WASN'T.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME
TO SAY, SAV?
YOU KNOW THAT THE REASON
MY LIFE IS A LIVING HELL
IS BECAUSE OF DREW!
ARE YOU SURE THAT
IT'S NOT BECAUSE MOM AND DAD
SAW YOUR FILE?
OR BECAUSE THEY THINK
YOU WERE SMOKING?
IT ALL TRACES BACK!
THE DAY I MET DREW
WAS THE DAY THIS ALL STARTED!
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL ASK
THE HEAVY METAL DUDE.
FORGET I EVEN
BROUGHT DREW UP.
DO YOU NEED A RIDE
TO THE LIBRARY?
IT'S BETTER
THAN TAKING THE BUS.
(SIGHS)
MORNING, CLARE.
HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
KEEPING A LOOKOUT.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
LIFE IS SO CRUEL.
YOU KNOW,
YOU FIND A GREAT DRUMMER,
BUT THEN YOU CAN'T
HAVE HIM
BECAUSE OF YOUR
SISTER'S BAGGAGE.
SHE HAS A REASON
TO BE MAD AT DREW.
I KNOW, BUT...
JUST GET OVER IT!
ALLI HAS NEVER MET A GRUDGE
SHE WON'T HOLD.
SAV.
I KNOW, I KNOW,
POOR ALLI.
I'M CALLING
THE HEAVY METAL DUDE
RIGHT NOW TO TELL HIM
THE GOOD NEWS.
IS HEAVY METAL DUDE
REALLY THAT BAD?
HONESTLY,
HE WAS TERRIBLE.
IN FACT,
THEY WERE ALL TERRIBLE,
EXCEPT FOR DREW.
CAN'T YOU PROGRAM DRUMS?
FOR MY LIVE MUSIC
RECORDING DEMO?
OKAY, YEAH.
SORRY.
(SIGHS)
YOU KNOW,
MY FUTURE IS RIDING ON THIS.
(COINS CLINK)
WHAT ALLI DOESN'T KNOW
WON'T HURT HER.
(PHONE BUTTONS CLICK)
HEY, DREW.
UH, IT'S SAV HERE.
LISTEN, I'VE GOT
SOME GOOD NEWS!
ALL RIGHT?
CALL ME BACK.
♪♪♪
JENNA:
SO?
DID YOUR BABY HOMEWORK?
TOTES.
REALLY?
WELL, DEFINTE...
CRADLE CAP.
A BABY'S HEAD IS SOFT,
SO THE CRADLE IS EQUIPPED
WITH A PROTECTIVE HELMET.
AM I EVEN CLOSE?
NO.
YOU SAID
YOU WANTED TO HELP.
I'VE GOT THE BASICS.
I NEED MORE THAN
THE BASICS FROM YOU!
JENNA,
YOU GOTTA CHILL.
LET THE GAME COME TO YOU,
YOU KNOW?
WHAT I KNOW IS THAT
WE HAVE OUR FINAL
PRENATAL CLASS TODAY,
AND IF YOU'RE NOT READY...
I'M READY.
(BELL RINGS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
THANK YOU!
CLARE:
ELI IS A LOT OF THINGS.
HE'S SWEET, CUTE,
FUNNY AND TALENTED...
HE'S DREAMY ALL RIGHT.
BUT THEN HE'S ALSO
WEIRDLY POSSESSIVE
AND OVER-PROTECTIVE.
AS IN, HE'S A GUY.
BEHIND THE FACE
OF EVEN THE SWEETEST,
MOST EMO GUY
IN THE WORLD,
LURKS A CAVEMAN.
PROTECTING YOU
IS LIKE...
HIS WAY OF SAYING HE CARES,
OR WHATEVER.
WELL, I WISH HE'D JUST
WRITE ME A POEM INSTEAD!
WHEN HE GETS ALL
SUPER PROTECTIVE,
I FEEL LIKE I CAN'T BREATHE.
ELI CAN BE...
OVERWHELMING.
BUT HE'S WORTH IT.
HE'S HERE?
ELI?
NO, FITZ!
FITZ IS HERE!
HE'S WORKING HERE?
SINCE WHEN?
SINCE THEY INSTITUTED
A NEW POLICY
TO HIRE KNOWN PSYCHOS?
WE DRINK OUR LATTES
SOMEWHERE ELSE FROM NOW ON.
NO!
NO, THIS IS OUR SPOT.
WE BELONG HERE,
NOT HIM.
COME ON,
I'VE GOTTA GET HOME ANYWAY.
NOT ME,
I'M STAYING.
(DOOR CLOSES)
BLAIR BONGARD:
MANY PARENTS DREAD DIAPERING.
BUT WITH MY METHOD,
WE SEE IT AS PRICELESS,
PRECIOUS BONDING TIME.
NOW, WHO'S GOING
TO WOW ME
WITH THEIR DIAPER SKILLS?
I'LL GIVE IT A TRY.
OKAY.
UH... DON'T YOU THINK
I BETTER DO THAT?
WHY DON'T WE BOTH DO IT?
HUH?
MAKE IT INTERESTING.
LIKE A LITTLE RACE?
(SIGHS) OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
1, 2, 3...
DIAPER!
♪♪♪
♪ Well, come out ♪
♪ For a night
on the town tonight ♪
♪ Come on stomp ♪
KC:
BIG DADDY WINS!
BLAIR BONGARD:
WELL DONE, KC!
KEEP AT IT, JENNA.
YOU'LL GET
THE HANG OF IT.
(LAUGHS)
WOMAN:
NICE ONE!
HEY, IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
IT'S JUST A DIAPER.
NO BIG DEAL?
(SNIFFLES)
I'M GONNA BE
A TERRIBLE MOM!
OH, PREGNANCY HORMONES
ARE A KILLER.
ALL I DO IS STUDY
AND STUDY,
AND I CAN'T GET
ANYTHING RIGHT.
YOU KNOW,
THERE'S SOMEONE IN HERE;
SOMEONE WHO NEEDS ME
TO BE READY.
I KNOW WHAT YOU NEED.
PRACTICE!
I HAVE A SIX-YEAR-OLD
WHO WOULD LOVE SOMEONE
TO TAKE HIM
TO THE PARK TOMORROW.
INTERESTED?
YEAH, VERY!
BLAIR BONGARD:
GREAT.
DID YOU JUST VOLUNTEER US
FOR BABYSITTING?
WE'RE GONNA NEED
ORGANIC FRUIT SNACKS,
NATURAL BUG SPRAY...
ARE WE BABYSITTING
"BUBBLE BOY"?
I REALLY DON'T WANT
TO SCREW THIS UP.
BUT IT'S GONNA BE
SUPER FUN!
YAY.
(LAUGHS)
(METRONOME TAPS)
(DRUMS BANG RHYTHMICALLY)
(SAV PLAYS FAST ROCK)
(SONG SLOWS TEMPO)
WHOA, WHOA, DUDE!
CUT IT, CUT IT,
LIKE WE GOTTA WRAP
THE GEAR.
I'M LATE FOR PICKING UP
MY SISTER.
OKAY.
YEAH, SURE.
SO HOW WAS MY DRUMMING?
DUDE, THAT WAS SICK!
DREW:
I WAS JUST ROLLING WITH
WHATEVER YOU WERE GIVING ME.
LOOK AT YOU TWO.
SO CUTE.
LET ME SEE
YOUR ROCKSTAR POUTS.
(CAMERA SHUTTER SNAPS)
(GASPS)
UM... YOU BETTER
LOOK BEHIND YOU.
SAV:
ALLI!
UH, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO PICK ME UP
FROM THE LIBRARY.
HEY, ALLI.
DRUMMING WITH THE ENEMY,
SAV?
SAV:
ALLI!
♪♪♪
WHY HERE?
I NEEDED A JOB.
WHERE YOU KNOW YOU'LL RUN
INTO CERTAIN PEOPLE
YOU SHOULDN'T BE
RUNNING INTO?
FATHER GREG HAS
A WORK PLACEMENT PROGRAM.
HE PLACED ME HERE
TO BE CLOSE TO HOME.
FATHER GREG?
THE CHAPLAIN AT JUVIE.
HE SAW HOW SCREWED UP
I WAS
AND HE SHOWED ME
ANOTHER WAY.
LOOK, I'M GLAD
YOU'VE FOUND GOD,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
YOU HAVE TO TALK TO ME.
FOR THE RECORD,
YOU'RE THE ONE TALKING
TO ME RIGHT NOW.
JUST KEEP YOUR DISTANCE
FROM ME AND ELI.
I'M SERIOUS.
I'M SORRY.
OKAY.
NO! I MEAN...
I'M SORRY.
WHAT I DID AT THE DANCE...
I NEVER MEANT
TO HURT ELI,
I JUST WANTED
TO SCARE HIM.
I FELT HE ASKED FOR IT.
AN EYE FOR AN EYE?
BUT IT WAS WRONG.
IS THERE ANY WAY
YOU CAN FORGIVE ME?
OKAY. I GUESS.
I FORGIVE YOU.
(SIGH OF RELIEF)
THANK YOU.
LOOK, FATHER GREGORY SAID
I NEED TO MAKE THIS RIGHT
NOT JUST WITH YOU,
BUT WITH ELI.
GOOD LUCK.
I CAN TRY...
WITH YOUR HELP?
IF YOU CAN FORGIVE ME,
MAYBE ELI CAN TOO?
DON'T YOU THINK THAT
WOULD BE LIKE
REALLY GOOD FOR HIM?
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
I GUESS I COULD TRY
TO TALK TO ELI,
BUT NO PROMISES.
I KNOW.
THANKS, CLARE.
ELI:
GET AWAY FROM HER!
ELI, CHILL.
BACK OFF,
I'M SERIOUS!
OKAY, I'M GOING.
YOU OKAY?
YES, I'M FINE!
FITZ WORKS HERE.
WE WERE JUST TALKING
FOR A MINUTE.
ABOUT WHAT?
TELL ME!
LOOK, MAN,
I JUST WANTED TO TELL
YOU AND CLARE...
I'M SORRY.
WHATEVER.
FITZ APOLOGIZES
AND THAT'S ALL YOU CAN SAY?
CLARE, I HAVE NOTHING
TO SAY TO HIM.
ARE YOU COMING WITH ME
OR NOT?
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S GO.
MRS. BHANDARI:
ONCE YOU'VE CLEARED
THE TABLE,
STRAIGHT TO HOMEWORK!
YOUR FATHER AND I WILL BE BACK
AFTER THE PLAY.
(HORN HONKS)
MRS. BHANDARI:
I'M COMING!
ALLI, ARE YOU EVER GONNA
TALK TO ME?
(SIGHS)
YOU WERE NEVER SUPPOSED
TO FIND OUT ABOUT DREW.
SO THAT MAKES IT OKAY?
I'M GOING TO MY ROOM.
NO, ALLI...
I ALWAYS TRY
TO HELP YOU.
BUT AS SOON AS
I NEED SOMETHING,
YOU CAN'T CUT ME
ANY SLACK?
IT'S A ONE WAY STREET
WITH YOU,
AND I'M SICK OF IT!
EXCUSE ME?
SINCE WHEN DO YOU NEED
MY HELP WITH ANYTHING?
SAV, YOU ALWAYS GET
WHAT YOU WANT!
ALWAYS!
PREDICTABLE.
NO, LET ME ASK YOU
SOMETHING:
HOW WAS I SUPPOSED TO TAKE
THIS SLAP IN THE FACE?
THE GUY WHO MADE MY LIFE
A LIVING HELL IS YOUR DRUMMER!
NO, ALLI!
YOU MADE YOUR OWN LIFE
A LIVING HELL!
DREW DIDN'T FORCE YOU
TO DATE JOHNNY,
OR TO SEXT,
OR TO LEAD YOUR SEX-CRAZED
DOUBLE LIFE!
THAT WAS YOU!
AND FROM THE MOMENT
YOU'VE COME TO DEGRASSI,
YOU'VE MADE MY LIFE
A LIVING HELL!
I AM SICK AND TIRED
OF YOUR BEING STUPID
AND SELFISH!
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
THE ONE PERSON
I COULD COUNT ON.
TURNS OUT YOU'RE JUST LIKE
EVERYONE ELSE!
ALLI!