CHANTAY:
LAST CHANCE TO SEND
A FRIEND
A POWER SQUAD WISHING STAR!
SO, I WAS THINKING.
SINCE I'M PREGNANT MAYBE
MY PHEROMONES ARE ENHANCED,
OR SOMETHING.
HOLLY J DOESN'T STAND A CHANCE.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW HOLLY J
AND SAV WERE TOGETHER,
AND I KNOW EVERYTHING.
I'M LOSING MY TOUCH!
THERE'S A REASON
THEY'RE NOT TELLING ANYONE.
OH, IS THERE NOW?
JENNA:
THEY'RE NOT IN LOVE.
CHECK OUT THEIR BODY LANGUAGE.
HOW ARE YOU SO SURE
HE'S INTERESTED IN YOU?
I HAVE A SIXTH SENSE
WITH THESE KIND OF THINGS.
A SIXTH SENSE
AIN'T GONNA CUT IT.
AND I HAVE PROOF.
WE KISSED!
AND HE LIKED IT.
SECRET PARTY,
SPREAD THE WORD.
FLOAT AWAY WITH
YOUR SECRET CRUSH!
TIME AND LOCATION
TO BE REVEALED,
TEXT 555 FOR DEETS!
COOL! (LAUGHS)
GUESS WHO'S GONNA
BE MY DATE?
KC:
HEY, JENNA.
SO...
I FEEL REALLY BAD ABOUT
BAILING ON BABY CLASS.
SO I WANNA COME WITH YOU
NEXT TIME.
I DON'T NEED YOU TO.
SAV'S COMING WITH ME.
WHAT?
HE CAME WITH ME
LAST TIME,
AFTER YOU DITCHED ME!
JENNA,
HE'S NOT THE DAD.
I AM.
BIOLOGICALLY,
BUT YOU'RE NOT DOING
A VERY GOOD JOB
OF ACTING LIKE ONE.
SAV'S DONE MORE IN A DAY
THAN YOU'VE DONE
SINCE YOU GOT ME PREGNANT!
FINE.
I JUST WANTED TO TRY.
BUY A WISHING STAR!
GOOD CAUSE?
WHOO...
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, whatever ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
HOLLY J:
REMINDER. CELL PHONE USE
IS NOW ALLOWED
DURING LUNCH PERIODS.
EXCITEMENT!
SO, DO YOU THINK
YOU'LL GO?
ANY EXCUSE
TO SHOWCASE COUTURE.
SO WHERE DO I RSVP?
WITH ME.
YOU'RE BEHIND THIS?
INSPIRED BY YOUR
NEW YORK PARTY.
UH...
YOU DIDN'T DO THIS
FOR ME, DID YOU?
YEAH, KINDA.
AND FOR THE PARTY DEPRIVED
CITIZENS OF DEGRASSI,
OF COURSE.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY.
WELL, SPEECHLESS
IS A GOOD THING, RIGHT?
I'LL SEE YOU THERE.
WESLEY:
SO, MY DATE PLAN
WITH ANYA JUST GOT AMPED!
I'M GONNA TAKE HER
TO THE SECRET PARTY!
YOU ALSO PLANNING TO BRING
A BACKUP PAIR UNDEROOS?
I WON'T NEED IT.
I GOT THIS.
HAPPILY EVER LASTER
PUTS ME IN CONTROL
OF "THE SITUATION."
(LAUGHS)
WELL, HEY THERE,
PRENATAL CLASS PARTNER!
I GOT YOUR TEXT.
I'M GLAD YOU CAME!
I WAS WORRIED
YOU WERE AVOIDING ME.
YEAH, UM...
THERE'S SOMETHING
WE SHOULD TALK ABOUT.
SAV, YOU DON'T NEED
TO SAY IT.
I KNOW ALL ABOUT HOLLY J.
I ALREADY TALKED TO HER.
(GASPS)
A-ABOUT WHAT?
I TOLD HER WE'RE GOING
TO BE TOGETHER.
UM, JENNA.
I AM NOT INTO YOU
LIKE THAT.
VERY FUNNY.
OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD!
THEN...
THEN WHY DID YOU INVITE ME
TO JOIN YOUR BAND?
AND-AND SEND ME
A WISHING STAR,
AND COME WITH ME
TO MY PRENATAL CLASS?
AND YOU EVEN SAID
WE HAD A STRONG CONNECTION!
YOU KISSED ME!
ONE DISCREPANCY.
YOU ACTUALLY KISSED ME.
AND YOU EVEN SAID
YOU WANTED TO BE A DAD,
WHEN ANYA GOT PREGNANT!
NO, JENNA,
THAT WAS ALL A LIE!
WHAT?!
DID THIS ALL JUST
HAPPEN IN MY HEAD?
SAV: OKAY, UH...
JENNA: AM I SEEING THINGS?
(HYPERVENTILATING)
OKAY, SIT DOWN.
OKAY, CALM DOWN.
OKAY, JUST...
CALM DOWN.
THIS RIGHT HERE
IS WHY I FELL FOR YOU!
YOU'RE TOO NICE,
AND I'M SO STUPID!
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
HERE, JUST...
HERE, HAVE SOME WATER.
YEAH.
NOW...
WHAT EXACTLY DID YOU
TELL HOLLY J?
WESLEY:
ANYA, OVER HERE!
SWEET MOTHER OF...
UH, HEY WESLEY!
(LAUGHS UNCOMFORTABLY)
YOU... YOU GOT A LIMO!
I GOT A LIMO!
(LAUGHS UNCOMFORTABLY)
WESLEY:
I-I HOPE IT'S NOT TOO MUCH.
IS IT TOO MUCH?
IT'S TOO MUCH.
IT'S, IT'S A LOT.
I MEAN, THE LAST TIME
I WAS IN A LIMO...
YOU DON'T NEED
TO KNOW THAT STORY.
UH, JUST SO WE'RE CLEAR,
ANY OTHER SURPRISES IN STORE?
I WAS GONNA TAKE YOU
FOR DINNER,
AND WELL,
THEN TO THE SECRET PARTY.
DINNER AND A PARTY
SOUNDS... GREAT.
ALL ABOARD!
(LIMO ENGINE STARTS)
(GIGGLES)
SAV:
SO I ACCIDENTALLY SENT
HER ALL THE WRONG SIGNALS,
AND SHE KISSED ME.
AND I KNOW...
THAT YOU WOULD NEVER
DO ANYTHING LIKE THIS,
LET ALONE KEEP IT FROM ME.
SO I FEEL SO GUILTY.
I WOULD NEVER DO ANYTHING
LIKE THAT, HOLLY J.
I KNOW.
NO, YOU'RE...
YOU'RE A GOOD PERSON.
(LAUGHS)
NOT LIKE ME.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHEN DECLAN VISITED,
WE...
(SIGHS)
DID YOU SLEEP WITH HIM?
IT WAS A MISTAKE.
A MASSIVE ONE.
MISTAKE SEX?
THAT DOESN'T JUST HAPPEN.
I KNEW HE WAS TRYING
TO GET YOU BACK.
SAV, I'VE BEEN FEELING
SO GUILTY.
AND YOU OBVIOUSLY STILL
HAVE FEELINGS FOR HIM.
(INDIGNANT SCOFF)
♪♪♪
ADAM: WATCH IT!
ELI: OKAY.
♪ Hummingbird is singing ♪
♪ I can hear her through
the trees ♪
WE HAVE OUR PARTY PAD!
NOT BAD.
I DEFINITELY SEE
ROMANTIC POTENTIAL.
STOP MAKING ME LOOK BAD.
YOU REALLY LIKE FIONA,
DON'T YOU?
IS IT SUPPOSED TO HURT
THIS MUCH?
OH, YEAH.
THAT'S THE GOOD STUFF,
MY FRIEND.
CLARE:
WELL, SHE'D BETTER BE WORTH
ALL THIS WORK.
GUESS I'LL FIND OUT
TONIGHT.
OKAY, WHO WANTS
TO HELP ME
RUN THIS LONG ASS
EXTENSION CORD?
I WILL.
♪ Say that it's all gone ♪
♪ Go ahead and count the days ♪
♪ Come on, come on,
Come on ♪
(PHONE BEEPS)
(JENNA GRUNTS WITH EFFORT)
SAV.
HOW DID IT GO
WITH HOLLY J?
OH, NO.
WHAT HAPPENED?
UM, WE BROKE UP.
BUT WE WERE JUST
CASUAL, SO...
IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
IT'S PROBABLY FOR THE BEST.
THEN WHY ARE YOU
SO SAD?
DO YOU LOVE HER?
I DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN FORGIVE HER.
WHAT DID SHE DO?
LET'S JUST SAY THAT
COMING SECOND
DOESN'T FEEL SO GOOD.
WELL, WHAT CAN I DO
TO FIX IT?
YOU NEED TO GET
BACK TOGETHER.
YEAH YOU'VE,
YOU'VE DONE ENOUGH...
FOR TODAY.
♪♪♪
♪ She walked with all my cds ♪
♪ She was too small
to take the big screen ♪
HOW DO I LOOK?
(LAUGHS SHYLY)
YOU LOOK LOVELY.
YOU ALWAYS LOOK LOVELY.
THANK YOU, WESLEY.
I ORDERED APPETIZERS
WHILE YOU WERE CHANGING.
I HOPE YOU DON'T MIND?
MM! NOT AT ALL!
I'M STARVING!
(BOTH LAUGH)
DEEP FRIED CHEESE STICKS
WITH RANCH DIP.
DON'T CHOKE ON IT.
UH...
SERVICE WITH A SMILE?
(BOTH LAUGH NERVOUSLY)
THESE LOOK DIVINE!
♪ That's why
you've got to know ♪
♪ I still believe in love ♪
♪ Don't you know ♪
(ECHOING, SLOW MOTION)
MMM...
YOU HAVE TO TRY
ONE OF THESE.
I DO?
(WESLEY'S HEART POUNDS)
(GASPS)
ANYA: AAH...
WESLEY: I'M SO SORRY!
YOU KNOW, DON'T WORRY.
I WILL UM...
I'LL GO TO THE BATHROOM,
AND DRY OFF.
OKAY.
(SIGHS)
I'M SO SCREWED.
(PILLS RATTLE)
(GULPS NOISILY)
KC:
WAIT UP!
(BUS ENGINE REVS)
HEY, WAIT UP!
(BUS RUMBLES)
YOU MISSED THE BUS.
SO DID YOU.
ARE YOU...
ARE YOU EMOTIONAL
BECAUSE OF YOUR...
HORMONAL CHANGES?
(SNIFFLES)
IF SAV MAKES YOU HAPPY,
THAT'S FINE.
BUT I STILL WANT
TO BE INVOLVED.
SAV LOVES HOLLY J,
AND I TRIED TO BREAK THEM UP.
I JUST KEEP ON COMING
IN BETWEEN GOOD PEOPLE.
HEY. YOU STOLE ME,
DIDN'T YOU?
YEAH,
AND THAT ENDED WELL!
DOES IT HAVE TO BE OVER?
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
I MADE A MISTAKE, JENNA.
WHEN I FOUND OUT
YOU WERE PREGNANT,
I'M NOT PROUD
OF HOW I ACTED.
BUT I LOVE YOU.
I WANT TO BE WITH YOU.
KC, I WANNA BE
WITH YOU TOO!
(JENNA SIGHS EMOTIONALLY)
I WANNA MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
HELP ME CLEAN UP MY MESS?
AND THIS IS WHY
I LOVE YOU.
(LAUGHS)
ANYA:
WELL, THAT WAS A DELICIOUS
AND SATISFYING MEAL.
(BOTH LAUGH)
WASN'T IT?
BUT UH,
THE NIGHT IS YOUNG.
ARE YOU READY
TO HIT UP THAT PARTY?
I NEED A SECOND.
OKAY, UH...
WHAT'S GOING ON?
(SIGHS)
IT WON'T GO DOWN.
WON'T GO DOWN,
W-WHAT WON'T GO...
ANYA: OH.
WESLEY: I TOOK THIS SUPPLEMENT,
AND MY HEART'S BEATING
REALLY FAST.
OH!
I'M SCARED.
UM, THEN UH, THEN LET'S
GET YOU TO A DOCTOR.
USE-USE THIS.
UM... AND UH,
LET'S GO!
(LAUGHS)
(DINERS CHATTER)
OH! (SIGHS)
WHAT NOW, JENNA?
HOLLY J,
I AM SO SORRY!
IT'S REALLY NOT
A GOOD TIME.
I TALKED TO SAV.
HE'S REALLY HURTING!
HE IS?
HE'S SAD ABOUT COMING
IN SECOND!
DO YOU KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS?
YEAH. IT MEANS HE'S BETTER
OFF WITHOUT ME.
HE TOLD ME HE LOVES YOU!
HE DID?
(PHONE BEEPS)
JENNA: OH!
OH, SECRET PARTY DETAILS.
IT'S AT AN ABANDONED CHURCH,
AND SAV'S... DJING.
S-SAV'S DJING!
YOU NEED TO GO!
TELL HIM THE TRUTH,
HE DESERVES IT.
I'M WORKING 'TIL ELEVEN.
JENNA:
SIR?
HOLLY J NEEDS THE REST
OF THE NIGHT OFF.
HOLLY J:
AH! DON'T LISTEN TO HER,
JUAN!
PREGNANT HORMONES.
JUAN,
IN THE NAME OF LOVE!
TABLE 14 ALL FINISHED?
YEAH?
THEN PUNCH OUT!
(JENNA LAUGHS HAPPILY)
JENNA: OKAY?
HOLLY J: OKAY.
(COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYS)
♪♪♪
TITO, ST. MIKE'S
HOSPITAL, PLEASE!
WAIT! WE NEED A RIDE
TO THE PARTY.
UH, BAD TIMING!
JENNA: IT'S AN EMERGENCY!
WE NEED TO GET HOLLY J
AND SAV BACK TOGETHER.
HI.
IT'S YOUR LIMO.
UH, FINE! DROP ME OFF
AT THE HOSPITAL FIRST,
THEN GO TO THE PARTY,
LET'S GO!
WHY DO YOU HAVE
A MENU ON YOUR...
ANYA AND WESLEY:
DON'T ASK.
WESLEY:
GO!
FEMALE DOCTOR:
"SUPER CHARGE YOUR SEX LIFE
WITH HAPPILYEVER-LASTER."
WHY DID YOU TAKE THIS?
FOR MORE STAMINA?
WERE YOU ENGAGED
IN SEXUAL ACTIVITY?
ANYA AND WESLEY:
NO!
WESLEY:
I-I JUST THOUGHT
I NEEDED IT
TO LAST OUR DATE.
I DON'T THINK THAT'S WHAT
THESE ARE MADE FOR.
YOU'LL BE FINE.
DRINK LOTS OF WATER, YOUR LAB
RESULTS SHOULD BE READY SOON.
ANYA, THANKS FOR
STAYING WITH ME.
WESLEY: I'M SUCH A DOOF!
ANYA: SHH-SHH-SHHH!
ANYA! HEY!
DR. CHRIS, HI!
HOW'S YOUR MOTHER?
BETTER EVERY DAY.
THANKS.
(LAUGHS FLIRTATIOUSLY)
I'LL SEE YOU
AT THE NEXT FOLLOW UP.
WESLEY:
HE SEEMS NICE.
HE'S MY MOTHER'S DOCTOR,
AND I HAVE A THING
FOR HIM.
NOW WHO'S THE DOOF.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
YOU DIDN'T THINK...
(SIGHS)
WESLEY, YOU'LL MAKE
ANOTHER GIRL
REALLY HAPPY SOME DAY.
YOU REALLY THINK SO?
I KNOW SO.
THAT WAS THE SWEETEST,
MOST WELL PLANNED DATE
I HAVE EVER BEEN ON.
(LAUGHS)
IT WAS ALMOST PERFECT!
HUH!
DO YOU MIND GRABBING
SOME COFFEES
WHILE WE WAIT
FOR THE RESULTS?
UH, SURE THING.
EXCUSE ME?
I'M FEELING A LOT BETTER.
CAN YOU ASK DR. CHRIS
IF I CAN TALK TO HIM?
(LOUD MUSIC PLAYS)
(PARTYGOERS LAUGH AND CHATTER)
♪♪♪
CLARE:
WE ACTUALLY PULLED IT OFF!
ELI:
I GUESS WE ARE THE PARTY
THROWING TYPES.
ANY FIONA SIGHTINGS?
I ANTICIPATE A GRAND
ENTRANCE ANY MINUTE NOW.
KC:
SAV.
SAV!
YOU'VE GOTTA COME WITH ME,
JENNA'S HAVING THE BABY!
WHAT?
DID YOU CALL A DOCTOR?
YES, BUT YOU DID
PRENATAL WITH HER, RIGHT?
YEAH, BUT...
OKAY, HURRY!
SHE'S IN THE LIMO.
COME ON, NOW!
SAV:
OKAY!
JENNA:
AH! AH! AH!
AAAAH! AAAAAAH!
AAH! AAH! AAH!
AAH! AAH!
UH, WHOA!
UH, YOU'RE HAVING A BABY!
NOPE, FALSE ALARM.
GOODBYE!
HOLLY J:
STAY!
PLEASE?
WOMAN ON HOSPITAL PA:
DR. FRIEDMAN, FROM PEDIATRICS.
DR. FRIEDMAN, PEDIATRICS.
ANYA:
HI, DR. CHRIS!
HAVE YOU SEEN MY FRIEND?
CURLY HAIR, GLASSES,
CAME IN WITH A BONER?
UH, HIS SYMPTOMS RELAXED,
AND HE WAS RELEASED.
(BOTH LAUGH)
AFTER HE CONVINCED ME
TO STAY PAST MY SHIFT
TO HAVE COFFEE WITH YOU.
DID HE NOW?
(ASTONISHED LAUGH)
(BOTH LAUGH)
PLEASE.
ANYA:
I HOPE YOU
LIKE COLD COFFEE.
DR. CHRIS:
I DO!
(ANYA LAUGHS)
DAVE:
SO, DATE'S OVER?
WESLEY:
YEAH. BUT ON THE UPSIDE,
I FIGURED OUT A WAY
TO SCORE
SOME SERIOUS POINTS
WITH ANYA.
SHE EVEN KISSED ME.
SERIOUS?
W-WHAT WAS IT LIKE?
A LITTLE STICKY,
SMELLED LIKE COTTON CANDY!
NICE.
(PARTYGOERS CHATTER)
(BASS THUMPS)
(PHONE RINGS)
NO ANSWER.
(SIGHS)
I KNEW IT.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
ELI:
ADAM?
I'VE GOTTA GO FIND
THE PRINCESS.
ADAM!
WHY?
WHEN I WAS WITH DECLAN,
SOMETIMES IT FELT LIKE
I WAS LIVING
IN THIS... FAIRYTALE.
YOU KNOW, PLAYING
THIS PRINCESS ROLE.
I PUT ALL THIS PRESSURE
ON MYSELF TO BE SOMEONE
I THOUGHT I HAD TO BE.
BUT WHEN I'M WITH YOU,
THERE'S NO PRESSURE
AT ALL.
(LAUGHS BITTERLY)
YEAH, THANKS.
IT TOOK MAKING A HUGE
MISTAKE TO REALIZE IT, BUT...
YOU COME FIRST RIGHT NOW.
PLEASE.
SAV?
♪♪♪
(PARTYGOERS LAUGH AND CHATTER)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
SAV:
HEY.
UM...
WHEN I HEARD YOU CHEATED,
OUR CASUAL RELATIONSHIP
DIDN'T SEEM SO CASUAL.
DO YOU THINK WE CAN GO BACK
TO THE WAY WE WERE?
I DON'T KNOW.
I MIGHT HAVE TO TEST
THAT OUT WITH A KISS.
♪ There are times
they walk from you ♪
♪ Like some passing afternoon ♪
THE STARS ARE OUT.
WHAT'S YOUR WISH?
IF I SAY IT OUT LOUD,
IT WON'T COME TRUE.
(ELI LAUGHS)
HOW CHEESY WOULD IT BE
IF I SAID THAT...
MINE ALREADY HAS?
THIS PARTY'S WHAT
EVERYONE NEEDED.
THANKS TO ADAM.
THE HERO.
I HOPE HE'S OKAY.
ADAM:
FIONA? IT'S ME AGAIN.
ADAM.
I'M-I'M OUTSIDE
YOUR BUILDING.
I TRIED TO RING,
BUT THERE WAS NO ANSWER.
MAYBE YOU'RE OUT.
I HOPE YOU'RE OKAY.
SEE YA.
♪♪♪
MAY I HAVE THIS DANCE?
(SIGHS)
EVERYONE'S STARING.
BECAUSE YOU'RE THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL GIRL HERE.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO SAY THAT.
I DON'T SAY THINGS
I DON'T MEAN.
SO...
DOES THE PREGGERS
PRINCESS LIVE
HAPPILY EVER AFTER?
I HOPE SO.
♪♪♪