♪♪♪
YOU CAN'T STAY
A LITTLE LONGER?
(CHUCKLES)
UH, HAVE YOU SEEN MY SHOE?
(LAUGHS AWKWARDLY)
YOU'RE SURE YOUR CURFEW
CAN'T BE...
YOU KNOW,
MAYBE A HALF HOUR LATER?
I ALREADY CALLED A TAXI.
MAN, THIS...
(LAUGHS)
THIS HAS BEEN
ONE AMAZING NIGHT.
I MEAN, FIRST,
YOU KNOW, THE THEATRE AWARD,
THEN WE RECONNECT.
I'M JUST SO HAPPY TO FEEL
THIS CLOSE TO YOU AGAIN.
THE CAB'S PROBABLY
DOWNSTAIRS.
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW?
YEAH.
OF COURSE.
OKAY.
(LAUGHS)
(GASPS)
(PENSIVE, SHAKY SIGH)
(HAPPY SIGH)
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever, Woo-ooh)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
FIONA:
SO, DID I MISS ANYTHING FUN
LAST NIGHT?
NO, NOT MUCH,
JUST THAT HOLLY J
AND I HOOKED UP!
WE'RE BACK TOGETHER!
OH!
I WAS INSPIRED TO MAKE US
SOME BREAKFAST, YOU HUNGRY?
FAMISHED!
SO, MY PLAN WORKED!
YOUR PLAN?
WELL, SOMEONE HAD TO GET HER
TO STAY OVER.
SO YOU GOT DRUNK
AND PASSED OUT ON PURPOSE?
I MAY HAVE EMBELLISHED
THE DRUNKENNESS A BIT.
ANYTHING TO HELP BRING
MY FUTURE SISTER-IN-LAW
BACK INTO THE FAM.
SO HOW'D YOU FINALLY
BRING HER AROUND?
WELL, I'M VERY PERSUASIVE.
OF COURSE,
THERE'S THE SMALL MATTER
OF HER CURRENT PARAMOUR,
BUT I'M CERTAIN
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME.
SO THEN, IT'S BACK
TO LONG DISTANCE?
NOPE, I'M RE-ENROLLING
AT DEGRASSI!
DON'T TEASE ME!
I'M NOT! I GOT AN EARLY
ACCEPTANCE TO YALE.
I JUST GOTTA KEEP
MY MARKS UP,
AND I CAN KEEP AN EYE
ON YOU.
WELL, DON'T KEEP
TOO CLOSE AN EYE.
MR. SIMPSON: (OVER PA)
FOR THOSE STUDENTS WHO CONTINUE
TO IGNORE THE DRESS CODE,
SUSPENSIONS WILL BE AWARDED
AFTER THREE WARNINGS.
SO WHAT CAN WE DO TO PROTEST
POWER SQUAD'S CANCELLATION?
YOU KNOW, WITHOUT THE REST
OF POWER SQUAD.
I GUESS A MILLION MAN MARCH
IS OUT?
HOW CAN WE GET PEOPLE TO LISTEN
TO ONLY TWO VOICES?
MAYBE WE CAN'T?
CHANTAY:
WHOA! CHECK THIS OUT!
ANYA:
UGH! NO THANKS!
I CAN IMAGINE;
WE ALL HAD THE CHILI YESTERDAY.
CHANTAY:
GROSS! NO!
COME IN HERE!
I STUCK THIS ONE UP
YESTERDAY
AND NOW IT'S JUST... GROWN.
IT'S LIKE AN ANALOG TWITTER.
A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE UPSET.
THIS IS BIGGER
THAN JUST POWER SQUAD.
YOU'RE PUTTING YOUR FAITH IN
A BATHROOM STALL
COMPLAINTS BOARD?
KINDA SEEMS LIKE
A LAST DITCH ATTEMPT.
THAT MIGHT BE
ALL WE'VE GOT LEFT.
♪♪♪
♪ Oh, Oh ♪
♪ I'm a leader ♪
♪ I'm a winner ♪
♪ And I'm cleaner ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm awesome ♪
♪ I don't need you ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm neato ♪
♪ And I beat you ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm awesome ♪
♪ That's right ♪
DECLAN: FIONA!
FIONA: OH, HEY!
I NEED YOUR HELP.
FIONA:
OH, NO.
DID SIMPSON KIBOSH THE PLAN?
OH, NO, NO, NO! I OFFERED
TO MOUNT ANOTHER MUSICAL
AND WIN ANOTHER AWARD
FOR THE TROPHY CASE,
ALL I NEED
ARE MY VANDERBILT RECORDS
AND MOM'S SIGNATURE.
SO, WHAT'S WRONG?
WELL...
I THINK HOLLY J'S AVOIDING ME.
SHE'S PROBABLY
JUST FEELING WEIRD
ABOUT YOU AND SAV
BEING IN THE SAME PLACE
AT THE SAME TIME.
YEAH, I GET IT.
I MEAN, SAV'S NOT A BAD GUY.
BUT HE'S NO DECLAN COYNE.
YES!
HEY, SAV!
HAVE YOU HEARD
FROM YOUR GIRLFRIEND?
UH, NOT SINCE LAST NIGHT.
WHY, IS SHE OKAY?
WELL, SHE...
SHE HELPED OUT
WITH FIONA,
AND THEN GOT A CAB HOME.
AND I'VE BEEN TRYING
TO CALL HER,
BUT ALL I GET
IS HER VOICEMAIL.
HAS SHE CALLED YOU,
LEFT A MESSAGE?
NO, YOU CAN'T CHECK,
THERE'S CELL PHONE JAMMERS
IN THE SCHOOL.
OH!
WELL, CAN YOU GET HER
TO CALL ME,
IF YOU SEE HER?
FOR SURE.
LATER.
SO WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO SAY IF SHE CALLS?
WELL,
I'LL TELL HER I'LL GIVE HER
ALL THE SPACE SHE NEEDS
TO BREAK IT OFF WITH SAV.
(LAUGHS)
WHOA! HEY.
FUN FIRST DATE LAST NIGHT.
WAS IT WORTH
THE PARENTAL MELTDOWN?
ABSOLUTELY!
SO, WHAT DO YOU WANNA DO
TONIGHT?
TATTOOS?
THEY DIDN'T FREAK OUT ENOUGH
ABOUT THE PIERCING?
WE COULD GET MATCHING DRAGONS
ACROSS OUR BACKS!
CAN WE SAVE SOMETHING
FOR OUR SIX MONTH ANNIVERSARY?
THAT'S A TAD OPTIMISTIC.
ONLY 'CAUSE YOUR PARENTS
MIGHT KILL ME FIRST.
DO THEY TOTALLY HATE ME?
TO BE HONEST,
I HAVEN'T TOLD THEM ABOUT YOU.
OH.
MS. DAWES:
TURN AROUND PLEASE.
OH! ELI,
I DON'T LIKE
THE NEW RULES EITHER,
BUT PLEASE TELL ME
YOU'VE GOT A DOCTOR'S NOTE
THAT SAYS YOU'RE ALLERGIC
TO COTTON AND KHAKI!
ELI:
THIS IS THE REAL ME,
MS. DAWES!
I CAN'T CHANGE OVERNIGHT.
OH! A NOBLE STANCE, ELI.
YOU KEEP ON BEING YOU...
IN DETENTION.
THAT'S IT!
I KNOW.
HOW CAN THE SCHOOL DICTATE
HOW I CHOOSE TO EXPRESS MYSELF?
NO, ABOUT MY PARENTS.
THEY SHOULD MEET
MY BOYFRIEND.
BOYFRIEND?
REALLY?
UH-HUH.
FOR DINNER, TONIGHT,
AFTER YOUR DETENTION.
JUST BE YOURSELF.
THEY'LL LOVE YOU.
HEY, CAN WE TALK
FOR A SEC?
SORRY, FI.
I'VE GOTTA FINISH THIS
AND GET TO WORK.
I CAN'T EVEN REALLY
FOCUS TODAY.
IF THIS IS ABOUT DECLAN-
PLEASE, NOT NOW.
HE'S COMING BACK.
HE'S COMING BACK HERE?
TO DEGRASSI!
HE REALLY LOVES YOU,
HOLLY J.
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE HAPPY.
DIDN'T YOU GUYS RECONNECT
LAST NIGHT?
I CAN'T EVEN TALK ABOUT THIS
WITH YOU,
YOU'RE HIS SISTER.
AND WE'RE FRIENDS.
I CAN'T SAY ANYTHING...
BAD ABOUT HIM TO YOU.
WHY, WHAT BAD THINGS
ARE THERE TO SAY?
LAST NIGHT,
I DIDN'T...
I DIDN'T WANT THINGS TO GO
AS FAR AS THEY DID.
LIKE, AS IN... SEX?
YOU AND DECLAN HAVE
DONE THAT BEFORE.
YEAH, UM...
LAST NIGHT, I FELT...
I FELT PRESSURED.
HOLLY J...
LOOK, I GOTTA GO
FINISH MY WORK, OKAY?
(FRUSTRATED SIGH)
HOLLY J!
(CAR RUMBLES)
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY!
WE'RE ALL HERE BECAUSE
SOMETHING THAT WE LOVE
HAS BEEN TAKEN AWAY
FROM US.
ISN'T THIS JUST ABOUT
POWER SQUAD?
NOT AT ALL!
THIS IS ABOUT OUR RIGHT
TO PURSUE OUR INTERESTS
OUTSIDE THE CLASSROOM,
AT SCHOOL.
LARPING, PHOTO CLUB,
JUNIOR ENTOMOLOGISTS.
WHATEVER.
WE COME FROM
DIFFERENT PLACES,
BUT WE ALL SHARE
ONE GOAL:
GET OUR EXTRA
CURRICULARS BACK!
WHAT IF WE GO STRAIGHT
TO SIMPSON?
WE DON'T HAVE
ANY LEVERAGE.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
CHANTAY:
THERE MUST BE A WAY FOR US
TO COMBINE OUR VOICES
TO FIGHT THIS THING!
IF ONLY WE COULD MAKE
A GIANT STICKY NOTE WALL
THAT SIMPSON COULDN'T IGNORE.
ANYA,
HAS ANYONE EVER TOLD YOU
YOU'RE A GENIUS?
YES.
(LAUGHS)
(DOOR SLAMS)
DECLAN:
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU
ALL DAY! WHAT'D SHE SAY?
UM...
DECLAN:
WAS SHE WITH YOU?
IS THAT WHY YOU COULDN'T
TELL ME OVER THE PHONE?
NO.
BUT YOU SMOOTHED THINGS OVER,
I CAN SEE HER.
I MEAN, YEAH, WE'LL PROBABLY
HAVE TO PLAY IT COOL
UNTIL SHE DUMPS OLD SAV,
BUT, YOU KNOW, SNEAKING AROUND
CAN BE KINDA FUN.
FIONA:
DECLAN!
YOU SHOULD GO HOME,
TO NEW YORK.
WHAT?
WHY?
WHAT'D YOU DO?
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING,
I...
I TOLD HER EVERYTHING
YOU SAID,
BUT SHE DOESN'T WANT
TO SEE YOU.
I DON'T GET IT,
W-WHAT DO I HAVE TO DO?
I'VE GROWN,
I'VE CHANGED,
I'M HERE!
PLUS, LAST NIGHT, WE-
FIONA:
DECLAN! THAT'S KIND OF IT.
WHAT?
LAST NIGHT.
SHE DIDN'T WANT TO.
WHAT?
NO, WE BOTH DID.
DID SHE SAY YES?
DID YOU ASK, OR...
DID YOU FORCE HER?
OH MY GOD.
SHE THINKS I RAPED HER?
(DINERS MURMUR QUIETLY)
MAN:
IS IT A LOBSTER SOUP,
OR A BISQUE?
IT'S JUST,
I HAVE A LACTOSE ALLERGY,
AND I CAN'T HAVE THE CREAM.
HOLLY J:
I'M SORRY, I DON'T KNOW.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO CHECK
WITH THE KITCHEN.
(COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYS
IN THE RESTAURANT)
HOLLY J, PLEASE,
WE NEED TO TALK.
NO, NOT THE PLACE.
DECLAN:
I THOUGHT WE HAD A GREAT TIME
LAST NIGHT.
NOW, FIONA TELLS ME
YOU THINK...
THAT YOU DIDN'T WANT TO.
DECLAN, NOT NOW!
YOU TELL ME, HOLLY J,
YOU TELL ME THAT'S NOT TRUE,
AND I'LL LEAVE.
I DIDN'T WANT TO!
I TOLD YOU THAT.
I THOUGHT THAT
WAS BECAUSE OF SAV!
DOES IT MATTER WHY?
YOU DIDN'T LISTEN,
YOU INSISTED.
YEAH, BUT THEN YOU KISSED ME
AND IT SEEMED LIKE BEFORE,
AND I THOUGHT MAYBE
YOU HAD CHANGED YOUR MIND.
MAYBE I DID!
I WAS CONFUSED,
AND I'M NOT SAYING
IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT,
I JUST...
CAN YOU PLEASE GO?
I HAVE CUSTOMERS.
(WHISPERS)
HOLLY J...
(CAR RUMBLES)
(DOG BARKS)
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYS)
MOM, THANKS SO MUCH
FOR LETTING ELI
STAY FOR DINNER.
SO, ELI.
HOW DO YOU AND CLARE
KNOW EACH OTHER?
WE'RE IN ENGLISH TOGETHER.
SHE'S ONE OF THE SMARTEST,
EVEN THOUGH SHE'S YOUNGER.
AND I HAVE A WONDERFUL EDITOR,
WHEN WE'RE NOT SKIPPING CLASS.
MRS. EDWARDS:
SO, WHAT DO YOUR PARENTS DO,
ELI?
CLARE:
OH, HIS DAD IS A SHOCK JOCK,
ON BULLFROG,
ON SOLID ROCK 98,
THAT STATION YOU HATE.
BET YOUR HOME LIFE
MUST BE COLOURFUL.
LESS COLOURFUL,
MORE BLACK.
ELI EVEN DRIVES
THAT HEARSE OUTSIDE.
WHY DON'T WE GET STARTED.
ELI, AS OUR GUEST,
WOULD YOU LIKE
TO THANK THE LORD
FOR THIS BEAUTIFUL MEAL
FOR US?
OH. W-WELL, I, UM...
DID I FORGET TO MENTION?
ELI'S AN ATHEIST!
CLARE.
NEVER MIND, ELI.
HELEN?
LORD, THANK YOU FOR BRINGING US
ALL TOGETHER THIS EVENING,
TO SHARE IN
THIS BEAUTIFUL FEAST, AMEN.
MR. EDWARDS:
AMEN.
MR. SIMPSON:
HEY, STEVE,
HOW'RE YOU DOING?
STEVE:
GOOD.
MORNING, JAN.
(SLURPS COFFEE)
(STUDENTS CHATTER AND LAUGH)
(SIGHS)
(CHOKES AND SPITS)
MR. SIMPSON:
MY CAR.
SWEET MERCIFUL CRAP.
(STUDENTS WHISPER)
(BIKE RATTLES)
(POST-ITS RUSTLE IN THE WIND)
ANY IDEA HOW THIS HAPPENED?
BEATS ME!
YOU WANT SOME HELP?
(BELL RINGS)
HJ!
AREN'T YOU COMING
TO PHYSICS?
OH! YOU GO,
I'LL-I'LL CATCH UP.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU'VE BARELY SAID A WORD TO ME
SINCE FIONA'S PARTY.
DID I DO SOMETHING WRONG?
MS. OH:
ANY NEWS?
HOLLY J:
NOT YET. (LAUGHS)
I'M FINE.
I JUST NEED
TO CHECK SOMETHING.
UM, I'LL SEE YOU THERE.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(KEYS CLICK)
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
OH MY GOD!
(GASPS)
GIRL: (OVER PA)
REMINDER, STUDENTS.
DEGRASSI HAS A STRICT
NON-VIOLENCE POLICY.
STUDENTS CAUGHT FIGHTING
WILL BE EXPELLED.
(SIGHS)
WHAT'S THIS?
FROM DECLAN.
HE'S SORRY,
AND HE'S OUT OF YOUR LIFE.
HE LEFT?
LEAVING.
FLIES OUT IN A FEW HOURS.
HOW COULD HE GO
WITHOUT TALKING?
YOU GAVE HIM
THE DISTINCT IMPRESSION
THAT YOU DIDN'T WANT
TO TALK.
NOT AT WORK!
SO YOU DON'T HATE HIM?
(SIGHS)
I DON'T KNOW HOW I FEEL.
'CAUSE HE THINKS THAT
YOU THINK THAT HE...
THAT HE...RAPED YOU.
I NEVER SAID THAT!
WHERE IS HE?
CAN I MEET HIM AT THE CONDO?
IF YOU HURRY.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(STICKY NOTES
LAND WITH A THUD)
"IT'S LONELY
WITHOUT FRENCH CLUB."
THESE PEOPLE HAVE A POINT,
DON'T THEY?
AND THAT POINT IS TO...
AGGRAVATE MY SLIPPED DISK!
THEY ALL WANT
THEIR CLUBS BACK.
YOU DID THIS.
NO.
WELL, NOT ALONE!
A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE UPSET,
I TOLD YOU.
LOOK, I KNOW
YOU'RE FRUSTRATED,
BUT THIS IS NO WAY
TO SEND A MESSAGE!
THEN WHAT IS?
TALKING TO YOU?
I TRIED THAT,
REMEMBER?
I TOLD YOU, THE SCHOOL NEEDS
TO MEND ITS IMAGE,
SO WE CAN'T BE AS PERMISSIVE
AS WE USED TO BE!
SO YOU KEEP SAYING,
BUT YOU NEVER SAY
HOW THAT'S SUPPOSED TO WORK!
LOOK, THIS IS DEGRASSI
COMMUNITY SCHOOL.
EMPHASIS ON SCHOOL!
FOR SOME PEOPLE,
THE EMPHASIS IS ON COMMUNITY.
SO WHEN YOU TAKE AWAY
OUR CLOTHING,
AND OUR CLUBS,
AND OUR INTERNET,
WE LOSE THAT COMMUNITY.
YOU MADE ALL
OF THESE CHANGES
WITHOUT TALKING
TO ANY OF US
ABOUT WHAT MIGHT
ACTUALLY HELP.
WE DIDN'T ALL BRING KNIVES
TO VEGAS NIGHT.
WHAT IF WE SET UP
A FORUM?
WHERE STUDENTS COULD VOICE
THEIR OPINIONS
AND SUGGEST SOLUTIONS.
AND WE CAN GET OUR CLUBS BACK?
MAYBE.
OR MAYBE SOME SORT
OF THEME WEEK?
WE'LL SEE.
THAT'S NOT GOOD ENOUGH.
I NEED A PROMISE.
FINE, IF YOU PROMISE
THAT NOTHING LIKE THIS
WILL EVER HAPPEN AGAIN.
SOUNDS LIKE
WE HAVE A DEAL.
(ASTONISHED SIGH)
♪♪♪
YOU WERE SO CUTE
LAST NIGHT.
WAS I? I FELT MORE
LIKE A PARIAH.
OH, MY PARENTS JUST HAVE
TO DEAL WITH THE FACT
THAT I HAVE A BIG,
SCARY BOYFRIEND!
(SIGHS)
HOW CAN I EVEN SHOW MY FACE
IN YOUR HOUSE AGAI...
WHO ARE YOU?
WHAT? I THOUGHT
YOU'D LIKE IT!
ELI:
CLARE! WE'LL GET A DETENTION.
(SCOFFS) SO?
COME ON,
LIVE DANGEROUSLY.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU'RE DOING ALL THIS!
BECAUSE I'M SCARED!
ELI...
OF WHAT? SANITY?
I AM SCARED...
THAT MY PARENTS...
ARE GONNA SIT ME DOWN,
LOOK ME IN THE EYE,
AND SAY,
"WE'RE GETTING A DIVORCE
AND THERE'S NOTHING
YOU CAN DO ABOUT IT."
AND HOW EXACTLY DOES
USING ME AS A PAWN
IN YOUR PARENTAL SHOWDOWN
STOP THEIR DIVORCE?
WHEN THEY'RE BOTH
MAD AT ME,
THEY HAVE SOMETHING
IN COMMON!
CLARE,
THEY'VE ALREADY DECIDED,
THEN MAYBE THEY'LL SEE
HOW IT'S SCREWING UP
THEIR DAUGHTER!
WELL, I'M NOT PLAYING
THAT GAME.
YOU TRIED TO HURT THEM,
BUT I'M THE ONE
THAT GOT BURNED.
WHA...
♪♪♪
HOLLY J:
DECLAN?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I'M ON MY WAY.
YOU CAN'T JUST GO.
THE MORE I'M HERE,
THE MORE I COMPLICATE YOUR LIFE.
SO YOU'RE
RUNNING AWAY?
YEAH!
SO I CAN STOP HURTING YOU.
YOU NEVER HAVE
TO SEE ME AGAIN.
THAT MIGHT NOT BE
SO EASY.
I GOT INTO YALE!
(HALF LAUGHS
AND SIGHS)
MR. EDWARDS:
I JUST CAN'T TAKE THIS ANYMORE!
MRS. EDWARDS:
OH, SO WHEN IT SUITS YOU,
YOU'RE REALLY INTO CHANGE!
MR. EDWARDS:
OH...
CLARE:
I...
I JUST NEED SOMEONE
TO SIGN THIS DETENTION SLIP.
STUPID... DRESS CODE.
YOU SEE WHAT YOU GET?
"LET HER COME AROUND,"
YOU SAID!
AND SHE'S TURNING
INTO A DELINQUENT!
I'M TRYING NOT TO HARP ON HER
ALL THE TIME!
MRS. EDWARDS:
I'M TRYING TO BE A PARENT!
(YELLING) STOP IT!
PLEASE!
WHY ARE YOU BEING SO HORRIBLE
TO EACH OTHER?
CLARE, YOUR FATHER AND I-
DAD.
SAY DAD.
YOU ALWAYS SAY DAD.
CLARE...
WE'RE GETTING DIVORCED.
DON'T!
DON'T, I'LL BEHAVE,
I SWEAR.
MRS. EDWARDS:
HONEY,
THIS HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH YOU.
THAT DOESN'T MAKE IT
ANY BETTER!
SWEETHEART...
WE DON'T WANT TO BE FIGHTING
ALL THE TIME, EITHER.
IT'S NOT FAIR TO YOU!
THIS WAY,
THERE'S NO MORE ARGUMENTS.
OH GOD, YOU...
YOU'RE DOING THIS FOR REAL,
AREN'T YOU?
(GASPS)
(CRYING)
(SNIFFLES)
DECLAN:
SO WE BOTH GOT INTO YALE.
(SIGHS)
I THOUGHT THIS WOULD BE
A HAPPIER MOMENT.
ME TOO.
I DON'T DESERVE IT.
YOU THINK I...
(SIGHS)
I CAN'T EVEN SAY IT.
I DON'T...
THINK YOU RAPED ME.
HONESTLY?
HONESTLY.
OKAY.
THAT'S GOOD.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
DO YOU HATE ME?
I REGRET WHAT HAPPENED.
WHAT CAN I DO?
HOW CAN I MAKE IT
UP TO YOU?
WE NEED TIME...
TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT HAPPENS NOW.
I WANT YOU IN MY LIFE,
HOLLY J.
WHEN I'M READY,
I'LL CALL.
THAT'S A "WHEN",
NOT AN "IF", RIGHT?
(SIGHS)
WELL, EITHER WAY,
I'LL BE WAITING.
BYE, DECLAN.
BYE, HOLLY J.
♪♪♪
♪ Hang on ♪
♪ 'Cause the ribbon
is slipping through your hands ♪
♪ And I'm falling
into the earth ♪
(CHOKES BACK A SOB)