(PANTING)
ELI:
THERE IT IS!
I'LL TAKE ALL OF THEM.
(LAUGHS)
(SIGHS HAPPILY)
FEAST YOUR EYES ON THIS!
THEY PICKED YOUR STORY?
ELI!
LOOK CLOSER.
OUR FIRST PUBLISHED
COLLABORATION.
BUT IT-IT'S YOUR STORY!
YOU WROTE IT!
WITH YOUR HELP,
EDITOR EXTRAORDINAIRE.
WE ARE A TEAM.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE
TO DO THAT.
NO, I WANTED TO.
IT'S THE BEGINNING
OF OUR DREAMS COMING TRUE.
WELL, THANKS,
I GUESS.
MY DARK INSTINCTS
COUPLED WITH YOUR FLARE
FOR ROMANCE?
WE ARE UNSTOPPABLE.
I SAY WE LOCK OURSELVES
IN A ROOM
AND COMMENCE WORK
ON OUR FIRST NOVEL TOGETHER -
JUST YOU AND ME.
ALLI: HEY!
CLARE: ALLI!
CLARE:
HEY, UH...
WE HAVE AN APPOINTMENT
TO DISCUSS DRESS OPTIONS
FOR THE SPRING FLING.
YOU'VE JUST BEEN PUBLISHED!
ISN'T A HIGH SCHOOL DANCE
A LITTLE TRIVIAL?
NOT REALLY.
DANCES ARE FUN.
(SCOFFS)
BALLOONS AND BANAL
TOP FORTY?
(LAUGHS DERISIVELY)
IF YOU'RE NOT INTERESTED,
DON'T COME.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever, Woo-ooh)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
SO, NO DRESS CODE
AT THE DANCE.
SIMPSON FINALLY CAVED.
MAYBE NOW I WON'T GO DOWN
AS THE WORST PRESIDENT
IN DEGRASSI HISTORY.
(HALF LAUGHS)
(BEEPING)
OH! TIME'S UP.
LET'S SEE...
I GOT...HEAL,
HEART, HERE,
SWEET, AND KITTEN.
(LAUGHS UNCOMFORTABLY)
UM, I GOT:
HAM, DEAD, OVER, END,
BYE, BAD, AND...
UNHAPPY.
SEVEN LETTERS,
THAT'S NICE.
YEAH.
YOU WANT TO PLAY
ANOTHER ROUND
BEFORE I GET ON
MY UNIVERSITY APPLICATION?
I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, WE COULD ALWAYS
MAKE OUT INSTEAD.
I'M REALLY NOT FEELING
TOO GOOD.
OH.
HOW ABOUT WE JUST
PLAY BOGGLE?
SURE.
YOU WANNA SHAKE IT UP?
(BOGGLE CUBES RATTLE)
♪♪♪
(BELL RINGS)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I HAVE CLASS!
I'M DRIVING MYSELF
INSANE.
IT'S CLARE.
I TRIED TO JOKE AROUND
WITH HER THIS MORNING,
LIKE ALWAYS,
BUT...
SHE WAS ALL PRICKLY!
YOU'RE JUST BEING PARANOID.
EVERY TIME
SHE DISAGREES WITH ME,
I PANIC!
I NEED A WAY TO FIX THIS;
A PLAN!
YOUR PLANS USUALLY MAKE THINGS
MORE COMPLICATED.
JUST RELAX FOR NOW.
I CAN'T!
I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING
THAT'S JUST FOR US;
OUR THING.
IN OR OUT, ADAM,
THE LATTER WILL EARN YOU
A DETENTION.
I'LL BE RIGHT IN,
MISS.
EVERYTHING'S GONNA BE OKAY.
JUST WHATEVER YOU DO,
TAKE IT EASY.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
♪♪♪
(ANYA AND FIONA LAUGH)
ANYA:
IS THAT A SAV'S PROS
AND CONS LIST?
NO, DON'T LAUGH.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO.
FIONA:
LEAVE IT TO HOLLY J
TO USE A LIST TO MAKE
A LIFE DECISION.
SHOW ME.
OKAY, PROS:
SWEET, SMART,
SUPPORTIVE,
FUNNY-ISH,
AND BIG - WAIT FOR IT -
HEARTED.
FIONA:
AND THERE'S ONLY ONE CON:
NOT FEELING IT.
DO YOU MEAN
THE L-WORD?
LESBIAN? WHY-
I'M PRETTY SURE FIONA
MEANT LOVE, WEIRDO.
(SIGHS)
HOLLY J HAS MENTIONITIS
SINCE I CAME OUT RECENTLY.
I'M GAY.
REALLY? COOL.
SO, DO YOU LOVE SAV
OR NOT?
EVERYTHING ELSE IS PERFECT.
I MEAN, DO ALL THESE PROS
OUTWEIGH THAT ONE...
PUNY CON?
IT'S THE MOST IMPORTANT ONE,
SILLY!
DO YOU AND SAV
EVEN HAVE FUN ANYMORE?
YEAH!
YEAH, WE HANG OUT.
WE... PLAY BOGGLE.
OKAY, NOT REALLY.
BUT IT'S ME,
I MEAN EVER SINCE
I GOT SICK,
I'VE BEEN HALF
A GIRLFRIEND.
LOOK AT ME.
YOU'RE PERFECT.
(BELL RINGS)
HOLLY J:
THERE'S NO REASON FOR US
TO BREAK UP
BECAUSE EVERYTHING IS FINE.
ON PAPER.
NO REASON TO LEAVE?
THAT'S NEVER A GOOD REASON
TO STAY.
(KNOCKING)
ELI:
MISS DAWES,
YOU WANTED TO SEE ME?
YEAH, COME ON IN.
THIS IS REALLY SOMETHING,
ELI.
YOUR WRITING IS BEAUTIFUL.
IT'S MACABRE.
(LAUGHS HAPPILY)
BUT I WONDER IF THERE'S ANYTHING
YOU WANNA TALK ABOUT?
W-WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL, YOUR PROTAGONIST
MURDERS HIS FIANCEE,
YOUR THEME IS SPENDING ETERNITY
WITH THE ONE YOU LOVE.
IT COULD BE READ
AS A...
A CRY FOR HELP.
IT'S FICTION!
I KNOW.
BUT, AS WRITERS,
WE TEND TO PULL
FROM OUR OWN LIFE EXPERIENCES
FOR INSPIRATION.
(LAUGHS)
MISS, I'M NOT GONNA
KILL CLARE
AND DRINK HER BLOOD.
I'M GOOD.
OKAY.
IT'S MY JOB TO CHECK.
CONGRATULATIONS, ELI,
I'M REAL PROUD OF YOU.
HEY, YOU KNOW,
THE GOTHIC FICTION CONVENTION
IS IN BLOOMINGTON
OVER SPRING BREAK.
WITH "STALKER/ANGEL"
UNDER YOUR BELT,
IT MIGHT BE WORTH
CHECKING OUT.
MAYBE IT WOULD.
THANKS.
(SIREN WAILS IN THE DISTANCE)
ALLI:
WELL, THAT WAS NICE
OF KC'S MOM
TO LET US HAVE
THE BABY SHOWER HERE.
I KNOW!
MY HOUSE ISN'T EXACTLY
BABY-Y.
LET'S CLEAN
THIS STUFF UP.
SO WHY ISN'T KC,
THE FATHER, HELPING?
UH, WELL HE SAYS
BABY SHOWERS ARE FOR GIRLS,
SO I TOLD HIM
TO GO PLAY BASKETBALL.
HE DESERVES SOME TIME OFF.
SHOULD I PACK
THIS STUFF UP?
JENNA:
OH NO, I'LL LEAVE IT HERE
FOR THE GRANDMA GUTHRIE NURSERY,
WHICH HANDYMAN KC
EVEN BUILT A CRIB FOR!
HMM!
THAT CRIB?
YEAH, I'M SURE YOUR BABY
WILL BE VERY COMFORTABLE
SLEEPING ON TOP
OF A CARDBOARD BOX.
HE SAID HE WOULD ASSEMBLE IT
BEFORE BASKETBALL.
OH, WHOA!
OH, FEEL THIS!
HOLY KICK!
YOU'VE GOT THE NEXT
CRISTIANO RONALDO IN HERE!
OH! THERE'S A REAL PERSON
IN THERE!
(LAUGHS) WHEW!
YOU NEED ALL THE HELP
YOU CAN GET.
(SIGHS)
YOU OWE ME FOR THIS,
KIDDO.
LUCKY FOR ME,
IT'S MY BIRTHDAY TOMORROW!
(LAUGHS)
ELI!
HI, MS. EDWARDS.
OH, THIS IS MY DAD,
BULLFROG.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
I'M SORRY,
CLARE'S NOT HOME RIGHT NOW.
I'M HERE TO ASK
YOUR PERMISSION.
YOU'RE NOT PLANNING
TO PROPOSE?!
NO, NO, NO!
I-I WONDERED IF CLARE COULD
COME WITH ME AND MY PARENTS
TO BLOOMINGTON FOR TWO DAYS.
THERE'S A LIT CONVENTION
SHE'D LOVE.
CLARE'S ONLY FIFTEEN,
I DON'T THINK
IT'S A GOOD IDEA.
BUT I'LL TELL HER
YOU CAME BY.
YOUR DAUGHTER'S
MY BEST FRIEND.
SHE'S THE KINDEST,
MOST PATIENT PERSON
I'VE EVER MET.
SHE WOULD LOVE YOU
FOR THIS.
(SIGHS)
WELL...
WHERE WOULD YOU BE STAYING?
WE BOOKED TWO ROOMS
AT A HOTEL;
CLARE'LL BUNK WITH MY WIFE.
AND YOU WOULDN'T LET THEM
OUT OF YOUR SIGHT?
I'LL WATCH HER
LIKE SHE'S MY OWN.
(LAUGHS DRYLY)
WELL, IT'S REALLY UP
TO CLARE.
THANKS, MRS. EDWARDS!
(ELI LAUGHS HAPPILY)
GUYS:
COME ON! COME ON! HEY!
JENNA:
HEY!
WHAT'RE YOU STILL
DOING HERE?
THE CRIB'S NOT EVEN MADE!
YOU TOLD ME TO CELEBRATE
BEING DONE EXAMS.
OH CRAP, DOMESTIC.
I'M OUTTA HERE.
I TOLD YOU TO PLAY
'CAUSE I THOUGHT THE NURSERY
WAS ALL READY!
OKAY, WELL,
IT-IT WILL BE.
ARE YOU DOING ANYTHING
TO PREPARE FOR THIS BABY?
I'M GONNA BUILD A CRIB,
JENNA.
JENNA:
YOU HAVEN'T EVEN OPENED
THE BOX!
WHERE'S THE BABY
SUPPOSED TO SLEEP?
THIS ISN'T JUST ABOUT CRAVINGS
AND PLAYLISTS, KC.
THIS IS REAL!
YOU TOLD ME
TO PLAY BASKETBALL!
KC:
LET'S GO!
(KEYS CLACK)
(SIGHS)
THOUGHT I'D FIND YOU HERE.
(LAUGHS)
20 PAGES
OF SHEET MUSIC DOWN,
LONG-ASS "STATEMENT
OF INTENT" TO GO.
SAV...
WHY DO YOU EVEN
LIKE ME?
'CAUSE YOU DON'T USUALLY
ASK QUESTIONS
LIKE "WHY DO YOU LIKE ME?"
SERIOUSLY,
WHAT DID YOU THINK ABOUT
WHILE I WAS AWAY
IN THE HOSPITAL?
I DON'T KNOW,
JUST THOUGHT ABOUT
HOW FRAGILE LIFE IS.
HOW SAD I'D BE
IF I LOST YOU.
OH, OKAY.
THAT'S GOOD TO KNOW.
CLARE:
I SPENT ALL AFTERNOON
TALKING ALLI OUT OF MATCHING
HER EARRINGS WITH HER SHOES,
WITH HER DRESS,
WITH HER HEADBAND.
LET'S JUST SAY ALLI'S NEVER
MET A PINK SHE DIDN'T LIKE.
OH MY GOD,
I LOVE THIS SONG!
(TURNS MUSIC UP)
♪♪♪
CLARE "MIDDLE OF THE ROAD"
EDWARDS!
I LIKE IT.
IT'S HAPPY,
LIKE SPRINGTIME.
OKAY, SORRY.
SPEAKING OF A BREATH
OF FRESH AIR,
ALL ACCESS PASSES
TO THE GOTHIC FICTION
CONVENTION!
THAT'S IN BLOOMINGTON!
I KNOW, WE'RE GOING ON
A SPRING BREAK ROAD TRIP
IN THE HEARSE!
MY PARENTS ARE CHAPERONING
FROM THE HOG.
YOUR MOM SAID YOU COULD GO!
YOU TALKED TO MY MOM?
YEAH.
WHY WOULDN'T YOU
TALK TO ME FIRST?
I-I WANTED IT
TO BE A SURPRISE.
SOMETHING SPECIAL
FOR MY GIRL.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU DID ALL THIS.
THIS CONVENTION'S A ONCE-
IN-A-LIFETIME OPPORTUNITY!
ME, YOU, MORTY...
NOTHING IN OUR WAY;
A CHANCE FOR US
TO RECONNECT.
I JUST THOUGHT
IT'D BE FUN.
OKAY, I'LL COME.
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE
A LITTLE MORE EXCITED.
WHAT MORE DO YOU WANT, ELI?
WE'RE GOING.
♪ This kind of love ♪
♪ Has got me bouncin' off
the ceiling now ♪
♪ This kind of love ♪
♪ Has got me kicking
and a screaming now ♪
♪ This kind of love
has got me now ♪
(BIRDS CHIRP)
(GUNSHOT FIRES)
DANG! MISSED AGAIN!
WE'RE NOT LEAVING 'TIL WE CATCH
MY BIRTHDAY DINNER, BOYS.
WOULD YOU STOP WAVING
THAT THING AROUND?
YOU'RE GONNA SCARE
THE WILD TURKEY!
CAN WE GO NOW?
HE WANTS TO CALL
HIS GIRLFRIEND.
OY VEY!
OH!
STAY LOW.
KEEP YOUR VOICES DOWN.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
HEY!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
CLARE WASN'T AS EXCITED
FOR THE TRIP
AS I THOUGHT
SHE WAS GOING TO BE.
WELL, MAYBE A SURPRISE
WASN'T THE BEST APPROACH,
SINCE PAST SURPRISES
WITH YOU HAVE BEEN...
INTENSE?
AND SCARY -
DEAD GIRLFRIEND?
HOARDING?
CLARE'S SAVED ME FROM MYSELF
ALL YEAR, HASN'T SHE?
WELL,
SHE DOES LIKE YOU
EVEN THOUGH
YOU'RE KINDA LOCO.
MAYBE, UH,
GIVE HER A BREAK.
YEAH.
AND AFTER TWO DAYS
IN THE HEARSE,
(GUNSHOT BOOMS)
WE'LL BE PERFECT AGAIN.
BULLFROG:
I GOT IT!
(BELL RINGS)
YOU REALLY WANNA SPEND
TWO DAYS IN A HEARSE
WITH THE GUY
THAT WROTE THIS?
IT'S WEIRD,
BUT IT'S WELL WRITTEN.
IT'S MESSED UP!
AND DIDN'T HE SAY
IT WAS ABOUT YOU?
NOT LITERALLY.
HE'S A GOOD GUY.
YOU DON'T KNOW HIM
LIKE I DO.
SURE.
LOTS OF GOOD GUYS GET THEMSELVES
BEAT UP ON PURPOSE
AND POISON OTHER PEOPLE
WITH IPECAC.
HE'S BEEN THROUGH A LOT.
HIS EX-GIRLFRIEND DIED
LAST YEAR.
WHAT?
SHE DIED A YEAR AGO,
OVER SPRING BREAK!
THAT EXPLAINS EVERYTHING.
HMM.
(ALLI SIGHS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
HOW'D THE BREAK-UP GO?
I TRIED
AND I FAILED MISERABLY.
REALLY?
SAV'S THE EASIEST GUY
TO BREAK UP WITH.
I'VE DONE IT
LIKE SIX TIMES.
(BOTH LAUGH)
THERE'S ALWAYS AN OUT.
WHAT, THE PENDING
ARRANGED MARRIAGE?
THEY COULD CATCH YOU
MAKING OUT IN HIS LIVING ROOM.
ONCE THEY FIND OUT
YOU'RE HIS GIRLFRIEND,
IT'S OVER!
THAT'S NOT REALLY
MY STYLE.
NO OFFENSE,
BUT YOUR STYLE
DOESN'T SEEM TO BE
WORKING VERY WELL.
TRUST ME, SAV'LL NEVER
STAND UP FOR YOU.
I COULD NEVER DO THAT
TO HIM, THOUGH.
(SIGHS)
SAV: (OVER PA)
THE CLEANING STAFF REMINDS YOU
TO PLEASE CLEAR OUT YOUR LOCKER
BEFORE SPRING BREAK.
THANKS.
APOLOGY BREAKFAST SANDWICH?
I'LL EAT IT
AFTER I FINISH
ASSEMBLING THE CRIB,
THE SWING,
AND THE CHANGE TABLE.
(LOCKER SLAMS)
GREAT.
YOU THINK I'M A MOMZILLA.
YOU'RE NOT.
I-I'M SORRY,
IT'S OUR BABY.
YOU'RE DOING YOUR SHARE
AND I WANNA DO MINE.
(SIGHS)
I DON'T TAKE ANY OF THIS
FOR GRANTED, YOU KNOW.
HEY, I GET IT.
I'M A DAD NOW;
THIS IS MY LIFE.
SEE YOU AFTER CLASS?
HEY MAMA, HOW'S THE NURSERY
COMING ALONG?
KC'S BEEN WORKING ON IT
NON-STOP.
ATTA GIRL!
YOU'VE WHIPPED HIM INTO
BABY DADDY OF THE YEAR!
I GUESS SO.
YOU KNOW, KC'S BEEN IN AND OUT
OF GROUP HOMES HIS WHOLE LIFE,
AND HE'S ABOUT TO LOSE
HIS TEENHOOD LIKE, FOREVER.
YEAH, WELL,
SO ARE YOU.
THERE'S NOTHING
YOU CAN DO ABOUT IT.
(SIGHS)
JENNA: DAVE!
DAVE: HEY, WHAT?
DON'T HURT ME.
WHAT?
I'M NOT GOING TO.
I WANT YOU TO THROW KC
A BABY SHOWER.
ISN'T THAT FOR GIRLS?
OKAY, THINK OF IT
MORE AS A BACHELOR PARTY?
NO RULES.
YOU SERIOUS?
YEAH. JUST AS LONG
AS HE'S AT THE DANCE
FOR THE LAST SONG,
AND DON'T TELL ME
WHAT HAPPENS.
OH, I CAN MANAGE THAT.
(BOTH LAUGH)
MAKE IT THE BEST NIGHT
OF HIS LIFE.
OKAY.
BEST NIGHT OF HIS LIFE.
(HOLLY J SIGHS)
HEY.
I THINK WE NEED TO TALK.
YEAH, I'VE BEEN THINKING
THE SAME THING.
YOU HAVE?
YEAH.
I MEAN THE SPRING DANCE
IS TOMORROW,
AND-AND I'VE JUST BEEN
SO BUSY
THAT I HAVEN'T HAD THE CHANCE
TO ASK IF YOU'D BE MY DATE.
UH...
(HORN HONKS)
(CAR RUMBLES)
I'LL COURIER YOUR APPLICATION
EXPRESS?
YEAH.
THE ADDRESS IS RIGHT THERE.
YOU'RE A LIFE SAVER.
UH, MOM,
THIS IS MY FRIEND HOLLY J.
THE CO-PRESIDENT.
I'VE HEARD SO MUCH
ABOUT YOU.
IT'S NICE
TO FINALLY MEET YOU.
YOU AS WELL.
DID SAV SAY
I WAS JUST HIS FRIEND?
YES. WHY?
WELL, IT'S NOT TRUE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M HIS GIRLFRIEND.
(LAUGHS)
YOU'RE SO FUNNY!
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
SAV:
SHE'S SO FUNNY, MOM.
A JOKER, REALLY.
YOU'RE HIS MOTHER.
YOU DESERVE TO KNOW THE TRUTH.
I'M SORRY.
IF YOU DON'T MIND,
I'D LIKE TO HAVE A WORD
WITH MY SON.
(CARS RUMBLE)
(PASSERSBY CHATTER)
CLARE!
WHAT BRINGS US
TO OUR SPECIAL BENCH?
WE'VE BEEN TOUGH
ON EACH OTHER LATELY.
I'VE BEEN TENSE,
YOU'VE BEEN...
INTENSE.
I'M SORRY.
BUT IT'S 'CAUSE
WE CARE ABOUT EACH OTHER.
I GET IT NOW, ELI.
YOU'RE SCARED OF LOSING ME
AFTER JULIA.
(SIGHS)
BUT YOU'VE GOT THINGS
TO DEAL WITH.
YOU'RE PRESSURING ME
BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT OVER HER.
I AM OVER HER!
THEN WHY DID YOU PLAN
A TRIP
DURING THE ANNIVERSARY
OF HER DEATH?
IT'S A COINCIDENCE!
I SWEAR!
HOW COULD THIS NOT
BE ABOUT HER?
EVERYTHING ELSE
HAS BEEN ABOUT JULIA -
THE HOARDING,
THE WORRY.
THAT'S NOT TRUE!
IT'S ABOUT YOU,
CLARE.
IT'S ONLY ABOUT YOU.
GIVE ME A CHANCE,
I'LL-I'LL PROVE IT!
AND I BET YOU COULD.
BUT, ELI, I THINK...
THAT WE SHOULD TAKE
A SMALL BREATHER.
NOT IN A BAD WAY.
CANCEL OUR MOVIE DATE?
I WAS THINKING MORE
LIKE A FEW DAYS.
IT'LL BE GOOD FOR US.
I DISAGREE.
AFTER EVERYTHING
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH -
THE FITZ STUFF -
WE NEED TIME TOGETHER,
AWAY FROM EVERYBODY,
JUST THE TWO OF US!
STOP IT!
YOU'RE SUFFOCATING ME!
YOU MAKE ALL THESE PLANS,
TALK ABOUT FOREVER...
I KNOW YOU'RE SCARED.
THIS SPRING BREAK TRIP
IS A BAD IDEA.
I'M SORRY.
♪ When you shine,
your heart is made of gold ♪
(CARS RUMBLE PAST)
ANYA:
YOU DID THE RIGHT THING.
THEN WHY DO I FEEL
LIKE A SCHMUCK?
I SHOULD'VE
JUST BEEN HONEST.
OKAY, SO YOU DID
THE RIGHT THING
THE WRONG WAY.
(DOOR OPENS)
AND NOW'S YOUR CHANCE
TO EXPLAIN YOURSELF.
(SIGHS)
SAV,
I'M-I'M REALLY SORRY.
YOU MUST BE ANGRY.
SO... IT TURNS OUT
MY PARENTS LOVE YOU.
THEY CALL YOU
"YALE GIRL"!
THEY DO?
YEAH.
I STOOD UP FOR YOU,
HOLLY J,
AND THEY LISTENED!
FOR REAL!
THAT'S GREAT,
BUT-
MY PARENTS ENCOURAGED ME
TO KEEP DATING YOU.
MY PARENTS, HOLLY J,
WANT ME TO DATE SOMEONE
WHO IS NOT FARRAH!
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
NO, ACTUALLY.
I'M-I'M SHOCKED.
YOU'RE SO SMART!
YOU COULD TELL THIS
IS WHAT I NEEDED -
A-A PUSH.
I HAVEN'T BEEN HONEST.
I TOLD YOUR MOM
BECAUSE...
I THOUGHT SHE'D FORCE YOU
TO BREAK UP WITH ME.
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
YOU WANNA BREAK UP?
WHAT'S WRONG?
NOTHING.
AND THAT'S THE THING.
IT'S JUST NOT THERE
BETWEEN US.
LOOK, WE ALWAYS TALKED
ABOUT AN EXPIRY DATE,
IT-IT FEELS LIKE
IT'S NOW.
AND YOU DECIDED THIS
BY YOURSELF?
YOU DIDN'T WANNA
TALK ABOUT IT?
I GUESS THIS IS
THE TALK.
(SCOFFS)
ANYA:
BREAK-UPS SUCK.
FIONA:
SO BRUTAL,
BUT GOOD FOR HOLLY J.
YOU'RE IN LOVE
WITH HOLLY J,
AREN'T YOU?
(LAUGHS)
YEAH, RIGHT.
I'M IN LOVE WITH HOLLY J.
I KNOW THAT LOOK,
I'VE SEEN IT
A THOUSAND TIMES.
WELL, YOU'RE WRONG,
OKAY?
DROP IT!
OH MY GOD,
FIONA!
HEY! YOU DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING, SO...
OH NO.
OKAY, I'M SORRY.
IT'S JUST I KNOW
WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO LOVE SOMEBODY
THAT YOU CAN'T BE WITH.
SO IF YOU EVER
WANNA TALK...
(SIGHS)
WELL, I DON'T.
JUST PROMISE TO KEEP IT
TO YOURSELF?
YEAH, I PROMISE.
(DEBRIS CLATTERS)
♪♪♪
♪ Backstabbing,
Money grabbing ♪
♪ Teenage punk ♪
♪ He's gonna kick it
with his new junk ♪
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT!
CLARE HATES ME
BECAUSE OF YOU!
YOU RUINED MY LIFE!
(SAFETY CLICKS)
NOT ANYMORE.
(GUNSHOT BLASTS)