(SUV DOORS SLAM)
DREW:
HEY, MY LITTLE SCIENCE
SUPERSTAR!
(SIGHS)
DAD, THIS IS DREW.
HE'S A FELLOW SCIENCE OLYMPIAN.
YEP. SCIENCE.
FANTASTIC.
WHAT'S YOUR FAVOURITE TOPIC?
IN MY DAY, I WAS MIGHTY GOOD
AT ORNITHOLOGY.
OH, FASCINATING!
WELL, YOU KNOW,
WE GOTTA GO,
THE TEAM'S WAITING.
MR. BHANDARI:
OF COURSE!
GOOD LUCK, YOU TWO!
AH, NOT THAT YOU NEED IT.
(CAR RUMBLES AWAY)
THANK YOU FOR COVERING.
SEE YOU AFTER CLASS?
I THINK I CAN
FIT YOU IN.
(BOTH LAUGH)
AH!
SO, WHAT HAPPENED
TO NO SECRET BOYFRIEND?
NO LYING TO PARENTS?
I'VE DECIDED THE NEW ME
DOESN'T HAVE TO GIVE UP
THE OLD ME COMPLETELY.
CLARE:
SO THAT'S IT?
DREW'S FORGIVEN?
HE'S ON PROBATION.
SOMETIMES PEOPLE DESERVE
A SECOND CHANCE.
DOES THAT MEAN BIANCA
GETS A SECOND CHANCE TOO?
NOT EXACTLY.
I MAY HAVE SENT
SKANKY PHOTOS OF HER
TO THE ENTIRE SCHOOL.
YOU DID THAT?!
WHAT,
SHE HAD IT COMING!
I BET SHE'S PLOTTING
YOUR DEATH RIGHT NOW.
LET HER.
I'VE GOT DREW BACK,
AND TODAY,
I'M GONNA WIN
THE SCIENCE OLYMPICS.
NOTHING CAN BRING ME DOWN.
NOT EVEN BIANCA!
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever, Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(BIRDS CHIRP)
I KNEW IT!
I'M NEVER DOUBTING
THE CHANTAY INSTINCT AGAIN!
I KNEW IT!
I GUESS YOU SAW
THE SHOW, HUH?
I SCREAMED SO LOUD,
THE NEIGHBOURS BANGED
ON THE WALL.
WAY TO DROP A BOMB,
MIDDLETON!
SO, IS IT KC'S?
YEAH.
(LAUGHS UNCOMFORTABLY)
UH, IT HAD TO SPILL
SOME TIME.
YOU JUST CHOSE
NATIONAL TELEVISION!
WELL, NOW ALL I HAVE TO DO
IS FACE THE WHOLE WORLD
KNOWING I'M PREGNANT.
IT'S SO EXCITING!
(LAUGHS)
UM...
(GASPS)
I BETTER GO.
(METAL DETECTOR WHINES)
JENNA:
(SIGHS) HI.
HEY.
I GUESS, UH, DID YOU SEE
THE SHOW LAST NIGHT?
YOU DIDN'T EVEN ASK ME!
IT HAD TO COME OUT
SOMETIME.
AND YOU DIDN'T THINK,
"MAYBE I COULD WARN KC
SO HIS MOM DOESN'T FIND OUT
FROM THE TV
AT THE STEAKHOUSE"?
SORRY, OKAY?
IT WAS NOW OR NEVER.
IT'S JUST SO
INCONSIDERATE.
(SCOFFS)
IT'S NOT ABOUT YOU, KC!
YOU DIDN'T WANT ANY PART
OF THIS, REMEMBER?
I HAD-
I'M ON MY OWN.
I MAKE MY OWN DECISIONS.
LIKE USING PREGNANCY
TO HELP YOU STAY
TWO MORE MINUTES
ON SOME PATHETIC SHOW?
(SCOFFS)
I'M TAKING CARE OF ME.
DEAL WITH IT!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
MR. SIMPSON: (ON PA)
BIANCA DE SOUZA,
REPORT TO THE OFFICE!
BIANCA DE SOUZA!
CONNOR:
BIOLOGY QUESTION:
WHAT'S THE AIRSPEED VELOCITY
OF AN UNLADEN SWALLOW?
AFRICAN OR EUROPEAN?
I DON'T KNOW,
LET ME JUST CHECK.
WOW, THAT'S CURIOUS,
AN EMAIL FROM BIANCA!
JUST CHECKING NOW?
IS IT SPICY?
(PHONE BEEPS)
WOW!
W-WHY WOULD SHE SEND THIS
TO ME?
APPARENTLY SHE SENT IT
TO EVERYONE.
HERE, LET ME SEE.
THAT'S A BOOB.
ALLI: DOWN, BOY!
THE ENTIRE SCHOOL'S
TALKING ABOUT IT.
THAT'S ALL I'LL BE ABLE
TO THINK ABOUT TODAY.
FOCUS! WE STILL HAVE
TO BEAT BARDELL!
SOMEONE'S GETTING BEATEN
ALL RIGHT!
ALLI:
UH, BIANCA.
YOU SEEM...UPSET.
I GOT SUSPENDED.
BECAUSE SOMEHOW
YOU SENT THOSE PICTURES AROUND!
LITTLE OLD ME?
NOW, IF ONLY YOU COULD
PROVE IT, HUH?
HERE'S YOUR PROOF!
(FIST CONNECTS WITH A THUNK)
ALLI: OOH! OH!
ALLI: AAAH!
BIANCA: OH!
(SCREAMS WITH RAGE)
BIANCA: OW!
ALLI:
AGH! GET OFF OF ME!
OOH!
BIANCA:
(GROANS)
OW!
ALLI:
ARGH!
BIANCA:
OH!
(BOTH GIRLS SCREAM)
ALLI:
TAKE THAT!
(DESKS SQUEAK AND CLATTER)
ALLI:
GET OFF OF ME!
BIANCA:
(SCREAMS)
MR. SIMPSON:
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA,
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
THAT'S ENOUGH, YOU TWO!
WE'LL SORT THIS OUT
IN MY OFFICE.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
ALLIA, ARE YOU OKAY?
THEY SAID THERE WAS SOME
SORT OF FIGHT!
MOM, IT WAS AWFUL.
I WAS PRACTICING FOR
SCIENCE OLYMPICS,
AND THEN THIS GIRL,
BIANCA,
LIKE, ATTACKED ME!
MR. SIMPSON:
UH, I'M GLAD YOU TWO
COULD MAKE IT.
MR. BHANDARI:
HAVE THE POLICE BEEN CALLED?
SOMEONE ATTACKS OUR DAUGHTER,
THERE MUST BE CONSEQUENCES!
MRS. BHANDARI:
WHY WOULD THAT GIRL
WANT TO HURT OUR ALLI?
(SIGHS)
WHY DON'T WE GO
INSIDE MY OFFICE?
MR. SIMPSON:
MR. AND MRS. BHANDARI,
UH...
ALLI AND BIANCA HAVE BEEN
IN CONFLICT FOR A WHILE.
UH, THERE WAS SOME
VERBAL FIGHTING
AT OUR SELF-ESTEEM SEMINAR.
WHAT SELF-ESTEEM
SEMINAR?
(SCOFFS) NEVER MIND,
IT WAS NOTHING.
UM, INCIDENTS
AT OUR VEGAS DANCE
INVOLVED ALLI
AND HER BOYFRIEND.
MR. BHANDARI:
THAT BOY WHO CAME
TO THE CAR THIS MORNING -
HE IS YOUR BOYFRIEND?
UH... YEAH.
MRS. BHANDARI:
WHY WERE WE NOT INFORMED
OF THIS BOYFRIEND?
WE DON'T ALLOW DATING!
MR. SIMPSON:
UH, WE DON'T EXACTLY TRACK
THAT KIND OF THING FOR PARENTS.
YOU KNOW, I'M GONNA MAKE
A NOTE IN ALLI'S FILE, AND-
MR. BHANDARI:
HER FILE? LET ME SEE IT.
(GASPS)
MR. SIMPSON:
MR. BHANDARI,
IT'S NOT CUSTOMARY TO-
MR. BHANDARI:
I AM HER FATHER!
(WHISPERS) NO!
(SIGHS)
MRS. BHANDARI:
THIS IS NOT MY SIGNATURE.
FOR A DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENT.
WHY DID YOU GO
TO THE DOCTOR?
MRS. BHANDARI:
WHICH DOCTOR?
ALLI:
IT WAS FOR A CLINIC.
BUT MOM, I-
MR. BHANDARI:
WHAT IS HAPPENING, ALLIA?
WHO IS REPRESENTED
IN THESE PAGES?
ALLI:
DAD, I'M SORRY,
BUT I CAN EXPLAIN!
MR. BHANDARI:
SEXTING.
WHAT IS SEXTING?
MR. SIMPSON:
MR. BHANDARI, WE'RE HERE
TO TALK ABOUT THE FIGHT
AND A POSSIBLE SUSPENSION,
(SIGHS)
WHAT IS IT?
TELL ME.
(CLEARS THROAT)
IT'S UM...
WHERE YOU SEND REVEALING
PICTURES OF YOUR BODY.
BUT IT WASN'T TO EVERYONE,
IT JUST GOT OUT.
DADDY, PLEASE DON'T BE MAD
AT ME!
(CRYING)
MRS. BHANDARI:
GET UP, WE'RE GOING HOME.
I'M SORRY ALLI HAS CAUSED YOU
SO MUCH TROUBLE!
♪ It's been a long year
of trying to stay afloat ♪
(SIGHS TEARFULLY)
♪ Oh the constant struggle ♪
♪ My mind fights for a reason ♪
♪ My heart fights for hope ♪
(FAN CHEERING SFX ON WEBSITE)
♪ Well have I spent
any of this time alone ♪
♪ That's what this is for ♪
♪ I've been hoppin'
in and out of bed... ♪
MR. SIMPSON:
DELIVERY FOR MS. MIDDLETON.
OH!
(SIGHS) I ASSUME THESE
ARE FOR YOUR NURSERY
FROM YOUR
"NEXT TEEN STAR" FANS.
(GASPS)
YOU'RE KIDDING ME!
NO! NOR AM I A UPS BOX.
FROM NOW ON, HAVE YOUR STUFF
SENT SOMEWHERE ELSE, OKAY?
(PHONE BEEPS)
♪ I could not be alone ♪
♪ But now something
has changed ♪
CLARE:
YOU'RE SUSPENDED
FOR THE REST OF THE DAY?
WHAT ABOUT SCIENCE OLYMPICS?
ALLI:
BIGGER PROBLEMS, CLARE!
I HAVE NEVER SEEN
MY PARENTS SO MAD!
SIMPSON TOLD THEM
EVERYTHING?
HE DIDN'T HAVE TO,
THEY SAW MY FILE!
WHERE ARE THEY NOW?
IN THE CAR.
THEY COULD BARELY LOOK
AT ME!
THIS IS HELL
AND IT'S ALL BIANCA'S FAULT!
(SLAMS DOOR VIOLENTLY)
YOUR FILE'S NOT HER FAULT.
WHOSE SIDE ARE YOU ON?
I'M SORRY!
THEY'RE GONNA GROUND ME
FOREVER.
I'LL NEVER SEE DREW AGAIN!
THAT MIGHT NOT BE
A BAD THING.
(SIGHS)
MY LIFE IS SO OVER!
ON THE BRIGHT SIDE,
THINGS CAN'T GET WORSE.
MR. SIMPSON:
OKAY, ALLI, TIME'S UP.
SUSPENSION STARTS NOW.
HANG IN THERE!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
HI!
YOU BROUGHT YOUR MOM.
ANYONE NEED MORE COFFEE?
NOT THAT I'M HAVING ANY,
OF COURSE.
LISA:
WE HEARD YOUR NEWS.
I WAS VERY SURPRISED TO HEAR
THAT YOU'RE PREGNANT.
I KNOW IT'S A SHOCK.
I-I WAS SHOCKED.
LISA:
HONEY, BABIES DON'T JUST
RAISE THEMSELVES.
IT TAKES PLANNING,
AND MONEY.
YOUR BROTHER WORKS?
PART TIME.
HE GOT CUT BACK.
LISA:
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
FOOD, DIAPERS,
CHILDCARE WHILE
YOU'RE IN SCHOOL?
I HAVEN'T FIGURED THAT OUT YET!
LISA:
ARE YOU THINKING OF TAKING
TIME OFF FROM SCHOOL
WHEN THE BABY'S BORN?
MAYBE!
LISA:
JENNA, ARE YOU REALLY SURE
YOU'RE READY
TO RAISE THIS BABY?
I'LL BE READY!
AFTER I WIN
"NEXT TEEN STAR"!
KC:
BUT WHAT IF YOU DON'T?
LISA:
LOOK, SWEETIE,
WHEN THE SHOW ENDS,
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS,
YOU WILL STILL BE PREGNANT
AND THEN YOU'LL HAVE A BABY!
BUT WHEN I WIN,
I'LL HAVE A RECORD DEAL,
AND A NANNY!
KC:
GOOD LUCK WITH THAT!
OH, BETTER THAN
WHAT YOU CAME UP WITH!
"I'LL PRETEND
THIS ISN'T HAPPENING
AND LEAVE JENNA ALONE."
YOU PRETENDED
IT WASN'T HAPPENING
UNTIL IT WAS TOO LATE!
IS THIS WHY YOU
CALLED ME HERE?
TO YELL AT ME?
I DON'T NEED THIS.
LISA:
JENNA, JUST, JUST WAIT!
OKAY?
WE'RE TRYING TO HELP.
I DON'T NEED HELP.
I'M MY OWN HERO RIGHT NOW.
WHAT IS THIS?
YOU KNOW
WHAT IT IS, MOM.
UNLOCK IT!
NO! IT'S PRIVATE!
YOU ARE 15 YEARS OLD,
WITH A DISCIPLINE FILE
THE SIZE OF A PHONE BOOK.
YOU DON'T GET PRIVACY.
ALLIA, NOW!
OR I'LL OPEN IT MYSELF!
ALLI:
NO!
I-I'LL TELL YOU WHAT IT SAYS.
(SIGHS)
I HAD A BOYFRIEND
AND I HAD SEX WITH HIM,
AND THEN I THOUGHT
I CAUGHT AN S.T.I.,
BUT I DIDN'T.
I'M OKAY.
WHAT,
THE BOY FROM THE DANCE?
A DIFFERENT ONE.
LAST YEAR, BUT THAT'S
THE WORST OF IT, MOM,
I PROMISE!
(SIGHS)
I DO NOT KNOW
MY OWN DAUGHTER.
(GASPS)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(CRICKETS CHIRP)
MR. BHANDARI:
WHERE DID WE GO WRONG?
WE GAVE HER EVERYTHING!
♪ I've done you wrong ♪
MRS. BHANDARI:
WE DID OUR BEST.
♪ I've made mistakes ♪
♪ You've seen the darkest
side of me ♪
MRS. BHANDARI:
KIDS MAKE MISTAKES.
NOT MY ALLI!
NOT MY LITTLE GIRL!
♪ Please don't think of me
that way ♪
WE CAN'T STOP HER
FROM GROWING UP.
(CRYING)
♪ Would it be too much
to ask ♪
♪ To remember the girl ♪
♪ Who made you laugh ♪
♪ Stay, stay, stay ♪
♪ Stay... ♪
("NEXT TEEN STAR" MUSIC PLAYS)
HOST:
HAYLEY, GREAT PERFORMANCE
LAST NIGHT.
(AUDIENCE CLAPS)
HOST:
GOOD LUCK.
NOW, TO JENNA!
HI, EVERYBODY.
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
HOST:
JENNA, SOON TO BE MAMA!
YOU UNVEILED YOUR SHOCKING
NEWS LAST NIGHT,
WHY TELL EVERYONE?
I WANT TO BE HONEST
WITH ALL MY FANS.
AND FOR MY BABY TO KNOW
I'M NOT ASHAMED
OF HIM OR HER.
AND WHAT HAS THE REACTION
BEEN LIKE?
ARE PEOPLE WORRIED
ABOUT A TEEN MOM?
UH, I'M STEPPING UP.
I'M RESPONSIBLE,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
IT'S EASY.
IT'S OKAY, JENNA.
WE'RE ALL HERE FOR YOU!
(AUDIENCE CLAPS)
MONEY'S TIGHT,
IT'S HARDER THAN EVER,
BUT...
I-I KEEP ON SINGING.
(CROWD CHEERS)
HOST:
WELL, CLEARLY EVERYBODY
FEELS FOR YOU.
BUT TIME IS TICKING,
AND IT IS TIME
TO LOCK IN YOUR VOTES!
RIGHT AFTER THIS,
WE FIND OUT...
WHO IS LEAVING
"NEXT TEEN STAR."
DON'T GO ANYWHERE!
DIRECTOR:
OFF THE AIR,
BACK IN FOUR!
(WORKERS, CONTESTANTS CHATTER)
PIMPING YOUR PREGNANCY?
SHAMELESS.
ARE YOU JEALOUS?
RIGHT.
ALLI:
(SIGHS)
SAV:
HEY.
MOM AND DAD WENT TO BED.
ALLI:
HOW MAD ARE THEY?
(LAUGHS UNCOMFORTABLY)
SCALE OF ONE TO TEN,
I'D SAY, 50?
MAYBE 60.
(SIGHS)
THEY THINK I'M DIRTY.
YOU'RE STILL THE ALLI
THEY KNOW AND LOVE.
MAYBE THEY JUST NEED
A REMINDER.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
("NEXT TEEN STAR" MUSIC PLAYS)
HOST:
WELCOME BACK
TO "NEXT TEEN STAR"!
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
HOST:
BEFORE THE BREAK,
YOU LOCKED IN YOUR VOTES.
NOW IT'S TIME TO FIND OUT
WHO STAYS...
AND WHO GOES!
WE HAVE OUR RESULTS.
ANDY, COME ON DOWN.
(CROWD CLAPS AND CHEERS)
JENNA, COME ON DOWN.
(CROWD CHEERS)
MAN:
GO JENNA!
ANDY,
SURPRISED TO BE UP HERE?
ANDY:
I TRIED MY BEST.
I LOVE YA'LL!
(CROWD CHEERS)
JENNA,
YOU HAD A BIG WEEK
AND A BIG REVELATION.
WHAT IF IT'S NOT ENOUGH
TO KEEP YOU RIGHT HERE?
MUSIC IS ALL I HAVE
TO KEEP ME GOING.
I REALLY HOPE I CAN STAY.
WELL, IT'S ALL DONE NOW.
THE VOTES ARE IN!
GIRL IN AUDIENCE:
COME ON, ANDY!
HOST:
ANDY, I'M SORRY.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO SAY GOODBYE
TO YOUR GOOD FRIEND JENNA.
SHE IS GOING HOME
TO DECORATE HER NURSERY!
N...NO!
(AUDIENCE CHEERS AND HOLLERS)
(CONTESTANTS CHATTER)
HANG IN THERE, CHAMP.
I'M FIFTEEN,
KNOCKED UP,
I'M NOT ON A TV SHOW,
I'M A STATISTIC!
ARE YOU GONNA KEEP
SINGING?
(CRYING)
I'LL HAVE TO LOOK
FOR A JOB.
WHAT ABOUT YOUR BABY DADDY?
(SIGHS)
LAST TIME I TALKED TO HIM,
I KINDA TOLD HIM OFF.
HIS MOM, TOO.
MAYBE IT'S ABOUT TIME
YOU SWALLOW YOUR PRIDE.
GOOD LUCK.
(SIGHS)
(LIGHTS CLICK OFF)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
HOLLY J: HEY.
SAV: SORRY I'M LATE,
WE HAD A LITTLE FAMILY DRAMA.
HOLLY J:
WHAT HAPPENED?
MAYBE IT'S NONE OF MY BUSINESS?
SAV:
NO, UM...
SLUTTY BIANCA HOOKED UP
WITH DREW IN THE BOILER ROOM,
AND NOW SOMEHOW,
I'M THE CHAPERONE.
GREAT, A SEX SCANDAL
AND NOBODY BLAMES THE BOY.
DREW'S THE VICTIM HERE,
JUST LIKE ME.
HOLLY J:
YOU CAN'T BLAME BIANCA
FOR WHAT HAPPENED WITH DREW.
DID SHE FORCE HIM
INTO THE BOILER ROOM?
SO THIS IS ALL
MY FAULT SOMEHOW?
FOR TURNING YOUR GUNS
ON BIANCA, YEAH,
BUT NOT FOR MAKING
DREW CHEAT.
I MEAN,
THAT WAS HIS CHOICE.
NOBODY'S FAULT
BUT HIS OWN.
SAV:
IF IT HADN'T BEEN BIANCA,
IT WOULD'VE BEEN ANOTHER GIRL.
AND I GAVE HIM A SECOND CHANCE.
(SIGHS)
I'M SO STUPID.
BOYS MAKE ME
DO STUPID THINGS.
NOBODY SHOULD MAKE YOU
DO ANYTHING.
YOU ALWAYS HAVE A CHOICE.
(SIGHS)
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I DO.
MAYBE I CAN FIX THIS.
(CUSTOMERS CHATTER)
JENNA:
HI. (CHOKING BACK TEARS)
THANKS FOR MEETING ME.
WELL, WHAT KIND OF GRANDMA
WOULD I BE IF I DIDN'T?
(SIGHS)
YOU WERE RIGHT.
I WAS, UH, LIVING
IN A DREAM WORLD.
SO, HOW ARE YOU
FEELING NOW?
(SNIFFLES)
AFRAID I'M GONNA SCREW UP
THIS BABY.
IT HAS A DUMMY
OF A MOM.
MAYBE...
MAYBE ADOPTION
IS THE ONLY OPTION.
JENNA,
YOU ARE NOT DUMB.
AND THERE'S TIME
FOR THAT DECISION.
KC HATES ME RIGHT NOW...
(TAKES A DEEP BREATH)
BUT...COULD I CALL YOU?
(LAUGHS)
WELL, I WAS NEVER
MOTHER OF THE YEAR,
BUT...
WHATEVER HAPPENS,
WE'LL MAKE IT WORK SOMEHOW.
IS IT... NORMAL
TO BE THIS SCARED?
OH, YEAH.
(SIGHS)
ALLI:
YOU HAVE EVERY RIGHT TO BE MAD.
MR. BHANDARI:
WE DO NOT NEED YOUR PERMISSION.
BUT WHY WOULD YOU
CHEAPEN YOURSELF?
ALLI:
I KNOW.
BUT I WILL DO ANYTHING.
JUST, PLEASE,
DON'T STOP LOVING ME.
MR. BHANDARI:
WE WILL NEVER STOP LOVING YOU.
BUT IT MAKES US QUESTION
WHAT WE DID WRONG.
YOU ARE SO FAR FROM YOUR PATH.
I KNOW.
AND IT'S ALWAYS
BECAUSE OF BOYS
EVERY TIME!
(TAKES A DEEP BREATH)
HOW CAN YOU BLAME BOYS
FOR YOUR ACTIONS?
WHEN I'M AROUND BOYS,
I DO DUMB THINGS.
I MAKE MISTAKES.
(TAKES A SHAKY BREATH)
SO WHAT IF I WENT
TO AN ALL GIRLS SCHOOL?
MAYBE I SHOULD LEAVE DEGRASSI.
(BELL RINGS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
I WASHED YOUR SWEATER.
KEEP IT.
SO...
YOUR MOM TOLD YOU WE TALKED?
YEAH. I HEARD.
SHE'S JUST GONNA
TRY TO HELP.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO DO ANYTHING.
JENNA?
MY MOM SENT YOU THIS.
JENNA:
(GASPS)
"25,001 BEST BABY NAMES."
THAT'S REALLY NICE.
THANKS.
DON'T CALL IT KEVIN,
OKAY?
HUH?
IT'S MY DAD'S NAME.
BAD LUCK.
♪♪♪
HEY.
CAN I WALK YOU TO CLASS?
(CRYING)
I'M LEAVING DEGRASSI.
MY PARENTS ARE WAITING FOR ME
IN THE CAR.
THEY'RE TAKING YOU
OUT OF THE SCHOOL?
I'VE MADE A LOT OF A BAD
DECISIONS THIS YEAR,
SO I NEED TO GET AWAY.
FROM ME.
(PANICKED SIGH)
ALLI, I'M SORRY.
YOU SCREWED UP,
BIG TIME.
BUT SO DID I.
I BECAME THE GIRL
THAT GIVES GUYS LIKE YOU
A SECOND CHANCE.
SO, THAT'S IT?
ALLI!
BYE.
(SIGHS)
CLARE:
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH.
I KNOW WHO YOU ARE.
A TOTAL SCREW-UP?
NO, NO!
YOU ARE A GOOD,
FUNNY,
SWEET PERSON.
YOU'RE ALLI!
AND YOU'RE THE BEST FRIEND
A SCREW-UP COULD EVER HAVE.
(BOTH CRYING)
I HOPE THAT DOESN'T CHANGE!
YOU'LL STILL BE
MY BEST FRIEND,
EVEN AT SOME SCHOOL
ACROSS TOWN.
ALLI:
(CRYING)
WISH ME LUCK.
(LOCKER SLAMS)
(CRYING) BYE.
(CRYING)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)