WHATEVER MY MOM TOLD YOU,
IT'S NOT THAT BAD.
(SIGHS)
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR EYE?
FOOTBALL IN THE FACE,
SIR.
NOW THAT STUDENTS KNOW
ADAM'S... A GIRL,
I THINK HE NEEDS
TO TRANSFER SCHOOLS IMMEDIATELY.
WHAT? MOM!
WE CAME TO DEGRASSI
SO I CAN START OVER.
I'M NOT DOING IT AGAIN.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENS
TO TRANS KIDS
IN HIGH SCHOOLS?
ADAM:
ENLIGHTEN US.
HARASSMENT, ASSAULT,
BULLYING,
OR WORSE!
DEATH THREATS, GRACE.
ADAM.
MOM, STOP BEING
SO DRAMATIC.
THIS ISN'T ME;
THESE ARE THE FACTS.
SIMPSON:
LOOK, WE UNDERSTAND
YOUR CONCERN, MRS. TORRES.
BUT I DON'T THINK YOUR SON
NEEDS TO CHANGE SCHOOLS.
REALLY?
AND THE BOYS
WHO HARASSED HIM?
FITZ AND OWEN HAVE BEEN
SUSPENDED,
AND WE'RE TAKING A NUMBER
OF PRECAUTIONS
TO ENSURE YOUR SON'S SAFETY
HERE.
LIKE WHAT?
AN ADULT WILL ACCOMPANY YOU
FROM CLASS TO CLASS.
AND YOU'LL HAVE TO USE
A DIFFERENT WASHROOM.
WELL I'M NOT USING THE GIRLS'.
YOU'RE NOT.
THE HANDICAP WASHROOM.
SPECIAL NEEDS.
YOU'VE GOTTA BE KIDDING ME.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh!
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever! Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
ELI:
WHO'S THE SHADOW?
MS. GOSNELL.
CIVICS TEACHER?
LGBT ADVISOR?
(SIGHS)
CAN ALL THIS JUST...
BLOW OVER
SO I CAN BE NORMAL
AGAIN?
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE THE NEXT SCHOOL SCANDAL
COMES TO A BOIL.
HANG IN THERE.
MY FAMILY'S PISSED.
THEY'LL BE EVEN MORE SO
WHEN I INTRODUCE GRANDMA
TO HER GRANDSON TONIGHT.
SURPRISE!
SHE'S NEVER MET YOU AS ADAM
BEFORE?
AND YOU'RE NOT WORRIED
ABOUT SENDING HER
INTO CARDIAC ARREST?
NOW I AM.
YOU'RE ONE
BRAVE WARRIOR.
YOUR GRANDMA WILL ACCEPT YOU
IN TIME.
HERE'S HOPING.
MOVING OUT!
DAVE:
MAN, I GIVE UP ON MS. OH.
SHE'S GONNA BE AN OLD,
DRIED UP, DIGI-WITCH
FOR THE REST OF HER LIFE.
CONNOR:
YOU'RE JUST MAD SHE DIDN'T FALL
FOR YOUR MOTORCYCLE BLOG TRICK.
DAVE:
THAT'S NOT IT.
SHE JUST THINKS
'CAUSE I'M YOUNG,
I CAN'T RELATE TO HER.
IT'S AGEISM, YO!
JUST DO YOUR WORK
AND GET BY, THEN.
(EXHALES)
MY INTELLECT ONLY GETS ME
SO FAR, WES.
MY CONNECTION
WITH MY TEACHERS
ARE WHAT GETS ME FROM A "B"
TO AN "A."
BESIDES,
IF I CAN'T MAKE HER LAUGH,
I'LL MAKE THE CLASS LAUGH.
HOW'S THAT GONNA HELP?
IT'S NOT.
I'M GOING KAMIKAZE.
TIME TO TEACH THIS TEACHER
A LESSON.
ANYA:
IT'S A MOUTHFUL,
READY?
UM, NON HODGKIN'S LYMPHOMA.
LEIA:
IS THAT, LIKE, CANCER?
ANYA:
YEAH.
IT'S WEIRD, THOUGH.
I MEAN, SHE DOESN'T LOOK SICK.
MY AUNT HAD CANCER.
SHE DIDN'T LOOK SICK EITHER
UNTIL SHE WENT THROUGH THE CHEMO
AND LOST ALL HER HAIR.
AND... HOW IS SHE NOW?
SHE GOT MUCH BETTER
AFTER THE CHEMO.
UH, BUT THEN SHE DIED,
LIKE, RECENTLY.
HOLLY J:
ANYA, IT'S TIME TO FINISH
POMPEII!
DO YOU HAVE THE PIECES?
WHAT, AM I INTERRUPTING?
NO! WE WERE JUST TALKING
AND STUFF.
UM, I GOTTA GO, GUYS!
BYE!
ANYA:
BYE.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
UM...
I DIDN'T, I DIDN'T MAKE
THE STUPID VILLAGE.
NONE OF IT?
THE HOUSES?
THE TREES?
WOW.
UM... I, I'M SORRY.
I WILL, I'LL COME HELP.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
UM...
I'LL HANDLE IT.
IT'S OKAY.
OKAY.
(SNIFFLES)
(DIALLING BEEPS)
SAV.
I THINK ANYA KNOWS.
THAT WE'RE TOGETHER,
IDIOT.
YOU KNOW, ON A SCALE
OF BAD THINGS
THAT COULD HAPPEN TO HER,
THIS IS THE WORST.
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
SO WE WERE AT MY LOCKER,
I RIPPED OPEN HIS SHIRT
AND... HE HAS BOOBS.
HE'S A GIRL.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
ARE WE GONNA DO THIS
OR WHAT?
I'M NO LESBIAN.
NEITHER AM I.
LOOK, YOU NEED A PARTNER,
I NEED A PARTNER...
YOU NEED THERAPY.
TOUCH ME AGAIN
AND I'LL KILL YOU.
IT LOOKS LIKE
WE ARE AN ODD NUMBER.
ARE YOU OKAY
TO PARTNER WITH ME?
UH, ACTUALLY MY ANKLE'S
WRECKED.
I'LL SIT THIS ONE OUT.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S UP TO YOU.
(CLASSIC TANGO MUSIC PLAYS)
WESLEY:
SHE'S COMING!
GO TIME!
(LOW MURMUR THROUGHOUT CLASS)
MS. OH:
I TRUST YOU'VE ALL BEEN BUSY
ON YOUR BLOG ENTRIES!
DAVE:
OH, MS. OH?
YES?
WELL, WHEN YOU ASSIGNED
THAT BLOG, I...
FELT CAUGHT
WITH MY PANTS DOWN.
WHY'S THAT, DAVE?
WELL, YOU KNOW,
IT WAS MY FIRST BLOG ENTRY
AND... YOUR INSTRUCTIONS
FELT RATHER BARE.
CLASS:
(STIFLED SNICKERS)
MS. OH:
TALK TO ME AFTER CLASS.
AH, NO, I THINK I'D REALLY
RATHER DISCUSS IT NOW
THAT I'M FEELING,
YOU KNOW...
LOOSE AND FREE.
ANYONE CARE TO SHARE
WHAT'S... FUNNY?
PUT YOUR PANTS BACK ON.
WHAT WAS THAT?
SHE DIDN'T EVEN YELL AT YOU!
DIDN'T EVEN CRACK
A SMILE.
CAN I GET THIS SHIRT
FOR DINNER TONIGHT?
UGH.
WHAT ABOUT, UH...
THIS?
I'VE THOUGHT ABOUT IT.
I WANNA INTRODUCE GRAMS
TO ADAM TONIGHT.
THEN DON'T COME.
WHAT?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY WE CAN'T JUST HAVE
A NORMAL FAMILY DINNER.
I DON'T DESERVE THIS.
IT'S NOT ABOUT YOU.
I KNOW.
(SIGHING)
IT'S ABOUT OUR WHOLE FAMILY.
WHAT'RE YOU SO SCARED OF?
I'M SCARED THAT YOU'RE GONNA
START HURTING YOURSELF AGAIN.
I HAVEN'T...
IN A LONG TIME.
YOU KNOW, ADAM,
I DON'T ASK FOR MUCH.
I JUST WANTED TO HAVE
A NICE FAMILY DINNER.
THAT'S ALL.
LET'S GO.
SO WHERE DID YOU GET
THOSE BOXER SHORTS?
MY COUSIN KNOWS
A GUY.
IT WAS WEIRD HOW MS. OH
WAS ALL CALM.
LIKE SHE WAS SAD
OR SOMETHING.
YEAH, SHE'S PROBABLY
RIDING ON THE HOG
WITH HER BOYFRIEND
BY NOW.
GUYS.
DAVE:
WHOA, HER TEAR DUCTS
ARE ACTIVE!
SHE IS HUMAN!
SOMETHING MUST BE UP.
SHE CHANGED HER PROFILE
PICTURE.
DAVE:
NO LONGER IN A RELATIONSHIP.
OUCH.
WESLEY:
SO THAT'S WHY SHE'S SAD.
(CAR STARTS UP)
SHE'S GOT A BROKEN HEART.
I JUST WANNA PASS.
I FEEL BAD FOR HER.
HAROLD:
(LAUGHS)
PAM AND HAROLD:
(LAUGHING)
SO, HOW'S THE RESURRECTION
OF POMPEII?
GREAT. THANKS.
MOM?
DOOR NUMBER THREE!
AWW!
I TOLD YOU!
WHAT'S UP, HONEY?
UM... WHEN YOU GO
THROUGH TREATMENT,
ARE YOU GONNA LOSE
ALL YOUR HAIR?
MM, NO,
NOT WITH RADIATION.
GOOD.
BUT IT STILL MIGHT BE SCARY.
I'LL BE TIRED;
PROBABLY FEEL SICK.
BUT SHE'S GONNA BE OKAY,
RIGHT?
WHAT, THIS OLD SOLDIER?
OF COURSE!
I'D REALLY LIKE YOU TO BE AT
THE DOCTOR'S MEETING TOMORROW.
TELL YOU WHAT.
AFTER DINNER,
WHY DON'T WE GIVE
EACH OTHER MANICURES.
I CAN'T LET THE CUTE DOCTOR
SEE ME WITH NAILS LIKE THIS.
LOOK AT THAT!
HAROLD:
LET'S HOPE HE'S MORE FOCUSED
ON YOUR HEALTH
THAN YOUR NAILS.
AWWW!
DON'T BE JEALOUS, HONEY!
WHATEVER!
HOW CAN YOU GUYS BE LAUGHING
RIGHT NOW?
ANYA!
NO, I MEAN, YOU JUST SAID
THAT SHE MIGHT NOT BE OKAY,
AND YOU'RE ARE ACTING
LIKE NOTHING'S WRONG.
AREN'T YOU SAD?
OR...
HAROLD:
OF COURSE, BUMBLE BEE,
BUT WE CAN'T STOP LIVING.
OKAY, I CAN'T DEAL
WITH YOU GUYS, RIGHT NOW.
I'M GONNA GO TO SCHOOL
AND I'M GONNA FINISH
MY PROJECT, OKAY?
ANYA?
(GROANS)
GRANDMA:
YOU ALWAYS TAKE ME
TO RESTAURANTS
WITH PICTURES ON THE MENU!
ARE YOU TRYING TO TELL ME
SOMETHING?
NO, MOM. WE JUST HEARD
THE FOOD'S GOOD HERE.
NOT EVEN A CHUCKLE!
GRACIE ALWAYS LIKES MY JOKES -
WHERE IS SHE?
UM, SHE'S SAD
SHE COULDN'T MAKE IT,
BUT, YOU KNOW, SHE HAD
COMMITMENTS AFTER SCHOOL.
HEY.
OMAR:
GRACIE.
GLAD YOU COULD MAKE IT.
DREW:
YEAH. HAVEN'T SEEN YOU
IN A WHILE.
(PHONE BEEPS)
HEY, HOLLY J,
WHERE ARE YOU GUYS?
I THOUGHT WE'D WORK
ON POMPEII...
AND OF COURSE YOU FINISHED IT
WITHOUT ME.
BYE.
♪ And I bleed
just like anybody ♪
♪ Sometimes doesn't everybody ♪
YOU'RE ALL ABOUT TO DIE
AND YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW IT.
♪ I know that sometimes
I am but running wild ♪
♪ I feel just like
a little child ♪
♪ But tell me ♪
♪ Doesn't everybody ♪
♪ Sometimes doesn't everybody ♪
♪ Sometimes... ♪
I WAS CLEANING OUT
AN OLD DRAWER,
AND THERE THEY WERE.
OH!
AUDRA:
GRACIE AND DREW
WERE THE BEST OF FRIENDS
FROM THE DAY THEY MET.
OMAR:
THAT WAS TAKEN
JUST AFTER OUR WEDDING.
SUCH A BEAUTIFUL GIRL.
OMAR:
OH YEAH, WHAT BOOK WERE YOU
SQUASHING THERE, GRACIE?
ACTUALLY, I HAVE SOMETHING
TO TELL GRAMS.
GRACIE, PLEASE.
I'M UH...
TAKING BALLROOM DANCING CLASS.
GRANDMA:
OH, THAT'S WONDERFUL.
I MISS YOU SO MUCH.
♪ I cried out
on a moonlit night ♪
♪ I was thinking back on time ♪
♪ Cold breeze
takes hold of me ♪
♪ Whoa...
He was a friend of mine ♪
DREW:
(KNOCKING) OPEN UP.
YOU'VE BEEN IN THERE FOREVER!
COME ON!
♪ I'll keep aiming
for the sun ♪
♪ So that my shadows
all fall behind ♪
♪ Whoa...
and life just wasting my time ♪
HOLLY J:
THIS IS A DISASTER.
WE'RE GONNA FAIL!
IS THERE ANYTHING
YOU HAVE TO SAY FOR YOURSELF?!
NO.
I SORRY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
YOU WOULD JEOPARDIZE OUR GRADES
OVER SOMETHING SO STUPID.
EXCUSE ME?
COME ON, ANYA!
DON'T YOU THINK
YOU'RE OVERREACTING, JUST...?
ANYA:
OVERREACTING?!
GET ME OUTTA HERE.
UGH.
LEAVE ME ALONE.
ANYA.
I KNOW WE WE'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE TOGETHER,
BUT I DIDN'T THINK
YOU'D SCREW UP OUR TERM.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
YOU RUINED THE PROJECT
BECAUSE SAV AND I ARE...
TOGETHER!
MY MOM HAS CANCER.
AND I CAN'T EVEN
LOOK AT HER
WITHOUT THINKING
ABOUT HER DYING.
OH.
I'M A HORRIBLE DAUGHTER.
YOU'RE NOT A HORRIBLE
DAUGHTER.
THEN WHY AM I HERE
AND NOT AT THE DOCTOR'S
APPOINTMENT?
A HORRIBLE DAUGHTER
WOULD NOT BRING
YOUR MOM SOUP
THE WAY THAT YOU DO.
YOU KNOW, SOUP'S NOT GONNA
CURE CANCER, HOLLY J.
BUT YOU MIGHT
REGRET IT LATER
IF YOU'RE NOT THERE
FOR HER NOW.
YEAH.
(SNIFFLES)
THANKS.
MENARD:
EVALUATION DAY!
AND REMEMBER, I'M DOCKING MARKS
FOR SPAGHETTI ARMS -
KEEP THAT TENSION ALIVE!
YOU MAKE ONE UGLY GIRL.
UH, IS IT GRACIE?
OR...?
TRANNY?
BIANCA,
PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE.
SIR, IF I GO ONE MORE TIME-
NOW!
IF YOU WANNA SKIP
EVALUATION...
UM, ACTUALLY, I WAS HOPING
TO DANCE WITH YOU.
SURE.
AND, UH, IT'S GRACIE.
OKAY, GRACIE.
(TANGO MUSIC PLAYS)
DAVE:
MS. OH.
I WANTED TO APOLOGIZE;
I'VE BEEN REALLY OUT OF LINE.
IT'S FINE, DAVE.
DON'T DO IT AGAIN.
IF IT HELPS,
IT GETS EASIER WITH TIME.
EXCUSE ME?
A BREAK-UP.
A STUDENT IS NOT GIVING ME
BREAK-UP ADVICE.
YOUR MOTORCYCLE ASSIGNMENT?
IT, IT HIT A NERVE.
RIDING WAS OUR THING.
SO I COULDN'T HAVE PICKED
A WORSE TOPIC
TO SUCK UP WITH, HUH?
(LAUGHS)
YEAH.
AW, COME ON,
I MADE YOU LAUGH.
SO, DOES THIS MEAN I CAN GET
A SECOND CHANCE ON THE BLOG?
CHARM DOESN'T GET YOU GRADES
IN MY CLASS;
HARD WORK DOES.
I CAN DO THAT.
AND DID I MENTION,
YOU COULD DO WAY BETTER
THAN THAT GUY.
ENOUGH, DAVE.
NO SUCKING UP.
COOL.
OKAY, GOTCHA.
(LAUGHS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SNIFFLES)
(PAINED BREATHES)
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
ADAM...
IF I'M GRACIE,
EVERYTHING'S EASIER, RIGHT?
FOR EVERYONE.
(SNIFFLES)
WHEN I WAS HER,
I USED TO BURN MYSELF.
IT'S HOW I LET THE ANGER OUT.
BUT YOU'RE NOT HER.
I HAVE TO BE HER.
FOR MY MOM,
MY FAMILY -
FOR EVERYONE.
I'M TRYING SO HARD.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO CHANGE
WHO YOU ARE;
EVERYONE ELSE DOES.
HERE, LET ME HELP
GET YOU HOME, OKAY?
COME ON.
NOT IN THESE CLOTHES.
COME INSIDE.
I'LL FIND YOU SOMETHING.
♪ Tonight I find ♪
♪ That I'm right back
where I was before ♪
ANYA:
SORRY I'M LATE!
I'M SO GLAD YOU CAME.
ANYA AND PAM:
MMMM!
HI!
HI, I'M DOCTOR CHRISTOPOULOS.
IT'S A MOUTHFUL,
SO DR. CHRIS IS FINE.
ANYA, PAM AND HAROLD:
HI, DR. CHRIS.
DR. CHRIS:
WOW. IN UNISON.
OKAY.
WELL, I'M GLAD YOU COULD
ALL COME IN.
IT'S IMPORTANT THAT YOU BE THERE
FOR EACH OTHER THROUGH THIS.
SO LAY IT ON US,
DOC.
WE CAUGHT THE CANCER
AT A GOOD TIME TO FIGHT IT.
(RELIEVED SIGH)
IT'S NOT GONNA BE EASY,
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO STAY STRONG THROUGH THIS.
THAT'S NOT GONNA BE
A PROBLEM.
ANYA'S MY ROCK.
♪ She's like an image of me ♪
♪ Not how she looks,
how she sees the world ♪
♪ We see the same thing ♪
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHEN YOU LOOK AT ME,
DO YOU SEE A BOY OR A GIRL?
UGH, ADAM...
JUST ANSWER ME.
A GIRL.
I SAID BYE TO GRACIE
A LONG TIME AGO,
BUT YOU HAVEN'T
AND THAT SUCKS.
CAN YOU LOOK AT ME?!
I'M TRYING MY BEST.
I JUST DON'T KNOW IF I CAN
SAY BYE TO MY DAUGHTER.
THE I ONLY GET TO SEE HER
IS WHEN GRAMS COMES,
IN PICTURES.
YOU MADE SUCH A PRETTY GIRL.
BUT I WAS NEVER HAPPY.
I KNOW.
I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO;
JUST ACCEPT.
ACCEPT WHAT?
THAT YOUR LIFE IS GONNA BE HARD?
MOM, IT'S HARDEST
WHEN I'M GRACIE.
IF I'M GONNA GET THROUGH IT,
I NEED YOU TO SEE ME AS ADAM.
YOUR SON.
WE HAVE TO PUT GRACIE TO REST.
♪ She's mine ♪
(FIRE CRACKLES)
ELI:
I LOVE ME SOME BONFIRE!
THOUGHT IT'D BE A GOOD WAY
OF SAYING BYE TO GRACIE
THAT DOESN'T INVOLVE
HURTING MYSELF.
WHAT DID YOUR COUNSELOR
SAY?
WE'RE GONNA TRY
REALLY HARD
TO ENSURE
THAT DOESN'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
DREW:
WOO-HOO.
YOU FORCE HER TO COME?
DREW:
NOPE. SO ARE WE GONNA DO THIS?
WE HAVE SOME UGLY-ASS CLOTHES
TO BURN.
ADAM:
AFTER YOU.
DREW:
(CHUCKLES)
ALL RIGHT.
(FIRE CRACKLES)
♪ She's got an innocent smile ♪
♪ She'll break your heart
for a while ♪
ARE YOU SURE?
NOT READY TO BURN IT?
IT'S STILL ME.
♪♪♪