FIONA:
YOU SURE YOU'RE OKAY
WITH ALL THAT?
HOLLY J:
UH...IT'S SO NICE
OF YOU TO ASK,
NOW THAT WE'RE ALREADY HERE.
FIONA:
I KNOW YOU DON'T MIND
BEING MY STUDY-SNACK-SHERPA,
BECAUSE I'M GONNA HELP YOU
COME UP
WITH A KILLER THEME
FOR THE DANCE!
AFTER EXAMS ARE DONE,
WE'LL NEED ONE.
YOU KNOW, THIS THEME
NEEDS TO BE SPECTACULAR,
LIKE A ONCE IN A LIFETIME
TYPE OF EVENT.
SO LONG AS YOU'RE NOT
SETTING YOURSELF UP
FOR DISAPPOINTMENT.
I'M KIDDING, HOLLY J.
I'VE BEEN TO COTILLIONS
AND BALLS
ALL OVER THE WORLD;
I CAN DO SPECTACULAR.
HOLLY J:
GREAT! FIRST WE STUDY,
THEN WE PLAN.
MRS. COYNE:
HERE SHE IS!
SHERMAN:
FIONA, IT HAS BEEN SO LONG.
FIONA:
YEAH, NOT SINCE THAT SPRING GALA
AT THE MET.
THAT'S RIGHT.
SO, SHERM, I DON'T MEAN
TO BE RUDE, BUT...
WHY HAS THE FAMILY LAWYER
FLOWN IN
ALL THE WAY FROM MANHATTAN
TO SEE YOU?
MRS. COYNE:
UH, FIONA,
THE CASE AGAINST BOBBY
IS MOVING AHEAD TO TRIAL.
SHERMAN:
AND THE COURT NEEDS TO HEAR
YOUR DEPOSITION
ABOUT THE ASSAULT.
IT'S NOT BAD ENOUGH
I HAVE TO GO THROUGH IT ONCE?
I HAVE TO GO THROUGH IT AGAIN?
I MEAN, ISN'T THERE SOME WAY
AROUND THIS?
SHERMAN:
WELL, UH, THE ONLY WAY
TO AVOID IT
WOULD BE TO DROP
THE CHARGES ALTOGETHER.
WHICH IS OUT
OF THE QUESTION.
RIGHT, FIONA?
RIGHT.
WELL, I GUESS I BETTER
START SHOPPING
FOR MY DEPOSITION OUTFIT.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever! Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
OKAY, I CAN'T DECIDE
BETWEEN THE TWO:
TAKE ME SERIOUSLY,
I'M IN ALL BLACK,
OR LOOK AT ME,
LITTLE MISS INNOCENT?
MRS. COYNE:
YOU DO NOT HAVE
TO LOOK INNOCENT.
YOU ARE NOT ON TRIAL;
BOBBY IS.
GOOD POINT, MOM.
BLACK IT IS.
WHAT'S THAT?
MRS. COYNE:
UH, THAT'S BOBBY'S DEPOSITION
ON VIDEO.
IT'S SOMETHING THAT YOU
DO NOT NEED TO SEE!
(DVD PLAYER WHIRS)
BOBBY: (IN VIDEO)
GOOD, AT FIRST.
SHE WAS VERY VULNERABLE
AND I WANTED TO HELP HER.
SHERMAN: (IN VIDEO)
YOU WANTED TO HELP MY CLIENT?
BOBBY: (ON VIDEO)
SHE NEEDED IT.
WHEN SHE WASN'T THREATENING
TO THROW HERSELF OFF ROOFTOPS,
SHE WAS FLINGING HERSELF
DOWN STAIRS.
I MEAN,
SHE WAS UNSTABLE.
ERRATIC.
PLAGUED WITH DEMONS.
I... I FELT SORRY FOR HER.
(BOBBY SIGHS)
DUDE, WAIT TILL YOU HEAR
WHAT I HAVE PLANNED
FOR GUYS' NIGHT!
DON'T YOU NEED GUYS
FOR THAT?
(SCOFFS)
ANYWAY,
GUESS WHAT I ORDERED FOR US
ON PAY-PER-VIEW.
I DON'T DO THAT
WITH OTHER GUYS.
DON'T BE GROSS, ELI.
I ORDERED
"MIXED MARTIAL ARTS MADNESS."
BAD NEWS,
I-I HAVE TO BAIL
ON GUYS' NIGHT.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
WHAT ABOUT YOUR BROTHER?
MAYBE HE CAN JOIN YOU.
(SIGHS) AND TEAR HIM
AWAY FROM ALLI?
WHY DO GUYS ALWAYS DITCH
THEIR FRIENDS
THE SECOND THEY GET
A NEW GIRLFRIEND?
SO LAME.
LOOK,
I'M ONLY BAILING
'CAUSE I HAVE TO STUDY.
RAIN CHECK?
I GUESS I'LL JUST HAVE TO GET
MY NEANDERTHAL ON BY MYSELF.
THANKS.
(CAR HORN HONKS)
FIONA:
I FEEL GOOD, DR. SANDLER.
ARE YOU TAKING A LOT OF NOTES,
OR AM I CRAZIER THAN NORMAL?
IT MEANS THERE IS A LOT
GOING ON WITH YOU
AND I NEED TO KEEP TRACK.
WELL, YOU HAVEN'T HEARD
THE BIG CRAZY-MAKING THING YET.
I HAVE TO GIVE MY TESTIMONY
AGAINST BOBBY.
THAT IS SERIOUS.
RELIVING A VIOLENT EVENT
CAN BE AS TRAUMATIC
AS EXPERIENCING IT
THE FIRST TIME.
YEAH, BUT I CAN HANDLE IT.
I MEAN...
I'M IN A GOOD PLACE.
OW!
UM, FIONA,
I THINK NOW IS THE TIME
TO DISCUSS
ALTERNATIVE STRATEGIES
TO HELP MANAGE YOUR ANXIETY.
LIKE, MEDICATION?
THERE IS AN ANTI-ANXIETY DRUG
I'VE HAD GREAT RESULTS WITH.
TAKE IT WHEN YOU NEED IT
TO FEEL MORE SELF-ASSURED.
GREAT.
IT'S OFFICIAL,
I'M CRAZY.
SO YOU THINK TAKING MEDICATION
FOR A MEDICAL CONDITION
MAKES YOU CRAZY?
DOESN'T EVERYBODY?
OH! UH,
YOU NEED TO GET TO SCHOOL.
UM, TAKE THIS,
AND FOLLOW THE DIRECTIONS.
LOOK, THE ONLY THING
THAT MATTERS
IS THAT YOU HAVE THE TOOLS
YOU NEED
TO DEAL WITH THE STRESS
IN YOUR LIFE.
SEE YOU NEXT WEEK.
(SIGHS)
♪ Should we say goodbye now ♪
♪ Oh oh oh ♪
♪ Or keep it goin' somehow ♪
♪ Doesn't even make sense ♪
♪ Oh oh oh ♪
♪ Livin' with the silence ♪
(CORK POPS)
♪ 'Cause it's clear
that I'm not that strong ♪
♪ Tryin' to keep it
all together ♪
♪ Don't you know ♪
♪ You're a stranger to me ♪
♪ I'm a stranger to myself ♪
(BELL RINGS)
I HAD A GREAT TIME LAST NIGHT.
ZANE:
ME TOO.
HOPE THERE'S A SEQUEL?
COUNT ON IT.
(LAUGHS)
ANYA:
HI!
LOOKS LIKE YOUR DATE
WITH ZANE WENT WELL!
I ACTUALLY MANAGED
NOT TO SCREW IT UP.
SO, WHEN'S THE BIG
COMING OUT PARTY?
IX-NAY ON THE OMING-CAY
OUT-GAY!
WHY ARE YOU BEING SO SECRETIVE?
YOU BOUGHT A DATE WITH ZANE
AT THE BACHELOR AUCTION.
EVERYBODY'S ALREADY
SPECULATING.
WELL LET THEM,
I WON'T CONFIRM OR DENY
UNTIL AFTER FOOTBALL SEASON.
WHY WAIT?
'CAUSE I WANNA WIN!
IF I COME OUT,
(SIGHS)
IT'LL BE BIG DRAMA,
THE TEAM'LL LOSE FOCUS,
AND...WE'LL LOSE.
SO WHEN THE SEASON'S OVER,
IT'LL BE PRIDE DAY.
BUT I NEED TO GO BIG,
SO ZANE KNOWS IT'S FOR REAL.
ANYA:
WELL...
NOTHING SAYS "REAL"
LIKE BEING CROWNED
KING AND KING.
NOW THAT'S BIG!
SAV:
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S HEAR THOSE IDEAS, GIRLS.
WELL, I WAS THINKING
WE SHOULD REVIEW
ALL THE DANCES
WE'VE HELD AT DEGRASSI,
AND ITEMIZE WHAT WE LIKED.
OKAY,
SO...MORE OF THE SAME?
MORE OF THE BEST!
SAV:
YEAH, NO.
WE NEED, YOU KNOW, FRESH.
WE NEED... HOT.
WELL, THE HOTTEST DANCE
I'VE EVER BEEN TO WAS CALLED,
"A NIGHT IN MONACO."
GUYS IN TUXES,
GIRLS IN COCKTAIL DRESSES.
THE WALLS DRAPED
IN RED VELVET,
ROULETTE TABLES EVERYWHERE.
WHOA! GAMBLING IN SCHOOL?
ALL THE MONEY WENT IN
THE SCHOOL'S KITTY
FOR SOCIAL EVENTS,
AND WE RAISED BUCKETS
OF CASH!
YOU HAD ME AT BUCKETS OF CASH.
(FIONA AND HOLLY J LAUGH)
(BELL RINGS)
SAV: OH! THAT'S STUDY PERIOD.
I GOTTA HIT THE BOOKS.
LATER, GIRLS.
WHAT, THEME TOO MUCH?
(SCOFFS)
TRY I'M BLOWN AWAY!
I THINK WE CAN REALLY MAKE
OUR MARK WITH THIS ONE!
(LAUGHS)
OH!
SPEAKING OF STUDY PERIOD,
I AM HEADED FOR A BIG FAT B
ON PERINO'S EXAM.
WEIRD.
WHAT'S THIS?
FIONA:
OH.
JUST SOMETHING MY THERAPIST
GAVE ME
TO HELP DEAL
WITH THE DEPOSITION.
AND YOU'RE USING IT
AS A BOOKMARK?
IF I NEED IT,
I'LL FILL IT.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
HEY, I THOUGHT
YOU WERE STUDYING.
YEAH! UH...
YEAH, I AM.
I MEAN, UM, WE ARE.
CLARE AND I JUST WANTED
SOME ONE-ON-ONE TIME.
TO STUDY.
SO WHAT, ARE YOU TWO LIKE
IN LOVE NOW OR SOMETHING?
ADAM,
WE'RE JUST FRIENDS.
YEAH.
AND YOU DON'T WANT ME AROUND
'CAUSE I'M THE THIRD WHEEL.
GUYS DON'T DO THIS
TO EACH OTHER, ELI.
DUDE, I'M SORRY.
WHATEVER.
I DON'T WANNA RUIN
YOUR LITTLE DATE.
(DOOR SLAMS)
MRS. COYNE:
SHERMAN SAID THIS'LL
JUST BE A DRY RUN,
BUT HE WANTED YOU
TO BE PREPARED
FOR A HARD LINE
OF QUESTIONING.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
I'LL BE FINE, MOM.
I'M FINE.
I SEE THOSE LITTLE WORRY LINES.
(SIGHS)
MAYBE I'M A TINY BIT NERVOUS.
MRS. COYNE:
YOU DIDN'T FILL
YOUR PRESCRIPTION!
I CAN DEAL.
I'M JUST GONNA TAKE IT IN,
JUST IN-
MOM!
SHERMAN:
ALL RIGHT,
WE ALL SET?
HUH?
LET'S GET STARTED!
YOU BET!
FIRE WHEN READY, SHERM.
YOU OKAY?
(SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
(CLEARS THROAT)
MS. COYNE.
WHERE ON YOUR BODY
DID MY CLIENT...
COME IN CONTACT WITH YOU?
BOBBY DID MORE
THAN COME IN CONTACT WITH ME;
HE HIT ME.
FIONA:
AHH!
SHERMAN:
SO YOU ALLEGE THESE POINTS
OF CONTACT
LATER SHOWED BRUISING?
YES. HE GAVE ME A BLACK EYE.
SHERMAN:
ARE YOU CURRENTLY IN THE CARE
OF A PSYCHIATRIST?
BOBBY:
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
TO BE THE CRAZY ONE AGAIN?
SHERMAN:
MS. COYNE,
DO YOU SEE A PSYCHIATRIST?
FIONA:
I'M NOT CRAZY!
YOU'RE A LIAR!
MRS. COYNE:
FIONA, THESE ARE THE KINDS
OF QUESTIONS
THAT BOBBY'S LAWYER WILL ASK.
(SIGHS)
I SEE A THERAPIST, YES.
I DON'T REALLY SEE WHAT THAT
HAS TO DO WITH ANYTHING.
SHERMAN:
IT GOES TO CREDIBILITY.
MY CLIENT HAS CHARACTERIZED YOU
AS "UNSTABLE"
AND "ERRATIC."
HOW DO YOU RESPOND TO THAT?
BOBBY:
GET BACK HERE!
OOF!
(PANICKED BREATHING)
I HAVE TO PEE.
(GASPS) OH!
MRS. COYNE:
OH, SWEETIE!
SWEETHEART,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
UH... BETWEEN THIS
AND EXAMS,
AND PLANNING A SCHOOL EVENT,
I'M...
I'M JUST REALLY TIRED.
THAT'LL BE ENOUGH FOR TODAY.
FIONA:
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
FIONA! HEY.
FIONA:
HEY.
HOLLY J:
HOW'D IT GO YESTERDAY?
BAD NEWS IS THEY'RE PUTTING
MY SANITY ON TRIAL;
GOOD NEWS IS,
I DESTROYED THE UGLIEST LAMP.
AM I SUPPOSED TO SEE
A CONNECTION?
NEVER MIND.
HEY!
YOU DON'T WANNA LOSE THIS.
(SIGHS)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M UPPING MY CREDIBILITY.
BY THROWING OUT
YOUR PRESCRIPTION?
I'M FINE, HOLLY J.
BUT I COULD REALLY USE
SOME GOOD NEWS RIGHT NOW.
HOW'S THE DANCE COMING?
IT'S GREAT!
IT'S REALLY GOOD,
NEVER BETTER.
OH NO, WHAT HAPPENED?
SIMPSON'S CONCERNED THE THEME
ISN'T PARENT FRIENDLY,
BUT HE GIVING US A CHANCE
TO PITCH TO THE PTA TODAY.
WELL, THAT'S GREAT!
I CAN TOTALLY HELP.
MEET ME AT LUNCH,
AND UH,
BRING YOUR BRAINSTORMING CAP?
I HAVE ONE IN EVERY COLOUR!
(LAUGHS)
HEY.
I'M, UH, SAVING THIS SEAT
FOR ROYALTY.
I KNOW WHAT YOU DID.
BOLDEST MOVE EVER!
THAT'S ME, BOLD.
COME HERE.
HEY! EASY, DUDE.
NO PDA POLICY
IS STILL IN EFFECT.
(CONFUSED LAUGH)
I DON'T GET IT,
I CAN'T HUG YOU IN PUBLIC,
BUT YOU OUTED US ONLINE?
I DID WHAT ONLINE?
I DIDN'T KNOW
IT WAS GOING ONLINE!
THEY GOTTA TAKE THAT DOWN!
BUT THE WHOLE SCHOOL'S
SEEN IT.
(SIGHS)
YOU'RE OUT, MAN!
RILEY, IT'LL BE OKAY.
(SIGHS)
ARE YOU NUTS?
THE WHOLE TEAM'S GONNA BE
FLIPPING OUT AT THE GAME!
MS. OH:
OKAY, TODAY IS EXAM PREP.
I HOPE YOU'VE ALL BROUGHT
SOME QUESTIONS,
AND PROBLEM AREAS TO REVIEW.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'RE LOST.
JUST TRYING TO FIND
A NEW PLACE.
(PATS SEAT)
ADAM: SERIOUSLY?
FITZ: FREE COUNTRY.
I KNOW WE GOT OFF
ON THE WRONG FOOT,
BUT I'M OVER IT,
IF YOU ARE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU TWO GET IN A LOVERS QUARREL
AT GUYS' NIGHT?
THERE WAS NO GUYS' NIGHT.
HE BAILED.
PROBABLY BLINDED HIMSELF
WITH TOO MUCH GUY-LINER.
YEAH, PROBABLY LISTENED TO EMO
AND GOT ALL EMOTIONAL.
(FITZ LAUGHS)
CLEVER, GUYS.
ANOTHER STUNNING DISPLAY
OF VERBAL ACUITY.
(MOCKING) ANOTHER STUNNING
DISPLAY OF VERBAL ACUITY!
(FITZ AND FRIENDS LAUGH)
HOLLY J:
UGH! SO...
SIMPSON SAID THE PTA MIGHT HAVE
THIS KNEE-JERK REACTION
TO GAMBLING.
WHICH IS WHY
I FOUND EXAMPLES
OF OTHER HIGH SCHOOL
CASINO NIGHTS
THAT RAISED A TON OF MONEY
FOR THEIR SCHOOL,
WITH NO INCIDENTS.
HOLLY J:
FIONA, THIS IS AMAZING!
I THINK THIS MIGHT
JUST PUT US OVER.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
(BUTTONS BEEP)
NO WAY.
NO WAY! SIMPSON WANTS TO MOVE
THE PITCH UP SOONER.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS!
WELL, I THOUGHT YOU WERE
GETTING OFF WORK EARLY?
NOT EARLY ENOUGH!
UGH!
I CAN DO IT.
WELL, YOU'D HAVE TO START
WITHOUT ME.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN
OF THE PTA,
GAMBLING IS ALL ABOUT
PROBABILITY,
WHICH IS AN ELEMENT
OF MATHEMATICS.
YOU COULD SAY IT'S EDUCATIONAL.
WOW!
THAT'S GOOD.
THANKS.
ADAM! HOLD UP!
ADAM!
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
LOOK,
I KNOW YOU WERE STOKED
ABOUT GUYS' NIGHT.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE BAILED.
OKAY. THANKS.
SO WHAT'RE YOU DOING TONIGHT?
THERE'S ANOTHER FIGHT ON-
ELI:
TONIGHT?
I'M SEEING CLARE.
BUT I CAN CALL YOU AFTER.
I DON'T WANT YOUR PITY.
WAIT!
DON'T BE SUCH A GIRL!
I-I DIDN'T MEAN LIKE THAT.
YEAH, WHATEVER, MAN,
I HAVE OTHER PEOPLE
TO HANG WITH.
ELI:
LIKE FITZ?
HE'S NOT YOUR FRIEND, DUDE.
REALLY. YET I DON'T REMEMBER
HIM REJECTING ME
FOR HIS GIRLFRIEND.
ELI:
YEAH, BECAUSE MOST GIRLS
ARE SMART ENOUGH TO AVOID HIM!
SO YOU'RE JEALOUS
AND PARANOID NOW?
(HALF LAUGHS)
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DO PITY YOU.
YOU'RE MAKING
A HUGE MISTAKE.
(SIGHS ANGRILY)
MRS. COYNE:
WORKING HARD ON YOUR PITCH?
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT NEGLECTING
YOUR STUDIES.
I JUST NEED TO SELL
THIS GAMBLING THEME TO THE PTA.
OH, JUST GIVE 'EM A LITTLE
COYNE FAMILY RAZZLE-DAZZLE.
ANYWAY,
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
SUITS THE DECOR BETTER,
IF YOU ASK ME.
WHATEVER.
CAN I JUST FOCUS ON THIS?
HOLLY J'LL LOSE HER MIND
IF I SCREW UP
IN FRONT OF THE PTA.
MRS. COYNE:
COMPARED TO ALL THESE LAWYERS,
IT'LL BE A BREEZE.
I'M TAKING THIS
IN TO BE PRESSED.
LIKE I ALWAYS SAY,
THE RIGHT OUTFIT MAKES
ALL THE DIFFERENCE!
THANKS, MOM.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
♪♪♪
♪ Something in the back
of your head ♪
♪ Little tiny rooms ♪
♪ That we never get back ♪
♪ To locking the doors ♪
♪ With the keys to the truth ♪
♪ Now your memory's coming
to life ♪
♪ Your memory's coming alive ♪
♪ Just like a ghost ♪
♪ Coming out of the void ♪
♪ Showing you pictures
that you thought you destroyed ♪
♪ And now it's come back
to haunt you ♪
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
DREW:
HEY, I GUESS IT'S OFFICIAL.
RILEY AND ZANE,
KINGS OF THE DANCE.
YOU THINK?
THE CAT'S OUTTA THE BAG
AND THE CAT IS GAY.
(SIGHS)
JUST LEAVE IT ALONE, OKAY?
WHO CARES?
CHECK IT OUT.
STRAIGHT UP.
DO YOU LIKE DUDES?
YES, I DO.
FOOTBALL PLAYERS:
OH! OH, MAN!
ONE IN PARTICULAR.
WELL, SOMEBODY OWES ME MONEY.
I HAD TEN BUCKS ON THIS!
(PLAYERS LAUGH)
FOOTBALL PLAYER:
AW, YEAH! AW, YEAH!
(FOOTBALL PLAYERS LAUGH)
GUYS!
HEY.
HEY!
THIS IS OUR LAST GAME!
WE NEED TO FOCUS!
LET'S END STRONG
AND WIN THIS ONE.
YOU WITH ME?
LET'S DO THIS!
TEAM:
YEAH! (BARKING)
PLAYER:
GO!
HEY! YEAH!
LET'S DO IT, MAN!
RILEY:
LET'S GO, LET'S GO.
PLAYER:
WOOO!
♪♪♪
AHH!
WHEW!
WELL, LET'S GET STARTED,
O CAPTAIN, MY CAPTAIN!
MR. SIMPSON:
UM, WHERE'S HOLLY J?
OH, SHE, UM, HAS A THING.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN
OF THE PTA,
I KNOW OUR CONCEPT
IS CONTROVERSIAL,
BUT I WANT TO GIVE YOU
A FEEL
FOR WHAT THIS DANCE
IS REALLY ABOUT.
AS THEY SAY,
THE RIGHT OUTFIT
MAKES ALL THE DIFFERENCE.
GLITZ, GLAM AND GAMBLING -
ALL FOR A GOOD CAUSE -
AT DEGRASSI'S
"A NIGHT IN VEGAS."
(LAUGHS)
(MR. SIMPSON GASPS)
UM... HMM.
UH, THANK YOU, FIONA,
UH, BUT IT UM...
I'M HERE!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I'M JUST WARMING 'EM UP
FOR YOU,
AND THEY'RE LOVING IT!
LOVIN' IT.
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
HOLLY J:
WOW, UM...
I'M SORRY,
NOW THAT FIONA HAS...
PAINTED A PICTURE,
I'D LIKE TO TALK THROUGH
SOME OF THE CONVINCING REASONS
WHY YOU'LL WANT TO APPROVE
DEGRASSI'S "A NIGHT IN VEGAS."
(FIONA HICCUPS)
(GIGGLES)
(STUDENTS CHEERING)
ZANE AND RILEY:
WOOOOOO!
ZANE:
WHAT A GAME!
UNH! YEAH!
YOU WERE ON FIRE!
(LAUGHS)
WHAT CAN I SAY?
I WAS IN THE ZONE.
COACH ARMSTRONG:
RILEY!
HEY, COACH!
THIS IS MATT BARNES.
HE'S A SCOUT FOR EASTERN.
EASTERN?
THE TIER 1 TEAM?
COACH TELLS ME YOU'RE LOOKING
TO PLAY SOME COLLEGE BALL.
MR. ARMSTRONG IS
AN OLD FRIEND OF MINE,
AND WHEN COACH SAYS
HE HAS A PROSPECT TO SHOW ME,
I'M THERE.
YOU CAME TO SCOUT ME?
AND YOU DIDN'T DISAPPOINT.
(LAUGHS)
I'D LIKE TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT YOUR FUTURE.
SEE IF WE CAN MAKE EASTERN
A BIG PART OF IT.
ARE YOU FREE TOMORROW?
YEAH. OF COURSE!
ZANE:
WHAT?!
THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE,
YOU JUST GOT SCOUTED
FOR A HUGE TEAM!
YOU'LL HAVE THOUSANDS OF FANS
SCREAMING YOUR NAME!
UNTIL THEY FIND OUT
I'M GAY.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
WHERE DID YOU EVEN FIND
THAT DRESS?
I WORE IT TO CASINO NIGHT
AT MY LAST SCHOOL.
EVERYBODY LOVED IT.
ESPECIALLY THE GUYS!
HAVE YOU BEEN DRINKING?
DON'T LIE.
SO A LITTLE BUBBLY
WAS IMBIBED.
BUT HEY,
WE DID GREAT!
WE?
NO, THERE WAS NO "WE."
I TRIED TO SAVE THE PITCH!
THEY'RE OUT THERE TALKING
ABOUT HOW HOPELESS IT IS!
I'M UNDER SO MUCH PRESSURE,
HOLLY J.
I'M BARELY HOLDING ON.
HOLLY J:
RIGHT, SO INSTEAD
OF TAKING MEDICATION
PRESCRIBED BY A DOCTOR,
YOU'RE SELF-MEDICATING
WITH ALCOHOL!
I KNOW WHAT WORKS FOR ME.
(DOOR OPENS)
WELL,
HOLLY J,
YOU WERE TERRIFIC!
AND FIONA YOU WERE...
MEMORABLE.
SO, IT LOOKS LIKE DEGRASSI'S
"NIGHT IN VEGAS" IS A GO!
YEP! WHOO HOO!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
FIONA:
LIKE I SAID.
I KNOW WHAT WORKS FOR ME.