ZANE:
HEY, HOLD UP!
YOU OKAY?
OWEN WROTE "HOMO"
ON MY LOCKER!
DO I LOOK OKAY?
RILEY, DON'T OVERREACT!
WHO'S OVERREACTING?
I'M JUST GONNA GIVE HIM
WHAT HE DESERVES.
IT SUCKS, I KNOW!
BUT HE'S JUST TRYING
TO HARASS ME THROUGH YOU.
LET'S REPORT IT TO SIMPSON,
PUT THE GUNS AWAY,
AND TALK!
OWEN'S AN IDIOT,
BUT WE DON'T KNOW FOR SURE
IF IT WAS HIM.
OKAY,
JUST TAKE A DEEP BREATH.
YEAH.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
(STUDENTS CHATTERING)
OWEN:
OH! (LAUGHS)
HEY, RILEY...
(CAN CLATTERS)
WANNA PICK THAT UP
FOR ME?
I MEAN I'D DO IT MYSELF,
BUT IF I BEND OVER,
YOU MIGHT GET ALL EXCITED.
OWEN, GET LOST.
DON'T WORRY,
I GOT THIS.
RILEY, BE COOL!
YOU DON'T WANNA...
BYSTANDERS:
OOH! HEY!
DO THAT.
GUY:
OH! NICE!
(SPITS FORCEFULLY)
ARGH! YOU'RE LUCKY
WE'RE ON SCHOOL PROPERTY.
(CROWD CHATTERS EXCITEDLY)
WHAT?
(GRUNTS ANGRILY)
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever! Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
ELI: (ON VIDEO)
JULIET, I WILL JOIN YOU
IN THE AFTERLIFE.
ELI NOT LIKING ME
IS ONE THING.
BUT ABANDONING OUR GROUP
AT THE ELEVENTH HOUR?
IT'S UNACCEPTABLE!
IT'S LIKE HE'S GOT THIS BIG,
DARK SECRET.
HE'S SO CONFUSING.
HE IS A WEIRD ONE.
HE TALKS TO YOU.
NEXT TIME YOU SEE HIM,
CAN YOU INVESTIGATE FOR ME?
PLEASE?
SO I'VE GONE FROM THIRD WHEEL,
TO GO-BETWEEN.
MS. DAWES:
ADAM? CLARE?
CURIOUS.
I SEE YOU TOOK SOME LIBERTIES
WITH THE MATERIAL.
YOU MEAN THE LAST SCENE?
(KEY CLICKS)
ELI: (ON VIDEO)
JULIET, I WILL JOIN YOU
IN THE AFTERLIFE!
DEATH COME QUICKLY,
SO I CAN BE WITH HER ASAP.
CLARE: (IN VIDEO)
ROMEO! YOU DRANK THE POISONOUS
HIGH-FRUCTOSE COLA BEVERAGE?
NO!
CLARE: (IN VIDEO)
JULIET COULD JOIN ROMEO
IN DEATH,
BUT INSTEAD DECIDES
HE'S NOT WORTH IT.
AND CHOOSES LIFE.
GO JULIET!
IT'S CREATIVE, BUT INACCURATE.
YOU ARE AWARE
I CAN'T ACCEPT THIS, RIGHT?
IT DOESN'T FOLLOW
THE INSTRUCTIONS.
IS MR. GOLDSWORTHY
STILL IN YOUR GROUP?
MAYBE HE CAN HELP.
SURE.
OKAY.
HE'S ALREADY HELPED
SO MUCH.
(BELL RINGS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
ZANE!
YOU DROPPED SOMETHING.
WAIT UP!
OR ELSE WHAT?
GONNA PUNCH ME TOO?
HEY, I DEFENDED YOU!
YEAH, WITHOUT THINKING
OF THE CONSEQUENCES.
OWEN WILL THINK TWICE
BEFORE MESSING WITH YOU AGAIN.
YOU'RE JUST LUCKY
THERE WERE NO TEACHERS AROUND.
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE AFTER ALL
YOUR ANGER MANAGEMENT THERAPY,
YOU'D LOSE YOUR TEMPER
LIKE THAT.
BUT I DIDN'T!
I WAS THINKING CLEARLY.
I'M GLAD I HIT HIM.
YOU'RE KIDDING,
RIGHT?
FISTS DON'T STOP
IGNORANCE.
HOW CAN I SAY THIS
SO YOU UNDERSTAND?
WHEN YOU BEAT UP
A HOMOPHOBE,
IT ONLY MAKES THEM
MORE HOMOPHOBIC!
DON'T TALK TO ME
LIKE I'M AN IDIOT.
YEAH, THEN STOP USING
YOUR FISTS,
AND USE YOUR BRAIN,
RILEY.
TALK TO OWEN!
LISTEN.
OWEN WASN'T GONNA LEARN
UNLESS HE GOT PUNCHED,
SO I TAUGHT HIM A LESSON.
CASE CLOSED.
KEEP IT.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
♪♪♪
♪ You... ♪
♪ Out there on your own ♪
(FRUSTRATED SIGH)
YOU'RE A GENIUS!
(CHOKES)
I GOT A B PLUS,
ALL THANKS TO YOU.
YEAH! PUT 'ER THERE!
(LAUGHS)
WE'LL GET THAT ONE DAY.
GOSH, I HOPE SO.
OH, WAIT,
IS THAT MY FIRST LESSON
ON HOW TO BE COOL
LIKE YOU?
IS THAT DAY TODAY?
OKAY,
IF YOU WANNA IMPRESS ANYA
SO SHE'LL BID ON YOU
AT THE BACHELOR AUCTION,
YOU'RE GONNA NEED
ONE THING.
A BOW TIE!
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING
WHEN TALKING TO ANY GIRL
IS SELF-CONFIDENCE.
YEAH...OF COURSE!
(LAUGHS)
AMAZING!
OH! HOW DO I GET THAT?
OKAY. IF YOU KNOW
YOU'RE IN CHARGE,
GIRLS WILL KNOW
YOU'RE IN CHARGE.
YOU GOT IT?
NOW, ALL RIGHT,
LET'S SEE...
TALK TO ME ABOUT ANYTHING -
WHAT YOU ATE FOR BREAKFAST.
OH! UM, O-OKAY.
UH, MY MOM MADE ME
BLUEBERRY PANCAKES!
ALL RIGHT,
NOW LET'S MAN THAT UP A BIT.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(IN A DEEP VOICE) UH...
WHICH WERE DELICIOUS,
TO THE MAX.
AND YOU-YOU BEST BELIEVE
I COVERED THOSE BAD BOYS
IN NO LESS THAN 100 PERCENT
PURE MAPLE...
UH...BUT THEN I KINDA GOT IT
ALL OVER MY HANDS,
AND, IT-
UH, STOP!
WE HAVE SOME WORK
TO DO.
(SIGHS)
(KNOCKING)
CLARE:
MS. DAWES,
MY PARTNER'S GONE AWOL.
CAN I RE-EDIT THE FILM
ON MY OWN?
UM, YEAH.
THAT'S OKAY.
HEY CLARE,
I LIKED YOUR ENDING,
EVEN IF IT WAS OFF CURRICULUM.
WHAT LED YOU TO THAT CHOICE?
I JUST COULDN'T JUSTIFY
WHY JULIET WOULD
THROW IT ALL AWAY
FOR THIS ONE IMPULSIVE BOY.
I MEAN,
SURE HE'S CUTE,
AND FUNNY,
WITTY,
A LITTLE MYSTERIOUS,
UM...
THIS ISN'T ABOUT
THE FILM PROJECT, IS IT?
IT'S ABOUT ME AND ELI.
FOR THE FILM PROJECT,
WE KISSED.
BUT SINCE THEN,
HE WON'T TALK TO ME,
LOOK AT ME...
HE EVEN SKIPPED CLASS
THIS MORNING.
CLARE, SOMETIMES...
A FRIENDSHIP CAN CRUMBLE
UNDER THE STRESS
OF ONE PERSON WANTING MORE
THAN THE OTHER.
BUT IF YOU CAN MOVE ON,
YOU MIGHT BE ABLE
TO SAVE THE FRIENDSHIP.
YOU DO STILL WANT TO BE
HIS FRIEND, RIGHT?
I GUESS I'D RATHER HAVE HIM
IN MY LIFE AS A FRIEND,
THAN NOT AT ALL.
OKAY.
AND IT MIGHT HELP
TO HEAR FROM HIM
WHY HE DOESN'T FEEL
THE WAY YOU DO.
(SIGHS) FUN.
YEAH, BELIEVE ME,
GETTING CLOSURE
IS NEVER EASY.
BUT YOU'RE STRONG.
HEY, I HOPE YOU'VE LEARNED
SOMETHING.
YEAH.
THAT YOU'RE CRAZY.
I'M NOT!
AND YOU NEED TO STOP
MAKING GAY JOKES -
FOR THE TEAM.
CAN YOU HANDLE THAT?
OKAY, SO YOU PUNCH ME,
AND THEN YOU WANT ME
TO DO WHAT YOU SAY?
MAN, YOU'RE A WHACK JOB!
(LOCKERS CLANG)
YOU SAY ONE MORE THING
EVEN REMOTELY HOMOPHOBIC,
AND I MEAN THE TINIEST
LITTLE DIG-
AND YOU'LL WHAT?
(LAUGHS HUMOURLESSLY)
LET'S JUST SAY I LET YOU OFF
EASY YESTERDAY.
GOT IT?
ALL RIGHT, NOW GO OVER THERE
AND SHOW ANYA
YOU KNOW YOU'RE THE MAN.
YES, SIR!
YO! HEH.
ANYA.
YOU. ME. THE DOT?
SMOOTHIES?
BAM.
I-IT'S ALL RIGHT.
JUST BE COOL.
BE COOL.
(SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
HI, WESLEY.
WHAT GIVES?
UH, SORRY?
WESLEY:
I SHOULD HOPE SO.
WHAT'S SO IMPORTANT
YOU GOTTA IGNORE ME FOR?
THAT WAS MY MOM.
I HAVE TO PICK HER UP
AFTER HER RADIOTHERAPY TODAY.
OH. UH...
WELL, I WISH HER ALL THE BEST.
(SIGHS)
GOT ANY MORE ADVICE?
YEAH.
DON'T GO TO THAT AUCTION.
(SIGHS)
OH...
(LOCKER DOOR RATTLES)
THIS NEW ISSUE OF THE GOON
IS PREPOSTEROUS.
I PREFER THE CHINATOWN SAGA,
WHERE THEY REVEAL
THE SECRET
BEHIND HIS HORRIBLY
SCARRED FACE.
YOU WOULD.
CLARE WANTS TO KNOW
WHAT'S UP WITH ALL THE MYSTERY.
I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING!
I-I WOULDN'T DO THAT.
BUT, YOU SHOULD.
SHE DOESN'T NEED TO KNOW.
CAN'T YOU JUST TELL HER?
THE GIRL IS DYING!
OKAY,
SHE'S JUST REALLY HURTING.
AND I'M TRYING TO PREVENT HER
FROM HURTING EVEN WORSE LATER.
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I'M MEAN TO HER,
I KNOW.
I'M TRYING
TO DISTANCE MYSELF.
I DON'T WANNA TAKE HER
DOWN THIS ROAD.
BUT IF THERE'S ANY GIRL
THAT CAN HANDLE IT,
IT'S CLARE,
AND YOU KNOW IT!
WHEN I'M AROUND HER,
ALL I CAN THINK ABOUT
IS GETTING HER TO KISS ME.
IT DOESN'T END WELL FOR ME.
ELI...
JUST SHUT UP
AND READ YOUR COMIC.
(GUYS LAUGHING)
ZANE:
(SCREAMING) HELP!
(LOUD THUMP)
HELP!
GUY:
PEACE OUT!
OWEN:
(LAUGHING) SEE?
TOLD YOU HE WAS DIRTY!
ZANE:
(COUGHING)
RILEY:
(PANTING)
WHAT HAPPENED?!
I WAS COMING TO MEET YOU.
THEY-THEY JUMPED ME!
WHAT DID YOU SAY
TO OWEN?
I JUST WANTED TO MAKE SURE
HE GOT THE POINT.
BY THREATENING HIM?
SO DO YOU THINK
HE GOT THE POINT?
I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T THINK-
YOU DON'T THINK!
PERIOD!
LET ME HELP.
NO, NO, NO.
YOU'VE HELPED ENOUGH!
OKAY?
JUST STOP.
ZANE!
DON'T FOLLOW ME!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
CLARE:
HAVE YOU SEEN ELI?
I'M FINE,
THANKS FOR ASKING!
(SIGHS)
HE TOOK OFF EARLY.
STILL AVOIDING ME.
WHERE'D HE GO?
HOME, PROBABLY.
WHICH IS WHERE?
I NEED CLOSURE
IF I'M GONNA GET OVER THIS!
YOU KNOW, CLARE,
MAYBE YOU SHOULD GIVE HIM
SOME SPACE.
SO YOU DID TALK TO HIM!
AND?
I KNEW I'D GET STUCK
IN THE MIDDLE OF THIS!
THEN DROP THE CLOAK
AND DAGGER ACT!
WHAT AREN'T YOU TELLING ME?!
I PROMISED I WOULDN'T SAY.
HEY!
THAT'S A LIMITED EDITION!
AND IT'S ABOUT TO GET
EVEN MORE LIMITED, OKAY?
WE CAN DO THIS THE HARD WAY
OR THE EASY WAY.
CLARE...
HIS HOUSE,
WHERE IS IT?
OKAY, BUT YOU DIDN'T
HEAR IT FROM ME!
IT'S NOT FAR FROM HERE.
ARE YOU SURE YOU DON'T WANT
TO TALK ABOUT IT?
ZANE'S THE BEST PERSON
LIKE EVER
AND I GOT HIM THROWN
INTO A DUMPSTER.
THERE'S NOTHING LEFT
TO TALK ABOUT.
NOT EVEN ABOUT OWEN
BEING SUSPENDED?
PEOPLE TOLD SIMPSON
WHAT HE WROTE ON THE BUS!
AND I SHOULD HAVE BEEN
ONE OF THEM.
WESLEY:
ANYA! HI, HOLD UP!
OH SORRY, WESLEY,
I'M BUSY.
I'VE GOT THAT APPOINTMENT
WITH MY MOM, REMEMBER?
I'LL BE QUICK.
WELL, I'D LIKE TO DROP OUT
OF THE BACHELOR AUCTION.
WHAT? WHY?
'CAUSE I'M NOT GOING
TO RAISE YOU ANY MONEY!
IF ANYTHING,
I'M JUST GONNA COST YOU MONEY.
GIRLS WON'T BID
ON A GUY LIKE ME.
DROP OUT, MAN.
IT'S NOT WORTH
THE HEARTACHE.
NO! WESLEY...
YOU'RE THE TYPE OF GUY
THAT GIRLS LOVE.
YOU'RE SWEET, NICE,
AND YOURSELF.
(SIGHS HAPPILY)
(LAUGHS)
IF YOU SAY SO.
(SIGHS)
(BIRDS SING)
(KNOCKING)
DAMMIT, ADAM.
YOU FOUND ME.
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU CAN STOP AVOIDING ME NOW,
I'VE TAKEN THE HINT.
THEN WHY ARE YOU HERE?
I NEED TO KNOW WHY
YOU DON'T LIKE ME.
IF WE'RE GONNA BE
FRIENDS.
CLARE, COME ON.
IF YOU CAN'T TELL ME THAT,
THEN I DON'T THINK I CAN
BE AROUND YOU ANYMORE.
MAYBE THAT'S FOR THE BEST.
(SIGHS)
THEN WE'VE WASTED
EACH OTHER'S TIME!
WAIT.
LEAVE YOUR BIKE HERE.
WHY?
I THINK IT'S TIME
WE WENT FOR A DRIVE.
♪♪♪
(KNOCKING)
MRS. STAVROS:
RILEY?
HOW DID YOUR DATE GO
LAST NIGHT?
NOT GOOD.
OH, BABY.
WHAT'S WRONG?
(SIGHS) I TRIED,
BUT I MESSED IT UP.
I'M NOT GOOD ENOUGH.
IS THIS GIRL SMART?
TOO SMART.
THEN SHE'LL SEE
HOW GREAT YOU ARE!
JUST BE YOURSELF!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
MOM, I HAVE SOMETHING
TO TELL YOU
AND I DON'T WANT YOU
TO FREAK OUT.
BUT THIS GIRL,
SHE ISN'T EXACTLY...
RILEY,
IF SHE'S NOT GREEK,
IT'S OKAY.
I JUST WANT GRANDKIDS
SOME DAY.
♪♪♪
(CAR RUMBLES TO A STOP)
CLARE:
OH. I GET IT.
NOW THIS IS THE PART
WHERE YOU, UH, DITCH ME
AND I HAVE TO FIND
MY OWN WAY BACK HOME.
BECAUSE THIS IS GONNA BE
THE FUNNIEST JOKE EVER.
YOU'RE MESSED, ELI.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I AM.
I CAN'T JUST BE FRIENDS
WITH YOU, CLARE.
I LIKE YOU TOO MUCH.
BUT I CAN'T BE WITH YOU,
I DON'T DESERVE TO!
IT'S JUST...
(SIGHS)
THIS IS WHERE I KILLED
MY GIRLFRIEND.
E-EXCUSE ME?
LAST YEAR.
WE HAD A FIGHT.
IT GOT MESSY,
I SAID THINGS I SHOULDN'T HAVE.
SHE WAS REALLY UPSET.
TOOK OFF ON HER BIKE
IN THE NIGHT.
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
GOT HIT BY A CAR.
I AM SO SORRY.
JUST LIKE THAT,
THE CLOSEST PERSON
IN MY LIFE WAS GONE...
BECAUSE OF ME.
I HAD NO IDEA.
IT'S NOT FAIR!
WHY SHOULD I GET TO BE HAPPY?
♪ If I fall to little pieces ♪
(CAR RUMBLES AWAY)
ANYA:
LAST CHANCE!
SOLD!
CONGRATULATIONS, ALLI!
COME TO MAMA!
(APPLAUSE)
CAREFUL, WE NEED HIM
IN ONE PIECE
FOR SEASON FINALS!
(AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
AND OUR NEXT BACHELOR
ON THE BLOCK,
WESLEY BETENKAMP!
(APPLAUSE)
(SCATTERED CHEERING)
LET'S START THE BIDDING
AT...
ONE DOLLAR.
DO I HEAR ONE DOLLAR?
WESLEY, WHY DON'T YOU COME
AND TELL EVERYONE
A LITTLE BIT ABOUT YOURSELF?
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
WELL, I LIKE PEOPLE.
(LAUGHS)
AND I'M...
AND I'M GOOD AT SCIENCE!
(AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
WELL, IT SOUNDS LIKE YOU'RE
A REALLY SWEET GUY, WESLEY.
WELL YEAH,
THAT'S WHAT MY MOM TELLS ME.
DO I HEAR ONE DOLLAR?
YOU GUYS DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE MISSING!
WESLEY'S A TOTAL CATCH!
I'LL BID TWO DOLLARS.
SO I'VE GOT TWO,
DO I HEAR THREE?
COME ON, GUYS,
THREE DOLLARS
FOR THIS CHARMING MAN!
IT'S A BARGAIN!
GOING ONCE...
GOING TWICE...
LAST CHANCE!
SOLD!
GUY:
YEAH!
ALLI:
WAY TO GO, WES!
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED!
THANKS, DREW.
I COULDN'T HAVE DONE IT
WITHOUT YOU.
ACTUALLY,
I THINK YOU JUST DID.
TEN! DO I HEAR FIFTEEN?
FIFTEEN DOLLARS.
DO I HEAR TWENTY?
(DREW AND WESLEY LAUGH)
ANYA:
TWENTY GOING ONCE,
GOING TWICE,
AND SOLD.
HEY. YOU GOT A SEC?
PLEASE?
KEEP IT SHORT.
DON'T WANNA MISS MY CHANCE
TO GET BOUGHT
BY A MISGUIDED
HEATHER POULETTE.
ZANE, I LIKE YOU.
I WANT ANOTHER CHANCE.
RILEY...
ONE MINUTE,
YOU'RE THIS SWEET GUY
WHO MAKES ME LAUGH.
THE NEXT, YOU TURN
INTO A VIOLENT JOCK!
WHICH ONE ARE YOU?
I'M THE FIRST GUY.
THE SWEET GUY
WHO LIKES YOU.
THEN BE THAT GUY
ALL THE TIME.
MAYBE THEN I CAN DECIDE
IF I WANT TO GIVE YOU
ANOTHER CHANCE.
(SIGHS)
ANYA:
SOLD TO BETH.
COME AND GET YOUR MAN!
AND NOW DEGRASSI,
FOR ONE OF OUR MOST
ELIGIBLE BACHELORS -
OR AS A FRIEND OF MINE
PUT IT,
"THE BEST PERSON LIKE EVER" -
ZANE!
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDS
AND CHEERS)
DO I HEAR FIFTEEN DOLLARS?
FIFTEEN!
DO I HEAR TWENTY?
TWENTY! THIRTY?
THIRTY TO THE GUY
IN THE PAINTER'S CAP!
DO I HEAR THIRTY-FIVE?
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT,
THIRTY-FIVE!
DOES ANYONE WANNA TOP THAT?
GOING ONCE,
GOING TWICE,
RILEY:
FIFTY!
(AUDIENCE MURMURS EXCITEDLY)
GUY: WHO?
GIRL: OH!
ANYA:
OH! HI.
UH, WOW.
(LAUGHS)
FIFTY. ANYONE?
SOLD TO THE STRAPPING QB-1.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDS)
CLARE: (ON VIDEO)
STAR-CROSSED? NOT FOR LONG!
I'LL SEE YOU IN THE AFTERLIFE,
ROMEO!
(TOY GUN PINGS)
(LAUGHS)
WELL DONE! SOME VERY
COMMITTED PERFORMANCES.
I STILL WISH WE COULD
CHANGE THE ENDING.
YOU MEAN, THAT MESS
YOU TRIED TO HAND IN?
JULIET GIVES UP
ON ROMEO?
NO!
IN THIS VERSION,
JULIET GIVES ROMEO
SOME TIME.
YOU KNOW, I CAN'T HELP
BUT NOTICE
THAT WE'RE ON
SPEAKING TERMS AGAIN.
WHAT HAPPENED YESTERDAY?
NOTHING.
I TOLD HER ABOUT JULIA.
OH, THANK GOD!
I DIDN'T KNOW HOW MUCH LONGER
I COULD KEEP THAT A SECRET.
HUH.
YOUR IDEA
FOR THAT NEW ENDING...
I LIKE IT.
ME TOO.
SO, WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO
ON OUR DATE?
ABOUT THAT...
MY SCHEDULE'S,
UH, PRETTY FULL.
HEY, I BOUGHT YOU
FAIR AND SQUARE.
THE WHOLE SCHOOL
IS MY WITNESS.
AND WHAT'RE THEY GOING
TO THINK?
DREW:
SO...
IT'S OFFICIAL?
WHAT'S OFFICIAL?
WELL, YOU KNOW.
PEOPLE ARE WONDERING
IF YOU'RE GAY.
HE WAS JUST HELPING OUT
A TEAMMATE.
COOL. HEY,
IT'S NONE OF MY BUSINESS.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO COVER
FOR ME.
I KNOW.
IT JUST BOTHERS ME
THAT PEOPLE FEEL ENTITLED
TO AN ANSWER.
(SIGHS)
YOU'RE AMAZING.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHY
YOU KEEP GIVING ME CHANCES.
ME NEITHER.
BUT YOU KEEP TRYING,
AND IF YOU DIDN'T,
THAT'D KINDA SUCK.
SO THAT MEANS...
THAT MEANS YOU'VE GOT
SOME DATE PLANNING TO DO.