HEY, LITTLE MISS.
WALK YOU TO HISTORY?
HMM, YOU TOOK THE LONG WAY
TO CLASS.
SO I CAN SPEND MORE TIME
WITH YOU.
WHY?
IS THAT SO WRONG?
(MOCK DRAMATIC)
AH, SO CHIVALROUS.
YOU KNOW,
IF YOU KEEP THIS UP,
PEOPLE ARE GONNA
START TO THINK
WE'RE A COUPLE.
PEOPLE CAN THINK
WHATEVER THEY WANT.
SO, IF WE'RE NOT A COUPLE,
WHAT ARE WE?
WE'RE DIFFERENT.
AND SO WHEN I INTRODUCE YOU
TO PEOPLE,
I SAY "HEY, THIS IS DREW.
HE'S MY-?"
I GET IT, I GET IT.
YOU WANT A LABEL.
WHAT'S SO WRONG
ABOUT THAT?
LABELS CREATE PROBLEMS.
LOOK, YOU'VE HAD BOYFRIENDS
BEFORE, RIGHT?
OBVIOUSLY.
AND I'VE HAD
GIRLFRIENDS.
BUT THOSE EXES,
WHERE ARE THEY NOW?
HISTORY.
RIGHT.
THAT LABEL DIDN'T MAKE
THE RELATIONSHIP ANY STRONGER.
BUT US?
WE'RE DIFFERENT.
RIGHT.
YOU CAN'T BREAK UP WITH SOMEONE
IF YOU WERE NEVER GOING OUT.
SO WHAT ARE WE?
FRIENDS WITH BENEFITS?
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
IF YOU NEED TO LABEL IT.
BUT RIGHT NOW WE'RE FRIENDS
WHO ARE GOING TO BE LATE
FOR HISTORY CLASS.
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever! Woo-ooh!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS)
(SIGHING HEAVILY)
WAKEY WAKEY!
(SLEEPY)
OH, HEY.
IS IT TIME FOR CLASS ALREADY?
LOOKS LIKE YOU NEED
A FEW MORE MINUTES BEAUTY SLEEP.
(GROANING)
FIONA:
COULDN'T MAKE IT
TO YOUR LOCKER?
UGH, I FORGOT MY COMBINATION.
I'M LOSING IT.
THAT BAD, HUH?
(SIGHING)
YEAH. UGH.
WELL, WOULD IT HELP
IF I TOLD YOU
MY BROTHER ASKS ABOUT YOU
EVERY TIME HE CALLS ME?
DO YOU WANT ME TO QUESTION
BREAKING UP WITH HIM MORE?
WAIT.
"BREAK UP"
OR "ON A BREAK"?
EITHER WAY,
IT'S THE SAME.
I HAVE TO ADJUST
MY ENTIRE OUTLOOK ON LIFE.
WELL, LET'S DO IT
OVER LUNCH AT BABA'S.
I FEEL LIKE A FALAFEL.
I'M SKIPPING LUNCH TODAY.
YOU CAN'T SLEEP,
YOU CAN'T EAT.
YEAH, AND CHECK OUT
MY NEW BREAK-UP ZIT.
HERE.
TRY MY ZENO.
I DON'T NEED
ANTI-DEPRESSANTS.
IT'S FOR YOUR FACE.
THE HEAT WILL ZAP IT AWAY.
LOOK, YOU AND DECLAN WILL BE
BACK TOGETHER IN NO TIME.
I MEAN, YOU BOTH STILL
WANT YALE AND STUFF,
SO, IT'LL ALL WORK OUT.
(ZENO BEEPS)
YEAH, I'M JUST NOT SURE
I WANT IT TO.
WHATEVER. COME ON.
(SIGHING DEEPLY)
JENNA:
FRIENDS WITH BENEFITS?
IF YOU HAVE TO LABEL IT,
JENNA.
IF IT LOOKS LIKE
A BOYFRIEND
AND ACTS LIKE
A BOYFRIEND,
IT'S A BOYFRIEND.
WHAT?
WE MAKE OUT,
HE WALKED ME TO CLASS,
HE...
SAYS I'M CUTE.
DOES HE CALL YOU EVERY NIGHT
TO SAY GOOD NIGHT?
NO.
DOES HE LEAVE SECRET NOTES
IN YOUR LOCKER...
(GIGGLING)
TELLING YOU HOW MUCH
YOU MEAN TO HIM?
MMM, NO.
JENNA:
DOES HE MAKE YOU FEEL LIKE
THE MOST SPECIAL PERSON
IN THE WORLD?
(SIGHING HEAVILY)
I GET IT.
SO...
HOW DO I GET HIM
TO MAKE IT OFFICIAL?
ASK HIM ON A DATE.
A REAL ONE.
MAYBE WE CAN ALL DOUBLE
FRIDAY NIGHT?
IT'LL BE LESS PRESSURE.
BABY STEPS. COOL.
(RELIEVED SIGH)
(GIGGLING)
REALLY? NOW?
JENNA:
SORRY.
MAN, CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS?
THE BAND SLAM'S FRIDAY
AND WE'VE ONLY GOT
THE "THREE TENNERS" SIGNED UP!
HEY, LOOKS LIKE ME AND THE BOYS
ARE HEADLINERS!
OKAY, YOU'RE AN AUTO-TUNED
NOVELTY ACT.
CAN YOU FILL
A TWO HOUR SET?
WELL,
WE HAVE THE ONE SONG.
SIMPSON:
SAV! FRIDAY'S A NO-GO.
WHAT?! WHY?!
GERIATRIC YOGA.
GYM'S BOOKED.
SIR,
WHERE AM I GONNA-?
SORRY.
MS. SINCLAIR.
WHAT IS WRONG
WITH THIS SCHOOL?!
YOU KNOW, THIS PLACE USED
TO BE ABOUT THE MUSIC.
WHAT HAPPENED?
THE BAND SLAM'S OFF!
GO TELL YOUR BOYS.
RUN ALONG! GO!
(SIGHS)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
HEY, MISERY,
YOU WANT SOME COMPANY?
YEAH,
WE'RE QUITE A PAIR.
YOU KNOW, I'M A SENIOR.
I'M THE PRESIDENT!
THIS WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
THE YEAR OF THE SAV.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
WE SHOULD BE HAVING FUN.
MY FUN HAS TO INVOLVE SCHOOL
OR STUDENT COUNCIL.
WHAT ABOUT A DANCE?
A DANCE.
YEAH, LIKE A REGULAR,
OLD-SCHOOL DANCE.
OKAY, COOL.
AS LONG AS I GET TO DJ.
OF COURSE.
WE HAVE PLANS TO MAKE,
STARTING WITH FINDING
A VENUE.
BOTH:
"ABOVE THE DOT."
NICE.
I'LL ASK PETE.
VENUE? CHECK.
AND EVERY GOOD DANCE
NEEDS A THEME, SO...
SAV:
HOW ABOUT UH...
YOU KNOW,
A GOOD OLD-FASHIONED HOE-DOWN?
SERIOUSLY?
YEAH.
COMBINED WITH MY PANDEMIC
TRACK SELECTION...
PANDEMIC?
YEAH,
IT'S GONNA BE A THING.
(HOE-DOWN MUSIC
WITH A HIP HOP BEAT PLAYS)
(CHUCKLING)
'KAY.
SAV:
ATTENTION, MY FELLOW CAMPADRES
IN LEARNING.
STUDENT COUNCIL IS VERY EXCITED
TO INFORM YOU
THAT THE BAND SLAM HAS BECOME
THE HOE-DOWN THROWDOWN!
HOLLY J:
COME SOLO, IN GROUPS,
OR BRING THAT SPECIAL
GUY OR GAL
TO KICK UP YOUR HEELS
AND BUST A MOVE
AT "ABOVE THE DOT"!
SAV:
TICKETS ARE AVAILABLE
IN THE STUDENT COUNCIL OFFICE.
BOTH:
YEE-HAW!
WESLEY:
(TO HIMSELF)
OH, MS. OH,
INFINITY DETENTION WITH HER,
PLEASE.
DAVE:
YEAH.
MIGHT AS WELL,
IF WE'RE NOT PLAYING
AT THE BAND SLAM.
MAN, THAT SUCKS.
WE WERE THIS CLOSE
TO SHOWING THE WHOLE SCHOOL
HOW COOL WE ARE.
MS. OH:
WESLEY? DAVE?
MIND IF I GET CLASS STARTED?
GOOD.
NO BOUNCING!
GIRLS!
CONNOR...
(HAND SLAPS DESK LOUDLY)
CONNOR!
UGH!
NO DROOL ON MY KEYBOARDS!
I'LL GIVE YOU GUYS A MINUTE
TO LOG ONTO YOUR ACCOUNTS
AND FIND YOUR QUIZ RESULTS.
DAVE:
CONNOR?
(LIGHT SLAP)
WAKE UP, BRO!
I WISH I DIDN'T HATE COFFEE.
WESLEY:
UP ALL NIGHT AGAIN?
YEAH.
OH MAN, HAVEN'T YOU CONQUERED
THAT VILLAGE OR WHATEVER YET?
IT'S A REALM,
NOT A VILLAGE.
I CAN CONQUER A VILLAGE
IN LIKE AN HOUR.
I LOVE RPGS AS MUCH
AS THE NEXT GUY,
BUT YOU'VE GONE TOO DEEP,
MAN.
COME UP FOR AIR.
DAVE:
YEAH.
YOU DON'T GET IT.
NOBODY IN REAL LIFE DOES.
REAL LIFE?
YOU SHOULD TRY IT
SOMETIME.
DAVE.
ANYONE HAVE ANY QUESTIONS
ABOUT THE RESULTS?
THERE MAY BE A TEST.
(SIGHING)
(FRENCH ACCENT)
"ECOEURANT."
I DON'T KNOW.
COME ON, HOLLY J.
NOT ALL OF US WENT
TO THE LYCEE FRANCAIS
AS CHILDREN.
TRANSLATION?
NAUSEATING,
DISGUSTING, GROSS.
SAV:
WHAT'S GROSS?
HOLLY J'S ZIT.
FIONA!
NAW, IT'S CUTE.
IT'S HUMANIZING.
UM...
SO I WAS THINKING ABOUT
THE DANCE AND UH...
BALLOONS - TOO CORNY?
IT'S A HARVEST HOE-DOWN.
I DON'T THINK ANYTHING
CAN BE TOO CORNY.
(CHUCKLES) YEAH, YEAH.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW HOW I WOULD SURVIVE
WITHOUT YOU.
(CHUCKLES)
(GIGGLES)
ALSO ECOEURANT?
SAV'S CRUSH ON YOU.
SAV?!
ALL THE SIGNS
ARE THERE:
DILATED PUPILS,
GOOFY GRIN,
UNDUE PRAISE.
TAKE IT FROM SOMEONE
WHO KNOWS.
PLEASE.
SAV JUST NEEDS SOMEONE
TO BE NICE TO HIM RIGHT NOW.
SOUNDS LIKE SOMEONE ELSE
I KNOW.
AND YOU AND SAV HAVE BEEN
SPENDING A LOT OF TIME
ON STUDENT COUNCIL
TOGETHER.
WELL, WE HAVE JOBS TO DO,
FIONA.
IT'S STRICTLY
PROFESSIONAL.
WHATEVER.
BOYS CAN SMELL
VULNERABILITY.
SOMEDAY, MISS COYNE,
YOU'LL LEARN THAT BOYS
CAN JUST BE FRIENDS.
AS LONG
AS THEY'RE GAY.
WHAT'S THE FRENCH WORD
FOR PESSIMISM?
JUST DON'T BE SURPRISED
WHEN SAV DECLARES HIS LOVE
FOR YOU.
IT'S NEVER GONNA HAPPEN,
BECAUSE WE'RE JUST FRIENDS.
PERINO:
THERE ARE TWO KINDS
OF STUDENTS:
KEENERS -
THOSE WHO TAKE ENOUGH TIME
AND DO THE WORK PROPERLY;
AND THOSE THAT START THE ESSAY
THE NIGHT BEFORE
AND THINK I WON'T NOTICE.
RESEARCH IS THE KEY
TO THIS ASSIGNMENT...
(QUIETLY)
DID YOU HEAR ABOUT
THE DANCE?
(QUIETLY)
FRIDAY, RIGHT?
RIGHT.
WE SHOULD GO TOGETHER,
WITH JENNA AND KC?
PERINO:
STEP FOOT IN THE LIBRARY
FOR THIS ONE.
BHANDARI!
GOT ANY HOT GOSSIP?
ALLI:
UH...
(CHUCKLES SHEEPISHLY)
AS I WAS SAYING,
YOUR ESSAYS ON
VICTORIAN ERA ENGLAND
ARE DUE ON THURSDAY,
AND I WANT YOU TO ILLUSTRATE
YOUR KNOWLEDGE OF WHAT?
DREW?
(GRUNTS)
PERINO:
MR. TORRES HAS NO IDEA.
SARAH?
WHAT?
OKAY, I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
YOU HAVE 2000 WORDS
TO ILLUSTRATE YOUR KNOWLEDGE...
(QUIETLY)
ANYWAYS...
DON'T YOU THINK
IT'D BE FUN?
KIND OF LIKE A DATE?
(QUIET)
A DATE?
I'D LOVE TO, ALLI,
BUT I'M BUSY.
FOOTBALL?
NO, HOMEWORK.
MY MOM'S ON MY BACK
ABOUT MY GRADES.
I'VE GOTTA BUCKLE DOWN.
HOMEWORK,
ON A FRIDAY NIGHT?
WHAT?
ARE YOU LIKE FAILING?
NO. DO YOU WANT ME TO?
UH, NO,
OF COURSE NOT.
THEN GET OFF MY BACK!
PERINO:
GUYS!
ZIP IT!
ESSAYS WILL BE DUE THURSDAY.
(UPSET HUFF)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
CONNOR:
NIGHTSHIFT'S FORTRESS IS...
(ANIMATED MONSTER ROARS)
DESTROYED!
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.
LOVEQUEEN16:
WHAT A RUSH!
IT FEELS LIKE WE CAN
DO ANYTHING
WHEN WE'RE TOGETHER!
NEXT UP, LEVEL 16 -
FORT DESTINY!
LOVEQUEEN16:
WE'LL RULE AS EMPEROR
AND EMPRESS!
EMPEROR AND EMPRESS.
I LIKE THAT.
LOVEQUEEN16:
ONLY IN REALM OF DOOM, HUH?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
LOVEQUEEN16:
THE TRUTH IS
IT COULDN'T BE FURTHER
FROM THE REALITY OF MY LIFE.
I BET YOUR FRIENDS
ALL THINK YOU'RE THE COOLEST.
MY FRIENDS?
I ONLY HAVE, LIKE, TWO
AND THEY DON'T EVEN
UNDERSTAND ME.
NOT LIKE YOU DO.
THEN WE'RE LUCKY
WE FOUND EACH OTHER.
(DOOR OPENING)
SIMPSON:
CONNOR, YOU READY?
SIMPSON SHUTTLE TAKING OFF
IN 5, 4, 3!
CONNOR:
(QUIETLY)
I HAVE TO GO TO SCHOOL.
LOVEQUEEN16:
IT'S MORNING ALREADY?
LET'S DO IT AGAIN SOON?
YEAH, FOR SURE.
I CAN'T WAIT. BYE.
SIMPSON:
CONNOR! I AM NOT PLAYING!
(MOUSE CLICKS)
(LOW MURMUR OF STUDENT CHATTER)
CAN WE TALK?
LOOK, ABOUT THE DANCE-
IT'S OKAY.
YOU'RE UNDER
A LOT OF PRESSURE.
AND ALL THIS TALK
OF DATING, IT'S...
I UNDERSTAND.
SO HOW'S YOUR PAPER
COMING?
GREAT.
CAN I SEE IT?
UH, IT'S NOT REALLY
DONE YET.
OKAY.
HEY!
"THE VICTORIAN ERA
WAS AN ERA
(LAUGHING)
WHERE LOTS OF THINGS
HAPPENED"?
IT'S NOT DONE YET.
(CHUCKLING)
WELL, GOOD.
BECAUSE I DID
SOME RESEARCH
AND I PRINTED THIS OFF
FOR YOU.
I DON'T NEED ANY HELP,
ALLI.
WELL, I JUST THOUGHT
THAT IF WE TAG-TEAMED
IT WOULD FREE UP SOME TIME
FOR THE DANCE.
ALLI!
JUST TRYING TO HELP.
AND I APPRECIATE IT.
BUT I CAN DO THIS ESSAY
ON MY OWN.
OH. OKAY.
BUT IF YOU GOT AN "A"
WOULD YOUR MOM MAYBE
RECONSIDER FRIDAY NIGHT?
SHE'LL ASK WHY
I DIDN'T GET AN A-PLUS.
WELL, WHAT IF YOU DID
GET AN A-PLUS?
(CHUCKLES)
DON'T GET YOUR HOPES UP.
HOLLY J:
UH, YEAH, YEAH.
TWO CASES SHOULD BE FINE.
BETTER MAKE IT THREE.
THANKS.
SAV:
UM, FOUR...
NO, FIVE...
FIVE HUNDRED BALLOONS.
HELIUM?
YEAH, THE FLOATY KIND, RIGHT?
OKAY, THANK YOU.
(PHONE BEEPS OFF)
LOOK AT US!
BUSY BEAVERS.
YEAH, YOU WERE RIGHT
ABOUT THE DISTRACTION.
THAT'S WHAT
THE DOCTOR ORDERED.
SO, HOW ARE YOU?
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH.
SKIN CRISIS SOLVED.
THAT WAS FAST.
YEAH, FIONA'S NEVER GETTING
HER ZENO BACK.
YEAH, THAT'S COOL,
BUT UM...
I MEANT HOW'S THE...
DECLAN BREAKUPY STUFF
GOING?
YEAH, I'M...
FEELING A LITTLE BETTER.
YEAH, GOOD.
NO, 'CAUSE I WAS GONNA SUGGEST
MAYBE MORE OF A DISTRACTION...
SAY TONIGHT?
SOUNDS TEMPTING...
BUT I HAVE TO WORK.
(SIGHS)
RIGHT, YEAH.
AND I MEAN, UM,
I'M SURE YOU'VE GOT TONS
OF WAY BETTER DISTRACTIONS
ANYWAYS.
YEAH, TONS.
(EMBARRASED EXHALE)
HOLLY J:
HEY.
(NERVOUS THROAT CLEAR)
MY SHIFT'S OVER AT 8:00.
WILL YOUR PARENTS
LET YOU COME MEET ME
FOR FREE SNACKS?
YEAH. AND, OF COURSE,
TO GO OVER, YOU KNOW,
STUDENT COUNCIL CONCERNS
WITH MY VP.
I COULD SELL IT.
(MOUSE CLICKS)
(CLICKING REPEATEDLY)
(DEJECTED SIGH)
HEY, CON MAN.
COMING TO SHOOT SOME HOOPS?
YEAH, I'LL, I'LL-
I'M JUST WAITING FOR A MESSAGE.
FROM WHO?
UH, LOVEQUEEN6...
I MEAN, JUST THIS GIRL.
A GIRLFRIEND?
SHE'S A GIRL
AND SHE'S A FRIEND, SO...
SHUT THE FRONT DOOR.
YOU HAVE A WOMAN?
CONNOR:
YEAH, WE CHAT WHILE
WE PLAY ONLINE,
AND I LIKE TALKING TO HER.
SHE LISTENS.
SHE UNDERSTANDS ME.
NO, YEAH, THAT'S GREAT.
YOU GOT ANY PICS?
YEAH,
THIS ONE RIGHT HERE.
WESLEY:
A PURPLE ALIEN WITH GOAT HORNS?
YOUR HEAD ISN'T PERFECT.
DAVE:
(SNICKERING)
YOU MEAN YOU'VE NEVER
SEEN HER?
NO, BUT I KNOW HER, DAVE.
YEAH, FOR ALL YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE TALKING TO A FAT DUDE
WITH NO TEETH.
(SIGHING HEAVILY)
WESLEY:
SO YOU'RE NOT GOING TO COME OUT
AND PLAY BASKETBALL?
I CAN'T TAKE DAVE ON
ALONE!
YEAH, DUDE,
SERIOUSLY,
LEAVE FANTASY LAND,
COME HELP WES OUT.
OKAY, FINE.
I'LL BE OUT IN A MINUTE!
COOL.
(SIGHING)
(FEMALE COUNTRY SINGER TWANGS)
♪ Don't go borrowing trouble ♪
♪ Don't go dancing for rain ♪
♪ It don't have to hurt, babe ♪
♪ Don't go beckoning pain ♪
♪ Take it easy lovin' ♪
♪ What more can I say? ♪
♪ Don't go borrowing trouble ♪
♪ And give love away ♪
♪ We make plenty of money ♪
♪ And so little time... ♪
(CLEARING THROAT)
FREE NACHOS?
THE COOK SCREWED UP
ANOTHER ORDER.
HOW DO YOU SCREW UP
NACHOS?
(SIGHING)
IT'S NOT A BURRITO.
AH, THANK YOU, JUAN.
THIS YOUR BOYFRIEND?
OH NO,
WE'RE JUST FRIENDS.
HI.
COULD YOU IMAGINE?
US TOGETHER?
RIDICULOUS.
TOTALLY.
♪ I'm right by your side,
babe ♪
♪ With every bit of my heart ♪
SAV:
TICKETS ARE GOING FAST
FOR FRIDAY NIGHT'S
HOE-DOWN THROWDOWN!
DON'T MISS OUT!
YEE-HAW!
(TYPING RAPIDLY)
(SIGHING)
JENNA:
YOU LOOK BUSY.
ALLI:
LATER. TYPING FURIOUSLY.
DID YOU HELP DREW
WITH HIS ESSAY?
SORT OF.
SORT OF?
I'M SORT OF HELPING HIM NOW.
PRINT.
YOU'RE WRITING IT FOR HIM?
NOT EXACTLY.
I'M JUST COMING UP
WITH A THESIS
AND OFFERING
SUPPORTING ARGUMENTS.
SO YOU'RE WRITING IT.
OKAY, FINE.
BUT IT'S FOR A GOOD CAUSE.
I MEAN,
IF DREW GETS A GOOD MARK,
THEN MAYBE HIS MOM'LL
LET HIM GO TO THE DANCE.
WHAT IF PERINO FINDS OUT?
HOW WOULD HE?
IT'S A DREW TORRES
ORIGINAL.
I GUESS IT'S WORTH IT.
WELL, YOU'D HELP
YOUR BOYFRIEND, RIGHT?
YEAH.
PUT IT ON
PERINO'S DESK,
DREW'S SURPRISED
AND HAPPY,
AND YOU AND I CAN PLAN
DANCE OUTFITS.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
(EXCITED GIGGLE)
(SIGHING)
HOW'D THE ESSAY GO?
ALLI:
FEELING PRETTY GOOD ABOUT IT.
YOURS TOO.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN MINE?
I DIDN'T EVEN FINISH.
SURE YOU DID.
A-PLUS MATERIAL,
I GUARANTEE IT.
WHOA, YOU WROTE IT?!
AH, SPELL-CHECKED,
PRINTED,
AND PUT IT ON
PERINO'S DESK.
YOUR MOM WILL BE
VERY IMPRESSED.
WHOA, DO YOU REALIZE-
PERINO:
EVERYBODY, PLEASE,
PASS YOUR ESSAYS TO THE FRONT
OF THE CLASS.
UM, MR. PERINO?
NO, MR. TORRES,
THERE WILL BE NO EXTENSION
ON THIS DEADLINE.
DREW:
NO, MR. PERINO,
THIS ISN'T ABOUT-
APPARENTLY YOU DO NOT
NEED ONE.
MR. PERINO,
THAT'S NOT MY-
YOUR USUAL
LAST-MINUTE EFFORT?
APPARENTLY NOT.
THIS INTRO'S PRETTY IMPRESSIVE.
REALLY?
PERINO:
YEAH.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
BY "DISAMBIGUATED POLICY"?
UM...
HMM.
I THINK YOU SAID IT
IN CLASS ONCE.
YEAH, DID I SPELL IT WRONG?
NO. NO, YOU DIDN'T.
AND ALONG WITH
"SOLIPSISTIC"?
DREW:
(NERVOUS CHUCKLE)
FEMALE STUDENT:
SOLIPSISTIC?
WHY DON'T YOU SAVE ME
THE ONLINE SCAN?
DID YOU PLAGIARIZE?
DID YOU BUY IT ONLINE
OR DID YOU GET SOME SMART GIRL
TO DO THE WORK FOR YOU INSTEAD?
NO, SIR, I UH...
YEAH, YOU BETTER
HIT THE OFFICE.
SIR, YOU'RE RIGHT!
I WROTE IT.
WELL THAT MAKES MORE SENSE.
BUT DREW DIDN'T KNOW.
I JUST WANTED HIM TO FINISH
AND GET A GOOD MARK.
I'M SORRY.
HE HAD NO IDEA.
IS THIS TRUE?
OKAY, ALLI,
YOU KNOW WHERE TO GO.
DREW? I'M DOCKING YOU A GRADE.
BUT, SIR,
I TOLD HER NOT TO!
I'M JUST HEDGING MY BETS.
(SIGHING)
I'M SORRY.
(HELIUM HISSES)
HOLLY J:
BALLOONS.
FESTIVE.
(CHUCKLES)
HOW ARE THINGS SHAPING UP
FOR FRIDAY?
UH, HOLLY J,
I HAVE A CONFESSION
TO MAKE.
SAV, ME TOO.
DON'T KILL ME,
BUT THOSE ARE THE REST
OF THE BALLOONS.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
THEY WEREN'T INFLATED?!
YEAH, APPARENTLY
YOU HAVE TO SPECIFY.
I DON'T KNOW.
ONLY 495 MORE TO GO THOUGH,
SO...
ANY CHANCE YOU COULD SKIP
NEXT PERIOD?
ANYTHING TO GET OUT
OF FRENCH.
THERE IS AN UPSIDE,
HOWEVER.
(AIR SQUEAKING)
(HELIUM VOICE)
YOU GET TO HANG OUT
WITH YOUR PRESIDENT!
WHOA!
EASY ON THE GAS, MR. PREZ!
(HELIUM VOICE)
ALL THE COOL KIDS
ARE DOING IT.
YOU KNOW YOU WANT TO.
MMM...
(AIR SQUEAKING)
(HELIUM VOICE)
THERE'S JUST SO MUCH
PEER PRESSURE.
BOTH:
(LAUGHING)
(AIR SQUEAKING)
"HELIUM:
IT'S THE RIGHT THING TO DO."
BOTH:
(LAUGHING)
WOW.
HI.
I'M SORRY.
UM...
I THOUGHT...
NO, YEAH, IT'S FINE.
(NERVOUS CHUCKLE)
SHOOT, UM...
I WAS SUPPOSED
TO MEET FIONA,
SO IS IT OKAY
IF WE FINISH THESE LATER?
UH, YUP. YUP.
♪ If there were a way ♪
♪ I would even the score ♪
♪ You would love me less
and I'd love you more ♪
(DOOR OPENS)
♪ I think I knew all along ♪
♪ We were just wrong... ♪
(SIGHING HEAVILY)
WELL, I GOT A MASSIVE
MAKEUP ESSAY,
BUT IT COULD'VE
BEEN WORSE.
HOW?
WELL, APPARENTLY DOING
SOMEONE ELSE'S HOMEWORK
WITHOUT THEIR CONSENT
IS A MORAL GREY AREA.
YOU'RE TOTALLY NOT IN TROUBLE,
BY THE WAY.
THAT'S NOT THE POINT!
WHAT, YOU THINK I CAN'T WRITE
MY OWN STUPID ESSAY?!
UM, I WAS JUST
TRYING TO HELP!
YOU SAID YOU COULDN'T GO
TO THE DANCE, SO-
YEAH, SO YOU MADE ME
LOOK LIKE AN IDIOT?
THAT WAS A GREAT PLAN.
I GUESS YOU NEVER
WONDERED WHY
I DIDN'T WANT TO GO
TO THE DANCE?
OKAY, WHY?
THERE'S A TRIAL PERIOD
BEFORE I CAN GIVE SOMEONE
THE GIRLFRIEND LABEL.
OKAY, SO WHAT?
I HAD TO PASS SOME KIND OF TEST?
YEAH.
AND YOU FAILED!
FORGET IT.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE WORTH IT,
BUT I WAS WRONG.
FOR A GENIUS,
YOU'RE NOT VERY SMART.
♪ 'Cause the heart wants
what the heart wants ♪
what the heart wants... ♪