♪ I never expected
what was easy ♪
♪ But I never really thought ♪
♪ That things
would get so hard ♪
(EXHALES)
I THINK WE'RE GOOD.
YOU LOOK NERVOUS.
ARE YOU NERVOUS?
IT'S THE FIRST NEW UNIFORM
IN 50 YEARS.
I HOPE THEY GET IT.
YOUR EYE.
IS THAT A BRUISE?
I GUESS I NEED
ANOTHER TOUCH-UP.
DID I...?
LOOKS WORSE THAN IT IS.
FIONA, I'M SORRY.
I FEEL TERRIBLE.
YOU SHOULD.
YOU HURT ME.
YOU DIDN'T...
TELL ANYONE
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHY ROCK THE BOAT
OVER NOTHING?
(SIGHS, RELIEVED)
I SAY IT'S SHOWTIME.
(MUSIC PLAYS,
LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
HM, THERE'S THE BUDDING
DESIGNER HERSELF.
BOBBY:
WHO'S READY
FOR A FASHION SHOW?
YOU ALL KNOW FIONA COYNE,
DESIGNER EXTRAORDINAIRE.
FIONA:
A NEW SCHOOL YEAR'S
AN OPPORTUNITY FOR CHANGE.
SO I PRESENT TO YOU:
MY ORIGINAL VANDERBILT
UNIFORM DESIGNS.
ARE WE SURE THIS ISN'T
TOO MUCH PRESSURE?
OH, YOU WORRY TOO MUCH.
HERE'S OUR CLASSIC CREST,
WITH A CONTEMPORARY TWIST.
GREEN REPRESENTS OUR COMMITMENT
TO THE ENVIRONMENT,
BLUE BORDERS REFLECT
OUR EFFORTS
TO HELP THOSE IN NEED
AROUND THE WORLD,
AND BROWN, TO KEEP US GROUNDED
IN OUR COMMUNITY -
AIDING THOSE
IN OUR OWN BACKYARDS.
MAN:
YOUNG LADY,
AN INSTITUTION'S CREST
SHOULD NOT BE TAMPERED WITH.
I SUGGEST YOU FIND
SOME OTHER OUTLET
FOR YOUR "CREATIVITY."
(GUESTS MURMURING)
UH...
(SEARCHING FOR WORDS)
WELL, I JUST THOUGHT...
BOBBY:
WITH ALL DUE RESPECT,
THE ORIGINAL CREST...
I MEAN, THE REFERENCE
TO BURNING WITCHES?
IT'S A LITTLE OUTDATED.
OR IS THAT STILL IMPORTANT
TO YOU?
THAT'LL SHUT HIM UP.
FIONA:
THANK YOU.
BOBBY:
LET'S KICK THIS YEAR OFF
WITH A TOAST, SHALL WE?
(HUM OF CHATTER)
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
♪ Woo-oo-oo-oo-oooo ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it,
I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, whatever ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
HOLLY J:
UH...
HAVE YOU TALKED TO SAV YET
TODAY?
NOPE. WHY WOULD I?
EXCELLENT! OKAY.
THIS IS GONNA SOUND CRAZY,
BUT I NEED A FAVOUR.
IT'S ACTUALLY KINDA
THE BIGGEST FAVOUR
ANYONE WILL EVER ASK.
EVER.
WHEN SAV TALKS TO YOU,
CAN YOU LIKE...
PRETEND THAT YOU'RE PREGNANT
WITH HIS BABY?
WHAT?!
ONLY UNTIL ELECTIONS
ARE OVER.
OH, THAT MAKES IT
MUCH MORE REASONABLE.
LOOK, YOU WANTED REVENGE.
THIS IS IT.
THE SCHOOL WILL NEVER
ELECT A "BABY DADDY"
AS ITS PRESIDENT.
HE BROKE YOUR HEART,
ANYA.
ONLY UNTIL ELECTIONS
ARE OVER?
THEN YOU'RE BABY-FREE.
WHY DO I SUDDENLY CRAVE
PICKLES AND ICE CREAM?
MAYBE DADDY BHANDARI
CAN PICK SOME UP.
(ANYA AND HOLLY J LAUGH)
(EXHALES)
MAN,
GIRLS ARE COMPLICATED.
ME? YEAH.
YEAH, UM, AH...
SUPER COMPLICATED.
THE RANKING THING?
THAT WAS WEAK.
I GOTTA BE DIRECT.
JUST TELL ALLI
WHERE I'M AT.
SHE'S "THE ONE,"
ISN'T SHE?
WHOA! DON'T SAY STUFF
LIKE THAT, WES!
SHE'S COMING,
SHE'S COMING!
AGH. WISH ME LUCK.
WES:
GOOD LUCK, DAVE!
GOOD MORNING.
HEY...
A GIRL CAN'T BE
IN A GOOD MOOD?
NO, YEAH, OF COURSE.
LISTEN...
WHAT IS THAT?
WELL, YOU'VE INSPIRED ME
TO PUT MY OWN LITTLE LIST
TOGETHER.
SEE FOR YOURSELF.
HAVE A NICE DAY!
DAVE:
"DEGRASSI LOSERS."
WESLEY:
OH, THERE'S ME!
AND YOU'RE NUMBER ONE!
OH, RIGHT.
THAT'S BAD.
(PAPER CRUMPLES)
I KNOW IT'S DAY ONE,
BUT I THOUGHT WE'D DIVE IN
AND GET OUR HANDS DIRTY!
I WANT YOU TO MOLD YOUR CLAY,
AND THEN WE'LL BAKE IT
IN THE OVEN FOR 9 MINUTES.
HEY, UH...
IS IT TRUE?
IS WHAT TRUE?
IS THERE REALLY
A BABY-IN-PROGRESS IN THERE?
YEAH.
(STAMMERS)
UH...
I NEED TO MAKE A VASE NOW.
WHY DIDN'T YOU SAY ANYTHING?
IT'S NOT LIKE
YOU WERE TALKING TO ME.
I WOULD'VE MADE
AN EXCEPTION.
WHOOPS.
WELL, ARE...
ARE YOU KEEPING IT?
LIKE HIM, OR HER.
I MEAN, I-I-I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK. YUP.
AND UH... I'M...
I'M THE DAD?
YES. WHO ELSE?
WELL, I THOUGHT YOU TOOK
THE MORNING AFTER PILL...
WELL, I GUESS I TOOK IT
TOO LATE.
DON'T WORRY,
I DON'T EXPECT ANY HELP
FROM YOU.
ANYA...
UM...
UNLESS YOU'RE ABOUT TO BREAK
INTO UNCHAINED MELODY,
IT'S BEST YOU GO NOW.
HERE'S TO THE MOST
DRAMA-FREE EVENT
THE COYNE'S HAVE THROWN
IN YEARS.
I PROMISED THINGS
WOULD BE BETTER
ONCE WE WERE BACK
AMONG OUR PEOPLE.
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
AND THOSE UNIFORMS,
THEY'RE GOOD.
THE SCHOOL'S GOING TO HAVE
TO CONSIDER A CHANGE.
I TOLD YOU,
YOU DON'T NEED TO WORRY.
DECLAN:
NO MORE EMBARRASSING
TABLOID PHOTOS
FOR EITHER OF US, RIGHT?
NO TABLOIDS, NO DRAMA.
IN FACT, YOU'LL HARDLY KNOW
I'M HERE.
WELL,
TO A NORMAL LIFE.
(GLASSES CLINK)
JUST LET ME GET MORE OJ.
(STUNNED GASP)
(DOOR CLOSES,
KEYS JINGLE)
ROOM FOR ONE MORE?
AT THE HOMEWORK TABLE?
ALWAYS.
UH...
I HAVE SOME NEWS.
IT CANNOT BE BETTER
THAN MINE.
YOUR FATHER SAID COUSIN ANIL
AGREED TO PRINT POSTERS
FOR YOUR CAMPAIGN.
THE FIRST BHANDARI PRESIDENT!
STOP!
I'M NOT GONNA RUN
FOR PRESIDENT.
WHAT?
HOW AM I GOING TO EXPLAIN THAT
TO COUSIN ANIL?
I HAVE TOO MUCH ON MY PLATE
THIS YEAR.
I HAVE RESPONSIBILITIES.
RESPONSIBILITIES?
YOU'RE A TEENAGER!
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOUR FATHER
WAS YOUR AGE-
SPARE ME, MOM!
YOU AND DAD CAN'T MAKE ME
DO THIS.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE CAN'T FORCE YOU.
SOMETIMES I THINK
MAYBE WE MADE YOUR LIFE
A LITTLE BIT TOO COMFORTABLE.
MISSED YOU AT SCHOOL.
OFFICIAL WORD
WAS YOU WERE SICK,
BUT I DID NOTICE THAT
BARNEY'S WAS HAVING A SALE.
HILARIOUS.
ARE YOU STILL SICK?
JUST A HEADACHE.
CAN YOU JUST GO?
BOBBY:
SURE... FI.
IS THERE A PROBLEM?
OH, LET'S SEE:
GOLDEN RETRIEVER HAIR,
GARISH ACCESSORIES,
SERIOUS CASE OF SKANK FACE?
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO BE
MORE CLEAR.
I SAW YOU WITH TINSLEY!
WHOA!
I DIDN'T TOUCH TINSLEY.
LIAR!
SHE WAS ALL OVER YOU.
OH... (HALF LAUGHS) THAT.
LOOK, I BROKE UP WITH TINSLEY
LAST YEAR
AND SHE WON'T LET IT GO.
SHE GOT JEALOUS SEEING ME
WITH YOU,
AND SHE TRIED TO JUMP ME.
OKAY, I KNOW WHAT I SAW,
BOBBY,
SO JUST-
FIONA.
I WOULD NEVER CHEAT ON YOU.
I LOVE YOU.
LARA:
OKAY, I'LL LET HER KNOW.
AH FIFI!
MRS. BECKONRIDGE
JUST CALLED.
SHE WANTS TO HAVE DINNER.
TONIGHT?
WELL... (SIGHS)
I CAN ALWAYS CANCEL
IF YOU'RE STILL UNDER
THE WEATHER.
OR YOU COULD GO
WITHOUT ME.
BOBBY'S GONNA BE THERE.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
THINGS ARE JUST INTENSE.
(SIGHS)
WELL, YOU KNOW,
YOU CAN BE A LITTLE INTENSE,
FIONA.
I KNOW, BUT-
JUST REMEMBER
WHAT DR. CHANDRA SAID.
DON'T GO LOOKING FOR PROBLEMS
THAT AREN'T THERE.
OH! I SHOULD GET US A TABLE
AT JEAN GEORGES
FOR DINNER TONIGHT.
OH WAIT!
I HAVE SOMETHING FOR YOU.
WHAT'S THIS?
IT CAME FROM BOBBY.
OPEN IT!
OH, ASPEN.
YOU WERE PROBABLY
TOO YOUNG TO REMEMBER.
ONESIE SKI SUITS
AND FONDUE SUISSE.
DECLAN AND BOBBY WOULDN'T
LET YOU INTO THEIR SNOW FORT
AND YOU THREW
SUCH A TANTRUM!
YOU SNOW-ANGELLED
RIGHT DOWN TO THE GRASS.
I WAS A HANDFUL,
WASN'T I?
YOU HAD YOUR MOMENTS.
BUT THEY'RE ALL BEHIND US
NOW, RIGHT?
RIGHT.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
YOU'RE BACK.
YEAH, TRANSFERRED.
OUT OF MUSIC?
WELL, YEAH, I FIGURED THAT
HAVING A FEW CLASSES TOGETHER
MIGHT COME IN HANDY,
CONSIDERING.
SAV, YOU LOVE MUSIC.
YEAH, BUT YOU COME FIRST
RIGHT NOW.
I DO?
I MEAN, YEAH, UH...
OF COURSE I DO.
SO... WHAT HAPPENS NOW?
UM...
UH...
I'M GONNA GET BIGGER.
I MEAN, HAVE YOU TOLD
YOUR PARENTS YET?
NOT YET.
I'D LIKE YOU TO BE THERE
WHEN I TELL MINE.
I MEAN, WHATEVER HAPPENS,
AT LEAST WE'LL BE TOGETHER.
THAT'S ALL I EVER WANTED.
YOU OKAY?
IT'S NOT MORNING SICKNESS?
OH, NO. UM...
IT'S JUST...
I NEVER EXPECTED YOU
TO BE SO AWESOME.
OH, WELL...
I COULDN'T LET YOU
GO THROUGH THIS ALONE.
WOW. UM...
(HALF LAUGHS)
CAN YOU GIVE ME A SEC?
YEAH, UH...
GOTTA GO BACK
TO THE IRONING.
(LOW HUM OF CLASSROOM CHATTER)
(CONNOR BEATBOXES)
(RAPPING)
♪ DAVE TURNER FOR REP,
HE'S GOTTA REIGN ♪
♪ HE'S PERMANENT, YEAH,
LIKE A NASTY STAIN ♪
♪ HE'S SO HOT,
HE'LL FOG YOUR GLASSES ♪
♪ HE'S KING OF ALL
YOUR GRADE TEN CLASSES! ♪
(CONNOR FINISHES BEAT-BOXING)
DAVE:
GUYS, STOP, NOW!
(STUDENTS LAUGH)
(AWKWARD CHUCKLE)
UH, MY NAME IS DAVE TURNER,
AND I DO NOT APPROVE
THIS MESSAGE. HEH.
UM, BUT I AM RUNNING FOR-
FITZ:
LOSER!
(STUDENTS LAUGH)
BIGGEST LOSER.
HE ALREADY WON!
THANKS FOR THE SUPPORT.
ANYWAYS, UM...
VOTE FOR ME GRADE 10 CLASS REP,
BECAUSE I WILL, UM...
ALLI:
42, CLARE.
42!
OKAY, YOUR TIME LIMIT
FOR BEING UPSET
ABOUT THIS STUPID LIST
HAS OFFICIALLY EXPIRED.
YEAH, EASY FOR YOU TO SAY,
MISS NUMBER 3.
CLARE:
WHAT CAN I SAY.
DO YOU REALIZE
THE DEVASTATING EFFECT
THIS COULD HAVE
ON MY FUTURE?
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
WHAT WILL THE UNIVERSITIES
SAY?
WHO CARES ABOUT UNIVERSITIES?!
I'M TALKING RELATIONSHIPS
HERE.
I MEAN WHAT GUY'S GONNA
WANNA DATE NUMBER 42?
I COULD BE SINGLE FOR WEEKS!
OH... MONTHS.
MAYBE EVEN YEARS!
WHAT ABOUT PROM?
FORGET ABOUT IT.
BUT PROM IS THE MOST
IMPORTANT EVENT
IN A YOUNG WOMAN'S LIFE.
OKAY,
I MEANT THIS LIST.
'KAY, YOU ARE THE ONLY ONE
THAT CARES ABOUT IT.
DAVE:
HEY, ALLI-O,
CAN WE TALK?
CLARE:
YES, PLEASE.
COME ON.
OKAY,
THE LOSER LIST THING?
SERIOUSLY UNCOOL.
COULD KNOCK OUT MY CHANCES
OF BECOMING CLASS REP.
RANKING GIRLS, DAVE?
I MEAN,
YOU KINDA ASKED FOR IT.
I ONLY MADE THAT LIST
SO YOU COULD BE NUMBER ONE.
IT WAS SUPPOSED
TO BE RIGGED!
MOST GUYS JUST BUY FLOWERS.
(HALF LAUGHS)
I'M NOT MOST GUYS.
AND I HAD THIS WHOLE SPEECH
PLANNED OUT.
YOU KNOW, I WAS GONNA TELL YOU
YOU'RE THE HOTTEST GIRL
AND...
YOU THINK I'M THE HOTTEST GIRL
AT THE SCHOOL?
YES.
NOW COULD YOU
SAY IT AGAIN
JUST SO I KNOW
HOW IT WOULD'VE SOUNDED?
ALLI, YOU'RE SMOKIN'.
THE LIST? BAD.
THAT? GOOD.
YOU HAVE MY VOTE
FOR CLASS REP.
I DON'T WANT YOUR VOTE.
I JUST... I...
I WANT YOU.
DOES THIS MEAN WE'RE...?
JUST FRIENDS, DAVE.
WITH BENEFITS?
TELL ANYONE ABOUT THIS
AND YOU'RE DEAD.
(LAUGHS)
(EXHALES)
DECLAN:
10 PERCENT OF MY TRUST FUND.
THAT'S HOW MUCH I'LL GIVE YOU
TO COME TO DINNER
WITH THE BECKONRIDGES
TONIGHT.
I TOLD MOM
I'M NOT FEELING WELL.
NO TEMPERATURE.
PALMS ARE DRY.
IS THIS
AN IMAGINARY ILLNESS?
YOU GOT A NAME
FOR THIS ONE?
JUST LEAVE.
YOU PROMISED NO DRAMA.
THIS TIME
IT'S NOT MY FAULT.
LIKE IT WASN'T IN JAKARTA
OR DUBAI?
COME ON, FIONA,
THIS IS A NEW START FOR US.
DON'T MESS IT UP.
I DON'T WANT TO.
THEN COME TO DINNER.
(EXHALES)
WE COULD ORDER IN.
SUSHI SAMBA
OR THAT NEW FRENCH PLACE
ON FIFTH.
AND EMBARRASS MOM AND DAD
WITH A NO-SHOW?
THAT'S NOT MY STYLE.
COME ON, PLEASE.
NO.
(SIGHS)
ENJOY YOUR SNOW GLOBE.
♪ One reason why ♪
♪ One day I woke up
and realized ♪
(EXHALES,
SNOW GLOBE SHATTERS)
♪ No, no, no, no ♪
♪ After some time,
it's something... ♪
SAV:
CAN'T SLEEP.
CAN'T EAT.
BUT THEN I'M LIKE,
WHAT ABOUT ANYA, YOU KNOW?
I CAN'T IMAGINE HOW HARD
THIS MUST BE FOR YOU.
ANYA:
SAV...
SAV:
LOOK, I KNOW THAT WE BROKE UP
AND MADE UP A HUNDRED TIMES,
BUT I...
I WANNA MAKE IT WORK.
SAV,
I WANNA MAKE IT WORK TOO.
WELL, WOO-HOO!
IT'LL BE DIFFERENT
THIS TIME.
A WHOLE NEW CRICKET MATCH.
HUH.
WE HAVE A PRETTY INSANE PAST,
DON'T WE?
SAV:
UM, YEAH, WE CONCEIVED A BABY
IN A LIMOUSINE.
(LAUGHS) PRIMO STORY MATERIAL
FOR OUR GRANDKIDS, RIGHT?
UM, NO YOU'RE NOT TELLING
OUR GRANDCHILDREN THAT STORY!
LOOK AT YOU,
ALL PRESIDENTIAL AND DECISIVE.
YEAH, UM...
I DON'T THINK THE WHOLE
PRESIDENT SAV THING'S
GONNA HAPPEN.
OKAY, BUT BEING PRESIDENT
MEANS RESPONSIBILITY,
JUST LIKE BEING A DAD.
IT'S PRACTICE.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
SO? GIVE ME THAT LIST
OF BABY NAMES.
I DON'T HAVE ONE.
HA! AS IF!
I CAUGHT YOU SCRIBBLING
THEM DOWN
AFTER OUR FIRST DATE.
OKAY, WELL, IF IT'S A BOY,
I'VE ALWAYS LIKED
THE NAME VICTOR.
VICTOR?
I LOVE IT!
(LAUGHS)
(MOUTHS "VICTOR")
(COMPUTER CHIMES)
HEY, SEXY.
IS IT HOT-STUFF-DANCE-TIME?
FIONA:
EW.
OH, YOU'RE NOT DECLAN SKYPING
FROM DECLAN'S COMPUTER.
(SIGHS)
YOU OKAY?
I DON'T KNOW ANYMORE.
CRYPTIC.
GO ON.
IT'S LIKE,
WHY CAN'T I BE HAPPY...
LIKE YOU AND DECLAN?
IT'S LIKE I'M NOT BUILT
THE SAME WAY.
HOLLY J:
COME ON, FI.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR PRINCE CHARMING?
LAST I HEARD,
MOMMA COYNE WAS READY
TO BOOK THE PLAZA.
EVERYONE THINKS BOBBY'S
SO GREAT.
LIKE HE'S THE BEST THING
THAT'S EVER HAPPENED TO ME.
HOLLY J:
WELL, SWEETIE, IF YOU DON'T,
END IT.
(KNOCK ON HOLLY J'S DOOR)
FIONA:
LOOKS LIKE YOU HAVE COMPANY.
YOU GONNA BE OKAY?
WELL, IF YOU NEED ME,
YOU KNOW WHERE I AM.
AND TAKE IT EASY ON THE DOM.
(EXHALES)
OKAY. BYE.
(COMPUTER CHIMES
ENDING THE CALL)
HOLLY J:
I GOT YOUR TEXT.
IF YOU'RE BAILING
ON THE LIE,
YOU BETTER BE HERE
TO GET YOUR MARKER ON.
GOOD NEWS.
I'M GONNA KEEP BEING PREGNANT!
SEE YA, POSTERS.
THAT'S NOT EVEN
THE BEST PART -
SAV AND I ARE GETTING
BACK TOGETHER.
OH.
YOU KNOW YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO TELL HIM THE TRUTH, RIGHT?
AFTER ELECTIONS?
NOT RIGHT AFTER.
JUST NEED ENOUGH TIME FOR US
TO FALL BACK IN LOVE.
AND THEN?
I'LL FAKE A MISCARRIAGE.
WOW! ANYA,
THAT'S A SMIDGE DARK.
WELL, WHAT OTHER WAY OUT
DO I HAVE?
I EITHER FAKE A MISCARRIAGE
OR I FAKE A BABY TO TERM,
AND WHO WOULD ADOPT
A FAKE BABY?
TOUCHE.
IT'S A WIN-WIN
FOR BOTH OF US.
WHATEVER IT TAKES,
RIGHT?
(LAUGHS)
BOTH:
(LAUGH)
SIMPSON:
PLEASE HAVE CAMPAIGN MATERIALS
APPROVED BY ADMINISTRATION
BEFORE PASSING THEM OUT
TO THE STUDENT BODY.
HOLLY J:
ANYONE LOOKING FOR A POSITION
ON STUDENT COUNCIL?
ALLI, I HAVE AN OPENING
ON THE SOCIAL COMMITTEE.
ANYONE?
HJ! HOW'S THE CAMPAIGN
COMING ALONG?
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
YOU KNOW YOU WON'T BE ABLE
TO HANDLE IT
FOR SOME VERY SPECIFIC
REASONS.
WELL, WHEN YOU HAVE
A STRONG SUPPORT SYSTEM,
YOU CAN DO ANYTHING.
WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT.
YOU MISSED A KILLER DINNER
LAST NIGHT.
JEAN GEORGES IS A GENIUS.
BOBBY,
PLEASE JUST LEAVE ME ALONE.
HEY, ARE YOU STILL MAD
ABOUT THAT TINSLEY THING?
I TOLD YOU
IT WAS A ONE TIME THING.
I THOUGHT NOTHING HAPPENED!
BABE, I THOUGHT WE WERE DONE
TALKING ABOUT THIS.
I DON'T CARE ABOUT TINSLEY.
ONLY YOU.
PLEASE DON'T BE MAD ANYMORE.
(PHONE RINGS)
WHO IS IT?
NOBODY.
WELL, I WANNA SEE.
BACK OFF!
IT'S PRIVATE.
THOUGHT IT WAS
A ONE TIME THING?!
(INFURIATED SQUEALS)
YOU'RE EMBARRASSING
YOURSELF!
IS THIS WHAT YOU WANT?
TO BE THE CRAZY ONE
AGAIN?
I'M NOT CRAZY!
YOU'RE A LIAR.
LEAVE ME ALONE
OR I'LL TELL PEOPLE
WHAT YOU'RE REALLY LIKE.
YOU THINK THAT ANYONE
WILL BELIEVE YOU?
HEY! GET BACK HERE!
FIONA:
LEAVE ME ALONE!
BOBBY:
GET BACK HERE!
UNGH!
FIONA:
(SHAKY, TEARFUL BREATHS)
DON'T MESS WITH ME, FIONA.
FIONA:
(SHAKY, TEARFUL BREATHS)
I WANNA BREAK UP.
NO YOU DON'T.
(CRYING QUIETLY)