(SPECTATORS CHEER)
♪ I built my soul ♪
♪ On rock and roll ♪
♪ Then someone told me ♪
♪ The kids don't rock
no more ♪
♪ Oh! ♪
♪ Oh! Oh! Oh! ♪
♪ It's time to win! ♪
♪ I got a red cup
You fill it up for me ♪
♪ I'm on the guest list
You better check for me ♪
♪ Head's heavy but the drink
Holds it up for me ♪
(BUZZER SOUNDS)
(SPECTATORS CHEER WILDLY)
SADIE AND JENNA:
YEAH!
DAVE:
WHOOO!
SEMI-FINALS,
HERE WE COME!
KC:
AAH! THANKS TO THIS MAN.
COULDN'T HAVE DONE IT
WITHOUT YOU!
OH GUYS, GET A ROOM.
DREW:
SO WHAT UP TONIGHT,
GUYS?
WINGS, LITTLE MISS STEAKS?
SADIE:
I'M THINKING DRIVE-IN.
I HEAR THERE'S A NEW
HORROR FILM.
OH WELL,
I'M DYING TO SEE IT.
SO YOU TWO PLAN TO WATCH
THE MOVIE THIS TIME?
KC:
YOU'RE ONE TO TALK,
LAST NIGHT,
YOU TWO BARELY CAME UP
FOR AIR.
DAVE:
IT'S WAS HER FAULT,
I'M JUST SAYING.
YOU KNOW WHAT GUYS, I THINK
I'M GONNA SIT OUT ON THIS ONE.
YOU DON'T NEED
A FIFTH WHEEL.
OH COME ON, MY DAD'S CAR
IS BIG ENOUGH TO FIT US ALL.
WELL, IF IT'S ALL
THE SAME,
I'M JUST GONNA STAY BEHIND
AND WORK ON MY JUMPSHOT.
KC:
ALL RIGHT YEAH,
HAVE FUN.
DREW:
(LAUGHS UNCOMFORTABLY)
YEAH, YOU TOO.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, whatever ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
OH! SWEET!
THE LAST CEREAL...
IS ALWAYS THE BEST CEREAL!
HI.
YOU WOULDN'T DEPRIVE A GIRL
OF HER FAVOURITE BREAKFAST
BEFORE FACING A LONG,
LONELY DAY
AT HER NEW SCHOOL,
NOW WOULD YOU?
SAV:
IT SOUNDS LIKE SOMEONE'S
REGRETTING THEIR DECISION
TO LEAVE DEGRASSI FOR...
BEECHWOOD PRIVATE PREPARATORY
SCHOOL FOR YOUNG LADIES!
I HAD TO PROVE
TO MOM AND DAD
THAT I COULD TURN OVER
A NEW LEAF.
AND THE 'RENTS
ARE FINALLY STARTING
TO FORGIVE ME FOR ALL
THE TERRIBLE THINGS
I DID AT DEGRASSI.
IF ONLY I COULD MAKE
A FRIEND OR TWO.
WELL, WHAT ABOUT
THE AHMADI'S DAUGHTER?
DOESN'T SHE GO THERE?
MALIKA?
YEAH.
THAT GIRL TREATS ME
LIKE A LEPER.
(LAUGHS)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
FINE, TAKE IT.
(ALLI SIGHS GRATEFULLY)
WELL, MOM AND DAD THINK
THAT THAT GIRL IS A SAINT,
SO IF YOU WANNA GET
IN THEIR GOOD BOOKS,
I WOULD START WITH HER.
I MEAN, 'CAUSE
IF I INVITE HER OVER,
SHE'LL HAVE TO TALK TO ME.
THEN WE'LL BECOME FRIENDS,
AND I'LL BE A SAINT
BY ASSOCIATION!
THANKS, SAV!
(BELL RINGS)
SAV: (ON P.A.)
LED BY TOP SCORER DREW TORRES,
OUR BOYS BASKETBALL TEAM
IS HEADING TO THE SEMI FINALS.
WAY TO GO PANTHERS!
DREW:
MORNING.
DID YOU CATCH
THE GAME YESTERDAY?
GIRL:
EW!
IT'S NO BIG DEAL, JUST THAT
I LED THE TEAM TO VICTORY.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
HEY! WE'RE GOING
TO THE SEMI-FINALS.
SO I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU WANTED TO HELP
CELEBRATE TONIGHT
WHEN WE WIN?
SORRY,
NOT INTERESTED.
AWW.
POOR ROMEO GOT SHOT DOWN!
YOU GONNA CRY ABOUT IT?
GET LOST, BIANCA.
PLEASE.
MAYBE NEXT TIME,
DON'T BRING YOUR A-GAME
TO THE B-SQUAD.
B-SQUAD?
LOOK WHO'S TALKING.
YOUR NUMBER'S IN EVERY STALL
IN THE GUYS BATHROOM.
SO YOU'VE GOT IT, THEN.
CALL ME.
(SIGHS)
SO, YOUR PAPERS ON VIMY RIDGE
ARE DUE TOMORROW,
WORTH 20 PERCENT
OF YOUR MARK.
SO DON'T LET THIS BE
YOUR DIEPPE.
YOU DONE YOURS,
'CAUSE I WAS HOPING
THAT WE COULD HANG TONIGHT.
GREAT, I WAS THINKING-
CHICKEN WINGS,
AND THE HOCKEY GAME
ON THE BIG SCREEN?
NOT EXACTLY.
I WAS GONNA ASK IF YOU
WANNA COME TO A SHOWING.
A SHOWING?
OF WHAT?
LOCAL ARTISTS,
I'M MEETING MY FRIEND THOMAS.
OH. THE EX-BOYFRIEND.
WE'RE JUST FRIENDS.
YOU SHOULD COME MEET HIM.
ZANE,
I'M JUST NOT VERY ARTY.
IT'D BE WEIRD.
(BELL RINGS)
I JUST THOUGHT WE COULD
DO SOMETHING I LIKE.
(SIGHS)
ANYA:
WHO WHIZZED IN YOUR CEREAL?
SAY YOU HAD A BOYFRIEND,
AND YOU ASKED HIM
TO DO SOMETHING,
BUT IT WASN'T HIS THING.
AND HE SAID NO.
WELL, HE BETTER HAVE
A DARN GOOD EXCUSE.
ZANE ASKED ME
TO AN ART SHOW.
AND YOU SAID NO?
WELL, I WON'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY.
IT'LL SUCK.
WELL, THAT'S WHAT BEING
A GOOD BOYFRIEND
IS ABOUT, RILEY.
DOING STUFF THAT SUCKS?
LOTS OF THE TIME, YEAH.
(LAUGHS)
WHAT DO YOU WEAR
TO AN ART SHOWING?
UH, SOMETHING ARTSY?
THEN I'M GONNA NEED
A MAKEOVER.
OH HEY, HOW WAS
THE MOVIE LAST NIGHT?
KC:
MEH, YOU DIDN'T MISS MUCH.
DAVE:
HEY, MAN! YO,
YOU MISSED OUT LAST NIGHT!
AFTER THE MOVIES
WE BROUGHT THE GIRLS
BACK TO KC'S PLACE,
MADE THIS INSANE NEW
WAY TO PLAY TWISTER,
I GOT MY RIGHT HAND ON RED.
YEAH!
OKAY, IT WAS A PRETTY
GOOD TIME.
I DIDN'T WANT YOU
TO FEEL LEFT OUT, THOUGH.
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.
HEY, DON'T SWEAT IT.
AFTER WE SLAY 'EM
IN THE SEMI-FINALS TONIGHT,
THERE'S TRIVIA NIGHT
AT LITTLE MISS STEAKS.
YOU KNOW WHAT,
YOU GUYS ARE GONNA BE BUSY
WITH YOUR LADIES, AND...
I'D BRING ONE BUT I CAN'T
SEEM TO FIND A GIRL
IF MY LIFE DEPENDED ON IT.
(LAUGHS SELF-CONSCIOUSLY)
COME HERE.
KC:
EVER SINCE VEGAS NIGHT,
WHEN YOU CHEATED ON ALLI
WITH BIANCA,
YOU GOT A BIT OF A REPUTATION.
I MEAN COME ON,
THAT'S-THAT'S CRAZY.
DAVE:
LOOK, BIANCA'S FAMOUSLY GROSS.
I MEAN, LORD KNOWS
WHAT SHE'S DONE, AND TO WHO.
AND YOU KNOW,
AFTER YOU TWO HOOKED UP,
IT'S GROSS BY ASSOCIATION.
SO I GUESS
I'LL JUST BE...
FLYING SOLO FOR
A LITTLE WHILE?
KC:
NO, YOU JUST NEED
TO FIND A GIRL
WHO DOESN'T CARE
ABOUT YOUR REPUTATION.
DAVE:
MAYBE BIANCA'S FREE.
(CHUCKLES)
UH.
HILARIOUS.
KC:
YEAH, GOOD LUCK.
(BELL RINGS)
MALIKA:
IT'S JUST SO HARD
AND FRUSTRATING,
LIKE, THERE SEEMS
LIKE NO POINT
IN HAVING A BOYFRIEND
SOMETIMES,
'CAUSE IT'S LIKE SO MANY
OBSTACLES, JUST TO SEE HIM.
MALIKA: IT'S HARD!
ALLI: HEY!
HOW'S IT GOING?
PEACHY.
HMM!
SO, MY PARENTS
ARE RIDICULOUS,
I MEAN, WHY EVEN
HAVE A BOYFRIEND,
IF I'M NOT ALLOWED
TO SEE HIM?
UGH, PARENTS THE WORST,
RIGHT?
I MEAN, DO THEY EXPECT
ME TO DO HOMEWORK
ALL THE TIME?
PLEASE!
ALLI:
IF YOU THINK YOURS
ARE ON YOUR CASE,
GIRL, WE SHOULD TALK.
DO I KNOW YOU?
UM... I'M ALLI.
ALLI BHANDARI?
AH, YOU'RE THE ONE.
I THINK MY MOM
HAS A GIRL CRUSH ON YOURS.
ACTUALLY, SHE WANTS ME
TO INVITE YOU OVER FOR DINNER.
MIGHT BE A CHANCE TO WIN
POINTS WITH BOTH OF THEM.
I TOLD HER YOU WOULDN'T
BE INTO IT,
BUT UH,
SHE INSISTED I ASK,
SO... (LAUGHS)
I GUESS IT COULDN'T HURT.
REALLY?
I MEAN, GREAT!
OKAY!
♪♪♪
♪ It's so easy ♪
♪ And love's got me shaking ♪
♪ If we're easy to stop ♪
♪ Why's it taking me
so long ♪
♪ I would like to know ♪
♪ Was I taking things
a little fast ♪
♪ Was I making things
up in my head ♪
♪ Will you call me ♪
♪ When you're all alone ♪
ARE YOU SURE
ABOUT THIS OUTFIT?
I'M SURE YOUR BOYFRIEND
WILL LOVE IT.
(DRUMS POUND)
(CYMBALS CRASH)
DON'T STOP ON MY ACCOUNT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I WAS GONNA ASK YOU
THE SAME THING.
SHOULDN'T YOU BE GETTING
PUMPED FOR THE GAME
WITH YOUR DUMBASS
JOCK FRIENDS?
YEAH, THEY'RE BUSY
GETTING PUMPED
WITH THEIR GIRLFRIENDS.
WHY LET THEM
HAVE ALL THE FUN?
YOU SHOULD LEAVE.
AND YOU SHOULD RELAX.
DREW:
I CAN'T, EVERY GIRL
IN DEGRASSI
WON'T TALK TO ME
BECAUSE OF YOU.
WHAT HAPPENED AT VEGAS NIGHT
TAKES TWO PEOPLE!
DREW:
WHATEVER.
I SEEM TO REMEMBER
YOU LOVED IT.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
MOVE ON TO WHOEVER'S NEXT
ON YOUR LIST
OF THINGS TO DO.
HEY, I DON'T TAKE JUST ANYONE
TO THE BOILER ROOM, YOU KNOW.
AND MAYBE,
JUST MAYBE,
YOU'VE BEEN GOING
FOR THE WRONG TYPE OF GIRL.
(SIGHS)
AND YOU THINK YOU'RE
THE RIGHT TYPE?
WE HAD A LOT OF FUN
TOGETHER.
WE COULD HAVE A LOT MORE.
YOU LIKE ME.
GET OVER YOURSELF.
JUST BECAUSE SOME GIRLS
THINK YOU'RE HOT STUFF.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I'M TOO BORED TO ARGUE.
♪♪♪
(SIGHS HAPPILY)
I THOUGHT YOU WANTED
ME TO LEAVE.
AND I'M PRETTY SURE
YOU WANTED ME TO RELAX.
(CURTAINS RASP)
BIANCA:
IS MY PHONE NUMBER
REALLY IN ALL
THE GUYS' BATHROOM STALLS?
(LAUGHS) NO.
'CAUSE YOURS IS IN
ALL THE GIRLS'.
OH, REPUTATIONS SUCK.
AGREED.
SO, HOW LONG HAVE
YOU BEEN DRUMMING?
UH, JUST A FEW YEARS.
I HAD NO IDEA.
NO ONE DOES, I'M...
I'M NOT THAT GOOD YET.
YOU CARE A LOT ABOUT
WHAT PEOPLE THINK.
NO, I DON'T.
WELL, FOR THE RECORD,
YOU SOUNDED AWESOME.
REALLY?
THOUGHT YOU DIDN'T CARE
WHAT PEOPLE THINK.
WHEN THEY LOOK LIKE YOU,
I DO.
I HAVEN'T HAD THIS MUCH
FUN IN A WHILE.
DOESN'T HAVE TO STOP HERE.
SO, WHAT DO YOU SAY WE GO
TO THE DRIVE-IN TONIGHT?
FOG UP SOME WINDOWS?
I'D LOVE TO,
IT'S JUST...
I'VE GOT THAT
BASKETBALL GAME.
RIGHT.
WELL, YOUR LOSS.
YOU SHOULD COME,
IT'LL BE FUN.
A BUNCH OF JOCKS
CHASING AFTER A BALL.
SOUNDS LIKE A BLAST.
WELL, SUIT YOURSELF.
BUT EITHER WAY,
WE SHOULD DO THIS AGAIN.
SOON.
PHEW!
(TRAFFIC RUMBLES)
(SOFT JAZZ PLAYS)
ZANE:
WHOA!
RILEY:
SURPRISE!
SURPRISE INDEED!
NICE HAIR.
THANKS, UH...
I HOPE I'M ARTSY ENOUGH.
NO DOUBT ABOUT THAT.
ZANE, WILL YOU STOP
ACCOSTING THE PATRONS!
THOMAS,
THIS IS RILEY.
RILEY!
I'VE HEARD
SO MUCH ABOUT YOU.
REALLY?
OH, YOU KNOW ZANE!
HE KEEPS A RUNNING COMMENTARY.
SO, YOU TWO HAVE REALLY BEEN
THROUGH THE RINGER, HUH?
AND IT'S ONLY MADE US
STRONGER.
IT SURE HAS.
THOMAS IS A HUGE SUPPORTER
OF THE LOCAL ART COMMUNITY.
THAT'S GREAT!
I LOVE THE LOCAL
ART COMMUNITY.
REALLY?
CAN'T GET ENOUGH.
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
KC:
EVENING GAMES ARE THE WORST.
DREW:
HEY AGREED,
IS IT TOO LATE TO RSVP
FOR TRIVIA NIGHT
AFTER THE GAME?
YOU'VE CHANGED YOUR MIND!
DREW:
YEAH, I MIGHT EVEN
BRING SOMEONE.
AW, YEAH!
I KNEW YOU COULD DO IT,
MY MAN PICKS UP A RINGER!
DREW:
THIS ONE'S NOT A RINGER,
SHE'S ACTUALLY PRETTY COOL.
ANYONE I KNOW?
UM... YEAH, BIANCA.
AS IN BIANCA, BIANCA?
YEAH OKAY, LOOK:
I KNOW SHE'S GOT A BAD REP,
BUT SHE'S KINDA AWESOME.
AND INCREDIBLY HOT.
LOOK MAN,
ALL THE GIRLS HATE BIANCA.
IF YOU BRING HER OUT THINGS'LL
JUST GET SUPER AWKWARD.
LOOK I GET IT,
SHE'S SUPER HOT.
CRAZY HOT.
LIKE THE SUN.
BUT YOU CAN DO BETTER,
YOU'VE DONE BETTER.
BESIDES,
WE'VE GOT A BIG GAME!
ALL RIGHT, YOU DON'T
NEED ANY DISTRACTIONS.
SAYS THE GUY WITH
THE PREGNANT GIRLFRIEND.
I'M JUST SAYING.
IT MIGHT BE BEST TO STAY
CLEAR OF THIS ONE.
♪♪♪
ALLI:
WOW MOM, THIS BUTTER CHICKEN
WAS AMAZING!
DON'T YOU THINK, MALIKA?
OH, IT'S JUST A SIMPLE
FAMILY RECIPE.
MALIKA:
MAY I PLEASE HAVE A COPY?
SO I CAN SLIP IT
INTO MY MOM'S RECIPES?
(LAUGHS)
HERE ALLI,
LET ME HELP YOU WITH THOSE.
SUCH A WONDERFUL YOUNG LADY.
YOUR MOTHER ALWAYS
TELLS ME HOW PROUD
SHE IS OF YOU.
SOMETIMES SHE GOES
A LITTLE OVERBOARD.
I'M GONNA TWIST MALIKA'S ARM
FOR A CRASH COURSE
ON MAKING PARENTS PROUD.
IT'S A SHAME
YOU HAVE TO GO.
UM, MAYBE SHE DOESN'T
HAVE TO.
COULD YOU MAYBE CALL
MRS. AHMADI,
AND SEE IF SHE CAN STAY OVER?
I DON'T SEE WHY NOT,
IF IT'S OKAY
WITH YOUR FRIEND?
SURE, IF YOU'RE SURE
IT'S NOT TOO MUCH TROUBLE,
MRS. BHANDARI?
IT WOULD BE OUR PLEASURE.
ALLI:
THANKS, MOM.
SLEEPOVER!
(LAUGHS SHYLY)
(SIGHS)
THIS PIECE IS INTERESTING.
VERY INTERESTING.
WHAT DO YOU THINK THE ARTIST
WAS TRYING TO SAY?
UM...
THAT SOMETHING DANGEROUS
CAN BE UM... BEAUTIFUL?
THOMAS:
HUH!
YEAH,
THAT MAKES A LOT OF SENSE.
HMM!
THOMAS:
SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
RILEY:
VERY INTERESTING.
WELL YES,
EVERYTHING'S INTERESTING.
CAN YOU BE MORE SPECIFIC?
VERY INTERESTING HOW
THE ARTIST THOUGHT
HE CAN PASS OFF A TERRIBLE
FINGER PAINTING AS ART.
(SCOFFS)
GOOD LUCK!
THOMAS...FARON.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR HONESTY.
THOMAS, I'M SORRY!
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
OH, BOY.
ZANE:
HEY!
(SPECTATORS CHEERING)
(PLAYERS SHOUT)
JENNA:
GO!
(PLAYERS' SHOES SQUEAK)
GIRL:
YEAH, WHOO!
(BUZZER SOUNDS)
COACH ARMSTRONG:
OKAY, HALFTIME.
LOCKER ROOM, LET'S GO!
(FANS CHEER AND APPLAUD)
HEY, NICE FINISH!
DREW:
THANKS MAN, YOU WERE A BEAST
ON REBOUNDS!
WHAT'S SHE DOING HERE?
I DIDN'T THINK SHE'D COME.
ALL RIGHT, WELL DON'T LET
HER DISTRACT YOU, HUH?
YES, SIR!
DREW:
THOUGHT YOU WEREN'T
INTO BASKETBALL.
YEAH WELL, MAYBE YOU
COULD CHANGE THAT.
I'M SERIOUS!
YEAH, I KNOW.
(DOOR SLAMS)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(SIGHS)
MRS. STAVROS:
RILEY, YOU'VE GOT COMPANY!
TELL ANYA I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
CAN I TALK TO YOU FIRST?
(SIGHS)
I SHOULDN'T HAVE GONE.
THOMAS WILL GET OVER IT.
ART'S YOUR SCENE,
SO...
I WAS TRYING TO PRETEND
LIKE IT WAS MINE, TOO.
WE JUST GOT OVER
THE TWO RILEYS PROBLEM!
NO NEED TO CREATE
ANOTHER ONE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO PRETEND
TO LIKE ART.
WHICH YOU SUCK AT,
BY THE WAY.
(LAUGHS)
HOW'D THOMAS TAKE IT?
AH!
(LAUGHS)
I HAD TO TALK HIM OUT
OF THE BATHROOM FOR AN HOUR.
(BOTH LAUGH)
SUCH A DRAMA QUEEN.
BUT HE'LL GET OVER IT.
(SIGHS)
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HOW LUCKY I AM.
(LAUGHS)
SNACKS FOR THE STUDY BUDDIES!
RILEY:
MA!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
I'LL JUST LEAVE THESE HERE.
(SIGHS)
I'M SO SORRY.
OH, GOD. I'M NOT READY
TO HAVE THIS CONVERSATION.
YEAH, READY OR NOT,
IT'S COMING.
YOU WANT ME TO STAY?
I'LL JUST DEAL.
OKAY.
GOOD LUCK.
(DOOR SLAMS)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
♪ You chew me up ♪
♪ Like chewing gum ♪
♪ I said you chew me up ♪
♪ You chew me up ♪
♪ Like chewing gum ♪
KC:
DREW!
(FANS HOLLER)
TIME OUT!
GET YOUR HEADS
IN THE GAME, GUYS!
DREW, FOCUS.
USE YOUR TEAM.
NOW WE ONLY HAVE A FEW
MINUTES LEFT,
SO LET'S GET IN THERE,
AND WIN THIS!
(REFEREE'S WHISTLE BLOWS)
KC:
DUDE, STOP SHOW BOATING
FOR BIANCA!
I'D BE MAKING
THOSE SHOTS
IF YOU GUYS BACKED ME UP
OUT THERE!
DAVE:
OH SERIOUSLY,
DON'T LET HER GET BETWEEN
US AND THE FINALS!
DON'T WORRY,
SHE WON'T!
♪ You chew me up ♪
(REFEREE'S WHISTLE BLOWS)
(FANS CHEER LOUDLY)
♪♪♪
(SPECTATORS CHEER)
YEAAAAH!
♪♪♪
♪ Rolling up to the highway ♪
♪ Like any other day ♪
♪ With my back to the blacktop ♪
(BUZZER SOUNDS)
(ALL CHEERING WILDLY)
(FANS APPLAUDING)
PLAYERS:
WHOOO!
DREW:
YEAH!
YOU GUYS PICK IT UP
LIKE THAT TOMORROW,
WE GOT OURSELVES A TROPHY!
DAVE:
YEAH, FINALS BABY!
AH! AH! AH!
WHOO!
BIANCA:
GREAT GAME, GUYS.
SO, WHERE ARE WE TAKING
THIS PARTY?
WE'RE ALL GOING TO LITTLE
MISS STEAKS, RIGHT?
SHE'S COMING?
(SIGHS)
THANKS, GUYS.
I CAN TELL WHEN I'M NOT WANTED.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
(BIANCA SIGHS)
(FANS CHEER)
ALL RIGHT WELL,
I'M GONNA GO HIT THE SACK.
I'LL SEE YOU GIRLS
IN THE A.M.
THANKS SO MUCH
FOR STAYING OVER.
IT'S OKAY,
YOUR FAMILY'S PRETTY COOL.
ACTUALLY, THAT WAS
THE FIRST FAMILY DINNER
WE'VE HAD IN WEEKS
THAT DIDN'T END UP
EITHER IN A HUGE FIGHT,
OR PAINFUL SILENCE.
WHY?
UH, LET'S JUST SAY
I WAS TRANSFERRED
TO YOUR SCHOOL
FOR A REASON.
BUT THIS TIME I WILL
NOT SCREW IT UP,
SO YOU'D BETTER GET
USED TO THIS.
(LAUGHS)
(SIGHS)
READY TO CALL IT A NIGHT?
WHAT'S WRONG?
TONIGHT'S SLEEPOVER PROVIDES
THE PERFECT OPPORTUNITY
FOR ME TO SLIP OUT
AND SEE MY BOYFRIEND.
AH... THE CLASSIC
SNEAK OUT MOVE.
WILL YOU COVER FOR ME?
I'LL OWE YOU BIG TIME.
I DON'T KNOW, I MEAN
IF MY PARENTS FIND OUT-
MALIKA:
THEY WON'T!
I'LL BE BACK BEFORE
SUNRISE.
UM...
OKAY.
THANKS.
TOSS ME MY PURSE?
YOU SMOKE?
WHAT DO YOUR PARENTS
THINK?
THAT THEY HAVE A DAUGHTER
WHO DOESN'T SMOKE.
(LAUGHS UNCOMFORTABLY)
SEE YOU TOMORROW?
I'LL LEAVE THE DOOR
UNLOCKED.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)