DON'T BE LONESOME TONIGHT!
GET YOUR TICKETS
TO "A NIGHT IN VEGAS"
SO THAT YOU CAN HIT
THE BLACKJACK TABLE
AFTER YOU'RE DONE
HITTING THE BOOKS.
DREW:
OKAY, ALL I HAVE TO DO
IS SUBTRACT THREE
FROM THE LEFT SIDE
OF THE EQUATION,
AND THEN SOLVE FOR X.
UM...MAYBE WE CAN START
WITH AN EASIER QUESTION?
OR ACCEPT
I'M GOING TO FAIL.
YOU CAN DO THIS!
YOU JUST HAVE TO FOCUS.
ON SOMETHING ELSE.
ONE KISS.
(DOOR SLAMS)
AUDRA:
(CLEARS THROAT)
OH.
WELL, I'M ASSUMING THIS IS WHY
YOU'RE FAILING MATH?
MOM, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
EMERGENCY SCHOOL BOARD MEETING.
I THOUGHT YOU CAME EARLY
TO STUDY.
ALLI AND I WERE JUST
TAKING A BREAK.
UH-HUH.
UM, NICE TO MEET YOU,
MRS. TORRES.
YOU KNOW, THAT STINK BOMB
GAVE YOU AN EXTRA DAY TO STUDY.
DON'T WASTE IT.
MM-HMM.
GREAT.
NOW YOUR MOM THINKS
I'M SOME SKANK LIKE BIANCA
WHO MAKES OUT WITH
A DIFFERENT GUY EVERY WEEK.
NO, SHE DOESN'T.
SHE JUST CAN'T ACCEPT
I SUCK AT SCHOOL.
SO, WHERE WERE WE?
ABOUT TO CONQUER
QUADRATICS.
(FRUSTRATED SIGH)
I WON'T BE THE REASON
YOU BOMB THIS EXAM.
YOU WON'T BE.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever, Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
HEY, LITTLE LADY.
LOOKS LIKE YOU LOST
THAT LOVING FEELING.
HOLLY J:
YEAH. SIMPSON'S STILL IN THERE,
WITH THE WOMAN
FROM THE SCHOOL BOARD.
YOU DON'T THINK
THEY'LL CANCEL VEGAS NIGHT
'CAUSE SOME JERK SET OFF
A STINK BOMB, RIGHT?
POSSIBLY.
THEY HAD TO EVACUATE
THE ENTIRE SCHOOL,
RESCHEDULE EXAMS...
MR. SIMPSON:
(EXASPERATED SIGH)
MRS. TORRES,
I ASSURE YOU, ONCE WE FIND
THE STUDENTS RESPONSIBLE,
THEY WILL BE PUNISHED!
(LAUGHS) YEAH.
I KNOW,
WITH THE SAME SEVERITY
AS THE BOYS
WHO HAZED MY SON, RIGHT?
DEGRASSI'S ON
OUR SCHOOL BOARD'S WATCH LIST.
BULLYING,
LOW TEST SCORES,
AND NOW A PRANK
THAT CAUSED MY SONS
TO MISS AN EXAM.
ONE MORE INCIDENT
AND THAT COULD BE
ANOTHER PRINCIPAL'S PROBLEM.
HMPH!
WELL, THE SCHOOL BOARD'S
RECOMMENDED
THAT I CANCEL YOUR VEGAS NIGHT.
SAV:
SIR, WE'VE ALREADY PAID
FOR THE EQUIPMENT.
HOLLY J:
IF WE DROP THE AXE NOW,
COUNCIL WILL BE IN THE RED
FOR YEARS.
PLUS IT'S UNFAIR TO PUNISH
THE ENTIRE SCHOOL
BECAUSE OF ONE BAD APPLE.
HOLLY J:
EXACTLY! THAT WOULD BE
THE OPPOSITE OF FAIR.
MM-HMM.
WAIT, DOES THIS MEAN
YOU'RE ON OUR SIDE?
MR. SIMPSON:
I WANT YOU TO DOUBLE
THE AMOUNT OF CHAPERONES,
AND IF THERE'S ANY SIGN
OF TROUBLE...
WE'LL CONTACT YOU
IMMEDIATELY.
MR. SIMPSON:
OKAY, I TRUST YOU TWO.
DON'T DO ANYTHING
TO CHANGE THAT.
HIDING FROM THE PO-PO?
(STARTLED GASP)
I'M JUST LOOKING FOR A BOOK.
SAVING THE WORLD
ONE STINK BOMB AT A TIME.
I KNEW IT WAS YOU!
SOMEONE HAD TO STOP FITZ
FROM FIGHTING ADAM!
ONE SECOND MORE
AND HE WOULD'VE KICKED
ADAM'S BUTT.
I WAS THE ONE
HE WAS GOING TO KILL!
(GASPS)
SIMPSON'S COMING OVER.
HE KNOWS I DID IT.
I'M GONNA GET EXPELLED!
THREE DAY SUSPENSION,
MAX,
AND ONLY IF YOU GET CAUGHT.
MAYBE I SHOULD JUST CONFESS,
THROW MYSELF AT HIS MERCY.
OR LET ME HANDLE IT.
SIR,
I HATE TO BE A RAT,
BUT I THINK YOU SHOULD QUESTION
MARK FITZGERALD
ABOUT THE STINK BOMB.
HEARD HIM BRAGGING ABOUT IT.
CLARE, IS THIS TRUE?
UH, POSSIBLY.
OKAY.
I'LL LOOK INTO IT.
JUSTICE HAS BEEN SERVED.
IF FITZ FINDS OUT?
I'LL HANDLE IT.
NOW, LET'S TALK ABOUT
SOMETHING MORE IMPORTANT,
LIKE HOW YOU'RE GONNA
THANK ME
FOR THROWING SIMPSON
OFF YOUR SCENT?
WHAT DID YOU HAVE
IN MIND?
WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
(GASPS)
I HAVE A FRENCH EXAM.
I THINK YOU JUST PASSED IT.
OKAY, SO FOR THIS ONE,
YOU JUST DIVIDE BOTH SIDES
OF THE EQUATION BY THREE,
AND THAT WAY,
YOU'VE ISOLATED THE VARIABLE.
SIMPLE, RIGHT?
KC:
UM, QUADRATICS.
SO QUADRATICS,
JUST REMEMBER THAT AX SQUARED
PLUS BX PLUS C
EQUALS ZERO.
THAT'S WHAT IT SHOULD
LOOK LIKE.
FROM THERE,
YOU'RE GONNA GO AHEAD
AND DO YOUR OWN THING.
YOU GOT IT?
OW! WHAT? SORRY?
DUDE, THE EXAM'S
IN TWO HOURS,
YOU HAVE TO LEARN THIS!
NO, BELIEVE ME,
I-I'VE TRIED.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY MY MOM FORCES ME
TO TAKE UNIVERSITY TRACK MATH,
WHEN I CAN BARELY HANDLE
LONG DIVISION!
BIANCA:
I HAVE A PROBLEM
YOU COULD SOLVE.
THE ZIPPER ON MY HOODIE'S
STUCK.
(LAUGHS UNCOMFORTABLY)
I GUESS I COULD TAKE A LOOK.
HOW CAN I EVER
THANK YOU?
I'M UH...
I'M SURE YOU'LL FIND A WAY.
(EXHALES NOISILY)
(KC LAUGHS)
WHAT, WHAT?
WE WERE JUST TALKING.
YEAH?
IT LOOKED MORE LIKE FLIRTING.
(LAUGHS)
MS. OH:
YOU WILL HAVE EXACTLY
TWO HOURS
TO COMPLETE THE EXAM.
EXAMS ARE IN THREE SECTIONS.
SO, HOW MUCH TONGUE
WAS INVOLVED?
ALLI, THAT IS NONE
OF YOUR BUSINESS!
WHAT? IF YOU WANT ME
TO ANALYZE THE SITUATION,
I'M GONNA NEED DETAILS.
WELL, YOU'RE NOT GETTING
THAT ONE.
JUST TELL ME
IF YOU THINK THAT MEANS
ELI'S OVER
HIS DEAD EX-GIRLFRIEND.
WELL, GIVEN THE LIMITED
INFORMATION YOU'VE PROVIDED,
THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
TO FIND OUT.
I PROMISED
I WOULDN'T PUSH.
CLARE, YOU HAVE
NO OTHER OPTION.
IN 24 HOURS,
YOU GO TO YOUR GRANDMA'S HOUSE
FOR A BREAK.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT COULD HAPPEN
IN TWO WEEKS?
ELI COULD MEET SOME CUTE GIRL
AT THE CAR WASH.
SHE ASKS IF HE'S TAKEN,
HE'S NOT SURE.
NEXT THING YOU KNOW,
THOSE TWO ARE MAKING OUT
DURING THE HOT WAX CYCLE.
HE SAID HE NEEDED TIME.
THAT GIRL AT THE CAR WASH
DOES NOT CARE!
SHE'S RUTHLESS.
(SIGHS)
SO, WAS THE KISS GOOD?
REALLY, REALLY GOOD.
THEN MAKE SURE
YOU GET TO KEEP DOING IT.
NO MORE TALKING.
EXAM STARTS NOW.
(EXAM PAPERS RUSTLE)
(SIGHS)
(LIGHTS HUM)
STUDENT: (OVER PA)
WILL HEATHER POULETTE
PLEASE COME DOWN TO THE OFFICE?
HEATHER POULETTE.
VIVA LAS VEGAS!
I GUESS I SHOULDN'T HAVE LEFT
MY SUNGLASSES IN MY SUITCASE.
NO CHAMPAGNE EYES.
I GOT THROUGH
MY DEPOSITION SOBER,
I CAN GET THROUGH ANYTHING.
AND YOUR ANTI-ANXIETY MEDS?
ARE IN MY PURSE
IF I NEED THEM.
MY PLANE BACK TO NEW YORK
LEAVES SOON,
SO IF THE JUDGE IS SATISFIED,
THE DEFENDANT REQUESTS
A GOODBYE HUG?
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE MISSING VEGAS NIGHT!
MY MOM THINKS IT'S BEST
I GO BACK WITH HER,
AND HONESTLY,
I COULD USE A BREAK
FROM ALL THE EXCITEMENT.
TWO WEEKS WITHOUT A COYNE.
HOW WILL I SURVIVE?
WELL, I'M SURE
PRESIDENT BHANDARI WILL HELP.
FIONA!
COME ON, HOLLY J.
DON'T DENY IT.
I WAS BLITZED LAST WEEK,
NOT BLIND.
I KNOW YOU AND SAV
ARE SWAPPING SPIT.
WE'RE JUST HAVING FUN.
WELL,
DON'T HAVE TOO MUCH.
I STILL EXPECT YOU
TO MARRY MY BROTHER SOMEDAY.
OH! I ALMOST FORGOT,
I BROUGHT SOMETHING FOR YOU
TO REMEMBER ME BY.
IN CASE YOU NEED SOMETHING
TO WEAR TONIGHT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH,
BUT THIS DRESS
IS STAYING IN THE BAG.
(LAUGHS)
(SIGHS)
(SIGHS WEARILY)
SCIENCE EXAM DONE,
ONLY MATH TO GO,
AND RUMORS ARE RAMPANT
QUADRATICS ARE DEFINITELY ON IT.
GREAT.
SOMETHING ELSE I DON'T KNOW.
(SCOFFS)
LAST MINUTE CRAM SESSION?
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
WHO'S THAT?
YOUR NEW GIRLFRIEND?
(GIGGLES)
(LAUGHS UNCOMFORTABLY)
WHY IS BIANCA SENDING YOU
SEXY PHOTOS?!
I DON'T KNOW.
(HUFFS ANGRILY)
I'M GONNA KILL HER!
DON'T GIVE HER
THE SATISFACTION!
BUT YOU'RE MY BOYFRIEND!
YES,
AND I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
(SIGHS)
SO I HAVE NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT?
ONLY TEACHING ME QUADRATICS
BEFORE THE BELL RINGS.
(LAUGHS)
FINE.
(SIGHS)
HOW WAS YOUR FRENCH EXAM?
WAY TOO LONG.
DOES THIS MEAN I HAVE A DATE
TO VEGAS NIGHT?
DEPENDS.
DO I GET A CORSAGE?
(LOCKERS CLANG)
JUST SPENT AN HOUR
IN SIMPSON'S OFFICE.
SOMEONE TOLD HIM
I SET OFF THE STINK BOMB.
ME AND MY LOOSE LIPS.
FITZ:
NOT SO LIPPY NOW,
ARE YOU?
WHAT'S A GUY GOTTA DO
TO GET YOU OUT OF HIS GRILLE?
THIS ISN'T OVER.
DUDE'S A MENACE.
SOMEONE NEEDS TO TEACH HIM
A LESSON.
BECAUSE THAT WORKED
SO WELL LAST TIME.
CAN'T YOU TWO JUST KISS
AND MAKE UP?
HE'S NOT REALLY MY TYPE.
I'M SERIOUS, ELI.
SOMEONE IS GONNA GET HURT.
THE ONLY WAY TO AVOID A BULLY
IS TO KEEP 'EM SCARED.
OR...
YOU COULD LAY LOW
WITH YOUR GIRLFRIEND?
TWIST MY RUBBER ARM...
GIRLFRIEND.
(SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
DID YOU GET MY TEXT?
I HAVE A GIRLFRIEND.
SO?
SO YOU CAN'T BE
SENDING ME SEXY PHOTOS.
YOU DIDN'T LIKE THEM?
NO, I-I DID.
IT'S...
IT'S JUST I...
YOU HAVE A GIRLFRIEND.
YEAH.
IT DIDN'T SEEM LIKE YOU HAD ONE
THIS MORNING.
WHY SHOULD THE BIGGEST CATCH
AT SCHOOL
JUST SETTLE FOR ONE GIRL?
I LIKE ALLI.
I DON'T CARE.
LISTEN,
CHANGE YOUR MIND,
I'LL BE IN THE BOILER ROOM
AT FOUR.
NO STRINGS.
REMEMBER,
WHAT GIRLFRIEND DOESN'T KNOW,
WON'T HURT HER.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(EXHALES NOISILY)
(BELL RINGS)
MS. OH:
FINAL EXAMS OF THE SEMESTER.
FOR THOSE AMONG YOU
THAT HOPED YESTERDAY'S
STINK BOMB WOULD SAVE YOU,
I APPLAUD YOUR OPTIMISM.
PHONES?
HOLY CRAP!
IS THAT BIANCA?
NOTE THE ROSE TATTOO
ON THE LOWER BACK.
I GUESS SHE'S A ROMANTIC
AT HEART.
YEAH, I KNOW,
IT'S NOT FAIR!
THEY PUT ALL THESE HOT GIRLS
IN OUR SCHOOL,
AND WE'RE EXPECTED
TO JUST CHOOSE ONE!
YOU REGRETTING YOUR DECISION?
NO. I LIKE ALLI.
MORE THAN ANY OTHER GIRL
I'VE EVER DATED.
PHONES?
BUT?
BIANCA ASKED ME
TO THE BOILER ROOM.
OH, MAN.
I KNOW.
DUDE, DIVULGE!
WELL, THAT'S WHERE PEOPLE GO
TO HOOK UP.
WAIT. HOOK UP.
YOU MEAN LIKE-
ORALLY.
NO STRINGS ATTACHED.
ANY TIME YOU GET INTIMATE
WITH A GIRL,
THERE ARE STRINGS ATTACHED.
(SIGHS)
YOU'RE NOT ACTUALLY
CONSIDERING IT?
BECAUSE THAT WOULD BE WRONG?
I DON'T KNOW.
ASK ALLI.
GOTCHA.
MS. OH:
OKAY, YOU HAVE EXACTLY
TWO HOURS.
MAKE THEM COUNT.
♪♪♪
♪ Oh give me
just a little bit ♪
♪ Of your sweet lovin' girl ♪
♪ Won't you give me
just a little bit ♪
♪ Of your sweet lovin' girl ♪
♪ I'll give you all
I have to give ♪
♪ Anything I can ♪
♪ As long as you say to me ♪
♪ That I'm your only man ♪
♪ Your only man ♪
TWO, PLEASE.
CLARE: THANKS.
FITZ: TWO TICKETS?
FITZ:
QUITE A GAMBLE.
THAT BOY O' YOURS
MIGHT NOT MAKE IT
TO VEGAS NIGHT.
HURTING ELI WON'T SOLVE
ANYTHING.
DUDE SET ME UP!
BECAUSE HE WAS TRYING
TO PROTECT ME!
I SET OFF THAT DIVERSION
TO STOP YOU FROM FIGHTING ADAM.
GOOD TO KNOW.
SO YOU'LL LEAVE ELI ALONE?
I'LL COME CLEAN TO SIMPSON,
I'LL TELL HIM
YOU WEREN'T RESPONSIBLE.
ANYTHING.
ANYTHING?
THAT DOESN'T INVOLVE
BREAKING A COMMANDMENT.
GOT PLANS FOR TONIGHT?
KINDA, YEAH.
BREAK 'EM,
FITZY NEEDS A DATE
TO VEGAS NIGHT.
OR I PUT YOUR LITTLE BOYFRIEND
IN THE HOSPITAL.
IF I GO WITH YOU,
YOU'LL LEAVE ELI
AND ADAM ALONE?
AS LONG AS THEY STAY
OUT OF MY FACE.
TAKE IT OR LEAVE IT.
OKAY.
TIME IS UP!
PENCILS DOWN.
COULD I HAVE YOUR PAPER,
MR. TORRES?
(STUDENTS MURMUR)
HMM!
HEY, HOW'D IT GO?
FINE.
SO EASY, RIGHT?
I BET YOU LAUGHED
WHEN YOU SAW
THAT LAST QUESTION.
WHICH ONE WAS THAT?
ALLI:
THE AREA OF A SPHERE!
WE WENT OVER THAT
LIKE A MILLION TIMES.
YOU GOT EIGHT,
RIGHT?
YUP, EIGHT.
ALLI:
AND THE QUESTION
WITH THE TRAIN?
DID YOU REMEMBER WHAT TO DO
WHEN N WAS LESS THAN 20?
ALLI, STOP IT.
WHY, WHAT'S WRONG?
IT'S JUST THE EXAMS ARE OVER.
I THINK WE SHOULD START FOCUSING
ON SOMETHING ELSE.
LIKE HOW WE'RE GONNA SPEND
THE NEXT TWO HOURS.
UM, I'LL BE AT CLARE'S
GETTING READY FOR VEGAS NIGHT.
RIGHT.
BUT I CAN CANCEL.
NO, NO. NO.
IT'S FINE, GO.
OKAY,
BUT DON'T FORGET ME.
I WON'T.
UM, THE CORRECT ANSWER
IS "I COULDN'T,"
BUT THAT'LL DO.
LOOK, I'M SURE YOU DID FINE
ON THE EXAM.
(SARCASTICALLY)
YEAH, ME TOO.
♪♪♪
♪ I say give me
just a little bit ♪
♪ Of your sweet love ♪
♪ I swear it's all I need ♪
(KC LAUGHS)
ADAM:
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
HOW COULD YOU DATE
THAT BASTARD?!
CLARE:
IT'S ONE DATE
TO A SCHOOL SANCTIONED EVENT.
YEAH, I'M SURE ELI
SNAPPED A GASKET.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
WAIT.
YOU HAVEN'T TOLD HIM YET?
I WILL, AS SOON AS HE'S OUT
OF HIS HISTORY EXAM.
I'M DOING THIS FOR HIM,
FOR US.
HE'LL UNDERSTAND.
AND IGNORE THAT THE GIRL
HE LIKES
IS GOING TO VEGAS NIGHT
WITH HIS NEMESIS.
YEAH,
SOUNDS JUST LIKE HIM.
ELI:
OKAY, PLEASE TELL ME AN OSTRICH
STARTED WORLD WAR ONE.
SPIT IT OUT, EDWARDS.
CLARE:
WELL, YOU KNOW,
IT'S-IT'S FUNNY THAT YOU SHOULD
MENTION WORLD WAR ONE,
BECAUSE, WELL, MANY SAY
THAT THE, THE, THE REVENGE
EN-ENACTED BY THE LEAGUE
OF NATIONS ON GERMANY POST-WAR
WAS RESPONSIBLE FOR THE OUTBREAK
OF WORLD WAR TWO.
WHAT IS SHE TALKING ABOUT?
CLARE'S GOING TO VEGAS NIGHT
WITH FITZ!
ADAM!
IT'S BETTER TO RIP
THE BANDAGE OFF.
MM!
(GUFFAWS)
I'M WAITING
FOR THE PUNCH LINE.
FITZ PROMISED TO LEAVE
YOU ALONE
IF I WENT TO VEGAS NIGHT
WITH HIM.
AND YOU SAID YES?!
I WANT THIS STUPID FEUD
TO BE OVER!
AND IF I GO WITH
FITZ TONIGHT,
I THINK I CAN MAKE
THAT HAPPEN.
I SUPPOSE CRAZIER THINGS
HAVE HAPPENED.
SO YOU'RE NOT MAD?
JUST A LITTLE BIT.
GOOD.
I HAVE AN HOUR
BEFORE I MEET ALLI.
COFFEE?
RAIN CHECK?
SURE.
♪♪♪
♪ Sold my only guitar ♪
♪ Put all my money
into a broken car ♪
ELI:
YOU'RE A BIG MAN, FITZY,
USING CLARE
TO GET BACK AT ME.
GIRL CAME TO ME,
MAN.
I GUESS SHE'S LOOKING
FOR A BOYFRIEND
WHO WEARS LESS EYE MAKEUP
THAN SHE DOES.
(FITZ'S FRIENDS SNICKER)
YOU HURT HER...
AND YOU'LL WHAT,
TOUGH GUY?
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
BUT DON'T YOU WORRY.
WHEN WE HAVE SEX,
I'LL BE GENTLE.
(FITZ'S FRIENDS LAUGH)
(CAR RUMBLES PAST)
OH! TWO WEEKS.
NO SCHOOL,
JUST REST, RELAXATION...
JENNA:
AND SNEAKING OUT
OF YOUR BEDROOM WINDOW
TO GO ON ROMANTIC DATES
WITH DREW.
COULD LIFE BE
ANY MORE PERFECT?
(SIGHS) DEPENDS.
HOW PREGNANT DO I LOOK?
UM...
IT'S NOTHING THIS BOA
CAN'T HIDE.
OH! IT'S SO UNFAIR.
KC HELPED ME
MAKE THIS BABY
AND I'M STUCK
DEALING WITH IT.
DON'T WORRY.
ONCE YOU WIN
NEXT TEEN STAR,
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO TAKE CARE
OF THE BABY WITHOUT HIM.
WHA...THE CONVENT CALLED.
THEY WANT THEIR OUTFIT BACK.
PERFECT.
I DON'T WANT FITZ GETTING
THE WRONG IDEA ABOUT TONIGHT.
UH... OKAY,
HELP ME OUT?
I THOUGHT YOU LIKED ELI.
I DO.
BUT YOU'RE GOING
TO VEGAS NIGHT WITH FITZ?
(SIGHS)
FITZ DAMAGED ELI'S CAR,
SO ELI TRICKED FITZ
INTO GETTING ARRESTED.
THEN FITZ TRIED TO FIGHT ADAM,
SO I SET OFF THE STINK BOMB
WHICH HE GOT BLAMED FOR.
SO TO STOP FITZ
FROM FIGHTING ELI,
I AGREED TO GO
TO THE DANCE WITH HIM.
CLEAR?
(LAUGHS)
CRYSTAL.
ALLI:
UH, JUST ONE QUESTION.
UM, WHEN DID YOUR LIFE
BECOME WEST SIDE STORY?
I JUST NEED
TO GET THROUGH TONIGHT,
THEN MAYBE ELI AND I CAN GO
ON A REAL DATE -
IF HE'S OVER
HIS DEAD EX-GIRLFRIEND.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
OH!
SPEAK OF THE DEVIL.
ELI: HEY.
CLARE: HEY.
CAN I TALK TO YOU
OUTSIDE?
YEAH, SURE.
♪♪♪
♪ I have love in my heart ♪
(JENNA AND ALLI GIGGLE)
♪ And deep down in my soul ♪
♪ You're empty girl ♪
♪ I'm hoping you for sure ♪
♪ You're what I need ♪
♪ To pay me back ♪
♪ Oh yeah,
I gotta feeling... ♪
IT'S IPECAC.
MAKES PEOPLE BARF.
MOST GUYS JUST BUY FLOWERS.
I WANT YOU TO SLIP IT
IN FITZ'S DRINK.
WHAT HAPPENED TO BEING
THE BIGGER MAN?
I CAN'T.
NOT ANYMORE.
BECAUSE?
DON'T BE NAIVE.
FITZ IS A BAD GUY.
HE WANTS TO HAVE SEX
WITH YOU.
OH, THEN YOU'RE RIGHT.
THE APPROPRIATE RESPONSE
IS TO POISON HIM.
I TOLD YOU!
THIS IS HOW
YOU CONTROL BULLIES.
KEEP 'EM SCARED.
DO YOU KNOW WHO ALSO USES
THOSE TACTICS?
TERRORISTS.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHOSE SIDE ARE YOU ON?
I'M NOT SURE.
BUT I KNOW IT'S NOT THE SIDE
THAT POISONS PEOPLE.
(DOOR SLAMS)
I HAVE A GIRLFRIEND.
SO I'VE HEARD.
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
DON'T BE NERVOUS.
(GASPS)
I'LL TAKE IT FROM HERE.
♪ I'll give you all
I have to give ♪
♪ Anything I can ♪
♪ As long as you say to me ♪
♪ That I'm your only man ♪
♪ Your only man ♪