♪♪♪
♪ Oh please return ♪
♪ People that we know ♪
♪ Places we've been... ♪
AH!
THE BELLE OF THE BALL.
YOUR MOM DIDN'T HAVE
TO DO THIS.
IT'S NOT FOR YOU.
HER POOR SON'S GONNA MISS
HIS GIRLFRIEND
SO MUCH NEXT YEAR.
EIGHT MONTHS.
THEN I SAY GOODBYE
TO DEGRASSI,
YOU BID ADIEU
TO VANDERBILT PREP,
AND WE BEGIN OUR LIVES.
AT YALE, TOGETHER.
THE PLACE IS FILLING UP.
WE'RE STILL ONE GUEST SHY.
YEAH, LEAVE IT TO MY SISTER
TO UPSTAGE YOU
AT YOUR OWN PARTY.
BY NOW I LOOK FORWARD
TO FIONA'S BIG ENTRANCES.
SHE'S GOT A FLAIR
FOR THE DRAMATIC.
NAH, YOU TWO WILL BE BFFS
IN NO TIME.
YEAH.
(LAUGHS AWKWARDLY)
I'M HERE!
AND YOU BROUGHT A GUEST!
DECLAN:
BOBBY BECKONRIDGE.
HEY, DEX.
WHAT'S UP?
SOMEONE DRAG YOU AWAY
FROM POLO WITH THE SULTAN?
MY BOYFRIEND CAME VOLUNTARILY.
WELL, WELL.
DOUBLE B.
I SHOULD GO THANK YOUR MOM
FOR PLAYING CUPID.
SEE 'YA.
(VIOLIN PLAYS,
HUM OF CONVERSATION)
BOBBY:
YOU LOOK AMAZING.
DECLAN:
SURE YOU WANT TO GO HOME?
THINGS COULD GET INTERESTING.
BIG BROTHER DOESN'T APPROVE
OF DOUBLE B?
DECLAN:
IT'S HER FIRST REAL BOYFRIEND.
LOOK AT YOU,
ALL PROTECTIVE.
YEAH. MAYBE IT'S NONE
OF MY BUSINESS.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, whatever ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can
make it through ♪
(CUSTOMERS CHATTER QUIETLY)
HELLO, ANYA.
HELLO, SAV.
PETER:
AWKWARD!
YEAH.
SHE STILL HATES ME.
SO THE LAST BREAKUP,
WAS FOR GOOD?
BELIEVE ME,
IT'S BEST FOR BOTH OF US.
IT'S GONNA BE A LONELY PLACE
BACK AT DEGRASSI.
DOUBLE ESPRESSO,
HIT ME.
THERE'S GOTTA BE
SOME COOL PEOPLE
YOU CAN HANG OUT WITH
THIS YEAR.
MAN, ALL MY FRIENDS
GRADUATED,
OUR BAND IS DEAD,
I GOT NO GIRLFRIEND...
AND I'LL HAVE A LARGE
DOUBLE-DOUBLE.
ONCE YOU LADIES ARE DONE
WITH YOUR SEWING CIRCLE.
WHO'S THIS GUY?
A FUTURE REGULAR CUSTOMER.
I JUST TRANSFERRED TO
THE SCHOOL DOWN THE STREET.
OH, THERE'LL BE TONS
OF COOL PEOPLE AT DEGRASSI.
OH. YOU GO THERE?
YEAH.
I GOT YOU.
THANKS.
I'M DREW.
HEY. SAV.
SEE YOU AT SCHOOL, BRO.
♪♪♪
♪ Hey! ♪
♪ I wake up
to the morning sun ♪
♪ Freedom,
a new realization... ♪
CLARE:
ALLI, YOU LOOK-
ALLI: HOW WAS YOUR SUMMER?
CLARE: IT WAS GREAT!
ALLI:
YOUR HAIR LOOKS GOOD.
(LAUGHS)
DAVE:
MY FUTURE GIRLFRIEND...
HEY, FELLAS.
HEY, PRINCIPAL SIMPSON.
AH. PRINCIPAL SIMPSON!
THAT'LL NEVER GET OLD.
HEY, DON'T FORGET ABOUT
THE ELECTIONS, ALL RIGHT?
CLASS REP SPOTS
ARE WIDE OPEN.
DAVE, REMEMBER THAT THING
YOU ASKED ME TO DO
TO IMPRESS ALLI?
WELL, THERE'S JUST
A LITTLE GLITCH.
ABOUT THE RANKING THING?
AH, DON'T SWEAT IT,
CON-MAN.
NEW STRATEGY.
ALLI WON'T BE ABLE TO RESIST
THE NEW GRADE TEN CLASS REP!
ALLI:
I HAVEN'T EVEN SEEN YOU
AT ALL!
CLARE:
I KNOW, IT'S RIDICULOUS!
WE SHOULD'VE SEEN-
HEY, ALLI.
WANNA WORK ON MY CLASS REP
CAMPAIGN?
AND WHY WOULD I DO THAT?
(LAUGHS AWKWARDLY)
SO WE COULD GET SOME
QUALITY TIME TOGETHER.
OH! UH...
WELL SEE,
I'D LOVE TO,
BUT I'M BUSY.
WITH WHAT?
I'LL FIND SOMETHING.
(CLARE GIGGLES)
START WRITING
YOUR VICTORY SPEECH!
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
I WISH YOU DIDN'T HAVE
TO LEAVE.
REALLY?
HOLLY J,
I'M IN A GOOD PLACE NOW.
I ADMIRE YOU,
AND I THINK WE COULD BE
REALLY GOOD FRIENDS.
WE NEED TO.
WOW, THE HAMPTONS
WERE GOOD TO YOU.
WHAT WAS IT,
THE SAILING?
THE TENNIS?
THE NEW BEAU?
AND A GOOD THERAPIST.
IT'S A SHAME
YOU HAVE TO GO.
ME AND BOBBY,
YOU AND DECLAN,
WE COULD'VE DOUBLE-DATED.
BELIEVE ME,
I WILL BE BACK HERE
AS SOON AS HUMANLY POSSIBLE.
(SIGHS)
HERE'S YOUR CARRY-ON.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
I'LL CALL,
AND VISIT...
WE'LL BARELY HAVE TIME
TO MISS EACH OTHER.
WITH YOUR SCHOOLWORK,
AND SATS,
AND RUNNING STUDENT COUNCIL,
THIS YEAR WILL FLY BY.
YEAH.
HERE. FOR YOU.
WOW, THAT'S SO ROMANTIC.
(SIGHS)
I LOVE YOU, HOLLY J.
WE DON'T HAVE TO CRY.
♪♪♪
♪ You reach for your keys ♪
♪ Now you're driving away ♪
♪ You can't hear your thoughts ♪
♪ For the sound of the rain ♪
♪ And we become ♪
♪ Who we are
When we fall apart ♪
♪ So don't you want to ♪
♪ Start a new day ♪
♪ Let yourself go ♪
♪ 'Cause your head
seems to know ♪
♪ This is right ♪
♪ But your heart isn't sure ♪
♪ And crash like a wave ♪
♪ 'Cause a wave needs
to crash ♪
♪ Don't be afraid ♪
♪ Just get on the train ♪
♪ Take a ride off
the tracks ♪
WESLEY:
WHERE ARE ALL THE CHAIRS?
42?!
DAVE!
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
SEE?
IT'S ALL TOO EASY.
WHAT CAN I DO YOU FOR?
THANKS TO YOU,
IT'S LIKE I BARELY EXIST
AS FAR AS THE SCHOOL'S
CONCERNED!
DAVE TURNER'S
GIRLS OF DEGRASSI PAGE?
42?!
DAVE:
THIS DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
HOW COULD YOU DO THIS?
I TOLD YOU THERE WAS
A PROBLEM WITH THE CODE.
MR. SIMPSON:
GOOD MORNING, PEOPLE.
ALL RIGHT UH,
EVERYONE UH, TAKE YOUR SEATS.
I MEAN UH, WHAT SEATS?
THERE ARE NO SEATS!
AS YOUR NEW PRINCIPAL,
I'VE INTRODUCED SOME CHANGES.
BIG, BIG CHANGES.
STARTING WITH...
WAIT FOR IT...
(STUDENTS GASP)
BALLS!
BALLS?
EXERCISE BALLS. YOU KNOW,
TO IMPROVE POSTURE,
UH, HEIGHTEN ATTENTIVENESS.
(STUDENTS LAUGHING)
ALLI:
IS HE OKAY?
MR. SIMPSON:
AND I'D LIKE TO INTRODUCE
YOUR NEW INSTRUCTOR, MS. OH.
HI.
ARE YOU EVEN OLD ENOUGH
TO BE A TEACHER?
NO BOUNCING.
♪♪♪
♪ Oh sugar you're
So hard to please ♪
♪ The way you look ♪
♪ I'm kinda weak
at the knees ♪
DECLAN:
HERE WE ARE.
DAY ONE AT VANDERBILT PREP.
YOU READY?
FIONA:
(SIGHS) I ALMOST FORGOT
WHAT PRIVILEGE LOOKED LIKE.
LET'S GO MEET
OUR NEW PEERS.
IN A MINUTE.
AREN'T YOU COMING
TO ORIENTATION?
BOBBY'S GIVING ME
THE PRIVATE TOUR.
OKAY.
JUST UH, BE CAREFUL.
WHY?
I KNOW IT'S A BIG DEAL,
YOUR FIRST BOYFRIEND,
BUT YOU'RE DEFINITELY NOT
HIS FIRST GIRLFRIEND.
I'M A BIG GIRL, DECLAN.
GOOD,
'CAUSE HERE HE COMES.
THE COYNES
ARE IN MY HOUSE!
READY FOR THE TOUR, FIFI?
YOU TWO HAVE FUN.
(BOTH LAUGH)
BOBBY:
I WANNA SHOW YOU SOME
PLACES NOT ON THE MAP.
DESERTED CLASSROOMS,
DARK CORRIDORS,
SECRET STAIRWELLS.
I'D BETTER BE THE ONLY GIRL
GETTING THE PRIVATE TOUR TODAY.
FIONA,
YOU ARE MY ONE AND ONLY!
BUT I'LL WARN YOU,
HERE AT VANDERBILT
THE LIES, THE GOSSIP,
IT CAN GET UGLY.
I'M FAMILIAR
WITH THE GOSSIP.
AND IF YOU WANT
TO TALK UGLY,
YOU KNOW MY OPINION
ON THESE UNIFORMS.
I MAY HAVE HAD A CHAT
WITH THE HEADMASTER.
TOLD HIM I KNOW A DESIGNER
WITH SOME GREAT IDEAS.
YEAH, AND?
GOLD DONOR'S BRUNCH.
YOU SHOW YOUR DESIGNS
TO THE PEOPLE
WHO DROP THE BIGGEST COIN
ON VANDERBILT.
MY DESIGNS?
FOR REAL?
WE HAVE TO GET STARTED
TONIGHT!
(SCOFFS)
WHAT DO I KNOW
ABOUT DESIGNING UNIFORMS?
WELL, I THOUGHT WE COULD
DO IT TOGETHER.
SCULLING TEAM'S NIGHT OUT.
SORRY.
HEY.
(SIGHS INDIGNANTLY)
I DID SOMETHING NICE,
YOU SHOULD BE HAPPY.
I AM.
DON'T WORRY.
YOUR BRO WILL BE THERE
KEEPING TABS ON ME.
(LAUGHS)
HOLLY J:
AUNT BRONWEN
AND AIRPORT PARKING LOTS
DO NOT MIX.
I ATE ON THE PLANE.
OKAY.
YEAH, I'LL SEE YOU
WHEN YOU GET HOME, MOM.
LOVE YOU TOO.
BYE.
(PHONE BEEPS)
(SIGHS)
(ZIPPER WHIRS)
(SIGHS WISTFULLY)
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
THIS IS WEIRD.
MRS. BHANDARI:
SO HOW WAS THE FIRST DAY
OF SCHOOL
FOR THE MOST POPULAR SENIOR
AT DEGRASSI?
SAV:
POPULAR?
SAYS WHO?
MRS. BHANDARI:
MY EYES AND EARS ON THE GROUND.
WHAT? ALL THE ACTUAL
COOL GUYS GRADUATED.
YOU WERE IN THAT BAND,
AND SOME INSANE GIRLS
ACTUALLY THINK YOU'RE CUTE.
REALLY?
WHATEVER, I'M JUST GONNA FLY
UNDER THE RADAR 'TIL GRAD.
OR, YOU COULD CAPITALIZE
ON THIS POPULARITY.
RUN FOR PRESIDENT.
HOLLY J'S GOING
TO BE PRESIDENT.
YOU YOURSELF TOLD ME
SHE HAS NO COMPETITION.
HARDLY SOUNDS LIKE A DEMOCRACY.
IT'S NOT DEMOCRACY,
IT'S HIGH SCHOOL.
HOLLY J HAS THE SUPPORT
OF THE ENTIRE STUDENT BODY.
ALLI:
UH YEAH, 'CAUSE SHE'S
THE ONLY ONE RUNNING.
MRS. BHANDARI:
THINK OF THE OPPORTUNITIES!
AND IT LOOKS GOOD
ON COLLEGE APPLICATIONS.
DECLAN:
SO DOES THE RETURNING PRESIDENT
ALWAYS GET TO SKIP
THE FIRST DAY OF SCHOOL?
NOTHING HAPPENS DAY ONE.
HOW WAS YOUR ORIENTATION?
WELL, I CAN RECITE
THE MOTTO,
LIST 200 YEARS
OF CHANCELLORS,
AND DIRECT YOU
TO SEVERAL FIRE EXITS.
HAVE YOU EVEN HAD A CHANCE
TO MISS ME?
EVERY SECOND OF EVERY MINUTE.
AND I KEEP THINKING ABOUT
HOW IT'LL ALL BE WORTH IT
WHEN WE'RE BACK TOGETHER.
(DOOR OPENS)
MARY KATE:
OH, THERE YOU ARE!
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE BACK,
SWEETIE.
HEY, MOM.
OH! H-HI DECLAN.
HI, MRS. SINCLAIR.
I'LL LET YOU TWO CATCH UP.
DON'T HAVE TOO MUCH FUN
AT DEGRASSI TOMORROW.
WITH THE GUYS TONIGHT.
BYE.
OKAY.
WHAT'S WITH THE BOXES?
WHAT?
NO, "I MISSED YOU,
HOW WAS YOUR DAY?"
(SIGHS)
WE...
WE SOLD THE HOUSE.
YOU WHAT?!
WELL, WE FOUND AN APARTMENT
JUST A FEW BLOCKS AWAY.
AN APARTMENT?
WELL, HOW BAD IS IT?
I MEAN,
I KNOW DAD'S BEEN
OUT OF WORK FOR A WHILE, BUT-
WELL, OUR FUND MANAGER.
HE... HE LOST OUR SAVINGS.
(GASPS)
ALL OF IT.
MY COLLEGE FUND!
YALE!
THERE ARE UNIVERSITIES
NEARBY.
AND WE ARE MOVING
SO THAT WE CAN AFFORD
TO SEND YOU TO ONE.
OH, SWEETIE.
WE'LL TALK ABOUT THIS MORE
WHEN YOUR DAD GETS BACK, OKAY?
YEAH!
(SIGHS)
AHH... I NEED TO HYDRATE.
WHAT'D YOU GUYS DO
LAST NIGHT?
YOU KNOW, JUST SOME GOOD,
CLEAN-ISH FUN.
CLEAN-ISH?
YOU KNOW UH, AT FIRST
I WASN'T TOO SURE ABOUT BOBBY.
IT'S A GOOD THING MOM
DIDN'T ASK MY OPINION
BEFORE SHE SET YOU UP.
(SCOFFS)
SHE DIDN'T "SET US UP".
OH COME ON FI, HE'S A GUY
FROM A CONNECTED FAMILY.
ANYWAY, LAST NIGHT BOBBY
WAS ON HIS BEST BEHAVIOUR,
SAID ALL THE RIGHT THINGS,
I THINK IT'S PROBABLY BEST
I JUST KEEP MY NOSE OUT OF IT.
SEE? YOU DON'T HAVE
TO BIG BROTHER ME ANY MORE.
I HEAR YOU'RE DESIGNING
NEW UNIFORMS.
I'M GOING FOR SOMETHING
STYLISH, YET TIMELESS.
HMM.
NOT LOOKING!
I WANT TO BE
JUST AS SURPRISED
AS ALL OF THE OTHER
GOLD DONORS.
(SIGHS)
FIRST WEEK AT VANDERBILT,
AND YOU'RE ALREADY MAKING
AN IMPRESSION.
WELL, IT HELPS TO HAVE
FRIENDS IN HIGH PLACES.
I'M GLAD THAT YOU AND BOBBY
ARE HITTING IT OFF.
(LAUGHS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
WHAT DO YOU SAY,
HOLLY J?
I... HOPE I CAN COUNT
ON YOUR VOTE?
I WAS STARTING TO THINK
YOU WEREN'T COMING BACK
FROM NEW YORK.
AND NEGLECT MY RESPONSIBILITIES
AS PRESIDENT?
NEVER.
RIGHT.
THEN, THERE'S SOMETHING
WE SHOULD TALK ABOUT.
CAN IT WAIT?
I HAVE LIKE,
A MILLION THINGS TO DO
FOR THE CLASS REP ELECTION.
DAVE TURNER?
I GUESS ANY LOSER THINKS
HE CAN RUN FOR OFFICE.
YEAH, I WAS-
I WAS THINKING OF RUNNING.
OH.
WELL, WE'VE GOT AN OPENING
FOR SECRETARY.
I WAS THINKING SOMETHING
A BIT MORE PRESIDENTIAL.
BUT I'M HER.
I MEAN, SHE'S ME.
NOBODY'S RUNNING AGAINST ME.
DREW:
AH SAV, MY MAN!
DREW, WHAT'S UP?
WHO'S THIS?
AH, THIS IS MY COMPETITION.
FOR STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT.
WHAT?!
OH! YOU'RE RUNNING?
GIRL:
HEY DREW!
COOL!
SAV, LISTEN.
YOU AND I BOTH KNOW THAT
YOU'RE NOT EXACTLY...
PRESIDENT MATERIAL.
BUT I'M GONNA NEED A VICE-
NO, REALLY. I...
THINK THE WORLD'S READY
FOR...
PRESIDENT SAVTAJ BHANDARI.
(FRUSTRATED SIGH)
BOBBY:
THERE'S MY GIRL!
(SIGHS)
YOU'RE LATE!
WE MISSED FIRST PERIOD!
LAW AND ETHICS?
WHATEVS.
I GOT IN LATE LAST NIGHT.
WHERE'D YOU GUYS GO?
JUST A PLACE.
SO, WHO ALL WAS THERE?
WHAT,
AM I ON TRIAL HERE?
I'M JUST TRYING
TO MAKE CONVERSATION.
IF I HAVE SOMETHING
TO SAY,
I'LL CONVERSE.
FINE, WHATEVER.
BOBBY:
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
OW!
THAT HURTS!
I'M SORRY.
LET ME FIX IT.
BETTER?
(SIGHS)
LET'S GO.
I'LL TELL YOU WHERE WE HID
THE ARMADILLO ON THE WAY.
YOU KIDNAPPED ARMIN?
OUR MASCOT'S FINE.
HOLLY J:
ATTENTION EVERYONE!
HI.
FOR ALL YOU NINERS AND NEWBS,
I'M HOLLY J SINCLAIR,
YOUR INCUMBENT
STUDENT COUNCIL PREZ.
NOW, I LOOK FORWARD
TO SERVING YOU ONCE AGAIN,
AND I URGE YOU ALL
TO VOTE FOR YOUR CLASS REPS
IN THE UPCOMING ELECTION.
EXCUSE ME.
CAN I SAY SOMETHING?
HI.
UM...
HOLLY J WAS A PRETTY
GOOD PRESIDENT.
BUT SHE THINKS SHE CAN
JUST WALTZ IN HERE
AND TAKE OVER AGAIN,
WITH NO COMPETITION.
NOW CALL ME CRAZY,
BUT THAT DOESN'T SOUND
LIKE DEMOCRACY!
IT'S TIME FOR CHANGE!
AND THIS RIGHT HERE?
THIS IS THE FACE
OF CHANGE.
VOTE SAV BHANDARI
FOR STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT!
(STUDENTS CLAPPING
AND CHEERING)
WE'LL SEE WHO'S NOT
PRESIDENT MATERIAL.
STUDENTS:
WHOO! YEAH!
(SIGHS)
ALLI'S BODY LANGUAGE
INDICATES SHE'S ANGRY.
PROBABLY BECAUSE OF YOU.
THANKS, GENIUS.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
WAIT, THAT WAS SARCASM.
WHAT DID I DO?
THE RANKING SYSTEM WAS SUPPOSED
TO BE RIGGED, REMEMBER?
ALLI'S NUMBER ONE
BY A MILE,
SHE'S FLATTERED,
SHE LIKES ME,
THAT WAS THE WHOLE POINT!
NOW EVEN IF I DO WIN
CLASS REP,
SHE'LL NEVER DATE ME.
I TOLD YOU
THERE WAS A PROBLEM.
THE ALGORITHMS
AREN'T WATERPROOF.
GREAT! ALL SUMMER
I'VE BEEN "JUST A FRIEND",
AND NOW I'M NOT EVEN THAT!
IT'S ALL GONE.
(SCOFFS)
NOW YOU'RE ANGRY.
THAT ASPERGER'S TRAINING
IS REALLY PAYING OFF, ISN'T IT?
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
ANYA:
WELCOME BACK.
NOT NOW, ANYA!
I'M SORRY.
I'M STRESSED.
STUPID SAV.
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
WHEN HE BROKE UP WITH ME
IT WAS A BLESSING IN DISGUISE.
YALE'S NOT GOING TO ACCEPT
A PRESIDENTIAL RUNNER-UP!
IF I LOSE,
I'M A LOSER,
I'LL NEVER BE WITH DECLAN,
AND MY LIFE IS OVER!
AND WHO WILL LOOK OUT
FOR THE BEST INTERESTS
OF THE STUDENTS?
RIGHT. THAT TOO.
SO HOW CAN I HELP
TAKE SAV DOWN?
STILL HAVEN'T FORGIVEN HIM
FOR DUMPING YOU ON PROM NIGHT?
MINUTES AFTER WE EXCHANGED
VIRGINITIES.
IMAGINE IF I HAD'VE
GOTTEN PREGNANT.
I WOULD'VE SPENT
SENIOR YEAR OUT TO HERE.
PLUS SAV WOULD'VE BEEN
A MAJOR PARIAH
FOR GETTING A GIRL
KNOCKED UP.
YEAH.
LET ME KNOW IF THERE'S
ANYTHING I CAN DO TO HELP.
COOL.
THANKS, ANYA.
(WATER SLOSHES)
THESE ARE CUTE.
YEAH, ANYWHERE
MY DAD'S EVER BEEN,
HE'S BROUGHT ONE BACK
FOR DECLAN AND ME.
A CHEESY LITTLE SURPRISE.
NOTHING WRONG
WITH A LITTLE FROMAGE.
WHAT IS ALL THIS STUFF?
IT'S FOR THE UNIFORMS.
SO YOU'RE ACTUALLY
GONNA LIKE, SEW THEM?
THE REAL THING'S BETTER
THAN A DRAWING.
AND IF WE'RE GONNA GET
VANDERBILT TO CHANGE...
BOBBY:
LET'S NOT GET TOO EXCITED.
THE HEADMASTER SAID
HE'D LOOK AT NEW DESIGNS.
AND ONCE HE SEES MY UPDATES,
HE'LL BE CONVINCED.
THE WHOLE SCHOOL WILL BE
STYLIN' BECAUSE OF MOI.
YOU MEAN,
BECAUSE OF US.
THAT'S RIGHT.
VANDERBILT'S NEW GOLDEN COUPLE.
YOU KNOW,
MY FAMILY LOVES YOU.
I KNOW WHAT I'D LOVE.
NOT NOW BOBBY,
PEOPLE ARE GONNA BE HOME SOON.
COME ON,
WE'LL MAKE IT QUICK.
BOBBY, PLEASE!
BOBBY:
YOUR PARENTS WOULD PROBABLY
THROW A PARTY
IF THEY CAUGHT US TOGETHER.
GET AWAY FROM ME!
BOBBY:
GET BACK HERE!
(FIONA WHIMPERS)
FIONA:
OW!
BOBBY:
OH!
(HARD SLAP, BOBBY GRUNTS)
FIONA:
GET OUT.
LOOK, WE BOTH JUST GOT
CARRIED AWAY.
I'LL-I'LL GET YOU SOME ICE.
OUT!
(RAGGED BREATHS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
SAV:
WHA?
MORNING!
TRYING TO GIVE ME
A HEART ATTACK?
WHY, DO YOU FEEL
ONE COMING ON?
I'LL LIVE.
WELL, IN THAT CASE,
I WANT TO APOLOGIZE.
I KNOW YOU'RE ONLY RUNNING
BECAUSE I SAID YOU COULDN'T,
SO, I'M SORRY.
OKAY?
YOU THINK
I'M THAT SHALLOW?
TELL ME SOMETHING HOLLY J,
WHY DO YOU WANT
TO BE PRESIDENT?
WELL, I LIKE BEING
IN CHARGE.
SAME HERE.
SINCE WHEN?
MIGHT BE TIME
I GAVE IT A TRY.
WELL, IT ALSO LOOKS GOOD
ON A RESUME,
ESPECIALLY IF THE IVY LEAGUE
IS IN MY FUTURE.
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE
WITH A FUTURE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT'S JUST THAT MY FUTURE
DOESN'T INVOLVE...
TEEN FATHERHOOD.
WELL YEAH,
THAT WOULD JUST BE WEIRD.
WAIT. WHAT?
I KNOW, SAV.
ANYA TOLD ME.
TOLD YOU...?
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE A LOT
ON YOUR PLATE NEXT YEAR
BEING STUDENT COUNCIL
PRESIDENT,
AND A DAD.
WHO SAID ANYTHING
ABOUT BEING A DAD?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO PRETEND
ANY MORE, SWEETIE.
ANYA TOLD ME SHE'S...
PREGNANT.
LARA:
READY, HONEY?
THE GUESTS ARE STARTING
TO ARRIVE FOR BRUNCH.
MRS. COYNE.
BEAUTIFUL AS ALWAYS.
OH BOBBY,
LOOK AT THOSE FLOWERS.
FIONA, COME SEE WHAT
A LUCKY GIRL YOU ARE!
BE RIGHT THERE.
♪ Will the days be this easy ♪
♪ Or will time pull us through ♪
♪ Love takes no prisoners ♪
♪ And some die alone ♪
♪ So I don't need ♪
♪ Another hand to hold ♪