(CELL PHONE RINGS)
(ANNOYED SIGH)
DOESN'T MATTER
HOW MANY TIMES YOU CALL,
I'M STILL GOING
TO VANCOUVER.
JOHNNY:
JUST COME BACK TO T.U.,
LET'S TALK.
HUH. YEAH.
AS IF YOU CARE.
JOHNNY:
I DO, AND I DON'T WANT
TO SEE YOU END UP
SOME SQUEEGEE KID.
ALLI:
I WON'T.
I'LL BE FINE.
I'LL GET A JOB.
YOU KNOW, IN FACT,
I'LL BE GREAT
BECAUSE I WILL BE AWAY
FROM MY BROTHER,
MY PARENTS, DEGRASSI,
AND YOU.
DO YOU ACTUALLY THINK
YOU CAN MAKE IT ON YOUR OWN?
ALLI:
I MADE IT LAST NIGHT
SLEEPING IN A PARK BENCH;
I'M SURE I CAN MAKE IT
FOR THE SUMMER
WORKING AT A CAMP.
JOHNNY:
NOT IF I CALL YOUR BROTHER
AND TELL HIM YOU'LL BE
ON A BUS THIS AFTERNOON.
JOHNNY,
YOU WOULDN'T DARE.
YOU'RE MAKING A MISTAKE.
I'VE MADE MISTAKES.
YOU WERE ONE OF THEM,
REMEMBER?
MY PARENTS JUST CAN'T
GET PAST THEM,
SO PLEASE LET ME GO SOMEWHERE
IT'S OKAY TO BE MYSELF.
WILL YOU CALL
WHEN YOU GET THERE?
YES.
JOHNNY.
FINE.
THEN GOOD LUCK.
(PHONE BEEPS OFF)
(SIGHS)
(PAPER RUSTLES)
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever, Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(KEYBOARD KEYS CLACK)
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
SO BASICALLY ANYTHING.
(KEYBOARD KEYS CLACK)
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
OH GOD.
HEY YOU!
(SIGHS)
I HAVEN'T TALKED TO YOU
IN FOREVER.
YEAH. WELL, I'VE BEEN
SO FOCUSED ON ALLI.
NO, I'M SORRY
I CAN'T HELP MORE.
YOU'RE STILL FEELING SICK?
(SIGHS)
JUST I CAN'T SEEM
TO SHAKE IT.
I'M TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT IT MIGHT BE.
YOU NEED TO STOP WONDERING
AND GO SEE A DOCTOR ALREADY!
THIS ISN'T GOOD!
I'LL GO SOON.
RIGHT AFTER OUR PRESENTATION
AT WORK-STUDY TODAY.
HEY, DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF THIS.
I COULD OIL IT UP.
MIGHT GET SOME GRIT
IN THE BEARINGS,
BUT AT LEAST
IT'D GO FASTER.
HEY MAN,
WHATEVER YOU GOTTA DO
TO GET THIS THING
TO SHATTER THAT RECORD!
YEAH, ABOUT THAT...
I DON'T THINK I CAN.
I MEAN...
DO WE REALLY HAVE TO MAKE
SUCH A BIG DEAL?
BRO, HALF THE SCHOOL'S
COMING TO SEE YOU DO THIS.
AND AFTER YOU
BREAK THE RECORD,
WHICH YOU WILL,
I MEAN, YOU'LL BE REELIN' IN
MAD LADIES!
THAT'S NOT THE POINT.
THE POINT IS TO BREAK
THIS RECORD
IN HONOUR OF
MY 11-YEAR-OLD SELF AND...
(SIGHS)
AND I'M NOT SURE I CAN.
WELL, GET SURE
BECAUSE WE MOVED THE EVENT
TO THE THEATRE
TO HOLD ALL YOUR FANS.
YEAH,
THIS THING IS HUGE!
ALL RIGHT?
YOU CAN DO IT.
(CLEARS THROAT)
♪ Well, I'll write it
all down for you ♪
♪ Bitter tea, bitter tune,
bitter you ♪
♪ Well, you sow what you sow
what you say ♪
♪ Still you killed her
when you came ♪
CHANTAY:
WHAT'S WITH THE PHARMACY?
OH, IT'S JUST A PRECAUTION.
YOU KNOW WHO HAS
THE GOOD STUFF?
DOCTORS.
LOOK, WE HAVE TEN MINUTES
TILL CLASS.
I'M GONNA UPLOAD
SOME MORE PICTURES
ON BEV'S TWITTER.
SEE YOU IN CLASS.
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
(SNIFFLING)
SQUEEGEE KID:
SPARE CHANGE?
ARE YOU A RUNAWAY?
NAH, I'M A TRAVELLING
SALESMAN.
CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
I'M RUNNING AWAY
TO VANCOUVER.
BUT WHAT DO I DO
WHEN I GET THERE?
WHATEVER YOU WANT,
I GUESS.
OKAY, BUT LIKE HOW DO I FIND
A PLACE TO STAY?
OR MAKE MONEY?
YOU WANT ME TO SHOW YOU?
YEAH, THAT'D BE GREAT!
THANK YOU.
GIMME YOUR BAG.
OH, I SEE.
EFFECTIVE.
NO, I'M SERIOUS,
GIVE IT.
GIVE IT!
NO, IT'S ALL I HAVE.
PLEASE.
(GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
MY TICKET!
DAVE:
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
IN TWENTY-FOUR HOURS,
WESLEY BETENKAMP WILL HOLD
THE WORLD RECORD.
PREPARE TO WITNESS HISTORY.
(CROWD APPLAUDS)
MY MAN, WES,
ARE YOU READY?
ALL RIGHT.
ON YOUR MARK...
GET SET...
POGO!
(SMALL CROWD CHEERS WES ON,
APPLAUDING)
GREAT, MARY,
YOUR KINDERGARTEN WORK-STUDY
SOUNDS LIKE A CHALLENGE.
NEXT, HOLLY J AND CHANTAY.
CHANTAY:
WE'VE BEEN INTERNING
FOR BEV GREYSON.
WE'VE BEEN WORKING ON
HER SOCIAL MEDIA CAMPAIGN.
RIGHT?
RIGHT.
BECAUSE GETTING
FIRST-TIME VOTERS OUT THERE
IS REALLY IMPORTANT.
I'M SORRY, GUYS.
YOU WERE GOING TO SHOW
THE TWITTER FEED YOU DID, RIGHT?
JUST LET ME PRESS
THE BUTTON.
(THUD)
CHANTAY:
HOLLY J!
HOLLY J:
OW...
(PAINED GASP)
(POGO SQUEAKS)
(BLOWS WHISTLE)
DAVE:
ALL RIGHT!
FIFTY-FIVE MINUTES!
(APPLAUSE)
WE'LL TAKE FIVE MINUTE BREAK!
TWENTY-THREE HOURS TO GO
AND MY MAN IS JUST OFF
RECORD PACE!
(APPLAUSE)
HEY MAN,
KILLER FIRST HOUR.
GUINNESS IS GONNA FLIP
OVER THIS!
AND GUESS WHAT,
THERE IS ALREADY A FAN
THAT WANTS SOME PRIVATE TIME
WITH YOU.
A FAN?
BIG RED.
OH, HANNAH!
HI!
I NOTICED YOUR RIG'S
A BIT SLICK.
WELL, I GREASED IT UP.
MADE IT FASTER.
IT'S, YOU KNOW,
IT'S TECHNICAL.
WHAT IF SOMETHING GETS
CAUGHT IN THE BEARINGS.
YOU KNOW ABOUT...?
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY
I CAN GET ENOUGH JPM.
JUMPS PER MINUTE.
YEAH, I KNOW.
OR YOU COULD WIPE OFF
THE GREASE,
SHORTEN THE PISTON LENGTH...
KEEPING MY BOUNCES LOWER!
LOWER BOUNCES
MEAN MORE BOUNCES.
EXACTLY.
BUT ONE FALSE MOVE,
I BOTTOM OUT,
HIT A PEDAL AND GO FLYING.
YOU WANNA SET THE RECORD
OR NOT?
I GUESS
IF IT'S NOT DANGEROUS,
IT'S NOT WORTH IT,
RIGHT?
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I WAS THINKING?
YOU'RE RIGHT,
I'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO MAKE IT ON MY OWN.
THANK YOU FOR LETTING ME
COME BACK.
SO WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
MAYBE I CAN JUST STAY HERE
A COUPLE MORE DAYS,
JUST UNTIL I FIGURE
EVERYTHING OUT.
SAV:
I HAVE A BETTER IDEA.
YOU COULD COME HOME.
YOU PROMISED
YOU WOULDN'T CALL HIM!
I COULDN'T
JUST LET YOU GO.
YES. YOU COULD.
NOW HE'S JUST GONNA DRAG ME
BACK HOME TO MY PARENTS!
I WON'T.
I BEGGED MOM AND DAD
TO LET ME COME ALONE.
I JUST WANNA TALK.
ARE YOU MAD AT ME?
SAV:
YEAH, I WAS.
BUT I'M REALLY GLAD
YOU'RE OKAY.
MOM AND DAD FEEL
THE SAME WAY?
YOU KNOW THEM...
EXACTLY. IF I COME HOME,
THEY'LL JUST YELL.
IT'S LIKE THEY'VE
GIVEN UP ON ME.
YEAH, I GET IT.
YOU DO?
YEAH. I WON'T FORCE YOU
TO COME HOME.
BUT IF YOU DO,
I'VE GOT YOUR BACK.
IT'LL BE DIFFERENT THIS TIME,
I PROMISE.
AND ALLI,
IF YOU DECIDE TO GO
SOMEWHERE ELSE,
PLEASE JUST TELL ME WHERE.
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
DOCTOR:
DON'T TOUCH IT.
COULD BE WORSE.
ONLY THREE STITCHES.
LUCKY ME.
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH MY VOICE?
OH, THE INITIAL TEST
SHOWED SOME ANOMALIES.
YOU'VE HAD
A SORE THROAT?
A LITTLE, BUT...
I MEAN, I'M FINE.
DID SOMEONE CALL
YOUR PARENTS?
I'M EIGHTEEN.
IT'S JUST A COUPLE
OF STITCHES;
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
CAN I GO? I HAVE A REALLY
IMPORTANT PRESENTATION.
I REALLY DON'T
ADVISE THAT.
LOOK, I JUST TOOK
LIKE SIX ENERGY DRINKS...
UH, SOME ASPIRIN,
COUGH SYRUP...
I OVERDID IT.
I'M SORRY.
SELF-MEDICATING CAN HAVE
DANGEROUS RESULTS.
YOU'RE LUCKY
NOTHING WORSE HAPPENED.
NOW LIE BACK, PLEASE.
(GROANS)
WHAT'S WRONG WITH ME?
I REALLY DON'T KNOW.
STREP, MONO...
WE'LL NEED TO DO THE TESTS
TO FIND OUT.
I FEEL FINE.
I'LL COME BACK LATER,
OKAY?
YOU NEED TO STAY HERE.
I'M GONNA SEND SOMEONE IN
TO TAKE SOME BLOOD.
(WINCING IN PAIN)
CHANTAY, I'M GONNA NEED TO
SIT DOWN FOR FIVE MINUTES.
WE HAVE TIME, RIGHT?
YOU REALLY DON'T
LOOK WELL.
(SIGHS)
THIS IS IMPORTANT.
I NEED TO WOW BEV
AND GET A GREAT EVALUATION.
CHANTAY:
WE HAVE A GOOD PRESENTATION.
IT'S STRONG.
WHY DON'T YOU GO HOME
AND REST
AND I'LL GIVE IT?
AND LET YOU TAKE
ALL THE CREDIT?
HEY, I JUST OFFERED YOU
AN OUT
THAT YOU CLEARLY NEED.
YOU'RE ACTING
LIKE A CRAZY PERSON.
I'M A TROOPER
AND I'M GONNA GET
THROUGH THIS.
(UNCOMFORTABLE EXHALE)
(SIGHS)
(DOOR OPENS)
WHERE IS SHE?
SHE'S SAFE.
I SAW HER.
AND YOU DIDN'T
BRING HER HOME?!
(SCOFFS)
YOU KNOW, DO YOU EVER...
DO YOU EVER THINK
THAT MAYBE THAT'S THE REASON
SHE LEFT IN THE FIRST PLACE?
WHATEVER SHE OR I DO,
IT'S NEVER GOOD ENOUGH FOR YOU.
YOUR FATHER AND I HAVE
EVERY RIGHT TO BE ANGRY.
YEAH, MOM,
BUT YOUR ANGER IS SUFFOCATING.
IT'S BIGGER
THAN EVERYTHING ELSE!
MR. BHANDARI: SAVTAJ!
SAV: NO, DAD!
I WASN'T GONNA FORCE HER
TO COME HOME.
SHE'S AFRAID.
SHE'S AFRAID?
OF US?
YEAH.
YOU ESPECIALLY!
SHE'S AFRAID YOU'RE GONNA
COME DOWN ON HER
NO MATTER WHAT SHE DOES.
SHE'S AFRAID
TO BE HERSELF.
AND YOU KNOW,
IF YOU KEEP IT UP,
EVEN IF SHE DOES
COME HOME,
SHE'S JUST GONNA
RUN AWAY AGAIN.
(CROWD APPLAUDS,
MUSIC PLAYS)
♪ You... ♪
♪ Unaffected fool ♪
♪ When... ♪
♪ You wanna feel a bit cool ♪
♪ It's the pogo life ♪
♪ Say it,
Everything's all right ♪
♪ When you're wasting time ♪
♪ You figure
everything is fine ♪
♪ In the pogo mind
♪ You figure
everything is fine ♪
♪ When you're wasting time ♪
(PAINED)
OH!
♪ It's all right ♪
CHANTAY AND HOLLY J
ARE GONNA SHOW US
WHAT WE'RE TOO OLD
TO KNOW
ABOUT GETTING
THE WORD OUT TO TEENS!
I'M ABOUT TO VOTE
FOR THE FIRST TIME
AND I WANT TO BE EXCITED,
BUT...
OUR GENERATION DOESN'T KNOW
ENOUGH ABOUT THE CANDIDATES.
SO THE SOLUTION?
TWITTER.
CHANTAY:
A CAMPAIGN OF TWEETS MEANS
IT'S ALWAYS ON
OUR YOUNG VOTERS MINDS.
THE IMPORTANT THING
IS THAT YOUNG VOTERS FEEL
LIKE THEIR ISSUES ARE
BEING TAKEN INTO ACCOUNT.
IT'S, UM, IMPERATIVE TO...
THAT...
THAT YOU...
OH MY GOD!
I'M SO SORRY.
HOLLY J!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH ME?
♪ Ain't no use in calling up
your friends ♪
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
♪ Ain't no use in hiding
in your bed ♪
♪ And ain't no use in standing
on your head ♪
♪ 'Cause no insides
can fill your loneliness ♪
♪ Seven days of time
to fix your head... ♪
(RELIEVED EXHALE)
♪ Seven days of time
you walk the ledge ♪
♪ And every time you catch
a side of your reflection, ♪
♪ You can't decide ♪
♪ If you should cry
or if it's time to live ♪
(GASPS)
MOM, CAN YOU COME GET ME?
I NEED TO GO TO THE HOSPITAL.
I DON'T KNOW,
I THINK SOMETHING
IS REALLY WRONG.
(SHAKY SOB)
ALLI:
I DIDN'T MEAN TO SCARE YOU.
THEN WHY DID YOU?
I'M SORRY.
MRS. BHANDARI:
WE'RE SORRY TOO.
WE DIDN'T MEAN TO MAKE YOU FEEL
UNWELCOME HERE.
YOU GUYS GAVE UP ON ME.
THE THINGS YOU DID...
WERE MISTAKES!
THEY'RE PART OF GROWING UP.
WHEN I WAS GONE,
I WAS AT JOHNNY'S.
AND HE MADE ME REALIZE
THAT I CAN THRIVE
IN UNIVERSITY.
WE NEVER DOUBTED THAT.
BUT TO GET THERE,
I NEED TO MAKE IT
THROUGH TWO MORE YEARS
HERE...
AS MYSELF.
AND, YOU KNOW,
MAYBE I'M NOT THE LITTLE GIRL
YOU WANT ME TO BE,
BUT I'M STILL GOOD.
YOU GUYS JUST GIVE ME
A CHANCE TO PROVE IT.
WE'VE BEEN FIGHTING WITH YOU
FOR SO LONG
THAT WE'VE LOST TOUCH
WITH EACH OTHER AS PEOPLE.
I THINK WE ALL NEED
A BLANK SLATE.
ALLI:
SO... HOW DO WE DO THAT?
MR. BHANDARI:
YOUR MOTHER AND I WILL
TRY TO UNDERSTAND
THE PRESSURES YOU FACE
AS A TEENAGE GIRL TODAY.
AND I WANT
TO CHANGE TOO.
MAYBE WE CAN TALK
TO SOMEONE?
LIKE A THERAPIST?
YEAH, SOMEONE NEUTRAL.
THAT'S, THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
A STRANGER IN
OUR FAMILY BUSINESS?
PERHAPS...
IT CAN HELP US.
TO TALK TO
EACH OTHER MORE.
ALLI...
WE'RE JUST...
WE'RE SO GLAD YOU'RE HOME.
(EMOTIONAL EXHALE)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
HEY! UP TOP!
I CAN'T.
IT'S SPRAINED.
ALL RIGHT. WELL, WHEN ARE YOU
GONNA GET BACK UP
ON THE POGO STICK.
(SCOFFS) HALF PAST NEVER.
ARE YOU CRAZY?
BUT YOU WERE BEATING
THE RECORD.
I GUESS,
BUT I'LL BE SIXTEEN
IN A COUPLE DAYS.
IT'S TOO LATE.
NO CAR, NO GIRL,
NO RECORD.
I LET MY 11-YEAR-OLD SELF
DOWN.
HI, WESLEY.
HANNAH!
I CAN'T BELIEVE I TRIED
TO SHOW OFF.
I'M SO DUMB.
NAH, IT WAS AWESOME!
WE BOTH KNEW THAT
MODIFICATION WAS RISKY.
I HAVE THE WRIST BRACE
TO PROVE IT.
I KNOW.
IT'S A BUMMER.
REALLY? WHY?
KINDA HOPED THAT
AFTER YOU BEAT THE RECORD,
WE COULD CELEBRATE...
AND MAYBE HOLD HANDS.
DAVE:
BRO. BRO.
DO IT!
OH! OH, WELL,
DO YOU MAYBE WANNA
GO ON A DATE TYPE THING
SOMETIME?
I'D LOVE TO.
LET ME KNOW WHEN.
OKAY.
DAVE:
HEY! YOU DID IT!
A GIRLFRIEND BEFORE SIXTEEN,
WITH TWO DAYS TO SPARE!
(CHUCKLES)
WE'VE GOT SOME
CONCLUSIVE RESULTS.
OH, GOOD.
DOCTOR:
IT LOOKS LIKE YOUR RENAL SYSTEM
WAS COMPROMISED
BY A STREPTOCOCCAL
INFECTION,
WHICH MAY HAVE RESULTED
IN GLOMEROLUNEPHRITIS.
I'M SORRY, WHAT?
DID YOU SUSPECT
YOU HAD STREP THROAT?
WERE YOU RUNNING A FEVER?
MAYBE. I'VE BEEN RUNNING
AROUND A LOT.
IF INFECTIONS LIKE THIS
GO UNTREATED,
THEY CAN AFFECT YOU
IN UNEXPECTED WAYS.
IN YOUR CASE,
YOUR KIDNEYS WERE COMPROMISED,
WHICH IS WHAT CAUSED
YOUR URGE INCONTINENCE TODAY.
YOU MEAN,
THAT'S WHY I WET MYSELF.
SYMPTOMS HAVE TO BE
TREATED IMMEDIATELY
TO AVOID COMPLICATIONS
LIKE THIS.
OH, CAN SHE TAKE SOME
ANTIBIOTICS?
YES, BUT WE ALSO NEED
TO RUN A COURSE OF DIALYSIS.
WHAT? FOR HOW LONG?
WELL, IT'S TOUGH TO SAY.
UNTIL THE DIALYSIS GETS
EVERYTHING UNDER CONTROL.
WAIT. AM I...
IS THIS SERIOUS?
WE REALLY DON'T KNOW
HOW YOU'RE GOING TO RESPOND
TO TREATMENT,
BUT IT IS IMPORTANT
WE START TODAY.
OH MY GOD.
I'M REALLY SICK?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
OKAY, WHAT GIVES?
I KNOW THEY WANNA IMPRESS
THE THERAPIST,
BUT THE SESSION'S
NOT UNTIL TOMORROW!
MOM JUST SAID
TO PUT THIS ON.
OKAY. WELL, DO YOU THINK
I LOOK OKAY FOR WHATEVER?
MR. BHANDARI:
I THINK YOU LOOK PERFECT...
FOR OUR FAMILY PORTRAIT.
ALLI:
REALLY?
SAV:
DIDN'T WE DO ONE
LAST YEAR?
ENOUGH TALKING.
EVERYBODY IN!
(CAMERA BEEPS)
THIS PHOTO WILL REST
ON THE MANTLE,
DEPICTING THE NEW AND IMPROVED
BHANDARI FAMILY.
THIS IS OUR BLANK SLATE.
SAY BHANDAREEEEEEZ.
THE BHANDARIS:
BHANDAREEEEZ!
(SHUTTER CLICKS)
(LAUGHING)
BEV:
I HAD SETBACKS;
EVERYONE DOES.
IT MAKES YOU STRONGER.
AND I COULD USE A TOUGHIE
LIKE YOU ON MY TEAM.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
I NEED DRIVEN, DETERMINED,
SUMMER STUDENTS
IF I RUN FOR MAYOR.
YOU AND CHANTAY
MAKE A GOOD TEAM.
I'M LUCKY SHE WAS THERE.
SAV:
SORRY TO INTERRUPT.
BEV:
NOT AT ALL.
I'LL SEE YOU SOON,
HOLLY J.
THANK YOU.
HEY.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
UNCOMFORTABLE.
EMBARRASSED.
IF I HAD KNOWN
YOU WERE THIS SICK...
YOU WERE BUSY.
WE BOTH WERE.
(EMOTIONAL SIGH)
SAV:
I WAS REALLY WORRIED
ABOUT YOU.
YOU'RE GONNA GET BETTER,
RIGHT?
I KNOW YOU WILL;
YOU'RE HOLLY J.
I'LL DO MY BEST.