SO, YOU WANTED TO TALK?
MY LIFE NEEDS A REBOOT,
MS. SAUVE.
IS IT THE ELECTION?
AND SOME OTHER STUFF.
I JUST...
I'M STARTING TO WONDER
IF I HAVE TO KISS
MY YALE DREAMS GOODBYE.
WELL, EVEN IF YOU DID
WIN THE ELECTION,
THERE ARE NO GUARANTEES.
YOU'RE COMPETING AGAINST
SOME OF THE BRIGHTEST MINDS
IN THE WORLD,
AND THERE ARE ONLY
SO MANY SPOTS.
YEAH, BUT I HAVE
MY EXTRA-CURRICULARS,
GOOD GRADES,
AND MY TVM INTERNSHIP.
ALL OF WHICH ARE GREAT.
WELL, WHAT ELSE CAN I DO?
HAVE YOU CONSIDERED
A TEAM SPORT?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
NO NEED TO GIVE UP
JUST YET.
YOU'LL NEED TO WRITE
ENTRANCE ESSAYS
WITH A STRONG HOOK,
ACE YOUR INTERVIEW,
NAIL YOUR SATS.
ARE YOU STUDYING?
A LITTLE?
HAVE YOU THOUGHT OF TAKING
A PREP COURSE?
MOST IVY LEAGUE APPLICANTS
GET SOME HELP.
WOW! $2000?
YEAH,
THEY AREN'T CHEAP.
(SIGHS)
THANKS, MS. SAUVE.
I'LL UM...
I'LL FIGURE SOMETHING OUT.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, Woo-oo! ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
STUDENT: (OVER PA)
POWER SQUAD AUDITIONS CONTINUE
TODAY AFTER SCHOOL.
COME OUT AND SHOW
YOUR PANTHER PRIDE.
WOW! A LITTLE LIGHT READING.
YEAH,
STILL CAN'T BELIEVE I WON.
WELL, I CAN.
YOU DESERVE IT.
AND YOU HAD A LITTLE HELP.
UH, YEAH.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
UM, GUYS?
ME AND THE NEW GRADE REPS
WERE TALKING,
AND, UH, WE WANNA THROW YOU
A BABY SHOWER.
WHAT?
UH... UH, NO.
(STAMMERING)
I MEAN, IT'S TOO SOON.
BAD LUCK, MAN.
YOU KNOW GIRLS.
AH, FOR SURE. WE'LL...
WE'LL HOLD OFF A WHILE.
OKAY. UM, THIS?
OR THE LACK OF THIS
IS A PROBLEM.
YEAH. PRINCIPAL SIMPSON
WANTS ME TO TALK
TO COUNSELOR SAUVE.
WE NEED TO TELL
THE TRUTH.
THE TRUTH - THAT WE LIED
ABOUT BEING PREGNANT.
GREAT.
SOCIAL SUICIDE.
YOU GOT ANY BETTER IDEAS?
OKAY.
♪ Slow down ♪
♪ Cool now ♪
♪ Moving much too fast ♪
FANTASTIC NEWS!
THAT WAS THE HEADMISTRESS
AT BROMLEY BROOK!
BROMLEY BROOK?
THAT'S IN MAINE!
VERMONT.
YOU LOVE TO SKI!
(SIGHS)
WELL, WE COULD ALWAYS
DISCUSS GROTON,
IF YOU LIKE.
BOARDING SCHOOL?
YOU SAID YOU DIDN'T WANT
TO GO BACK TO NEW YORK.
THERE'S ANOTHER OPTION.
OH, NO.
NO, NO-NO.
YOU CANNOT STAY HERE.
YOU NEED A STABLE
ENVIRONMENT.
WELL, THAT'S WHAT
DEGRASSI WOULD BE.
I HAVE FRIENDS HERE.
OR A FRIEND.
BUT WHO WOULD WATCH
OVER YOU?
HOLLY J'S PRACTICALLY
FAMILY.
SHE'S ONLY 17.
(SIGHS)
I KNOW YOU'VE BEEN
DOING REALLY WELL
WITH YOU'RE THERAPY,
BUT...
I'LL GET A THERAPIST HERE!
AND WE COULD HIRE SOMEONE,
DAY TO DAY, LIKE A...
AU PAIR OR GUARDIAN.
I'D HAVE TO GO BACK
AND FORTH.
YOU'RE THE BEST MOM EVER!
YOU HAVE TO GET
GOOD GRADES.
NO DISTRACTIONS.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
WHATEVER!
ANYTHING!
MOM, WHATEVER HAPPENED
WAS BOBBY'S FAULT.
HE'S THE ONE WITH THE PROBLEM,
NOT ME, I PROMISE.
OH, HONEY, I'M SO SORRY
I PUT SO MUCH PRESSURE ON YOU.
I BETTER MAKE
SOME PHONE CALLS.
THANK YOU. THANK YOU.
THANK YOU!
♪♪♪
♪ This is all that we said ♪
♪ This is all that we know ♪
WE MOVE IN A MONTH.
THOSE BOXES AREN'T GOING
TO PACK THEMSELVES.
YEAH, I'LL GET ON THAT.
RIGHT AFTER I FINISH PLANNING
A FUTURE FOR MYSELF
THAT DOESN'T INVOLVE
THE POORHOUSE.
YOU KNOW,
COMPARED TO OTHER KIDS,
YOU HAVE A LOT.
YEAH, JUST NOT THE TWO GRAND
I NEED FOR AN SAT TUTOR.
IF I'M EVER GOING
TO GET TO YALE...
UGH! WHAT IS IT WITH THIS
OBSESSION WITH YALE?
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
MAYBE IT WAS A MISTAKE
LETTING YOU STAY
WITH THE COYNE'S IN NEW YORK
THIS SUMMER.
THAT WAS THE FIRST TIME
I FELT I WAS IN A PLACE
I BELONGED.
HOLLY J,
YOU ARE A SMART GIRL.
BUT IT'S TIME
FOR A REALITY CHECK.
THAT MY LIFE SUCKS
AND THERE'S NOTHING I CAN DO
ABOUT IT?
THAT YOU'RE GONNA
GO PLACES.
REALLY GOOD PLACES.
BUT MAYBE NOT TO YALE
WITH DECLAN.
YEAH, SO PRETTY MUCH
WHAT I SAID.
♪ And all that I know ♪
♪ Is all that
I'm leaving behind ♪
♪ You can never be sure... ♪
ALLI:
SO, HOW ARE THEY?
IS EVERYTHING FUZZY?
AT FIRST,
BUT NOW I'M 20/20.
I JUST WISH SOMEONE
WOULD NOTICE
I'M NOT WEARING
MY UGLY GLASSES ANYMORE.
KC:
DID SHE DO IT?
OH, SHE DEFINITELY
DID IT!
WHY WOULD ANYONE DO THAT?
SHE HAD A PROBLEM,
SHE FIXED IT.
IF YOU COULD FIX YOUR ASPERGERS,
WOULDN'T YOU?
NO.
WE SHOULD ALL BE HAPPY
THE WAY WE ARE.
HOW DO THEY GET THEM
IN THERE?
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
OKAY, LET'S WARM UP
WITH SOME JUMPING JACKS!
OH, UH, SIR?
OH, RIGHT.
WELL, YOU CAN SIT THIS ONE OUT.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
SHE DOESN'T LOOK
ANY DIFFERENT.
MAYBE IT'S
SOMETHING ELSE?
WELL, SOMEONE'S GONNA HAVE
TO FIND OUT FOR SURE.
♪♪♪
HOLLY J:
NOW IF ONLY DECLAN
WOULD COME VISIT ME
ON MY LUNCH BREAK,
EVERYTHING WOULD BE
PERFECT.
YOU KNOW HE'D BE HERE
IF VANDERBILT
WASN'T THE FAST TRACK
TO YALE.
RIGHT. YALE.
DO YOU LIKE
THIS CREDENZA?
MY MOM AND I ARE LOOKING
AT CONDOS THIS WEEKEND.
AND YOU'RE ALREADY
PICKING OUT FURNITURE?
I NEED TO KNOW WHAT
TO TELL MY DESIGNER.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
IT'S...ALMOST FOUR GRAND!
OH, YEAH.
SAME AS MY BOOTS.
(KEYBOARD KEYS CLACK)
FIONA:
DONE!
HOLD ON, YOU JUST BOUGHT
A $4000 CREDENZA ONLINE?
I KNOW, SO EASY!
IT'S EASY FOR YOU TO SAY.
WHAT? IT'S ONLY MONEY.
BESIDES, WE'RE GONNA NEED
SOMETHING TO PUT THE TV ON
WHEN WE WATCH
CHICK FLICKS.
OKAY,
FIRST RULE OF PLASTIC:
PAY IT OFF RIGHT AWAY.
OH, MY OLD ACCOUNT
STILL WORKS!
JUST NEED A NEW PASSWORD.
"GOT-2-BE-FIONA-C."
HOLLY J:
SO MUCH FOR ONLINE PRIVACY.
YOU'RE RIDICULOUS!
FRIENDS HAVE NO SECRETS.
ALL RIGHT, TIME TO SHOP
FOR A PLASMA SCREEN!
(KEYBOARD KEYS CLACK)
CLARE!
CAN I WALK YOU
TO CLASS?
YEAH. SURE, WESLEY.
SO, ARE THEY,
LIKE, SORE?
YOU NOTICED!
AT FIRST, A LITTLE BIT,
BUT NOW
THEY'RE GOOD AS NEW.
WOW.
CAN I TOUCH 'EM?
WESLEY, THAT'S...WEIRD.
FOR PROOF.
TO SEE HOW THEY FEEL.
WELL, I'M SURE
THEY FEEL THE SAME,
BUT...OKAY.
REALLY?
YEAH, JUST BE GENTLE.
(GASPS)
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?!
I'M SORRY,
ARE THEY TENDER?
WAIT, YOU THINK
I GOT A BOOB JOB?
EVERYONE DOES.
I GOT MY EYES FIXED,
DUMMY!
WHO STARTED THIS RUMOUR?
JENNA. I HAVE TO GO.
I'M SORRY!
READY?
SMILE.
HI, DEGRASSI.
PRESIDENT SAV BHANDARI HERE
WITH ANYA MCPHERSON.
HI.
I'D LIKE TO THANK YOU ALL
FOR YOUR SUPPORT
THROUGHOUT MY CAMPAIGN.
BUT THERE'S SOMETHING THAT
WE NEED TO TELL YOU.
ANYA?
ME? OKAY.
UM, THE TRUTH IS THAT...
SAV AND I AREN'T
PREGNANT.
STUDENTS:
(ASTONISHED MURMURS)
ANYA:
I...
I UM...
I HAD A MISCARRIAGE.
SUPER BUMMER.
I'M FINE. UH...
BUT, UH, PLEASE GIVE US
SOME SPACE
TO DEAL WITH THIS, OKAY?
THANKS, ANYA!
AND I'LL LET YOU GET BACK
TO YOUR ANNOUNCEMENTS.
SAV:
LOCKER ASSIGNMENT DISPUTES
CAN BE TAKEN UP
WITH YOUR STUDENT OMBUDSMAN.
STUDENT TRANSIT PASSES
ARE ON SALE
IN THE STUDENT COUNCIL ROOM.
I'M REALLY SORRY.
THANKS.
SYMPATHY FLOWERS.
EVERYONE'S BEING SO NICE.
SMELL?
YOU REALIZE THAT THIS WILL
GET BACK TO MY PARENTS,
WHO WILL KILL ME.
AND THEY'LL HEAR ABOUT
A VICIOUS RUMOUR
STARTED BY
THE BITTER CANDIDATE
YOU DEFEATED
IN THE ELECTION.
WOW. THAT'S SCARY.
YOU MIGHT BE
A POLITICAL GENIUS.
(LAUGHS)
WE MAKE A PRETTY GOOD TEAM,
YOU KNOW?
WAIT.
(SIGHS)
I NEED TO KNOW
THAT IT'S GONNA BE DIFFERENT
THIS TIME.
DECLAN:
THOUGHT YOU'D BE CONDO SHOPPING
WITH FI.
MY YALE ESSAY CALLS.
WHO'S YOUR GREATEST
INFLUENCE?
DALAI LAMA.
SINCE WHEN?
SINCE I HAD TO WRITE
MY ESSAY.
WHATEVER IT TAKES, RIGHT?
HOLLY J:
YEAH.
IT'S JUST, THERE'S A LOT MORE
TO GETTING INTO YALE
THAN I THOUGHT.
THERE ARE OTHER SCHOOLS,
RIGHT?
GOOD SCHOOLS.
YEAH, BUT YOU'RE BETTER
THAN THOSE OTHER SCHOOLS.
HOLLY J:
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
WHAT IF I DON'T GET IN?
DECLAN:
COME ON.
YOU'RE CONFIDENT,
YOU'RE CAPABLE.
I LOVE THAT.
YOU'RE NOT LIKE ANY
OF THE OTHER GIRLS I KNOW.
THE OTHER GIRLS WITH MONEY?
DECLAN:
THE GOLD-DIGGERS!
HMM... RIGHT.
WELL, I BETTER GET BACK
TO THAT ESSAY.
SO, TALK LATER?
SURE.
STAY POSITIVE, OKAY?
OKAY.
♪♪♪
♪ Look at the sky ♪
♪ It's changing ♪
♪ Take a picture in my mind ♪
♪ We're sailing ♪
♪ I watch it fade away ♪
I'M NOT DIGGING,
I'M JUST...
SHARING THE WEALTH.
♪ Don't pass me by ♪
ANYA:
(LAUGHS QUIETLY)
I'M NOT SURE THIS COUNTS
AS FRENCH HOMEWORK,
BUT I LIKE IT.
(BOTH LAUGH)
REMIND ME AGAIN,
WHY DID WE EVER BREAK UP?
YOUR DIRTY SECRET
NAMED FARRAH.
RIGHT. MY PARENTS
"LITTLE ARRANGEMENT."
WELL, THAT'S NOT GONNA WORK
FOR ME.
SAV,
YOU'LL TELL THEM?
(KEYS JANGLING)
(DOOR CLOSING)
SOMEONE'S HOME!
OH!
QUICK! UM...
UH... HERE. BACK DOOR.
BACK DOOR! UH...
YOU SAID IT WOULD BE
DIFFERENT THIS TIME.
ANYA, COME ON
LET'S JUST...
GO! PLEASE!
MRS. BHANDARI:
SAVTAJ?
WHAT IS ANYA DOING HERE?
MOM. HI.
UH, TRUTH IS...
ANYA NEEDED
MY FRENCH NOTES,
AND WE CAME BACK HERE
TO GET THEM.
AND SHE WAS JUST LEAVING,
RIGHT?
WE WERE MAKING OUT.
ANYA.
SORRY, SAV.
NO MORE LIES.
BUT DON'T WORRY,
MRS. BHANDARI,
IT WILL NEVER
HAPPEN AGAIN.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
OH! HEY.
OH, WHAT'RE YOU
DOING HERE?
RE-ENROLLING!
I START TOMORROW!
S.A.T. PREP COURSE, HUH?
YEAH. PRIVATE TUTORING.
GOTTA GET A LEG UP.
GOOD FOR YOU.
IT'S REALLY AN INVESTMENT
IN YOURSELF.
GOTTA SPEND IT TO MAKE IT,
AS THEY SAY.
WELL, IF ANYONE
DESERVES THE BEST,
IT'S YOU.
SO LUNCH AT THE DOT?
FEWER RAGING MALE
HORMONES THERE.
SURE.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
SO I CONFIRMED
WITH DAVE;
JENNA WAS GROUND ZERO
OF HOOTERGATE.
SO WHEN DO WE GET
HER BACK?
WAY AHEAD OF YOU.
WATCH THIS.
HEY, JENNA.
NOTICE ANYTHING?
SO... IT'S TRUE.
YOU WENT THROUGH
WITH THE SURGERY.
YEAH, I KEEP HEARING
SOME CRAZY RUMOUR ABOUT THAT.
IT'S OBVIOUSLY
NOT A RUMOUR.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT
MORE HIGHLY OF YOU, YOU KNOW.
AND THAT'S CHANGED?
IT'S DESPERATE,
IT'S SLUTTY,
AND I'M STARTING TO THINK
IT'S ALL PART
OF SOME CRAZY PLAN
TO GET KC BACK.
(LAUGHS)
WOW, YOU ARE SO INSECURE.
I'M NOT THE ONE
WHO GOT A BOOB JOB.
NEITHER AM I, JENNA!
I GOT LASER EYE SURGERY.
SEE? NO GLASSES?
OH...
UH HUH.
OOPS?
IF I WANTED KC BACK?
I WOULDN'T NEED
FAKE BOOBS TO GET HIM.
(LAUGHS)
WANT ME TO TELL THE WHOLE SCHOOL
I MADE IT UP?
THEY CAN THINK
WHAT THEY WANT.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
MS. DAWES:
OKAY, WE'LL FINISH UP
TOMORROW.
SAV:
ANYA! WAIT UP.
(SIGHS)
IT'S OKAY, SAV.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO APOLOGIZE.
YES, I DO.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE LIED
TO MY MOM.
BUT YOU DID.
AGAIN.
WE ARE BAD FOR EACH OTHER,
AND UNTIL YOU LEARN
TO STAND UP TO YOUR PARENTS,
THAT'S NEVER GONNA CHANGE.
ANYA, COME ON.
I'M SORRY.
GOOD LUCK,
MR. PRESIDENT.
YOU KNOW, IT'S PROBABLY
NOT TOO LATE
TO TRANSFER BACK TO MUSIC.
♪ Sunset sang
the sweetest tune ♪
♪ Just the song he wrote ♪
♪ For his true love the moon ♪
THANKS.
OKAY, SO I'VE NARROWED IT DOWN
TO THREE OPTIONS.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU WANT A CONDO
IN THIS ONE HORSE TOWN?
I LIKE IT HERE.
THIS CITY, THIS PLACE,
DEGRASSI.
EVERYTHING IS PERFECT.
UGH!
EXCEPT FOR THE COFFEE.
BUT SERIOUSLY,
I ONLY HAVE ONE FRIEND
IN THE WHOLE WORLD.
I'M SO LUCKY THAT IT'S YOU.
YEAH, I'M LUCKY, TOO.
THAT'S WEIRD.
WHAT, NOT ENOUGH
CLOSET SPACE?
NO, I, I JUST...
DON'T REMEMBER MAKING
AN EMAIL TRANSFER.
WELL, YOU ARE A FREQUENT
ONLINE SHOPPER.
YEAH, BUT I KEEP TRACK.
WHEN WOULD I HAVE...?
HOW MUCH WAS
YOUR S.A.T. COURSE?
MM, I'M NOT SURE.
A BUNCH.
I TOLD YOU MY PASSWORD.
DID YOU DO THIS?
NO!
(SIGHS) YES.
YOU STOLE FROM ME?
BORROWED.
I REALLY THOUGHT
I COULD PAY IT BACK
BEFORE YOU NOTICED.
I DIDN'T HAVE
ANY OTHER WAY.
HOW COULD YOU DO THIS?
IT WAS A MISTAKE.
IT WAS A HUGE MISTAKE.
AFTER BOBBY, I CAME HERE
BECAUSE OF YOU.
YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO BE
THE ONE PERSON
IN THE WHOLE WORLD
THAT I COULD TRUST.
BUT YOU USED ME.
WHY, HOLLY J?
I'M BROKE.
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT IT'S LIKE.
YEAH, WELL,
THE SADDEST PART,
IF YOU HAD JUST ASKED,
I WOULD'VE GIVEN YOU THE MONEY.
(SIGHS)
ALLI:
I GIVE YOU A NINE
FOR MAKING JENNA SQUIRM,
AND A 9-9 FOR WIPING THAT GRIN
OFF HER FACE.
CLARE:
IT WAS PRETTY SATISFYING.
I HARDLY RECOGNIZE YOU
ANY MORE.
AND YET, SO FEW PEOPLE
HAVE NOTICED
HOW I REALLY CHANGED.
MAYBE I SHOULD JUST,
I DON'T KNOW,
GO BACK TO THE OLD ME.
UH, NO WAY!
GIVE ME THOSE.
CLAIRE:
OH! MY GLASSES!
(HEAVY METAL MUSIC
BLARING FROM CAR)
I THINK THEY'RE DEAD.
IT-IT'S OKAY.
I, UH, I DON'T NEED THEM
ANY MORE.
GOT LASER SURGERY.
YOU HAVE PRETTY EYES.
THANKS.
I'LL, UH,
SEE YOU AROUND?
I GUESS YOU WILL.
ALLI:
UH-OH.
I'VE SEEN THAT LOOK
BEFORE.
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
NEW LOCKER.
SO I GUESS
YOU'RE STAYING?
I CALLED YOU A MILLION TIMES
LAST NIGHT.
(SIGHS)
I'D STILL RATHER BE HERE.
DON'T WORRY.
I DIDN'T TELL DECLAN.
THANKS.
PLEASE, FIONA.
LOOK, I KNOW
I MADE A MISTAKE,
BUT YOU HAVE
TO FORGIVE ME.
WHY?
BECAUSE WE'RE BOTH
LACKING
IN THE FRIEND DEPARTMENT.
WE NEED EACH OTHER.
(SIGHS)
SO THAT MONEY THING.
THAT WAS JUST...
BAD JUDGMENT, RIGHT?
IT'LL NEVER,
NEVER HAPPEN AGAIN.
AND I'LL FIND A WAY
TO PAY YOU BACK.
I KNOW A WAY.
$2000 DIVIDED
BY MINIMUM WAGE...
YOU OWE ME ABOUT
200 HOURS OF YOUR TIME.
OH. OKAY.
GOOD.
SO, I'M GONNA SLEEP OVER
TONIGHT.
TOO MANY NIGHTS
IN A HOTEL.
MY PLACE?
WITH ALL THE BOXES?
NO BIGGIE.
OH, ANOTHER THING!
I'M TRANSFERRING INTO
YOUR HISTORY CLASS.
OH, AND CALCULUS.
DO YOU HAVE FRENCH
THIS SEMESTER?
YEAH. WHY?
SWITCH IT TO NEXT,
SO WE CAN HELP EACH OTHER.
SURE. YOU GOT IT.
WALK ME TO CLASS?
I'M STARTING TO FEEL PRETTY GOOD
ABOUT THIS YEAR.
YEAH.
YEAH, ME TOO.