♪♪♪
THANKS FOR THE ESCORT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU CAME
ALL THE WAY HERE
FOR THE THEATRE AWARDS.
WE'LL MEET UP
TO GET GLAM LATER?
I THOUGHT I'D STICK AROUND,
SEE IF I RUN INTO
ANY OLD FRIENDS.
HOLLY J.
CAN YOU BLAME ME?
I HAVEN'T SPOKEN TO HER
IN A MONTH!
(BELL RINGS)
CAN I WALK MY SISTER
TO CLASS?
(LAUGHS)
YOU'RE NOT EXACTLY DRESSED
FOR THE OCCASION.
ALSO NOT ALLOWED?
NON-STUDENTS.
STRANGER DANGER.
WHAT, YOU'VE GOT
SOME BIG PLAN
TO WIN HOLLY J BACK?
A CHARMING GRIN,
AN HONEST TALK.
AN OFFER TO TAKE HER
ON A ROMANTIC MAKE UP WEEKEND
ANYWHERE SHE WANTS?
MR. COYNE!
I'M SURPRISED YOU LEFT
NEW YORK
FOR OUR LITTLE AWARDS.
WELL...
THE PLAY WAS VERY IMPORTANT
TO ME, MS. SINCLAIR.
I WOULDN'T MISS IT.
HOW ABOUT LUNCH?
YEAH... YEAH, SURE.
MEET YOU BACK HERE?
OKAY.
(SIGHS)
WHAT?
IT'S ONLY LUNCH.
I WANT HER BACK
IN THE FAMILY
AS MUCH AS YOU DO,
DECLAN.
JUST...
DON'T GET YOUR HOPES UP.
NO, TRUST ME.
THIS TIME WILL BE DIFFERENT.
(SIGHS)
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, whatever ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
SO, HOW IS MY FAVOURITE
PRINCIPAL THIS MORNING?
FINE, THANKS.
IS THERE SOMETHING
I CAN HELP YOU WITH?
JUST A LITTLE MATTER OF,
DON'T SHUT DOWN POWER SQUAD!
IT'S NOT FAIR!
DIDN'T YOU READ
THE LETTER HOME?
(AGGRAVATED SIGH)
LOOK. AFTER THE INCIDENTS
AT VEGAS NIGHT,
WE HAVE TO GET A HANDLE
ON STUDENT CONDUCT.
THE POWER SQUAD'S
IN THE SAME BOAT
AS EVERY OTHER UNSUPERVISED
SCHOOL GROUP OR TEAM.
SO, GIVE US A STAFF SUPERVISOR!
OUR TEACHERS ARE STRETCHED
TO THE LIMITS AS IT IS.
I'VE BEEN WORKING FOR YEARS
TO MAKE CAPTAIN,
AND NOW YOU'RE TAKING
IT ALL AWAY
BECAUSE OF A FEW STUPID KIDS?
MR. SIMPSON:
THIS ISN'T UP FOR DISCUSSION.
YOU'LL HAVE TO RETURN
YOUR UNIFORMS.
NOT COOL, MR. SIMPSON!
(FRUSTRATED GROAN)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
WHOA,
WHAT WAS THAT MOVE?
IT'S A SIDE HUG!
(WRY CHUCKLE)
WHAT?
IT'S STILL ALLOWED.
BUT MAYBE AT LUNCH,
WE CAN LOCK UP
THE STUDENT COUNCIL ROOM
FOR A LITTLE TLC?
I'M SORTA BUSY AT LUNCH.
WHAT? NO, I THOUGHT
WE HAD TO UH...
FINALIZE THE DETAILS
ON THAT AWARDS DEALIE.
I'M HAVING LUNCH WITH DECLAN.
(CLEARS THROAT)
SO...
THE EX IS BACK.
HE'S "SPACE AWAKENING'S"
DIRECTOR.
OKAY, HE'S ONLY HERE
FOR THE AWARDS.
YEAH, AND PROBABLY
TO TRY AND GET YOU BACK!
WITH THAT SMILE,
AND THAT CHARM.
AND THAT MONEY!
I'M-I'M PROBABLY NOT
EVEN ALLOWED
TO CARE ABOUT ANY
OF THIS, AM I?
I JUST, I DON'T WANNA BE
GOTTEN BACK.
THIS,
IS EXACTLY WHAT I'M LOOKING
FOR RIGHT NOW.
(LAUGHS)
MS. DAWES:
MR. GOLDSWORTHY.
THE NEW DRESS CODE
IS NOT "MORTICIAN."
THAT'S DETENTION,
YOU KNOW THE RULES!
ELI:
ACTUALLY, NO, I DON'T.
I MISSED LAST WEEK,
REMEMBER?
SUSPENSION?
MS. DAWES:
WELL, THAT'S A FAIR DEFENSE.
BUT THIS IS YOUR ONLY WARNING.
(GRUNTS WITH EFFORT)
(SIGHS)
DODGED A BULLET THERE!
I THOUGHT YOU ONLY
DODGED KNIVES.
REALLY?
THREE WEEKS AND I'M STILL
IN THE DOGHOUSE?
I ONLY MESSED WITH FITZ
TO DEFEND YOUR HONOUR,
AND IF I'D KNOWN THAT PSYCHO
WOULD PULL A KNIFE...
EIGHT...
NINE...
TEN.
NOW YOU'RE FORGIVEN.
THANK YOU.
(LAUGHS)
I'LL MAKE IT UP
TO YOU TONIGHT!
ON OUR FIRST OFFICIAL DATE!
YOU GOT CHUCK PALAHNIUK
TICKETS?
HE'S READING AN UNPUBLISHED
FIGHT CLUB EXCERPT TONIGHT!
I'VE GOT THE THEATRE
AWARDS TONIGHT.
AND BOTH MY PARENTS
ARE COMING.
AH.
THEY'RE NOT FIGHTING ANYMORE?
OH, THEY'RE STILL FIGHTING!
FIGHTING JUST MIGHT BE
THE NEW NORMAL.
BUT THE TALK DOESN'T START
'TIL EIGHT,
SO DO YOU THINK THAT
PARENTAL MEDIATION
WILL BE DONE BY THEN?
YOINK!
SIMPSON WOULDN'T LISTEN?
NO, HE WANTS THE UNIFORMS BACK.
SO THAT'S IT, THEN.
POWER SQUAD'S KAPUT?
OH, IT'S FAR FROM KAPUT.
I'M GONNA FIGHT THIS!
(KEYS CLICK)
CHANTAY:
WHAT?
I CAN'T GET ON MY BLOG!
MS. OH:
OR TWITTER, MYSPACE,
LINKEDIN,
ANY NUMBER OF SOCIAL
NETWORKING SITES.
WHEN WILL THEY BE BACK UP?
MS. OH:
WHENEVER THE SCHOOL DECIDES
TO LIFT THE FIREWALL.
APPARENTLY,
KEEPING KIDS IN THE DARK
KEEPS THEM SAFE.
(BUTTONS CLICK)
(PHONE BEEPS)
CHANTAY:
STUPID PHONE!
SORRY, HON.
CELL PHONE JAMMER.
ARGH!
♪♪♪
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
HOLLY J:
SO, "SPACE AWAKENING"
BROUGHT YOU ALL THE WAY
FROM NEW YORK?
I CARED ABOUT THAT PLAY.
(SIGHS) AND...
I THOUGHT I'D RUN
INTO YOU.
WHEN YOU SAID I SOLVED
ALL MY PROBLEMS WITH MONEY,
I REALLY TOOK IT TO HEART.
MY MOM'S HELPING ME
SET UP A CHARITY.
TO PROVIDE SCHOLARSHIPS
FOR INNER CITY KIDS.
WOW.
I'M IMPRESSED!
CAN'T TAKE IT WITH YOU, RIGHT?
NO.
SO, ANY CUTE GIRLS
VOLUNTEER IN YOUR CHARITY?
NAH.
I'VE BEEN A MONK.
(LAUGHS)
HOW ABOUT YOU,
ANY COWBOYS AMBLE
INTO YOUR STEAKHOUSE?
WELL, THAT'S ACTUALLY WHY
I THOUGHT WE SHOULD CATCH UP.
IT'S ABOUT ME AND...
SAV.
(LAUGHS)
SAV?
ARE YOU LIKE,
BOYFRIEND, GIRLFRIEND?
IT'S NOT SERIOUS.
IT'S ACTUALLY UNTIL
WE GRADUATE.
AND THEN WE'RE GONNA GO
OUR SEPARATE WAYS.
(STUMBLES OVER WORDS)
...O-OKAY.
I MEAN,
IT'S NONE OF MY BUSINESS.
I'M JUST GLAD
WE'RE TALKING AGAIN.
(LAUGHS)
(MUFFLED CHATTER OF AUDIENCE)
YOU KNOW, WE COULD ALWAYS
WAIT FOR DAD IN THE THEATRE.
YOUR FATHER SAID
HE'D MEET US,
SO WE COULD ALL
WALK IN TOGETHER.
NOT THAT HE'S EVER ON TIME.
EASY, MOM.
(SIGHS)
IS IT OKAY
IF I GO OUT TONIGHT,
AFTER THE AWARDS?
THERE'S THIS AUTHOR READING
AT THE BOOKSHELF-
NO, NOT TONIGHT.
THAT'S GETTING PAST
YOUR CURFEW, ANYWAY.
COULD YOU CALL,
AND SEE IF HE'S CLOSE?
HE'LL SNAP AT ME IF I DO.
SO YOU TWO ARE GOING TO BE
THIS ANNOYING ALL NIGHT,
BUT YOU WON'T LET ME GO OUT?
(TAKES A DEEP BREATH)
YOUR FATHER AND I WANT
TO TALK TO YOU AFTERWARDS.
IT'S IMPORTANT.
WHY, WHAT'S HAPPENING?
NO...
NO.
(SIGHS)
(AUDIENCE CHATTERS)
DECLAN:
(SIGHS) HOLLY J AND SAV.
I STILL CAN'T WRAP
MY MIND AROUND THAT.
FIONA:
FIX YOUR TIE.
WHY'D YOU WAIT SO LONG
TO TELL ME?
FIONA:
I DIDN'T WANNA RUIN
THE HOLIDAYS!
HEY!
HOW ARE YOU?
I'M SORRY I'M LATE.
BUT I WANTED TO GIVE
YOU FLOWERS.
EXCUSE ME, LADY.
I'VE GOT A GOOD FEELING
ABOUT TONIGHT.
OH YEAH, I HOPE WE WIN TOO!
(LAUGHS)
MR. SIMPSON:
GOOD EVENING,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
I AM SO PROUD,
THAT DEGRASSI IS HOSTING...
THE GRUNDY AWARDS!
(AUDIENCE CHEERS AND APPLAUDS)
MR. SIMPSON:
WE HAVE THE YOUNGEST,
BRIGHTEST, TALENTED MINDS,
FROM HIGH SCHOOLS ALL
ACROSS THE CITY.
AND ALSO WE HAVE...
THE LEGEND HIMSELF.
PLEASE GIVE HIM
A WARM DEGRASSI WELCOME,
EAMONN GRUNDY!
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDS AND CHEERS)
THERE'S A FLOWER SHOP
ON CARLAW.
YOU COULDN'T HAVE GONE THERE?
COME ON HELEN,
I ALREADY APOLOGIZED
TO CLARE FOR BEING LATE.
CLARE:
IT'S FINE!
WE'RE ALL HERE NOW.
FOR MY AWARDS, REMEMBER?
...IS FOR OUTSTANDING USE
OF SETS AND PROPS,
MUSICAL DIVISION.
IT'S MY CATEGORY!
MR. EDWARDS:
YOU KNOW,
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE MAD,
BECAUSE I TRIED TO DO
SOMETHING NICE!
MRS. EDWARDS:
WHAT WOULD BE NICE IS FOR YOU
TO CARE ENOUGH TO BE ON TIME!
EAMONN GRUNDY:
...SPACE AWAKENING.
AND THE WINNER IS...
CLARE EDWARDS!
(GASPS)
(AUDIENCE CHEERS AND CLAPS)
GUYS! I WON!
(EXASPERATED SIGH)
CLARE:
SO, SO MANY PEOPLE TO THANK.
FIRST OF ALL, UH...
TO OUR AMAZING
PRODUCER DIRECTOR,
DECLAN COYNE,
I'M GONNA GO USE
THE FACILITIES.
AND MISS CLARE'S SPEECH?
DON'T LET IT GO TO YOUR HEAD.
SAVE MY SEAT?
DECLAN: OF COURSE.
SAV: SURE.
CLARE:
IT WAS AN EXPERIENCE
I'LL NEVER FORGET.
I'M DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH LONGER
I CAN PLAY THIS GAME.
(QUIETLY)
DON'T MAKE A SCENE!
CLARE: (WITHOUT EMOTION)
AND I'D LIKE TO THANK
MY PARENTS,
WHO INSTILLED A LOVE
FOR THEATRE IN ME
AT A VERY EARLY AGE.
THANKS.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDS)
(AUDIENCE MEMBERS CHEER)
GUY:
YEAH!
(CLAPS)
ELI:
BRAVO.
I COULDN'T HAVE
SAID IT BETTER.
MAYBE SHORTER.
AW, AT LEAST YOU LISTENED.
MY PARENTS ARE LOSING
THEIR MINDS OUT THERE.
BUT AT LEAST SOON
YOU'LL BE COMFORTED
BY THE DISTURBING PROSE
OF CHUCK PALAHNIUK.
OH, NO.
THEY SAID NO.
(SIGHS)
SO WHAT?
WHY SHOULD THEY GET
TO RUIN MY NIGHT?
COME ON.
YOU LITTLE DEVIL!
...JAMES HENDERSON!
FOR "SPACE AWAKENING",
DECLAN COYNE!
AND THE WINNER FOR
BEST DIRECTION IS...
DECLAN COYNE!
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDS LOUDLY)
(AUDIENCE MEMBERS CHEER)
MAN:
WHOO HOO HOO!
I'D LIKE TO THANK
SO MANY PEOPLE.
MY CO-PRODUCER,
JANE VAUGHN,
IS OFF TO BIGGER AND BETTER
THINGS AT STANFORD,
BUT...THERE ARE SO MANY
PEOPLE IN THIS AUDIENCE
HERE TONIGHT,
THAT WERE A PART OF THIS.
COME UP HERE, GUYS!
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDS)
BUT MOSTLY,
I'D LIKE TO DEDICATE
THIS TO ONE WOMAN
WHO INSPIRED ME
THROUGH THE LAST SEMESTER.
AS A COLLABORATOR,
MUSE,
AND DEAR FRIEND,
NOBODY COULD'VE MADE
THIS PRODUCTION,
OR MY LIFE, GREATER.
THANK YOU,
HOLLY J SINCLAIR.
(ALL APPLAUD)
CONGRATULATIONS.
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
(CAMERAS CLICK)
(AUDIENCE CHEERS AND CLAPS)
QUITE A HAUL FOR DEGRASSI.
YOU MUST BE FEELING GENEROUS.
HAVE YOU FINISHED COLLECTING
THOSE UNIFORMS YET?
HI, HOW ARE YOU?
GOOD TO SEE YOU!
CHANTAY:
(EXASPERATED SIGH)
HEY!
THE WOMAN,
THE INSPIRATION?
PLEASE TELL ME DECLAN
IS NOT TRYING
TO GET YOU BACK.
AGAIN.
HE FLIES BACK
TO NEW YORK TOMORROW!
WHY ARE YOU BEING
SO PARANOID?
I DON'T KNOW, BECAUSE YOU'RE
BEING NAIVE, THAT'S WHY!
SAV, IF IT'S GOING
TO BOTHER YOU THIS MUCH,
WE CAN END THIS,
AND THEN IT WON'T BE A PROBLEM!
NO, YOU KNOW THAT'S NOT
WHAT I WANT.
NEITHER DO I!
BUT DECLAN HASN'T DONE
ANYTHING WRONG.
AND NEITHER HAVE I!
DECLAN:
TELL ME DEGRASSI'S HOTTEST
POWER COUPLE
CAN MAKE AN APPEARANCE
AT AN IMPROMPTU SOIREE
AT THE COYNE'S?
IT'LL BE A RAGER.
(HALF LAUGHS)
YEAH, UM...
I THINK WE CAN SWING THAT,
RIGHT, HJ?
WE WOULDN'T MISS IT.
PERFECT!
♪ I like a punk rock chick ♪
♪ With hair just Rihanna ♪
♪ Like a go go girl ♪
♪ Who dance like Lady Gaga ♪
♪ They the girls
that start the party ♪
♪ So baby could it be you ♪
♪ Could it be you ♪
♪ Be you be you be you ♪
♪ I like a punk rock chick ♪
♪ With hair just like Rihanna ♪
♪ Like a go go girl ♪
BEEF SASHIMI?
UGH.
SO WHAT'S THE BIG PLAN,
ANYWAY?
YOU READY FOR THIS?
GET HOLLY J ALONE,
HAVE A QUICK CHAT,
FIX THINGS UP,
WE'RE BACK TOGETHER.
THAT EASY, HUH?
I DON'T KNOW, WHAT CAN I SAY?
I HAVE SKILLS.
ONE HITCH: SHE AND SAV
ARE TOTALLY SIAMESE TONIGHT.
FIONA, THE TRICK IS NOT
TO GET HER AWAY FROM HIM,
BUT TO GET HIM
AWAY FROM HER.
WATCH AND LEARN.
HEY YOU GUYS,
I'M GLAD BOTH OF YOU
COULD MAKE IT.
ME TOO.
I WAS HOPING YOU COULD
REGALE SAV AND I
WITH SOME OF YOUR
PRIVATE SCHOOL TALES.
ACTUALLY, I WAS HOPING
FOR SOME ALONE TIME.
WITH SAV.
THIS THING HAS AN AMESOME
DJ APP ON IT.
HUH? HUH?
YOU WANNA HOOK IT UP
TO THE SYSTEM?
YES. HELL, YES!
I WOULD LIKE TO HOOK
IT UP TO THE SYSTEM!
LATER, LADY!
I UNDERSTAND.
(LAUGHS)
GOD, I LOVE PALAHNIUK'S PROSE!
IT'S JUST SO RAW
AND FORCEFUL, AND DARK!
BUT NOT HALF AS DARK
AS HIS CHARACTERS!
JEEZ, THEY'RE SOCIOPATHIC!
BUT TO BE A TRULY GREAT WRITER,
YOU NEED SOME DAMAGE
TO DRAW ON.
GUESS YOU'RE HALF WAY
TO THE PULITZER, THEN.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
OH.
ELI:
PARENTS CALLING
TO END OUR FUN?
(SIGHS)
DOESN'T MATTER,
BECAUSE I'M NOT ANSWERING.
AN AWARD,
AN AUTHOR'S TALK,
AND YOUTHFUL REBELLION.
BIG NIGHT!
HEY,
I CAN BE REBELLIOUS!
OH, YEAH?
WHAT'S UP NEXT?
SNEAKING INTO AN R-RATED MOVIE?
MATCHING PIERCINGS?
WON'T YOUR PARENTS HATE THAT?
DEFINITELY.
WHAT?
SCARED TO KEEP UP WITH ME?
♪♪♪
(PARTYGOERS CHATTER)
DECLAN:
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
DJ SAV BHANDARI
ON THE ONES AND TWOS!
(CROWD CHEERING)
HOLLY J:
WHOOO!
♪♪♪
♪ We know ♪
♪ We know you all too well ♪
♪ Bre-bre-bre-bre-break it up ♪
♪ Sha-sha-sha-shake it up ♪
♪ We know ♪
♪ We know you all too well ♪
(LAUGHS)
WHAT, THIS DOESN'T MAKE
YOU WANNA DANCE?
I'M STILL NOT REALLY
THE START THE DANCE FLOOR TYPE.
HMM...
(HOLLY J LAUGHS)
HEY, THANK YOU.
FOR BEING SO COOL WITH HIM.
YEAH.
I'D DO LITERALLY
ANYTHING FOR YOU.
WELL.
(LAUGHS)
I MISS YOU, HOLLY J.
DECLAN. (SCOFFS)
NOT NOW!
YEAH, WHY NOT?
WE'RE PERFECT FOR EACH OTHER,
AND WE'RE WASTING TIME
BEING APART!
THESE FEELINGS JUST
DON'T GO AWAY, HOLLY J!
I MEAN,
YOU CAME HERE TONIGHT,
AFTER YOU HEARD MY SPEECH?
LOOK, I'M SORRY IF I GAVE
YOU THE WRONG IMPRESSION.
I LOVE YOU HOLLY, J!
I KNOW!
LOOK, NOTHING IS GOING
TO HAPPEN BETWEEN US TONIGHT!
♪ Sha-sha-sha-shake it up ♪
♪ We know ♪
♪ We know you... ♪
ANYA:
SORRY WE'RE LATE!
WHERE IS EVERYONE ELSE?
DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE THEY DIDN'T GET
YOUR TEXT?
SOME OF THE GIRLS
ALREADY HAD PLANS.
I THINK THEY DON'T REALLY CARE.
CHANTAY:
THEY DON'T CARE? IT'S NOT FAIR
WE LOSE OUR ENTIRE TEAM,
BECAUSE SOME PEOPLE ACTED
LIKE IDIOTS AT A DANCE!
MARISOL:
FAIR, OR NOT FAIR,
THE SCHOOL'S CRACKING DOWN,
AND I DON'T WANT
TO GET SUSPENDED.
SOMETIMES JUSTICE COMES
WITH A PRICE.
(SCOFFS)
THAT'S TOO STEEP FOR ME.
ANYWAY, I JUST CAME
TO MEET MY BF.
HOPEFULLY THEY LET
US CHEER NEXT YEAR!
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
MAYBE THERE'S ANOTHER WAY
TO GET OUR MESSAGE OUT.
RIGHT?
CLARE:
LET ME SEE IT.
ELI: NO! NO, PLEASE!
CLARE: COME ON, COME ON!
CLARE: I WANNA SEE IT!
ELI: OKAY, OKAY.
CLARE:
OH, MY GOD!
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME
THIS WOULD HURT SO MUCH?
CLARE:
REBELLION IS NOT FOR
THE FAINT OF EAR.
HERE.
HOT SAUCE WILL TAKE
YOUR MIND OFF THE PAIN.
(BOTH LAUGH)
I LOVE FIRST DATE CLARE!
DO YOU THINK SHE'LL MAKE
AN APPEARANCE ON DATE TWO?
HEY!
DATE ONE IS NOT OVER YET!
(LAUGHS)
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
(SIGHS)
I'M AN HOUR LATE, MOM!
DEAL WITH IT!
(SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
THAT'S THE TENTH TIME
THEY'VE CALLED.
WON'T THEY WORRY?
WHO CARES? LET THEM!
I GUESS... I CARE.
I REALLY LIKE YOU,
ERGO,
I WANT THEM TO LIKE ME.
WHAT'S NOT TO LIKE,
CAPTAIN CURFEW?
THEY'RE GONNA BLAME ME
FOR KEEPING YOU OUT SO LATE.
(TAKES A DEEP BREATH)
YOU KNOW HOW PUBLIC DISPLAYS
OF AFFECTION
ARE BANNED AT SCHOOL?
CAN I CONVINCE YOU TO...
STAY OUT FOR SOME
CONTRABAND KISSING?
(FIONA SIGHS)
WHY SO GLUM, CHUM?
(SIGHS)
DECLAN:
IT'S ALL OVER.
(SIGHS)
NOT NECESSARILY.
CHAMPERS?
NO.
HEY, I THOUGHT YOU WERE
GOING STRAIGHT EDGE
OVER THE HOLIDAYS.
(GULPS)
I'M JUST DRINKING
'CAUSE I'M HAPPY, DECLAN.
BESIDES,
YOU'LL THANK ME LATER.
(SAV AND HOLLY J LAUGH)
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
MMM.
WHEN DID THIS ROOM
GET SO SPINNY?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, I'M FINE.
JUST...
DO YOU HAPPEN TO HAVE
A BUCKET?
OH, OKAY.
WE...WE GOTTA GET YOU TO BED.
S-S-SHE COULD USE SOME HELP.
(SIGHS ANGRILY)
IS SHE DRINKING AGAIN?
STAY WITH ME,
AND I'LL BE OKAY.
YEAH, WE CAN UH,
HELP, I GUESS.
OH, SAV.
YOU CAN GO.
I KNOW THE DRILL.
YOU SURE YOU'LL GET HOME OKAY?
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT. CALL ME.
DUDE.
FUN PARTY.
AW, HUGGING!
ISN'T THIS NICE?
MM-HMM.
YEAH, IT'S COZY.
FIONA COME ON,
YOUR BED IS CALLING YOU.
DECLAN:
YOU DON'T NEED TO STAY,
SERIOUSLY.
NO, I'LL STAY.
YOU NEED ME.
(SIGHS HAPPILY)
(DOOR SLAMS)
I'M JUST GONNA GO AHEAD
AND ASSUME
YOU LOST YOUR PHONE!
NO.
I-I DIDN'T, IT'S RIGHT HERE.
CLARE DIANA EDWARDS!
IT'S MIDNIGHT!
OH! SO IT IS.
WELL, I AM GOING TO TUCK IN.
DON'T TELL ME YOU GOT
A PIERCING!
OKAY.
I WON'T.
YOUNG LADY,
WE HAD PLANS TONIGHT!
OH, YEAH. OKAY,
GIVE ME THE BIG SURPRISE,
IF YOU THINK I CAN HANDLE IT.
WE WILL FIND SOME TIME
TOMORROW,
WHEN YOU'RE NOT BEING
SO BELLIGERENT.
WOW, YOU'RE BOTH MAD AT ME
FOR A CHANGE,
INSTEAD OF EACH OTHER!
REFRESHING!
(SIGHS)
SHE'S WELL WATERED
AND PLANTED,
I JUST WOULDN'T PUT HER
IN DIRECT SUNLIGHT
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
THANKS FOR STAYING AFTER,
YOU KNOW...
HEY. SHE'S MY FRIEND.
DOES SHE DO THIS A LOT?
SHE'S NOT USUALLY THIS BAD.
UH, HAVE YOU CALLED ME
A TAXI YET?
NO, NOT YET.
(SIGHS) I JUST FEEL
LIKE I'VE ABANDONED HER,
I FEEL LIKE SUCH A BAD BROTHER.
DECLAN...
YOU'RE A GOOD GUY.
BUT NOT HALF AS GOOD
WITHOUT YOU.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
JUST KEEP AN EYE
ON HER TONIGHT.
NO...
ABOUT US.
(SCOFFS)
I THOUGHT WE AGREED
THIS WASN'T GONNA HAPPEN.
NO.
WE SHOULDN'T BE DOING THIS.
COME ON.
THIS IS RIGHT.
YOU KNOW IT IS.
PLEASE.
I LOVE YOU!
♪♪♪
♪ I cannot give you my love ♪
♪ No I cannot give you my love ♪
♪ When I... ♪
♪ I only got fight ♪
♪ In these roses ♪
♪ I still can't be scared... ♪