♪♪♪
Second class dreams
she's daddy's little oh-oh
Too late, too late for you
♪ To say no, no ♪
DJ BULLFROG: (ON RADIO)
CALL THE POLICE,
THE SOLID ROCK 98 TICKET
WINDOW'S BEEN SMASHED!
AND WE HAVE SAV ON THE LINE!
WASSUP BULLFROG!
DJ BULLFROG:
THESE TICKETS CAN BE YOURS
IF YOU CAN FINISH THIS LINE:
SONG:
♪ I've seen your pattern ♪
♪ And I can match it... ♪
♪ JUST TRACE THE LINES
OF YOUR PAISLEY JACKET! ♪
DJ BULLFROG:
WE HAVE A WINNER!
YOU'RE GOING TO HAMILTON!
♪♪♪
WHOOOOO!
MR. BHANDARI:
HEY, CAN YOU TURN THAT DOWN?
DAD, I JUST WON
FOUR TICKETS
TO THE DEAD HAND
REUNION SHOW!
FOUR TICKETS?
WHO ARE YOU GOING WITH?
THREE FRIENDS.
SO WHEN IS THIS CONCERT?
M-MONDAY NIGHT.
AND WHERE IS THIS CONCERT
ON A SCHOOL NIGHT?
UM, IT'S-
IT'S IN... HAMILTON.
HAMILTON?
THAT'S 50 MILES AWAY!
I DON'T THINK SO,
SAVTAJ.
BUT DAD,
I WON BACKSTAGE PASSES!
SO IT WILL COST YOU NOTHING
TO GIVE THEM AWAY
TO SOMEONE WHO DOESN'T
HAVE SCHOOL ON TUESDAY.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, whatever ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
MRS. COYNE:
YOU'RE SURE YOU'LL BE ALL,
RIGHT?
IT'S ONLY A COUPLE DAYS!
GO!
FOLLOW YOUR LUGGAGE!
I JUST WORRY ABOUT YOU
BEING HERE ALL BY YOURSELF.
FIONA:
WELL, DON'T. I'VE BEEN LOOKING
FORWARD TO SOME ALONE TIME.
I CAN DO THIS.
YOU PROMISE YOU'LL DO YOUR
SESSIONS WITH DR. SANDLER?
SHE DOESN'T
REALLY GET ME.
WELL, WHAT IF YOU HAVE
TO TALK ABOUT-
BOBBY?
I'M OVER IT.
OR AT LEAST,
I'M BORED OF IT.
YOU ARE GOING TO THERAPY.
OKAY, FINE.
I'LL TALK TO DR. SANDLER!
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE READY
FOR ME TO LEAVE?
I MEAN, MAYBE I CAN HAVE
THE NEW YORK OFFICE
SET UP A VIDEO
CONFERENCE, OR-
IF I NEED ANYTHING, I'VE GOT
HOLLY J ON SPEED DIAL.
I'LL BE FINE, MOM!
OKAY. I'LL GO.
SAV:
YEAH, YEAH. FAMILY NIGHT.
I GOT IT.
HOLLY J:
THAT'S A NICE TRUCK.
MY DAD'S NEW BABY.
HEY, DID YOU THINK OF ANY
FUND-RAISING IDEAS?
BECAUSE WE ARE SCREWED
IN THE STUDENT COUNCIL
FINANCE DEPARTMENT.
WELL...
MAYBE WE CAN SELL
THESE FOUR BACKSTAGE PASSES
TO THE DEAD HAND
REUNION SHOW.
WHY WOULD ANYONE
GET RID OF THESE?
I WON THEM, BUT MY DAD
WON'T LET ME GO,
SO IF THEY CAN
MAKE US SOME MONEY...
I'VE GOT IT!
HANDS-ON-A-HARD-BODY.
SOUNDS DIRTY.
NO, IT'S WHERE A BUNCH
OF PEOPLE
PUT THEIR HANDS ON A CAR
AND THE LAST GUY
LEFT TOUCHING IT WINS.
THE CAR?
THE TICKETS, DUMMY!
OH, YEAH.
CHARGE 10 BUCKS A HEAD,
GET LIKE, 50 PEOPLE...
THAT'S LIKE... 500 BUCKS!
YOUR DAD HAS A PRETTY
NICE NEW TRUCK.
WHOA. NO.
HE'S, HE'S A LITTLE
OVER-PROTECTIVE.
BUT...I AM THE STUDENT
COUNCIL PRESIDENT.
AND THAT AS TO COUNT
FOR SOMETHING, RIGHT?
YEAH, IT SHOULD,
SHOULDN'T IT?
GOOD, SO I'LL TELL EVERYONE
THE EVENT'S ON FOR TOMORROW.
YEAH.
YEAH, OKAY.
JENNA:
♪ I'm just a girl living
in this crazy world ♪
ANYONE COMING?
ALLI:
NO, BUT THE BELL'S GONNA RING
ANY SECOND.
DO YOU NEED TO TRY IT ON NOW?
JENNA:
WE JUST GOT NEW UNIFORMS
FOR THE POWER SQUAD
CALENDAR SHOOT NEXT WEEK!
POWER SQUAD PIN-UP
AND YOUTUBE COUNTRY SUPERSTAR!
HAVE YOU SEEN
THESE COMMENTS?
NAW, INTERNET PEOPLE
ARE WEIRDOS.
OH MY GOD.
ALLI-
IT'S STUCK!
JUST SUCK IN.
I AM SUCKING IN.
WELL, WRIGGLE AROUND A BIT.
I'M TRYING!
MAYBE IT'S SUPPOSED
TO GO HIGHER.
I GAVE MY MEASUREMENTS
IN THE SUMMER.
AM I GETTING... FAT?
(SIGHS)
YOU'RE NOT FAT.
BELIEVE ME.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
(FRUSTRATED SIGH)
HOLLY J:
WHAT DO YOU THINK TENEBRIFIC
MEANS?
FIONA:
CAN'T THIS WAIT 'TIL NEXT
WEEK?
HOLLY J:
UH, NOT IF I WANT HALF
A CHANCE OF GETTING INTO YALE.
BUT VIVALA'S SENDING
TWO MASSEURS
FOR OUR SPA DAY
TOMORROW.
SPA DAY?
AND SUNDAY, A PASTRY SAMPLING
WITH CHEF AUSTIN,
FROM THE DANISH.
BETWEEN S.A.T. PREP, CLASS,
AND THIS NEW COUNCIL EVENT,
I'M SNOWED IN.
YOU SAID YOU'D BE THERE
FOR ME, HOLLY J.
"THERE" IS MY CONDO
TOMORROW.
I CAN PENCIL YOU IN
FOR... TUESDAY.
WOULD THAT WORK?
NEVERMIND.
WOULDN'T WANNA MESS WITH
YOUR PRECIOUS SCHEDULE.
KC:
SO WHEN DO I GET TO SEE YOU IN
YOUR NEW POWER SQUAD UNIFORM?
JENNA:
OH, IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
SAME AS THE OLD ONE,
BASICALLY.
KC:
GUESS I CAN WAIT
FOR THE CALENDAR.
OH, AND I'LL NEED THREE!
ONE FOR MY LOCKER,
ONE FOR MY FOOTBALL LOCKER,
AND ONE FOR MY BEDROOM.
SWEET.
MMM.
ALSO SWEET?
THESE CHILI CHEESE FRIES.
YOU SHOULD TRY 'EM.
I LOVE THAT YOU'RE
THAT KINDA GIRL.
WHAT KIND?
THE KIND WHO
EATS JUNK FOOD.
YOU MEAN, LIKE,
A FAT GIRL.
NO, JUST-JUST NOT A SKELETOR
GIRL WHO RUNS AROUND ALL
"I'M SO FULL FROM THAT MINERAL
WATER AND BREATH MINT."
SO OPPOSITE OF SKELETOR?
AS IN FAT?
(SCOFFS)
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
YEAH,
I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
YOUR SON.
MM-HMM
CUTE, NAIVE, SMALL.
(LAUGHS)
THIS IS HOW
YOU STILL SEE HIM.
BUT THIS IS HOW I AM NOW.
I'M A YOUNG ADULT.
TALL, STRONG, SMART.
IN GERMANY, AT 16,
YOU CAN DRINK.
IN-IN NORWAY,
AT 17,
YOU CAN JOIN THE ARMY.
IN-IN THE UNITED STATES,
AT 17, YOU CAN GET
YOUR PILOT'S LICENSE.
I DON'T WANT TO DO
ANY OF THESE THINGS.
I DON'T WANNA DRINK OR FIGHT,
OR FLY PLANES,
BUT IF ENTIRE COUNTRIES CAN
SEE THAT I'M A YOUNG ADULT,
WHY CAN'T YOU?
I THINK YOU ARE
VERY MATURE.
YET I STILL HAVE TO LIVE
BY ALL THE SAME RULES I DID
I DID WHEN I WAS 12.
THIS PAST YEAR,
I WAS IN A MOVIE,
I BECAME STUDENT COUNCIL
PRESIDENT,
I KEPT AN 'A' AVERAGE.
I CAN DO GREAT THINGS.
MAYBE BE THE NEXT OBAMA.
BUT I NEED
A LITTLE MORE SUPPORT.
WHAT IS THIS ABOUT,
SAV?
I WANT TO BORROW YOUR TRUCK.
HA! I TOLD YOU, NO-
NOT FOR THE CONCERT!
FOR A STUDENT COUNCIL
FUND-RAISER.
IT JUST HAS TO SIT
IN THE PARKING LOT.
LAST PERSON WITH THEIR HAND
ON IT WINS THE TICKETS-
THAT I'M GIVING AWAY.
YOU'LL WASH IT
AFTERWARDS?
REALLY?!
IF IT COMES BACK WITH
SO MUCH AS A SCRATCH-
I WILL NOT LET YOU DOWN.
♪♪♪
♪ If you've got a house
on cherry tree street ♪
♪ Three car garage
full of SUVs ♪
♪ Nanny's in the kitchen
cooking up a feast ♪
♪ Kids under weather
watching wreck TV ♪
♪ If I never knew
this life existed ♪
GUY:
YO BUD, HIGH FIVE.
OH, HEY!
SAV:
OH! AND THEN THERE WERE 19.
WHO WILL BE TODAY'S
LUCKY WINNER?!
I'M PRETTY SURE IT'S US,
'CAUSE THIS IS HILARIOUS!
HOW LONG DO YOU THINK THESE
SUCKERS WILL LAST?
IT'S ALREADY BEEN TWO HOURS.
MAYBE A COUPLE MORE?
WHAT DO I CARE?
THEY'VE ALREADY GIVEN
US THEIR MONEY, RIGHT?
600 BUCKS
FOR STUDENT COUNCIL!
YEAH, TOTALLY WORTH
GIVING UP THE TICKETS.
YOU GAVE UP BACKSTAGE PASSES
TO THE DEAD HAND?
ALL FOR A GOOD CAUSE.
BECAUSE YOU'RE CRAZY?
UGH, WHAT REEKS?
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD
OF DEODORANT, DR. DOOM?
YEAH, BUT TODAY,
INSTEAD OF "OCEAN SURF,"
I USED "DAY-OLD TROUT."
(FRUSTRATED GROAN)
I NEEDED THOSE PASSES.
NOW RON-RON'S
GONNA GO WITHOUT ME!
I'D LITERALLY DO ANYTHING
TO SEE THIS CONCERT.
SAV:
IS IT TOO LATE TO ENTER
THE CONTEST?
I'M SORRY, MR. PRESIDENT.
THAT'S A CONFLICT
OF INTEREST.
CHANTAY:
GREAT JOB GIRLS!
LAST HARD PRACTICE 'TIL NEXT
WEEK.
NOW? WE JUST FOCUS ON LOOKING
GOOD FOR THE CALENDAR!
JENNA:
7 DAYS TO LOSE 10 POUNDS.
ANYA:
NOTHING A WEEK OF SPINACH
AND EGG WHITES CAN'T FIX!
(LAUGHING) OH...
YOU'RE SERIOUS?
SO ARE YOU ON A DIET, TOO?
OH GOD, NO!
I EAT WHATEVER I WANT.
CHANTAY:
YEAH, BUT WE CAN'T ALL HAVE
THE GENETICS
OF STRING BEAN MACPHERSON.
SO YOU TOO, THEN?
I WATCH MY CALORIES,
BUT I DON'T OBSESS ABOUT IT.
YOU COWS REALLY
WANNA LOSE SOME WEIGHT?
I GOT PILLS
THAT'LL MELT IT OFF.
FAT INHIBITORS.
MY AUNTIE LOST
A HUNDRED POUNDS.
LIKE A WHOLE YOU.
OR AT LEAST HALF
OF YOU.
IF YOU DON'T GET LOST,
BIANCA,
ALL OF ME IS GOING TO
MAKE YOU WISH YOU DID.
ANYWAY, IT'S SIMPLE.
I JUST FOCUS ON BURNING MORE
CALORIES THAN I EAT.
AND I CERTAINLY EAT MORE THAN
SPINACH AND EGG WHITES.
SAV:
♪ And what makes me most sad ♪
♪ Is I had to give up
my Dead Hand tickets... ♪
WESLEY:
DO YOU GUYS MAYBE WANNA JUST-
WANNA SPLIT THE TICKETS?
HOW EXACTLY
DO YOU PROPOSE
WE SPLIT FOUR PASSES,
THREE WAYS?
I DON'T KNOW. I JUST-
OH! I REALLY GOTTA GO.
(STUDENTS LAUGHING)
JUST YOU AND ME
FISH-PITS.
I'VE GOT THE BLADDER
OF A CAMEL.
SAV:
GUYS? UH, I'M NO MATHLETE,
BUT I THINK YOU CAN SPLIT
FOUR TICKETS TWO WAYS.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
I'VE GOT PLACES
TO BE ANYWAY.
SAV:
WELL, SWEET! HERE YOU GO.
CAN YOU GUYS HELP ME UNLOAD
THE TRUCK, TOO?
I'VE GOTTA GET IT HOME BEFORE
MY DAD STARTS FREAKING.
ADAM:
YEAH, IT'S THE LEAST
WE COULD DO.
(GRUNTS WITH EFFORT)
CAREFUL, IT'S HEAVY.
ELI:
PASS ME THE GUITAR.
GUYS? LITTLE HELP HERE?
(LOUD SMASH, ALARM SOUNDS)
ELI:
CHILL. JUST-
JUST-JUST DON'T,
DON'T FREAK OUT.
DON'T FREAK OUT?
MY DAD'S GONNA-!
(FRUSTRATED YELL)
200 BUCKS PLUS LABOUR
FOR A TAIL LIGHT!?
MY DAD'S NEVER GONNA LET ME
OUT OF THE HOUSE AGAIN!
PETER:
MEH. EVER SINCE THE STUDZ
SPLIT UP,
YOU BEEN SPENDING MOST
OF YOUR TIME
MOPING AROUND HERE ANYWAY.
WHAT'S THE DIFF?
HEY, MAN.
SORRY ABOUT THE TAIL LIGHT. I-
I'M PRETTY DECENT
WITH CARS.
MAYBE I CAN HELP YOU
REPLACE IT?
YEAH? WITH WHAT?
YOU KNOW, A GENEROUS DONATION
FROM THE TAIL-LIGHTS-FOR-TOTS
CHARITY DRIVE?
THEY'RE EXPENSIVE!
HERE, ADAM AND I WANT YOU
TO HAVE THE EXTRA PASSES.
MAYBE YOU CAN SELL 'EM.
THANKS.
PETER:
NEW FRIEND?
AH NO, HE'S JUST ONE OF
THE GUYS WHO WON THE CONTEST.
NO, BUT LIKE,
HE'S INTO DEAD HAND
SO MAYBE HE COULD BE
YOUR NEW FRIEND.
NO.
HE'S IN GRADE 11.
DUDE, YOU WERE IN GRADE 10
WHEN WE FORMED STUDZ.
THE YOUNGER GUYS
ARE JUST LOST.
THEY'RE LOOKING
FOR A HERO.
YEAH, I COULD BE HIS
OBI-WAN...
MAN, I'D BE GOING
TO THIS CONCERT
IF I DIDN'T HAVE MY FIRST
UNIVERSITY MIDTERM.
WHAT'S YOUR EXCUSE?
OH, HEY! UM...
DO YOU STILL NEED A PASS
TO THE DEAD HAND REUNION SHOW?
A BACKSTAGE PASS?
DON'T BE JERKING ME
AROUND HERE.
NO, SERIOUSLY!
I GOT ONE MORE.
YOU'RE A LIFESAVER!
NAME YOUR PRICE.
UM, SAY... 200 BUCKS.
I PLANNED THIS
FABULOUS WEEKEND.
MASSAGES,
DESSERT TASTINGS.
AND SHE JUST SAID NO!
LET ME ASK YOU THIS:
WHY DID YOU ARRANGE
TO HAVE THE MASSAGES
HERE AT YOUR CONDO?
WELL, BECAUSE I WANTED
HER TO COME OVER.
YOU SPENT ALL THAT MONEY
TO AVOID BEING ALONE?
DOESN'T THAT SOUND LIKE TRYING
TO BUY COMPANIONSHIP?
I DON'T NEED TO BUY HOLLY J.
SHE ALREADY OWES ME.
AND WHY DO YOU FEEL
SHE OWES YOU?
IT'S A LONG STORY.
SHARPEN YOUR PENCIL.
SO IT ALL STARTED WHEN HOLLY J
CAME BACK FROM NEW YORK-
(TIMER BEEPS)
OH, FIONA,
UNFORTUNATELY,
I'M OUT OF TIME.
WE'LL CONTINUE THIS
NEXT WEEK.
CAN'T YOU JUST STAY
FOR LIKE, ONE MORE HOUR?
I REALLY HAVE TO GO.
I'LL PAY FOR
A SECOND SESSION?
HAVE YOU THOUGHT
ABOUT CALLING YOUR MOM?
MAYBE SHE CAN
COME HOME EARLY.
GOODBYE, FIONA.
ORANGE IS...
CAULIFLOWER.
ONLY 34. HMM. NOT BAD.
KC:
HEY.
OH, HEY. WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
COACH HAS US WORKING
OUT SIX DAYS A WEEK.
I'VE NEVER SEEN YOU
HERE BEFORE.
OH, JUST TRYING TO LOOK
MY BEST FOR THE CALENDAR.
COOL.
WANNA SPOT ME?
WAIT- 120 CALORIES!
IS THIS THING BROKEN?
HOW LONG WERE YOU ON?
LIKE 15 MINUTES!
SOUNDS ABOUT RIGHT.
BUT A BANANA'S
120 CALORIES!
YEAH. BURNING
CALORIES IS HARD.
ALL RIGHT.
HEY, UM,
ABOUT THE CALENDAR,
YOU THINK YOU MIGHT BE
MISS DECEMBER?
WHY? BECAUSE I'D MAKE
A GOOD SANTA?!
WHOA! WHAT?
NO, I WAS THINKING MORE
LIKE SEXY ELF!
DON'T LEAVE.
I WAS DONE FOR THE DAY,
ANYWAY.
I JUST REALLY LIKE CHRISTMAS!
SAV:
IT LOOKS LIKE NEW. AMAZING!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU GOT IT IN THERE!
HA, THAT'S WHAT
MY EX-GIRLFRIEND SAID!
WHAT?
GROSS.
SAV:
ANYWAYS, WE'RE NOT OUTTA
THE WOODS, YET.
TEST RUN!
BOO-YAH!
DUDE. 'BOO-YAH'?
WHO ARE YOU?
SORRY.
OKAY, WELL WE'RE GOOD TO GO!
DUDE, ELI, WHERE'D YOU LEARN
THESE MAD MECHANIC'S SKILLS?
MORTY BREAKS DOWN
ONCE A WEEK.
LIKE RIGHT NOW.
I'VE HAD TO LEARN
A LOT ABOUT CARS.
WELL, YOU SAVED
MY LIFE OUT HERE.
WE SHOULD HANG OUT
SOME TIME.
YEAH, UH-
HOW'RE YOU GETTING
TO THE CONCERT?
I STILL GOT TO FIGURE OUT HOW
TO TELL MY DAD I'M GOING.
AND AFTER HE FINDS OUT
I BUSTED A TAIL LIGHT-
JUST KEEP YOUR MOUTH SHUT,
HE'LL NEVER KNOW
THE DIFFERENCE.
YEAH, AND THEN YOU CAN DRIVE
THIS BAD BOY TO HAMILTON.
NO WAY.
HOW ELSE WE ALL
GONNA GET THERE?
WE KINDA NEED YOU,
MAN.
YOU'RE SCREWED WITHOUT ME,
RIGHT?
ALL RIGHT, WELL THEN,
LET'S DO THIS.
♪♪♪
JENNA: (ON VIDEO)
♪ Light shinning out
you saved the day ♪
♪ It was not big deal
but I changed my way ♪
MS. OH:
♪ I'm just a girl ♪
♪ And I started to blush when
you swept me away... ♪
I LOVE YOUR SONG!
THANKS.
WELL, I'M GONNA GO TRY
AND HAVE A WEEKEND.
SIMPSON IS STILL
IN HIS OFFICE.
LET HIM KNOW TO LOCK UP
WHEN YOU LEAVE.
HEY, I HEARD ABOUT
THE POWER SQUAD CALENDAR.
GREAT IDEA.
YOU KNOW, I USED TO BE
A CHEERLEADER.
SEE YOU MONDAY.
JENNA: (ON VIDEO)
♪ Living in this crazy world ♪
♪ Trying to find a way ♪
♪ I'm a fat girl ♪
♪ Just a chunky girl ♪
♪ Getting fatter every day ♪
♪♪♪
BUSINESSMAN:
THEY LOOK REALLY GOOD!
FIONA:
OH, YOU THINK? I WASN'T SURE.
BUSINESSMAN:
WHAT? OH-
UH, NEVERMIND.
BUSINESSMAN:
NO, IT'S NOBODY.
ANYWAY, THE RATES THROUGH
2011? SUPERB.
♪♪♪
♪ And I wish
And I wish ♪
♪ That you were by my side ♪
♪ And I wish
And I wish ♪
♪ That you were in my car
tonight ♪
(PIG SNORTS)
HEY.
BARGAIN BIN
AT THE MEN'S WEARHOUSE.
ALL THIS?
FOR 90 DOLLARS.
I HOPE YOUR DAY
WAS AS FRUITFUL.
YEAH, WE RAISED 600 BUCKS!
THANKS FOR GIVING ME
THE TRUCK.
NO, YOU WERE RIGHT, SAVTAJ.
YOU'RE A GOOD KID.
AND TRUCK PRIVILEGES
ARE MORE THAN REASONABLE.
WELL, CAN WE TALK ABOUT
EXTENDING THOSE.
TO INCLUDE WHAT?
I STILL HAVE A TICKET
TO THE CONCERT ON MONDAY
AND I REALLY WANNA GO.
SAV-
DAD, I WORK SO HARD,
AT SCHOOL AND COUNCIL.
I THINK I'VE EARNED
SOME FUN.
YOU ARE RIGHT.
I AM?
I MEAN, I HAVEN'T DONE
MY TRUCK INSPECTION YET,
BUT I ASSUME THERE WEREN'T
ANY PROBLEMS, SO WHY NOT?
DAD!
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
THERE WEREN'T
ANY PROBLEMS, RIGHT?
UM...
WELL, THERE WAS ONE.
UM, THE REAR TAIL LIGHT
KINDA...
SORTA, GOT LIKE A...
A LITTLE... SMASHED.
SMASHED?!
YEAH, YEAH, NO.
(STAMMERS)
BUT I FIXED IT THOUGH!
I THINK CONCERT'S
OUT OF THE QUESTION, THEN.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
THAT'S NOT FAIR!
IT'S EXACTLY THE SAME WAY
IT WAS WHEN I TOOK IT.
YOU WEREN'T EVEN DRIVING IT
AND YOU SMASHED A TAIL LIGHT.
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN
YOU'RE FACED WITH TRAFFIC.
AND NIGHT DRIVING.
OH NO. NO.
DAD, I'M 17!
YOU'RE BEING SO UNFAIR!
DO YOU WANT TO BE
GROUNDED, TOO?
(SIGHS)
♪♪♪
BIANCA:
YOU THINK I DON'T KNOW WHAT
OREGANO SMELLS LIKE?
YOU SEVERELY UNDERESTIMATE
MY LOVE OF THE FOOD NETWORK.
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT,
PROM QUEEN?
UH, NOTHING.
NEVERMIND.
(SIGHS)
SORRY. LONG DAY.
YEAH. UM, I NEED
TO KNOW WHERE TO GET
THOSE FAT INHIBITING
PILLS... FOR A FRIEND.
ONLINE. BUT MY AUNTIE'S
STILL ON 'EM.
I CAN SWIPE YOU SOME.
OH YEAH?
THAT'D BE GREAT.
WE CAN DISCUSS PAYMENT
ON DELIVERY.
WILL IT BE A LOT?
DEPENDS. DOES YOUR FRIEND
HAVE A BIG PROBLEM?
I GUESS.
YOU GUESS?
YOUR FRIEND KNOWS THESE PILLS
ARE ONLY FOR OBESE PEOPLE,
RIGHT?
YEAH,
SHE'S KINDA DESPERATE.
♪ The whole world's watching ♪
♪ The whole world wants
so much more ♪
♪ All you hold so dear ♪
♪ You better learn
to hold it near ♪
ADAM:
SO, WHAT'S THE WORD?
DAD SAID TRUCK'S A NO-GO.
OH, NO. YOU TOLD HIM
THE TRUTH, DIDN'T YOU?
OKAY. UM, HOW WAS I
SUPPOSED TO KNOW
THAT HONESTY SUDDENLY STOPPED
BEING THE BEST POLICY?
SO,
WHAT'RE WE GONNA DO?
THE STARTER FOR THE HEARSE'LL
TAKE AT LEAST A WEEK.
BACKSTAGE PASSES TO
THE CONCERT OF THE CENTURY
AND WE'RE GONNA MISS IT.
NO, NO, NO.
WE'RE NOT GONNA MISS IT.
I DON'T FOLLOW.
WELL, IF MY DAD WON'T GIVE ME
THE TRUCK,
I'LL JUST HAVE TO TAKE IT!
♪ The whole world's watching ♪