♪♪♪
♪ Don't look down ♪
(CORK POPS)
♪ Don't slow down ♪
♪ Fire escape's sunny ♪
MRS. COYNE:
YOU SEEM CHEERY FOR SOMEONE
FACING A LEGAL DEPOSITION.
I AM CHEERY.
THE SCHOOL APPROVED MY PITCH
FOR VEGAS NIGHT.
GOOD FOR YOU!
HOW WERE THE NERVES?
I THINK I'M FINALLY READY
TO STICK IT
TO MY ABUSIVE EX-BOYFRIEND.
WELL, THAT'S GOOD.
'CAUSE SHERMAN WARNED ME
ABOUT BOBBY'S LAWYER.
(KETTLE WHISTLES)
THEY CALL HER GREAT WHITE.
ONCE SHE SMELLS BLOOD
IN THE WATER,
IT'S OVER.
I CAN HANDLE IT.
YOU'RE SURE YOU WOULDN'T
RATHER I POSTPONE
UNTIL AFTER I CAN GET YOU IN
TO SEE DR. SANDLER?
MOM, I DON'T NEED MY MOOD
ALTERED WITH MEDS.
TODAY, I AM A NEW FIONA.
TODAY, I AM KEVLAR!
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever, Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
REMEMBER THE WHOLE
RILEY'S-COMING-OUT-
OF-THE-CLOSET THING?
HOW CAN I FORGET?
TRY. REALLY HARD.
IN FACT, DON'T TRY,
ONLY DO.
BUT YOU SAID YOU WERE
ALL FIRED UP
FOR BEING OUT AND PROUD.
UNTIL I MET MATT BARNES,
A SCOUT FROM EASTERN.
FOR REAL?
THIS IS LIKE
A DREAM COME TRUE!
BUT IF EASTERN FINDS OUT
WHICH TEAM I PLAY FOR,
IT BECOMES A NIGHTMARE.
OKAY.
ARE YOU SURE EASTERN'S
GONNA EVEN HAVE A PROBLEM?
I'M NOT ABOUT TO FIND OUT.
IT'S BACK IN THE CLOSET
FOR ME.
RILEY,
JUST WANTED TO SAY
THAT I'M PROUD
OF WHAT YOU DID YESTERDAY.
REALLY?
WHAT DID I DO?
YOU'RE BEING FUNNY.
THERE'S A CAMPAIGN
TO GET YOU AND ZANE
ELECTED KINGS OF THE DANCE!
IT'D BE A DEGRASSI FIRST!
LOOKS LIKE THE CLOSET DOOR
IS BOLTED ON THE INSIDE.
WOW.
I'M ACTUALLY...OUT.
BUT I HAVE MY INTERVIEW
AT LUNCH HOUR.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
WELL, YOU COULD TELL
MR. HOTSHOT SCOUT THE TRUTH.
(SIGHS)
SHERMAN:
AH, FIONA,
THIS IS, UH, BOBBY'S LAWYER,
TONI STARK.
FIONA:
(GIGGLES)
TONI STARK?
TONI WITH AN "I."
AH, MAY WE BEGIN?
YEAH, I'M JUST IMPRESSED
THAT BOBBY'S LAWYER
IS IRON LADY.
(LAUGHS HUMOURLESSLY)
GO AHEAD, MS. STARK.
IN YOUR OWN WORDS,
WHAT HAPPENED THE NIGHT
OF THE FIRST ALTERCATION?
FIONA:
I WAS GETTING READY TO GO OUT
WHEN I GOT INTO AN ARGUMENT
WITH BOBBY.
SO YOU STARTED IT?
BOBBY GAVE ME A BLACK EYE,
DON'T YOU FACT-CHECK?
WE HAVE THIS...PHOTO.
THERE'S YOUR PROOF.
BRUISING IS EASY TO FAKE.
FIONA:
WHATEVER.
I ENHANCED IT TO MAKE A POINT.
SO, YOU'RE LYING.
I'M NOT LYING!
TAKE A BREATH, FIONA.
SHERMAN:
UH, DO YOU NEED A MINUTE?
YEAH, I'M JUST
A LITTLE PARCHED.
WE'LL WAIT.
(SIGHS)
ADAM:
UNH! (GROANS)
AH!
(FRUSTRATED SIGH)
NEXT TIME, USE THESE.
THANKS.
NO BIG DEAL.
BUT LISTEN,
YOU GOTTA GET OUTTA HERE.
ME AND THE BOYS,
WE GOT SOME PRIVATE BUSINESS.
GO AHEAD, DO WHATEVER.
I'M NOT GONNA DROP A DIME.
FITZ:
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT IS THIS?
NOTHIN'.
FIRST RULE
OF FIGHT CLUB?
THERE IS NO FIGHT CLUB.
CHECK.
ANYWAY,
CAN I GET IN ON THIS?
REALLY?
YOU WANNA FIGHT?
YEAH, I WANNA FIGHT.
(GUYS LAUGH)
COOL.
I'LL FIND YOU
A SPARRING PARTNER.
JUST DON'T TELL ANYONE.
SECOND RULE OF FIGHT CLUB,
RIGHT?
SHERMAN:
OKAY, CAN WE CONTINUE NOW?
FIONA:
YEAH, I'M ON IT.
SO TO ANSWER YOUR QUESTION,
BOBBY HIT ME, IRON-LADY.
TONI STARK:
MY CLIENT HAS SAID YOU SUFFER
FROM A MOOD DISORDER.
FIONA:
WELL, I WOULDN'T LISTEN
TO A THING YOUR CLIENT SAYS.
HE'S A LIAR
WITH A VIOLENT STREAK.
TONI STARK:
YOUR STATEMENTS ABOUT MY CLIENT
ARE ALREADY ON RECORD.
IT IS TRUE YOU SUFFER
FROM A MOOD DISORDER?
I DON'T KNOW,
YOU'D HAVE TO ASK MY THERAPIST.
THEN YOU HAVE BEEN
SEEING A THERAPIST?
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO SAY?
THAT I'M CRAZY?
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE CRAZY?
NO, BUT I THINK YOU'RE A BITCH!
MRS. COYNE:
FIONA!
HOW COULD...
(BREATHING HARD)
WHAT IS IN HERE?
THIS IS HOW
YOU'RE HANDLING THINGS?
BY PUTTING CHAMPAGNE
IN A WATER BOTTLE?
WOULD YOU PREFER
I USE A GLASS?
YOU ARE IN SO MUCH TROUBLE,
YOUNG LADY!
(DOOR SLAMS)
I THINK WE'RE DONE.
RILEY, DO YOU KNOW WHAT
THE WORD PERSPICACITY MEANS?
UH, NOT REALLY.
IS IT BAD?
(LAUGHS)
IT'S A WORD
OUR COACH NEWMAN USES.
IT MEANS YOU SEE
THE WHOLE FIELD IN ONE GLANCE,
AND YOU SHOWED THAT YESTERDAY.
THANKS.
AND THAT'S JUST WHAT
EASTERN'S LOOKING FOR
IN A QUARTERBACK.
I'D LIKE YOU TO LOOK
AT OUR CAMPUS.
(SIGHS)
YOU SEEM HESITANT.
AM I MISSING SOMETHING?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
LOOK, SOME THINGS
JUST DON'T GO TOGETHER:
OIL AND WATER,
CATS AND DOGS,
FOOTBALL AND...GAYNESS.
ARE YOU FOLLOWING ME NOW?
WELL, EASTERN'S
A PROGRESSIVE SCHOOL...
AND RECRUITING
AN OPENLY GAY PLAYER
MIGHT EVEN BOOST OUR PROFILE.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
MATT BARNES:
RILEY?
(SURPRISED LAUGH)
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY!
(GRUNTS WITH EFFORT)
FITZ:
I GOTTA ADMIT,
YOU SURPRISE ME.
YOU REALLY GOT
THE KILLER INSTINCT.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT,
JUST THOUGHT SPARRING
MIGHT BE FUN.
BUT YOU WANT TO WIN.
I CAN TELL.
MAYBE ON THE OUTSIDE
I DON'T LOOK LIKE
YOUR TYPICAL GUY,
BUT UP HERE I AM.
WELL, THAT'S GOOD,
MY MAN.
'CAUSE WE JUST GOT
THE RIGHT PERSON FOR YOU
TO PROVE YOUR MANLINESS!
SO, WHO'S THE CHICK
THAT'S LOOKING FOR A SMACKDOWN?
UGH! NO WAY.
WHAT'S BIANCA DOING HERE?
YOU SAID YOU WANTED
A SPARRING PARTNER.
NOT WITH A GIRL!
AND I'M PROUD OF IT,
FREAK!
WHAT DID YOU EXPECT?
THERE'S A CODE.
NO GUY'S GONNA HIT
A GIRL.
I'M NOT A GIRL!
FITZ:
YEAH, YEAH,
NOT BETWEEN THE EARS.
PROBLEM IS,
WE FIGHT WITH OUR FISTS,
NOT OUR BRAINS.
SO, WE GONNA DO THIS?
CATFIGHT!
(SNAPS A PHOTO)
YOU GUYS ARE LOSERS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE EASTERN
IS COOL
WITH YOU BEING OUT
OF THE CLOSET.
BARNES SAID THEY HAVE
A REPUTATION
FOR BEING OPEN-MINDED
OR WHATEVER.
EASTERN ALSO HAS
A REPUTATION
FOR ITS AWESOME
ENGINEERING PROGRAM.
MAYBE YOU'LL HAVE
A FRIEND THERE.
AW, REALLY?
SWEET!
YEAH.
YOU'LL BE A TRAILBLAZER,
A HERO!
LIKE HARVEY MILK.
WHO'D HE PLAY FOR?
REALLY?
HARVEY MILK WAS THE FIRST
OPENLY GAY POLITICIAN,
BACK IN THE '70S.
OH, COOL.
WHAT'S HE DOING NOW?
HE WAS ASSASSINATED
IN '78.
THEY KILLED HIM
BECAUSE HE WAS GAY?
NO, HE WAS A HERO
TO MILLIONS!
WHAT GOOD IS THAT
WHEN YOU'RE DEAD?
(SIGHS)
HOLLY J:
HEY! HOW'D THE DEPOSITION GO?
(SIGHS)
IT WENT.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
IT MEANS WE SHOULD STUDY
FOR PERINO'S EXAM.
CHAMPAGNE EYES.
YOU WERE DRUNK
AT YOUR DEPOSITION?
SO I SELF-MEDICATED.
WHAT DIFFERENCE DOES IT MAKE
WHAT I USE?
HOLLY J:
(SCOFFS) IT MAKES A DIFFERENCE.
MOOT! I JUST NEED TO FOCUS
ON THE EXAM
AND THEN THE DANCE.
THERE'S STILL THE TRIAL
TO FOCUS ON.
NOPE, 'CAUSE I'M DROPPING
THE CHARGES.
OOPS. BOBBY WINS.
WHOA, YOU'RE JUST GONNA
GIVE UP?
CONCEDING DEFEAT.
IT'S THE ONLY SMART MOVE.
HOLLY J:
WHAT ABOUT OTHER GIRLS?
WHAT IF BOBBY HITS
SOMEBODY ELSE?
MY THERAPIST SAYS
I CAN ONLY CONTROL
MY OWN EMOTIONS,
AND I CHOOSE TO BE HAPPY.
IF YOU'RE SO HAPPY,
WHY ARE YOU DRUNK
DURING AFTERNOON
STUDY PERIOD?
FIONA, WE HAVE TO HAVE
A LITTLE TALK.
(SIGHS IRRITABLY)
MOM, I'M STUDYING-
MRS. COYNE:
NOW!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
STUDENT: (OVER PA)
VOTE FOR DANCE KING AND QUEEN
AT DEGRASSI'S HOME PAGE.
HOLD THE PHONE,
THE BIG DAY IS FRIDAY.
HOW'D YOU DO ON YOUR EXAM?
(SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
WAITING FOR SOMEONE?
YEAH.
FITZ.
AW, AND HOW IS FITZY BOY?
HE STILL YOUR SUPER AWESOME
BFF?
(ADAM EXHALES NERVOUSLY)
ADAM,
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
YOU WERE RIGHT,
ELI.
FITZ:
OH!
STUDENTS:
(STUNNED LAUGHTER)
ELI:
LET'S GO, ROCKY,
BEFORE A TEACHER COMES.
FITZ:
SAY YOUR PRAYERS, FREAK.
I'M FINDING YOUR ASS
AFTER SCHOOL!
ADAM: YEAH, DO IT!
ELI: ADAM, LET'S GO!
I CAN FIGHT MY OWN BATTLES.
(STUDENTS WHISPER AND LAUGH)
FIONA:
MOM, I CAN'T HAVE
A BIG SCENE RIGHT NOW,
I HAVE AN EXAM!
WE NEED TO TALK ABOUT
YOU BEING DRUNK
AT YOUR DEPOSITION!
THERE'S NOTHING
TO TALK ABOUT
BECAUSE I'M DROPPING
THE CHARGES.
YOU'RE DOING NOTHING
OF THE SORT!
GOD! WHY WON'T YOU
JUST LET THIS GO?
BECAUSE...
IT'S PARTIALLY MY FAULT.
MOM, THAT'S INSANE.
THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH YOU.
I PUSHED YOU ON BOBBY,
I PUT YOU IN
THAT TERRIBLE SITUATION.
I NEED TO MAKE
THIS RIGHT, FIONA.
AND WHAT IF HE DIDN'T
DO ANYTHING?
PLEASE DON'T PLAY GAMES
RIGHT NOW.
I'M NOT!
WHAT IF HE NEVER HIT ME?
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS,
FIONA!
YOU'RE NOT HEARING ME!
HE NEVER HIT ME!
HE NEVER PULLED ME
DOWN THE STAIRS.
I MADE IT ALL UP.
WHY ON EARTH
WOULD YOU DO THAT?
HAVEN'T YOU HEARD?
I'M CRAZY!
FIONA...
MOM, IT'S OVER!
PLEASE, JUST LET ME STUDY.
LET ME DO MY EXAM.
LET ME BE NORMAL, PLEASE!
(RAPID SUCCESSION OF PUNCHES)
ELI:
THERE YOU ARE.
BROUGHT REINFORCEMENTS,
HUH?
ELI:
I THOUGHT I MIGHT NEED
SOME HELP
TALKING YOU OUTTA
CERTAIN DOOM.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO,
ELI?
I HATE FITZ.
I WANT TO MAKE HIM HURT.
CLARE:
GHANDI SAID,
"AN EYE FOR AN EYE
MAKES THE WHOLE WORLD BLIND."
YEAH, WELL,
GANDHI NEVER MET FITZ.
I THINK YOU'RE MISSING
THE POINT, ROCKY.
THE POINT IS,
WHEN SOMEONE DISSES ME,
I FIGHT BACK.
EVEN IF IT MEANS YOU GET HURT?
(BELL RINGS)
WE HAVE TO STOP HIM.
YEAH. HOW?
WHAT?
FOR ONCE,
YOU HAVE NO SNEAKY PLAN
UP YOUR SLEEVE?
(SIGHS)
♪ We're undercover,
over it ♪
♪ So get down low
and savour it ♪
♪ This will be the last spree ♪
♪ Or the crime ♪
♪ So take your time ♪
♪ Turn your mind ♪
♪ And you could be
my Seth Cohen ♪
♪ I could be your Loralei ♪
♪ And we'd live under the sun ♪
♪ Talk so fast ♪
♪ And how we'd laugh ♪
♪ We wouldn't last ♪
♪ But I can't fight back ♪
♪ even in my dreams ♪
♪ My fortitude is nothing
like it seems ♪
♪ At night they come ♪
♪ And I just let them in ♪
♪ I never win ♪
♪ As it stands
you took your half ♪
♪ And I walked past ♪
♪ And curtseyed back ♪
♪ No one who knows us both ♪
♪ Would ever guess ♪
♪ What could be next ♪
♪ We are relentless ♪
♪ And you could be
my Seth Cohen ♪
♪ I could be your Loralei ♪
♪ And someday soon
these two fantasies ♪
♪ Could meet ♪
♪ The rest of conceit ♪
ALL DONE, MR. P.
THERE'S STILL 30 MINUTES
ON THE CLOCK.
IT'S OKAY,
I'M TIRED.
(STUDENTS MURMUR)
MR. PERINO:
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
SIR, CAN I GO CHECK ON HER?
MR. PERINO:
YES.
FIONA.
FIONA!
I THINK SHE'S SLEEPING.
OH.
NOW I HAVE SEEN IT ALL.
(STUDENTS GASP)
MR. PERINO:
BACK TO WORK.
FIONA.
FIONA?
(GASPS)
(SIGHS)
HOW LONG WAS I ASLEEP?
A HALF HOUR AT THE EXAM,
ANOTHER HOUR,
AFTER I DRAGGED YOU HOME.
YOU'RE WATCHING
BOBBY'S VIDEO?
THAT'S CREEPY.
HOLLY J:
NO, YOU'RE GONNA WATCH IT.
I'VE SEEN IT ALREADY.
HOLLY J:
WELL, YOU'RE GONNA
WATCH IT AGAIN,
AND AGAIN,
UNTIL YOU GET IT.
BOBBY:
THE TRUTH IS,
I FELT SORRY FOR FIONA.
SHERMAN:
SORRY? WHY?
BECAUSE SHE'S SO MESSED UP.
I MEAN, I NEVER HIT HER.
NOT ONCE.
SHERMAN:
AND WHY WOULD SHE LIE, BOBBY?
BOBBY:
TO PUNISH ME...
FOR DUMPING HER.
I MEAN, I AM THE VICTIM
IN ALL OF THIS!
I JUST HOPE SHE DOESN'T DO
TO OTHER GUYS
WHAT SHE'S TRYING TO DO TO ME.
WHY ARE YOU MAKING ME
WATCH THIS?!
HOW CAN YOU LOOK
AT THAT SMUG FACE
AND NOT WANNA FIGHT BACK?
(SIGHS,
ON THE VERGE OF TEARS)
MAYBE I DESERVED IT.
NOBODY DESERVES
TO GET HIT.
DO YOU,
DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
NOBODY!
I HAVE SOMETHING
OF YOURS.
(PILLS RATTLE)
WHERE'D YOU GET THOSE?
I FISHED THE PRESCRIPTION
OUT OF THE TRASH.
GOT YOUR MOM TO FILL IT.
THAT'S PRETTY SNEAKY.
WELL, I HAVE MY MOMENTS.
NO MORE DRINKING?
(SIGHS)
THANKS, HOLLY J.
NOT SO FAST.
I HAVEN'T TOLD YOU
ABOUT THE LONG TALK
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
WITH YOUR MOM
AND YOUR THERAPIST
TOMORROW MORNING.
(SIGHS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
RILEY:
COACH?
CAN YOU GIVE A MESSAGE
TO MR. BARNES?
WELL, I CAN GIVE YOU HIS NUMBER,
YOU CAN TELL HIM YOURSELF.
IT'S NOT GOOD NEWS.
YOU'RE FEELING PRESSURE
TO BE THE FIRST OPENLY GAY
FOOTBALL PLAYER.
TONS OF IT, COACH.
COACH ARMSTRONG:
LISTEN.
I'VE SEEN YOU HANDLE
THE PRESSURE OF LEADING A TEAM;
YOU CAN HANDLE THIS.
RILEY:
I DON'T WANT TO!
I DON'T WANNA BE A HERO;
I JUST WANNA PLAY BALL.
COACH ARMSTRONG:
SON, YOU'VE GOT A GIFT.
BUT IF YOU WANT TO USE
THAT GIFT,
IT'S GONNA TAKE SACRIFICE
AND COMMITMENT.
SO YOU'VE GOTTA ASK YOURSELF,
HOW BAD DO I WANT TO USE
THAT GIFT?
ADAM!
DON'T GET TOO EXCITED,
I'M HERE TO TELL YOU
YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
COULD'VE JUST TEXTED
AND SAVED THE EFFORT.
IT'S NOT TOO LATE TO BAIL.
FITZ IS GONNA BE HERE
ANY MINUTE.
IF YOU DON'T WANNA BE HERE,
THEN GO.
(SIGHS ANGRILY)
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
YEAH? WHAT ABOUT CLARE?
SHE DOESN'T GET GUYS.
SOMETIMES YOU HAVE TO STAND UP
FOR YOUR BUD.
(CHUCKLES)
HEY, FREAK!
♪♪♪
FITZ:
YOU SHOULD'VE BACKED OFF.
NOW SOMEONE'S GONNA GET HURT.
YEAH? BRING IT.
ELI:
ADAM, CALM DOWN.
ADAM:
WHAT'RE YOU GONNA DO, HUH?
ELI:
ADAM, TAKE IT EASY!
OOF!
FITZ:
WHAT THE HELL?!
I TOLD YOU, I CAN'T HIT A GIRL!
I'M NOT A GIRL!
(FUSE HISSES)
(STRUGGLING)
EASY, SWEETHEART.
I COULD MAKE AN EXCEPTION.
UNGH! OH...
GUY: STINK BOMB!
(ALARM BELL RINGS)
STUDENTS:
UGH! EWWW!
(PANTING)
NICE!
YOU OKAY?
YEAH.
CHANTAY:
SOME GENIUS SET OFF
A STINK BOMB!
LET'S GO.
YOU'RE DEAD!
(GROANS)
♪♪♪
♪ Did you wake up today ♪
♪ To find the strength to say ♪
♪ The world is your own ♪
♪ Did you look up today ♪
♪ Did you find the words
to say ♪
♪ The world is your own ♪
♪ You gotta believe ♪
♪ And you'll find ♪
♪ Your own way ♪
DUDE, YOU DID IT!
THAT'S GREAT!
YEAH!
♪ You gotta smile ♪
♪ You gotta be strong ♪
♪ You've gotta believe ♪
♪ In your own way ♪
TONI STARK:
I NEED AN ANSWER, FIONA.
FIONA:
I KNOW.
TONI STARK:
THEN STOP STALLING.
YOU'VE BEEN SEEING
A PSYCHIATRIST FOR HOW LONG?
IT'S A SIMPLE QUESTION!
(SIGHS)
BEING IN THERAPY
DOESN'T AFFECT MY RECOLLECTION
OF WHAT HAPPENED.
BOBBY HIT ME!
HE HIT ME
AND HE PULLED ME
DOWN THE STAIRS,
AND THAT'S ALL THAT'S RELEVANT.
ANY MORE QUESTIONS,
MS. STARK?
TONI STARK:
A LOT, ACTUALLY.
FIONA:
GREAT.
BRING IT.