(GRUNTS OF EFFORT)
ZANE:
FEEL THE BURN!
YOU CALL YOURSELF
A FOOTBALL PLAYER?
FOUR MORE!
C'MON!
(GRUNTING)
(ZANE LAUGHS)
BOTH:
(PANTING HEAVILY)
GELATO BREAK?
NO, DUDE, I CAN'T.
RIGHT.
WOULDN'T WANT TO PACK
ANY GRISTLE
ON THAT CHISELED FRAME.
WE'RE BACK AT SCHOOL NOW.
YOU KNOW I HAVE TO GO
BACK TO NORMAL.
NORMAL.
RIGHT.
SO THAT'S IT?
RILEY AND ZANE
ARE OFFICIALLY ON HOLD?
ONLY UNTIL FOOTBALL
SEASON'S OVER.
I MEAN,
BEING THE SENIOR QUARTERBACK,
GETTING THE START,
MAYBE EVEN CAPTAIN -
IT'LL NEVER HAPPEN
IF I'M OUT.
YOU CAN ONLY STUFF YOURSELF
IN THE CLOSET SO LONG.
WE CAN STILL HANG OUT.
BE TEAMMATES?
(LAUGHS)
MAYBE MY SOCCER SKILLS'LL
TRANSLATE TO FOOTBALL.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
YOU DO LOOK KINDA CUTE
IN A JERSEY.
I GOTTA GET BACK
TO MY WORKOUT.
I GOT SIX MORE K TO DO.
GUESS I'LL SEE YOU
AT SCHOOL.
HEY, ZANE!
I HAD A FUN THIS SUMMER.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
ALLI:
(SIGHS) SUCH A BEAUTIFUL DAY!
YOU KNOW,
ONE OF THOSE DAYS
WHERE YOU FEEL LIKE
ANYTHING'S POSSIBLE.
YEAH, LIKE SOMETHING
NON DEEP-FRIED IN THE CAF?
UGH. LUNCHTIME.
WHERE DO YOU THINK
WE'LL SIT?
UH, STUDENT COUNCIL OFFICE?
I HAVE YEARBOOK COMMITTEE.
SO YOU'RE DITCHING ME?
FOR 45 MINUTES.
I'M SURE YOU'LL SURVIVE.
WE MIGHT STILL NEED
A PHOTOGRAPHER.
YIPPEE. SO I'LL SPEND
MY GRADE TEN YEAR
TAKING PICTURES
OF OTHER PEOPLE'S FUN.
I MEAN, LOOK AT JENNA
EXPERIENCING ALL THE WONDERS
OF HIGH SCHOOL:
HAPPINESS, POPULARITY,
CUTE BOYS.
WHY CAN'T THAT BE US?
UH, BECAUSE WE'D HAVE
TO JOIN THE POWER SQUAD.
CHANTAY'S ALREADY
STARTED TRYOUTS.
BUT MAYBE IT'S NOT TOO LATE.
WAIT. YOU'RE SERIOUS?
YOU WANT TO BECOME
A CHEERLEADER?
IF YOU'RE AT YEARBOOK,
I'LL NEED SOMEWHERE TO SIT.
WHY SHOULDN'T IT BE WITH
THE COOLEST KIDS IN SCHOOL?
AH, CAN I BORROW YOUR PEN?
YEAH, SURE.
ARE YOU NEW HERE?
DREW.
RILEY.
DREW:
YEAH, I HEAR THE TEAM'S GOOD.
BETTER THAN
IT USED TO BE.
THAT'S ONE OF THE REASONS
I BUGGED MY MOM
TO LET ME COME
TO THIS SCHOOL.
I ALSO HEAR
OUR CHEERLEADERS ARE SMOKIN'.
RILEY:
OH, YEAH.
DEGRASSI GIRLS ARE CLASSY GIRLS!
ZANE:
(CLEARS THROAT)
YOU GUYS GOT A PEN?
DREW:
YEAH. HERE. IT'S HIS.
ARE YOU REALLY
TRYING OUT?
TEAM NEEDS A KICKER.
GOTTA SHOW GAY GUYS
CAN PLAY SPORTS.
YOU'RE GAY?
UH, ZANE,
THIS IS DREW.
DREW'S NEW HERE
AND UM...
ZANE'S IN MY ALGEBRA CLASS.
DREW:
COOL. SEE YOU GUYS AROUND.
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
YOU SAID I LOOK CUTE
IN A JERSEY.
WHAT? I THOUGHT
IT WOULD BE FUN,
YOU AND ME ON THE TEAM.
UNLESS YOU'RE NOT
COOL WITH IT?
SEE YOU IN CLASS.
KING:
YOU HAVE 20 MINUTES TO DEVELOP
A FULL EXAMPLE,
USING THE SCARCITY PARADIGM.
OKAY?
DUDE, I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT THAT IS.
SCARCITY PARADIGM?
WELL, BASICALLY,
WHEN A COMMODITY IS LIMITED,
YOU HAVE TO EXPEND
MORE CAPITAL TO GET IT.
DO YOU SPEAK ENGLISH?
OKAY, LOOK.
THERE'S JESS T,
JESS M, JESS B,
AND THEN THERE'S FIONA.
DREW:
WOW! ONE OF THESE THINGS
IS NOT LIKE THE OTHERS.
EXACTLY.
SO LAST YEAR WHEN I HAD
A DATE WITH FIONA, I...
NICE!
I HAD TO WORK WAY HARDER
THAN I WOULD'VE
TO GET A DATE
WITH A JESSICA.
I HAD TO EXPEND
MORE CAPITAL.
WOW. FOR THE FIRST TIME,
I THINK I GET ECONOMICS.
KING:
GENTLEMEN? GO ON.
MOST OF THE TIME,
ONCE I TELL A GIRL
I'M A QUARTERBACK,
I'M PRETTY WELL IN.
YOU PLAY Q.B.?
YEAH, AT MY OLD SCHOOL.
SENIOR TEAM.
BUT YOU'RE ONLY
IN GRADE 11.
YOUNGEST STARTER EVER!
CHANTAY:
OCTOBER 2ND, POWER SQUAD MIXER.
WE INVITE THE TEAMS
FROM BARDELL, CENTRAL,
ST. GEORGE'S-
OH MY GOD, I HEARD ABOUT
THAT LAST YEAR.
IT SOUNDS LIKE
SO MUCH FUN!
IT IS.
THE NIGHT BEFORE,
WE'LL HAVE FREE MAKEOVERS
AT KELLI'S MOM'S SPA
FOR THE CALENDAR SHOOT.
FUN!
AND THE NEXT WEEK,
DATE-A-CHEERLEADER AUCTION
FOR THE SICK KIDS FUND -
ALLI:
OKAY, I WOULD TOTALLY PAY
FOR A DATE WITH ONE OF YOU!
I MEAN,
IF I WAS A GUY.
AND WHY ARE YOU
EAVESDROPPING?
YOU'RE NOT EVEN
ON POWER SQUAD.
WELL, NOT YET.
IS IT TOO LATE
TO TRY OUT?
SWEETIE, WE'VE BEEN AUDITIONING
FOR A WEEK.
BUT I'M A FAST LEARNER.
RIGHT, JENNA?
OH, TOTALLY.
ALLI:
PLEASE.
PLEASE. PLEASE.
PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE.
FINE. AFTER SCHOOL.
THANK YOU, SO-
I'LL NEED A SKINNY LATTE
AND A PACK OF SPEARMINT GUM.
YEAH.
YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND,
YOU LET ME KNOW.
WE COULD REALLY USE YOU!
JENNA:
WHAT WAS THAT?
ARMSTRONG WANTS ME
TO TRY OUT FOR FOOTBALL.
WIDE RECEIVER.
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA!
WE COULD SIT TOGETHER
ON THE BUS TO THE GAMES!
I SAID NO.
AFTER LAST YEAR...
COACH CARSON.
I TOTALLY GET IT,
BUT YOU CAN'T LET WHAT HAPPENED
WITH SOME PERV
AFFECT YOUR WHOLE LIFE.
♪♪♪
♪ Oh I'm building a boat
to get me out of town ♪
♪ So I'm cutting big tall trees
down to the ground ♪
♪ I'm gonna cut 'em up
into bends ♪
♪ With a couple of my friends ♪
♪ We're gonna have her goin'
so fast ♪
♪ By the spring, yeah ♪
ARMSTRONG:
TIME.
NUMBERS?
4.9 K.
5-4.
NICE WORK, RILEY.
SOMEONE'S BEEN TRAINING
OVER THE SUMMER.
A LITTLE.
YOU FOCUSING ALL YOUR EFFORTS
ON LOWER BODY?
NO, UPPER BODY TOO.
MY BENCH PRESS
IS ABOUT 200 POUNDS.
WELL, YOU KEEP IT UP
AND YOU'RE A SHOO-IN FOR QB 1.
THANKS, SIR.
DON'T WORRY, DUDE.
THERE'S ALWAYS NEXT YEAR.
YOU'RE ALREADY
IN GAME SHAPE.
I COULDN'T HAVE BEEN THAT BIG
A DISTRACTION THIS SUMMER.
SHH! NOT HERE!
YOU WANT A SPOTTER?
OWEN:
IS, UH, PRINCESS HERE
BOTHERING YOU?
ZANE:
NAME-CALLING? REALLY?
OWEN:
NICE PANTS.
LIKE 'EM?
OH, THEY'RE FABULOUTH.
YOU BORROW 'EM
FROM YOUR SISTER?
WHAT, YOU DON'T DO YOGA?
AS IF.
ZANE:
HELPS BUILD UPPER ARM STRENGTH.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
GIVE IT A TRY.
OH! WE COULD GO SHOPPING FIRST.
MUST BE TOUGH FOR YOUR BUD.
MY BUD?
I BARELY KNOW THE GUY.
DOESN'T BOTHER ME,
BUT LET'S SAY HE MAKES IT.
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN
THE BARDELL GUYS FIND OUT
WE HAVE A KICKER WHO, UH...
WHO KISSES DUDES?
(STUNNED LAUGH)
(COACH BLOWS WHISTLE)
CHANTAY:
SO REMEMBER, KEEP IT CRISP,
KEEP IT SHARP,
AND KEEP IT CHANTAY.
MUSIC. READY? AND...
AM I LATE?
WHOA.
WHERE DID YOU GET THAT?
WHAT? OH, THIS?
WELL, YOU SEE MY FRIEND CLARE
IS DARCY'S LITTLE SISTER.
YOU HATE IT.
NO. IT'S CUTE ON YOU.
SO... RETRO.
YOUR LATTE,
YOUR GUM.
GOOD.
NOW WHAT?
THE "HIPS OVER THE FIELD"
ROUTINE.
AWESOME.
WHAT ARE THE STEPS?
YOU'LL PICK IT UP.
POSITIONS!
AND LET'S DO THIS!
5, 6, 7, 8.
1, 2, 3, 4,
♪♪♪
RILEY:
(CLAPPING) FIELD GOAL!
I CANNOT WAIT
TO PRACTICE OUTSIDE.
THOSE GUYS ARE JERKS.
YUP.
SORRY I DIDN'T DEFEND YOU.
WELL, YOU'RE SCARED OF WHAT
PEOPLE WOULD THINK.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU WANNA DO THIS?
WHY NOT?
DUDE, OWEN'S STILL GOING ON
ABOUT YOU IN THERE.
OWEN'S AN ASS.
RILEY:
YEAH, BUT I NEED HIS RESPECT
IF I'M GONNA LEAD THE TEAM.
(SIGHS) LOOK, I KNOW I SAID
I WAS OKAY IF YOU TRIED OUT,
BUT I DIDN'T KNOW
IT WAS GONNA BE THIS RISKY.
ZANE...
I LIKE YOU.
THEY'LL KNOW.
HOLY COW!
I AM NOT GONNA JUMP YOU
IN THE LOCKER ROOM!
ALL RIGHT?
IF THOSE GUYS EVEN SEE ME
TALKING TO YOU,
THEY'LL THINK I'M GAY.
THEN I CAN KISS
BEING CAPTAIN GOODBYE.
I TOLD YOU,
THERE'S THE RILEY
THAT YOU HANG OUT WITH,
AND THEN THERE'S THE RILEY
WHO PLAYS FOOTBALL.
RIGHT.
THE "TWO RILEY'S" THEORY.
DREW WANTS MY SPOT.
I CAN'T LOSE MY EDGE.
THIS IS THE WORST
POSSIBLE TIME TO-
BE WHO YOU ARE?
MY BACK ROW MOVIE PARTNER?
MY GREEK FOOD TOUR GUIDE?
MY THOUGHTFUL BIKE FIXER?
MY GUY.
PLEASE, DON'T DO THIS.
I THOUGHT FOOTBALL
WAS SOMETHING
WE COULD DO TOGETHER.
BUT NOW THAT I'M HERE,
I LIKE IT.
AND I'M NOT GONNA LET JERK-WAD
FOOTBALL RILEY
TREAT ME LIKE A LEPER,
LIKE IT OR NOT.
(KICKS THE FOOTBALL)
BHANDARI, HANG BACK.
DO YOU WANNA TALK
UNIFORMS?
I COULD WHIP UP
SOME SKETCHES AND-
I DON'T CARE
ABOUT UNIFORMS.
IF YOU WANT THIS,
YOU NEED TO SHOW ME
SOME SKILLS.
I DO WANT THIS.
CHANTAY,
I WANT YOUR LIFE.
I WANT YOUR FRIENDS
TO BE MY FRIENDS.
AND I WANT MY WEEKENDS
BOOKED UP TO JULY.
I DON'T WANT TO SPEND MY LUNCH
AT YEARBOOK MEETINGS
WONDERING WHAT MY LIFE
COULD REALLY FEEL LIKE.
I WANT TO KNOW.
THEN LET'S RUN
THE ROUTINES AGAIN.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO WORK REALLY HARD.
I CAN DO THAT.
OKAY, REMEMBER "HIPS"?
5, 6, 7, 8.
LEFT, TWO, UP, ARM,
HIP, KICK,
DOWN, SWITCH.
HOW'D YOU GET THAT LEG?
OH. SO AFTER YOU KICK,
THEN YOU SWITCH IT.
OKAY.
LET'S TRY IT AGAIN.
♪ You've got me
staring out my window ♪
♪ Just in case I see you
on my street ♪
THE TEAM I'M LOOKING FOR
IS NOT MADE OF BABIES;
IT'S MADE OF MEN.
WHAT I WANT ON THIS TEAM
IS LEADERSHIP.
AND I DON'T NEED TO REMIND YOU
THAT THERE IS A STRICT CODE
OF CONDUCT
THAT WE EXPECT
ALL OUR ATHLETES TO UPHOLD.
NOW, SOME OF YOU...
I'VE BEEN COACHING
FOR A LONG TIME.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE CAPABLE OF.
WHAT ABOUT
THE REST OF US?
WELL, NOW'S YOUR CHANCE
TO PROVE YOURSELF.
CAN I MAKE
A SUGGESTION?
NO.
(GUYS LAUGHING)
I THINK WE NEED
TEAM BONDING.
AT MY OLD SCHOOL,
WE HELD A TAILGATE BARBECUE
IN THE PARKING LOT.
EVERYONE CAME
AND IT WAS GREAT
FOR SCHOOL SPIRIT.
SO, WHAT DO YOU GUYS THINK?
TOMORROW AFTER PRACTICE?
GUYS:
SURE. SOUNDS GOOD. ALL RIGHT.
WELL, IT'S LATE NOTICE,
BUT I CAN, UH,
RUN IT BY PRINCIPAL SIMPSON.
NOW GO HOME AND GET SOME REST.
YOU'RE GONNA NEED IT
FOR TOMORROW'S TRYOUT.
OH, WAIT. GUYS?
DON'T FORGET:
BRING A DATE.
ANOTHER ONE FOR THE CORKBOARD!
YOU DON'T HAVE TO KEEP
PUTTING THOSE UP, TODD.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
YOU'RE DOING SO WELL.
THAT MAKES ME LOOK GOOD.
ALL I DO
IS KEEP HIM HONEST.
SHE EVEN CONVINCED ME
TO TRY OUT
FOR THE FOOTBALL TEAM.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT
ALL THIS MEANS?
WHAT'S THAT?
A REWARD.
I CAN TACK AN HOUR
ONTO YOUR CURFEW.
REALLY?!
THAT'S AWESOME!
NINE P.M. MOVIES, KC!
YOU'VE TURNED INTO
A REAL SUCCESS STORY.
BUT I GUESS I DON'T DESERVE
ALL THE CREDIT.
YOU CAN TAKE SOME CREDIT.
IT'S GOOD HERE.
♪♪♪
THIS IS IT!
AMBER, JADE,
LATIESHA, KAREENA...
WHERE AM I?
NO, NO, NO, NO.
CHANTAY, I THINK
THERE'S A MISTAKE.
THE LIST-
NO. THERE ISN'T.
YOU SAID ALL I HAD TO DO
WAS WORK HARD,
AND I DID!
I'M SORRY, ALLI,
BUT YOU JUST
COULDN'T GET IT.
OH, I GET IT.
YOU JUST DON'T WANT ME
IN YOUR STUPID
CHEERLEADER CLUB.
HERE'S THE THING:
WE HAD 5 SPOTS
AND 23 GIRLS TRIED OUT.
THAT MEANS NOT EVERYBODY
CAN BE ON THE TEAM.
I THOUGHT YOU LIKED ME.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHO LIKES WHO.
YOU HAVE TO EARN IT.
YOU CAN TRY OUT AGAIN
NEXT YEAR.
GREAT! WELL, WHO AM I SUPPOSED
TO HANG OUT WITH UNTIL THEN?
HONEY,
THAT'S NOT MY PROBLEM.
♪ No, no, no, no, no, no, no! ♪
♪ Ahh... Ahh... Ahh... ♪
(SIZZLING)
TEAMMATE:
OWEN, YOU WANT ONE?
♪♪♪
RILEY:
HEY, OWEN.
VIRGIL.
DREW!
HOW ARE YOU, MAN?
GOOD.
GOOD TURNOUT, EH?
YEAH. I'D YOU TO MEET MY DATE.
THIS IS MARILOU.
IT'S MARISOL.
RIGHT.
AND MARISOL IS GOING
TO GET HERSELF SOME WATER.
SO WHERE'S YOUR DATE,
MAN?
I DON'T KNOW ANY GIRLS
AT DEGRASSI YET.
ALTHOUGH, NOT KNOWING THEM
DOESN'T SEEM TO STOP YOU.
YOU CAN ONLY KEEP SO MANY
GIRLS' NAMES IN YOUR HEAD
AT ONCE, Y'KNOW?
YOU SURE DON'T SEEM TO HAVE
THE SAME PROBLEM
WITH BOYS' NAMES.
WHAT'RE YOU
TRYING TO SAY?
THAT'S THE SECOND TIME
I'VE CAUGHT YOU
CHECKING OUT MR. GAY.
I'M JUST WONDERING
IF SOMETHING'S GOING ON.
LIKE WHAT?
NOTHING!
JUST JOKING, MAN!
♪♪♪
HOT DOG?
NO, THANKS.
I HAVE TO WATCH
WHAT GOES INTO THIS TEMPLE.
JENNA:
HEY GUYS!
THIS IS SO GOOD!
BITE?
I'M SO HAPPY YOU DECIDED
TO TRY OUT FOR THE TEAM!
YEAH. YEAH, ME TOO.
ALL OF US ARE!
GO PANTHERS!
HMM. AND HERE I WAS
WORRIED YOU'D BE WAITING HERE,
ALL UNCOMFORTABLE
AND ALONE.
EVERYBODY LOVES
A FOOTBALL STAR.
(GIRLS GIGGLING)
YEAH.
THEY SURE DO.
ALLI:
CLARE, I GOT HUMILIATED.
DITCHED.
AND NOW I FEEL UNCOOL.
IDIOTIC. SUB-PAR.
RIDICULOUS.
STOP ME, 'CAUSE I COULD
GO ON FOREVER.
TWO DAYS AGO, YOU DIDN'T CARE
ABOUT THE POWER SQUAD,
AND NOW NOT MAKING IT
IS THE WORST THING EVER.
WHAT GIVES?
I DON'T FIT... ANYWHERE.
TRY AGAIN.
THIS TIME WITH MORE WORDS.
I THOUGHT HIGH SCHOOL
WOULD BE THE COOLEST.
YOU KNOW,
HAVE A LOT OF FRIENDS,
ALWAYS HAVE SOMETHING
TO DO.
INSTEAD, I'M IN GRADE 10
AND STILL WORRIED ABOUT
WHERE I'M GONNA SIT AT LUNCH.
YOU HAVE ME.
NOT WHEN YOU'RE BUSY WITH ALL
YOUR CLARE-RRIFIC ACTIVITIES.
WHAT ABOUT CONNOR?
OR WESLEY?
NOT EXACTLY THE BUDS
YOU WANT TO HANG OUT WITH
AT A FOOTBALL GAME.
I NEED MY OWN GROUP.
IT'S JUST THE ONE I WANTED
DIDN'T WANT ME.
WHAT DO YOU DO WHEN LIFE
HANDS YOU LEMONS?
THROW THEM AT CHANTAY?
YOU KNOW,
THIS ISN'T CHANTAY'S FAULT.
YOU CAN'T EXPECT
INSTANT FRIENDS.
YOU HAVE TO WORK AT IT.
FIND PEOPLE
WHO SHARE YOUR INTERESTS.
GREAT. I'LL PUT UP A PERSONAL AD
IN THE SCHOOL NEWSPAPER.
PATHETIC LOSER
SEEKING LUNCH COMPANION.
OR... YOU COULD START
YOUR OWN CLUB,
SEE WHO SHOWS UP.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S ACTUALLY
NOT A BAD IDEA.
IT COULD BE A DANCE CLUB.
SURE!
AND WE COULD CRUSH
CHANTAY
AND HER STUPID ELITIST
POWER SQUAD
INTO A BILLION
TINY PIECES.
YEAH. YOU MIGHT WANT
TO LEAVE THAT ONE
OFF THE POSTER.
♪♪♪
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
AGAIN?
INTERESTING TEXTS?
YOU KEEP CHECKING.
SORRY.
YOU HAVE MY UNDIVIDED ATTENTION.
THIS FOOTBALL PLAYER
CHEERLEADER DYNAMIC?
I COULD REALLY
GET USED TO IT.
TOLD YOU IT WOULD BE OKAY
TO TRUST COACH ARMSTRONG.
I TRUST YOU.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(IMPATIENT SIGH)
(RINGING STOPS)
YEAH.
UH, WHAT WAS I SAYING?
SOMETHING NICE.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
WOW. SOMEONE'S PRETTY
DESPERATE TO GET YOU.
JUST IGNORE IT.
DID YOU GIVE THOSE GIRLS
YOUR CELL?
JUST MARISOL.
SHE'S KEEPING THE CONTACT LIST
FOR THE WHOLE TEAM.
OH, IS THAT WHAT
SHE TOLD YOU?
KC, THAT GIRL COLLECTS BOYS
LIKE OTHER PEOPLE
COLLECT RINGTONES.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
I'M TURNING IT OFF.
(RINGING STOPS)
IT'S OFF. SEE?
♪♪♪
MUSTARD?
OH, YOU'RE ACKNOWLEDGING
MY EXISTENCE?
IN FRONT OF EVERYBODY?
YOU WANT TO TRY OUT?
I CAN'T STOP YOU.
BUT I NEED YOU
TO KEEP YOUR DISTANCE
IN THE LOCKER ROOM.
EXCUSE ME?
I DON'T SEE
ANY OTHER WAY.
SO WE CAN BE
ON THE SAME TEAM,
BUT WE CAN'T TALK
OR ANYTHING?
PEOPLE ARE STARTING
TO SUSPECT
THAT SOMETHING'S GOING ON,
SO IT NEEDS STOP.
YOU'RE PATHETIC.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET'S EXPAND
THE NOT BEING FRIENDS
BEYOND THE LOCKER ROOM.
HOW 'BOUT EVERYWHERE,
HUH?
ZANE, WHAT'S UP?
OH, SORRY.
AM I INTERRUPTING?
NO, WE'RE DONE.
THERE YOU GO,
CALLING THE SHOTS AGAIN.
SO, YOU STILL
GONNA DENY IT?
DUDE, I'M NOT IN THE MOOD
FOR YOUR STUPID JOKES.
DREW:
WHO SAYS I'M JOKING?
I SAW YOU TWO ARGUING
IN THE GYM.
I KNOW ALL ABOUT
THE "TWO RILEY'S" THEORY.
SO, UNLESS YOU WANT ME
TO TELL THE ENTIRE TEAM,
I SUGGEST YOU STEP ASIDE
FOR QB 1.
HEY, OWEN.
HOW ARE YOU?
WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF THE NEW KID?
OWEN:
WHAT, DREW?
HE'S A COCKY LITTLE BASTARD.
SOMEONE NEEDS TO REMIND HIM
HE'S A ROOKIE.
RILEY:
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE WELCOME
THE NEW GUY TO THE TEAM?
♪♪♪