(MUSIC PLAYS)
(STUDENTS HOLLER AND CHEER)
(CLAPPING)
(ROULETTE WHEEL TICKS)
GIRL:
OH, YEAH!
ALL RIGHT!
(DICE CLATTER)
HOLLY J:
WELCOME TO "A NIGHT IN VEGAS"!
WITH A LITTLE BIT OF LUCK,
ANYTHING COULD HAPPEN!
THAT'S RIGHT,
AND THE STUDENT
AT THE END OF THE NIGHT
WITH THE MOST CHIPS,
WINS A BRAND NEW
FLAT SCREEN TV!
(CROWD CLAPS AND CHEERS)
LET'S GET SOME MUSIC
IN HERE!
(MUSIC PLAYS)
TIME TO MAN UP,
AND TELL ALLI THE TRUTH.
ABOUT BIANCA IN THE BOILER
ROOM, ARE YOU NUTS?
ADAM:
SHE'S GONNA FIND OUT.
ORAL SEX IS HOT GOSSIP.
YOU WORRY TOO MUCH.
DREW:
HEY. LET'S GET OUT OF HERE,
JUST THE TWO OF US.
WHERE WOULD WE GO?
(BOTH LAUGH)
BOILER ROOM'S FREE.
BOILER ROOM?
YEAH, IT'S NOTHING.
SO THAT'S WHAT THEY'RE
CALLING IT THESE DAYS?
WELL, IT SEEMED LIKE
A LOT MORE THAN NOTHING
WHEN WE WERE IN THERE.
♪♪♪
♪ She's a heartbreaker... ♪
WHAT IS SHE TALKING ABOUT?
UM...
WELL, WHATEVER IT IS,
IT CAN'T BE WORSE
THAN WHAT I'M THINKING.
WELL, THIS AFTERNOON,
AFTER OUR EXAMS...
ME AND BIANCA-
OH MY GOD,
YOU HAD SEX?!
DREW:
NO, NO, NO!
NO, WE JUST...
YOU KNOW...
KISSED?
KISSED.
(SIGHS) OH...
IT WAS A HUGE M-MISTAKE.
IT MEANT NOTHING.
I'D DO ANYTHING
TO TAKE IT BACK!
I'M SO SORRY.
(SIGHS)
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, whatever ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(MUFFLED MUSIC PLAYS)
I'M SO SORRY!
AS SOON AS IT HAPPENED,
I KNEW IT WAS WRONG.
PLEASE,
YOU HAVE TO FORGIVE ME.
IT WAS JUST A KISS, RIGHT?
YEAH.
YOU CAN NEVER TALK
TO HER AGAIN.
IF YOU SEE HER
IN THE HALL-
I'LL TURN THE OTHER WAY!
(SIGHS)
DOES THIS MEAN YOU'LL GIVE ME
ANOTHER CHANCE?
SHOULD WE TRY TO AT LEAST ENJOY
WHAT'S LEFT OF THIS EVENING?
ABSOLUTELY.
(DOOR OPENS, MUSIC BLARES)
(DOOR CLICKS SHUT,
MUSIC BECOMES MUFFLED)
IS THAT CORSAGE FOR ME?
MY MOM MADE ME BRING IT.
(LAUGHS)
I LIKE IT.
BUT, I'M NOT GONNA HAVE
SEX WITH YOU.
WHOA!
WHERE DID THAT COME FROM?
I KNOW WHAT YOU TOLD ELI.
CLARE, IN THEORY,
ALL GUYS WANT TO HOOK UP
WITH A CUTE GIRL LIKE YOU.
IT'S LIKE PHYSICS.
BIOLOGY.
WHATEVER.
I WOULDN'T TRY ANYTHING ON YOU.
UNLESS YOU WANT ME TO.
IN THEORY, NOT A CHANCE.
(LAUGHS)
BETCHA ELI OVERREACTED.
UH-HUH, KINDA.
(LAUGHS)
WOULDN'T IT JUST BE EASIER
IF YOU TWO JUST GOT ALONG?
FITZ:
ONE WOULD THINK.
BUT LAST TIME
I TRIED TO END THIS FEUD,
YOUR LITTLE BOYFRIEND
GOT ME ARRESTED.
WOULD AN APOLOGY STILL WORK
TO END THIS FEUD?
SURE.
BUT GOOD LUCK GETTING IT.
♪ Baby there's a shark
in the water ♪
♪ Water ♪
♪ There's something underneath
my bed ♪
♪ Oh please believe I said ♪
♪ Baby there's a shark
in the water ♪
EXCUSE ME.
NEXT ONE'S GONNA COST YOU.
STOP IT.
WHAT'S GOT YOUR JOCK STRAP
IN A TWIST?
YOU BLABBING ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED.
IF ALLI FINDS OUT,
SHE'S GONNA DUMP ME.
AND I CARE BECAUSE?
YOU'RE A DECENT HUMAN BEING.
WHO WANTS TO WIN
THE FLAT SCREEN TV.
BUT, I NEED
A WHOLE LOT OF CHIPS.
FINE. HAVE MINE.
I GUESS IT'S YOUR LUCKY DAY.
ALLI:
WHAT ARE YOU DOING WITH HER?!
UM, I'M TRYING TO KEEP
HER QUIET.
WE MADE A DEAL.
MY LIPS ARE SEALED.
AND YOU SHOULD KEEP THEM
THAT WAY.
EXCUSE ME?
ALLI:
STOP KISSING OTHER
PEOPLE'S BOYFRIENDS.
IT'S PATHETIC.
KISSING?
(SCOFFS)
IS THAT WHAT YOU TOLD HER?
I-I CAN EXPLAIN.
OH, LET ME HELP.
YOUR BOYFRIEND AND I GOT
INTIMATE IN THE BOILER ROOM.
BUT ALL MY CLOTHES
STAYED ON.
DEAL'S OFF.
YOU TWO ARE DISGUSTING.
ALLI!
SAV:
SINCLAIR, WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
THE PUNCH BOWL?
I'M ON IT.
NOPE, ACTUALLY,
THE PROBLEM'S BIGGER THAN THAT.
THE NIGHT IS NEARLY OVER,
AND UH,
(CLEARS THROAT)
I HAVEN'T KISSED YOU YET.
WHAT WOULD THE SCHOOL
BOARD SAY?
I DON'T KNOW.
SHOOT. UM,
YOU KNOW WHAT,
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO CROWN
THE KING AND QUEEN.
YOU GET THE CROWNS.
GUESS THERE'S ALWAYS
NEXT SEMESTER.
♪♪♪
♪ There's something underneath
my bed ♪
♪ Oh please believe I said ♪
♪ Baby there's a shark in- ♪
(CLEARS THROAT)
HI, EVERYONE.
HI, HI.
UM, SO NOW FOR THE MOMENT
YOU'VE ALL BEEN WAITING FOR,
I'VE GOT IT RIGHT HERE...
SO, YOUR KING...
DREW TORRES.
AND YOUR QUEEN,
ALLI BHANDARI.
(CLAPPING AND CHEERING)
GREAT.
GUESS THERE'S ALWAYS PROM.
GUESS SO.
UM... HAS ANYONE SEEN
OUR QUEEN?
DREW?
OKAY, WELL, UM...
WHILE WE WAIT FOR OUR LUCKY
COUPLE TO TAKE THE STAGE,
THERE'S SOMETHING I'VE BEEN
MEANING TO SAY
...TO SOMEONE,
AND I THINK THIS MIGHT
BE MY ONLY CHANCE.
(SMATTERING OF APPLAUSE)
♪ IT STARTED OUT WITH A KISS ♪
♪ INNOCENT BLISS ♪
♪ I TOUCHED HER
INTO DESIRE ♪
♪ YOUR HEART IS A FIRE ♪
♪ THAT MELTS THE ICE ♪
(STRUMS GUITAR)
♪ ALL OUR FRIENDS TOLD US... ♪
ELI:
COME ON, LUCKY SEVEN.
HAVING FUN ON YOUR DATE,
JUDAS?
BET FITZY'S A REAL
DREAMY KISSER.
YOU CAN'T BE MAD AT ME
BECAUSE I WOULDN'T SLIP IPECAC
INTO FITZ'S DRINK.
CAN I BE MAD
YOU'RE WITH HIM?
HE THREATENED TO HURT YOU!
WHAT WAS I SUPPOSED TO DO?
LET ME HANDLE IT.
BECAUSE THAT WAS WORKING
SO WELL.
FITZ ISN'T THE MONSTER
YOU THINK HE IS.
HE'S WILLING TO BURY
THE HATCHET.
HE JUST WANTS ONE THING.
YOU'RE GONNA SLEEP WITH HIM?
NO! YOU'RE GOING
TO APOLOGIZE.
(SCOFFS)
FOR WHAT?
CLARE:
ANYTHING HE WANTS!
PLEASE, ELI.
FINE.
REALLY?
YOU'LL APOLOGIZE?
BUT I WON'T MEAN IT.
CLARE:
AS LONG AS YOU SELL IT.
I'M GONNA GO GET HIM.
SAV:
♪ MY HEART IS A FIRE ♪
♪ YOUR HEART IS A FIRE ♪
♪ THAT MELTS THE ICE ♪
(AUDIENCE CLAPS AND CHEERS)
(AUDIENCE CHEERS LOUDLY)
GIRL:
ALL RIGHT!
SAV:
SO WHAT'D YOU THINK,
THE ELVIS THING TOO MUCH?
MEET ME IN THE THEATER,
IN TEN.
♪♪♪
(LAUGHS)
YEAH!
♪♪♪
OKAY, WE'RE HERE.
ALL SET FOR THE APOLOGY.
YOU KNOW,
IN SOME PLACES,
THIS WOULD BE CONSIDERED
BLACKMAIL.
ELI,
STOP PROCRASTINATING.
FITZ:
YEAH, ELI.
DO WHAT THE LADY SAYS.
I'M SORRY.
FOR EVERYTHING.
THAT'S NOT GONNA DO.
YOU SAID THE WORDS,
BUT I DIDN'T FEEL THEM.
OKAY, ENOUGH.
FITZ, YOU GOT YOUR APOLOGY.
NOW, SHAKE HANDS.
ELI: OR...
WE COULD TOAST.
TO A CEASE-FIRE!
STOP!
TRADE CUPS.
IT'S AN ANCIENT ROMAN CUSTOM.
SHE'S THE BOSS.
L'CHAIM!
(RETCHING)
(LAUGHS)
(FITZ VOMITS)
(STUDENTS LAUGH)
WHAT DID YOU DO?
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO MADE US SWITCH.
OH, DON'T YOU DARE
PUT THIS ON ME!
WHATEVER FITZ DOES TO YOU,
YOU DESERVE IT!
(DOOR CLICKS SHUT)
(SIGHS)
(CRYING)
UM...
HAVE YOU SEEN BIANCA?
SHE'S PROBABLY OUT STEALING
SOMEONE ELSE'S BOYFRIEND.
DO I HAVE TO BEAT SOMEONE UP?
I DON'T LIKE TO SEE
A PRETTY GIRL LIKE YOU CRY.
(SNIFFLES)
COME ON,
TELL OWEN WHAT'S WRONG.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
DREW CHEATED ON ME.
WELL, I ALWAYS THOUGHT
THAT GUY WAS A MORON.
DO YOU THINK I'M SEXY?
I BET SOME GUYS
WOULD PAY BIG MONEY
TO HOOK UP WITH A GIRL
LIKE YOU.
ALLI:
REALLY?
HOW MUCH?
I DON'T KNOW.
A MILLION DOLLARS.
A MILLION DOLLARS?
OWEN:
YEAH.
TOO BAD I DON'T HAVE
THAT TYPE OF CASH.
BUT I DO HAVE FIFTY.
YOU'D PAY FIFTY DOLLARS
TO HOOK UP WITH ME?
YOU KNOW, I BET IT WOULD
MAKE YOUR BOYFRIEND
SUUUUUPER JEALOUS.
AND YOU'D MAKE SURE
HE HEARD ABOUT IT?
(LAUGHS)
I'LL GET MY WALLET.
♪ Too late no sweet sixteen ♪
♪ Just a veteran of this scene ♪
♪ I'm calling you out ♪
(STUDENTS LAUGH AND CHATTER)
HAVE YOU SEEN ALLI?
NOPE.
HIT ME.
YESTERDAY, WE WERE LAUGHING,
STUDYING AND MAKING OUT.
SO WHY'D YOU DO IT?
BIANCA MADE ME FEEL
LIKE A ROCK STAR.
YEAH, AND NOW YOU'VE GOT
ROCK STAR PROBLEMS.
YEAH, AND IT'S ALL
THAT SLUT'S FAULT!
MY FAULT?
YOU CHEATED ON HER
THE FIRST CHANCE YOU GOT.
GUESS SHE WASN'T WORTH KEEPING.
NO, SHE'S WORTH
A LOT MORE THAN YOU.
BIANCA:
REALLY?
WELL ACCORDING TO OWEN,
SHE'S WORTH 50 BUCKS.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THEY'RE IN THE BOILER ROOM.
GO SEE FOR YOURSELF.
(LOCKER CLANGS)
CLARE:
THERE YOU ARE.
ARE YOU OKAY?
YUP.
CLARE:
I SHOULD'VE KNOWN ELI
WOULD PULL SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
HE'S ALWAYS TRYING
TO COME OFF AS THIS BAD ASS.
WORSE PART IS,
I FELL FOR HIM.
I GUESS THAT MAKES ME A-
A REGULAR ASS?
CLARE:
NO, I WAS GOING TO SAY NAIVE.
(LAUGHS) WELL...
I SHOULD UM...
I SHOULD PROBABLY GET
BACK THERE.
SEE YOU AROUND.
OKAY.
(LOCKER CLANGS)
(MUSIC BLARES)
(STUDENTS LAUGH AND CHEER)
WHOA!
WHAT'S UP, BRUTUS?
WHERE'S ELI?
IF YOU'RE GOING
TO LECTURE HIM AGAIN,
FITZ HAS A KNIFE!
DO YOU THINK
HE'S GONNA USE IT?
I-I-I DON'T KNOW,
JUST TELL ME WHERE ELI IS.
HE WENT LOOKING FOR YOU.
(SIGHS)
TELL SIMPSON.
OKAY, OKAY.
OWEN:
SO...
FIFTY BIG ONES.
THIS ISN'T ABOUT THE MONEY.
OH, COOL.
A FREEBIE!
UM...
SO UH, DO YOU WANT TO TALK,
OR SOMETHING?
THAT'S NOT REALLY
HOW THIS WORKS.
I'M JUST...
I'M GONNA GO TO THE WASHROOM
FOR A SECOND.
I'LL BE BACK.
HEY!
NO WONDER YOUR BOYFRIEND
CHEATED ON YOU,
YOU'RE A TEASE!
(SIGHS INDIGNANTLY)
DON'T TOUCH ME.
LOOK, I'M SORRY.
ALLI: NO, STOP!
DREW: HEY!
ALLI:
LET GO OF ME, STOP!
DREW:
GET AWAY FROM HER!
SORRY DUDE,
GET IN LINE.
LEAVE HER ALONE.
SO NOT WORTH IT.
WHY ARE YOU HERE?
TO STOP YOU FROM
MAKING A HUGE MISTAKE.
(LOUD MUSIC PLAYS)
MR. SIMPSON:
TURN THE MUSIC OFF!
CAN YOU TURN THE MUSIC OFF,
PLEASE?
OKAY, NO ONE PANIC.
BUT FROM THIS MOMENT ON,
THE SCHOOL IS IN LOCKDOWN.
AND THE POLICE ARE MANAGING
THE SITUATION.
CHAPERONES, COULD YOU PLEASE
TAKE YOUR POSITIONS
AT THE DOORS?
WHAT IS GOING ON?
THERE'S A STUDENT
WITH A KNIFE.
OH MY GOD!
W-WHAT-WHERE'S DREW?!
I DON'T KNOW.
TRYING TO HAVE ORAL SEX.
BOILER ROOM.
MR. SIMPSON:
AUDRA, YOU CAN'T LEAVE!
OH, NOW YOU'RE GOING
TO START ENFORCING RULES?
(CLEARS THROAT) H-J!
HOLLY J:
JUST TAKE A SEAT, SAV.
I KNOW THE SONG
WAS A BIT MUCH.
UH...
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE,
LITTLE LADY?
COULD YOU JUST SHUT UP,
AND WATCH?
(MUSIC PLAYS)
♪ Took a big try ♪
♪ With your own back ♪
♪ To your holdout ♪
For the wrong man
♪ But connect plans ♪
♪ For your own sake ♪
♪ Hope they don't bow ♪
♪ Hope they don't break ♪
♪♪♪
I LIKED YOU SO MUCH,
AND YOU TREATED ME
LIKE... DIRT.
MAYBE I THOUGHT I WASN'T
GOOD ENOUGH FOR YOU.
WELL, YOU SURE PROVED IT.
I'M SO SORRY!
(DOOR OPEN)
DREW!
WHAT DID SHE DO TO YOU?
(GASPS)
♪ Keep the smile ♪
♪ But you burn at heart ♪
♪ It's a mad mad world ♪
♪ Na na na na ♪
WOW, I'VE NEVER SEEN
THIS SIDE OF YOU.
DO YOU LIKE IT?
YES. VERY MUCH.
FEMALE COP:
HANDS WHERE I CAN SEE THEM!
(RUNNING FOOTSTEPS)
CLARE:
(GASPS)
COME WITH ME.
FITZ HAS A KNIFE!
THIS IS WHERE WE RUN,
LET'S GO!
I'M NOT GOING TO LET
THAT JERK SCARE ME.
ELI, HE HAS A KNIFE!
FITZ:
AWW... DON'T YOU TWO LOOK CUTE?
(DOOR SLAMS)
YOU SHOULD GO.
FITZ:
AND LET PRETTY BOY
MAKE TIME WITH MY DATE?
CLARE:
PLEASE FITZ, DON'T DO THIS.
FITZ:
SHUT UP, BITCH!
ELI:
GET AWAY FROM ME.
LOOK, I'M SORRY ABOUT BEFORE.
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
YOU WIN.
I'VE HEARD THAT BEFORE.
ELI:
THIS TIME I'M SERIOUS.
FITZ:
SO AM I.
YOU'VE HAD THIS COMING
FOR A WHILE.
WHAT'S WRONG, EMO BOY?
OUT OF SMART ASS COMMENTS?
ELI:
PLEASE DON'T,
DON'T DO THIS.
SOMEONE'S GOTTA SHUT YOU UP.
ELI: FITZ, NO!
CLARE: (SCREAMS)
(GASPS)
(RELIEVED SIGH)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
FITZ:
DON'T WORRY, YOU CAN BLEACH OUT
URINE STAINS.
POLICE OFFICER:
HANDS UP!
NOBODY MOVE.
(RELIEVED SIGH)
(POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
I AM SO DISAPPOINTED IN YOU.
NOTHING HAPPENED!
AUDRA: ONLY BECAUSE I SHOWED UP
BEFORE SHE COULD DO
ANYTHING TO YOU!
NOW, WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU,
YOUNG LADY?
TRADING FAVOURS
LIKE SOME COMMON WHORE!
WHAT?
I DIDN'T EVEN-
MOM, IT'S NOT HER FAULT!
PLEASE,
DON'T DEFEND HER, OKAY?
GO FIND ADAM,
WE NEED TO GO HOME.
GO!
(DISGUSTED SIGH)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
MR. SIMPSON:
LOCKDOWN'S OVER,
EVERYONE GO HOME.
COME ON!
WHEN I WAS NINE,
THERE WAS THIS KID, MIKE.
HIS HOBBY WAS BEATING ME UP.
DIDN'T MATTER HOW FAST I RAN,
HE WAS ALWAYS FASTER.
(SIRENS WAIL)
YOU'RE NOT NINE ANYMORE.
WELL, NEITHER ARE THE BULLIES,
SO WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
CLARE:
I DON'T HAVE THE ANSWER.
BUT IF IT'S THIS,
THEN I CAN'T BE WITH YOU.
(CAR DOORS SLAM)
IS SOMEONE GOING TO EXPLAIN
WHAT HAPPENED?
(SIGHS)
FITZ WAS GONNA FIGHT
SOME KIDS AT SCHOOL.
SO TO STOP IT,
I SET OFF THE STINK BOMB.
WHEN YOU STARTED QUESTIONING
PEOPLE I PANICKED-
SO, I BLAMED FITZ.
GUESS HE GOT MAD AND DECIDED
TO TEACH ME A LESSON.
SO YOU LIED TO ME?
YES, SIR.
WELL, THERE WILL BE
CONSEQUENCES.
FEMALE COP:
EXCUSE ME, SIR.
I FOUND THIS ONE STRIPPING
IN AN EMPTY CLASSROOM.
MR. SIMPSON,
I AM SO, SO SORRY.
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR IT!
I TRUSTED YOU.
ALL OF YOU.
AND I'VE NEVER BEEN
SO DISAPPOINTED IN MY LIFE.
HOLLY J:
WE DIDN'T MEAN FOR
ANY OF THIS TO HAPPEN.
YEAH, THERE MUST BE SOMETHING
WE CAN DO TO MAKE IT BETTER.
NO, IT'S TOO LATE.
THERE'S GONNA BE CHANGES.
BIG CHANGES.
WHEN YOU ALL GET BACK
FROM BREAK,
YOU WON'T RECOGNIZE
THIS SCHOOL AT ALL.
(POLICE RADIO CHATTER)