(STUDENTS CHATTER)
CLARE:
I LOOK LIKE
BARNEY THE DINOSAUR!
ALLI:
I THOUGHT YOU'D LIKE
THE UNIFORM.
(SCOFFS) BESIDES,
ISN'T THE NEW ATTIRE
COURTESY OF YOUR LITTLE
GANG WAR?
WHY WON'T IT OPEN?
ELI'S FIGHT WITH FITZ?
MAYBE,
BUT I BET IT DIDN'T HELP
WHEN YOU GOT CAUGHT
IN THE BOILER ROOM!
I TOLD YOU NOTHING HAPPENED
IN THERE.
I WENT IN WITH OWEN
TO MAKE DREW JEALOUS,
SO I DON'T NEED ANYONE THINKING
SOMETHING DID HAPPEN!
(METAL DETECTOR WHINES)
CLARE:
METAL DETECTORS?! POLICE?!
PLEASE!
WHO KNOWS IF WE'LL EVEN BE
ALLOWED TO THINK
AT THIS NEW DEGRASSI!
OH, NO.
YOU DIDN'T THINK
HE'D DISAPPEAR?
(SIGHS) SPENT ALL BREAK
HOPING HE WOULD.
HOW CAN YOU MISS SOMEONE,
AND WANT TO TEAR
THEIR ORGANS OUT?
STAY STRONG.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
DREW:
HEY.
(SIGHS)
I SPENT A LOT OF TIME
THINKING ABOUT US
OVER THE BREAK.
YEAH? ME TOO.
REALLY? THAT'S-THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'S REALLY GOOD.
IS THERE ANY CHANCE
YOU THOUGHT ABOUT US
GETTING BACK TOGETHER?
AND I REALIZED IT WOULD BE
THE BIGGEST MISTAKE OF MY LIFE.
TWO WEEKS,
AND YOU'RE STILL MAD?
YOU CHEATED,
THEN LIED ABOUT IT!
I TOLD YOU,
IT WASN'T MY FAULT.
BIANCA THREW HERSELF AT ME,
AND SHE KEPT ON SENDING ME
THESE SEXY PHOTOS!
(SIGHS)
SO THAT'S IT?
NO SECOND CHANCE?
YOU LET BIANCA TREAT
YOUR BODY
LIKE HER OWN PERSONAL
AMUSEMENT PARK!
SO, NO.
ONE STRIKE,
AND YOU'RE OUT.
(GASPS)
(SIGHS DISGUSTEDLY)
COME ON, CLARE,
LET'S MOVE ON.
IT'S TIME FOR
MY FRESH START!
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever, Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
(METAL DETECTOR BEEPS)
MR. SIMPSON:
BACKPACKS STAY IN YOUR LOCKERS,
PEOPLE!
YOU ALL GOT THE LETTER HOME!
HOLLY J:
SIR! UH, AGAIN,
WE ARE SO SORRY
ABOUT OUR BEHAVIOUR
AT "A NIGHT IN VEGAS."
YEAH, IT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
AT LEAST,
NOT AT SCHOOL.
MR. SIMPSON:
YOU'RE LUCKY STUDENT COUNCIL
ISN'T CANCELED.
BUT I THINK YOU CAN HELP
BY SETTING A POSITIVE EXAMPLE,
STARTING BY READING
THE NEW RULES.
OKAY? READY?
CHANGES ARE AFOOT, DEGRASSI.
THE NEW DRESS CODE
MUST BE FOLLOWED AT ALL TIMES.
HOLLY J:
PHOTO ID WILL BE DISTRIBUTED
BY YOUR HOMEROOM TEACHERS
AND MUST BE VISIBLE
AT ALL TIMES.
SAV:
NO PUBLIC DISPLAYS
OF AFFECTION
AND NO STUDENTS WILL BE
ALLOWED IN CLASSROOMS
WITHOUT SUPERVISION.
HOLLY J:
MOST IMPORTANT,
THE FOLLOWING OFFENSES
MAY FIND YOU EXPELLED:
VIOLENCE,
CARRYING A WEAPON,
SEXUAL CONDUCT AT SCHOOL,
TRANSMITTING SEXUAL IMAGES
TO OTHER STUDENTS...
THIS IS RIDICULOUS!
WE'RE LIVING IN A POLICE STATE!
MAYBE, BUT...
I CAN WEAR THE SAME CLOTHES HERE
AS AT HOME,
NO MORE STUPID SECRET BOYFRIEND
TO CHEAT ON ME,
AND NO LYING TO PARENTS.
CLARE, I CAN STOP LIVING
A DOUBLE LIFE!
WELL, WHAT DOES YOUR SEMESTER
LOOK LIKE?
OTHER THAN PLAYING
KISSY KISSY WITH ELI?
AFTER ELI'S SUSPENSION
IS OVER,
I'LL BE QUESTIONING
MY SANITY
FOR BEING WITH HIM.
AND I'LL BE BUSY.
WELL,
I WANNA REINVENT MYSELF -
PUT MY ENERGY
INTO SOMETHING POSITIVE,
NOW THAT I'M BOYFRIEND FREE.
AND THINK I'VE FOUND
MY NEW CALLING.
(JENNA STRUMS GUITAR)
JENNA: (SINGING)
♪ INDEPENDENCE IS ALL I NEED ♪
♪ I COULD BE YOUR HERO ♪
♪ SHINING STAR ♪
♪ ALL I EVER WANTED WAS FOR US
TO MAKE IT FAR ♪
♪ INDEPENDENCE IS ALL I NEED ♪
MEG:
GOOD JOB, JENNA.
STAY FOR LIGHTING CUES
FOR A SEC.
STANDBY, HAYLEY!
(WORKERS CHATTER BACKSTAGE)
HAYLEY:
OH, MY TURN NEXT?
I WAS HOPING YOU'D MESS UP
SO I'D HAVE MORE TIME
BEFORE MY REHEARSAL.
(LAUGHS ARTIFICIALLY)
OH, I'M KIDDING.
WELL, GOOD LUCK.
IT'S HOT UNDER THE LIGHTS!
WHY DON'T YOU LOSE
THE SWEATSHIRT?
UM...
CAN'T.
NOTHING UNDERNEATH.
SOME VOTERS MIGHT
LIKE THAT, THOUGH.
WELL, WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO GET MORE VOTES, RIGHT?
WELL, MY WHOLE HIGH SCHOOL
IS VOTING FOR ME,
SO I'M PRETTY LUCKY.
HMM, GOOD FOR YOU!
YEAH, MY TWITTER FEED
HAS LIKE, 32,000 FOLLOWERS.
32,000?
YEAH. HOPEFULLY IT'LL BE
HIGHER NEXT WEEK.
I HAVE BEEN WORKING
NIGHT AND DAY
TO BUILD MY BRAND.
UH, OH, RIGHT.
BRAND...
TOTALLY!
I'M SURE YOUR PEOPLE
ARE ALL OVER THAT.
YOU HAVE PEOPLE?
YEAH, MY AGENT
AND MY MANAGER.
MEG:
OKAY!
THANKS, JENNA!
WE'LL SEE YOU AT YOUR SCHOOL.
MY SCHOOL?
SURE, TO SHOW
A BUDDING STAR
IN HER NATURAL HABITAT.
LET'S MOVE ON TO HAYLEY'S
REHEARSAL, PEOPLE!
HEY, YOU WANT A TIP?
WINNING "NEXT TEEN STAR,"
IT'S NOT ABOUT
THE SINGING.
HAYLEY:
CHECK!
CHECK, ONE, TWO!
YEAH, YEAH.
YEP, THAT'S GOOD RIGHT THERE.
(SIGHS)
(BELL RINGS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY WE CAN'T COMPETE!
SCIENCE OLYMPICS IS ONE
OF THE ONLY CLUBS LEFT!
HEATHER POULETTE'S GOT
THE MUMPS.
EPIDEMIC PAROTITIS!
CORRECT!
BUT SHE'S OUT FOR A WEEK
AND WE NEED FOUR
TO BE ELIGIBLE
FOR WEDNESDAY'S MATCH
AGAINST BARDELL.
WHO'S LAME ENOUGH TO BE
ON THE SCIENCE OLYMPICS?
I MEAN, BESIDES US?
IS THIS THE SCIENCE
OLYMPICS TEAM?
WESLEY:
ALL 6.7 TIMES 10
TO THE 27TH ATOMS OF US!
ANY CHANCE YOU HAVE ROOM
FOR ONE MORE?
CONNOR:
NEXT ASK FOR A MILLION DOLLARS!
SINCE WHEN DO YOU CARE
ABOUT SCIENCE,
MS. DANCE TEAM?
HEY, WHEN YOU WERE LEARNING
HOW TO RIDE A BIKE,
MY DAD WAS DRILLING ME
WITH PHYSICS QUIZ CARDS.
NEWTON'S SECOND LAW
OF MOTION?
NET FORCE EQUALS MASS
TIMES ACCELERATION.
NAME ONE GAS HEAVIER
THAN AIR.
BUTANE.
CONNER: HEAVIEST ELEMENT?
ALLI: OSMIUM...
BY DENSITY.
BUT, BY ATOMIC WEIGHT,
UNUNOCTIUM!
WHOA!
I MEAN,
WE KNEW YOU WERE SMART,
BUT WE THOUGHT YOU'D BE
TOO COOL FOR OUR SQUAD.
YOUR SQUAD IS EXACTLY
WHAT I NEED RIGHT NOW.
SO, AM I IN?
MR. BETENKAMP:
WELCOME TO THE TEAM!
(BELL DINGS REPEATEDLY)
JENNA:
ALL RIGHT,
THIS IS DEGRASSI,
A GREAT SCHOOL,
AND I'M TOTALLY LUCKY
'CAUSE EVERYONE HERE
IS VOTING FOR ME!
MEG:
LET'S GO INSIDE!
OH, YOU CAN'T ACTUALLY
GO INSIDE THOUGH.
MY DRACONIAN PRINCIPAL
HAS JUST OUTLAWED ANYTHING FUN.
(LAUGHS AWKWARDLY)
SO, WHAT'S IT BEEN LIKE
TO BE A "NEXT TEEN STAR"?
HARD? INTENSE?
IT'S BEEN GREAT!
MY FRIENDS ARE AWESOME,
THEY TOTALLY SUPPORT ME.
WHAT ABOUT PRESSURE
ON YOUR FAMILY?
MY BROTHER SUPPORTS ME
A HUNDRED PERCENT!
ISN'T IT TRUE THAT YOUR DAD
IS AWAY AN AWFUL LOT?
WELL, HE'S A TRUCK DRIVER,
BUT HE WATCHES THE SHOW
AT TRUCK STOPS!
(FRUSTRATED SIGH)
YOUR COMPETITION,
HAYLEY,
SANG AT A FUNDRAISER
FOR HER BROTHER
WITH CYSTIC FIBROSIS.
THAT'S A STORY!
WHEN PEOPLE HEAR
THE NAME JENNA MIDDLETON,
WHAT DO THEY THINK?
SHE'S A GIRL WHO SINGS
GREAT SONGS?
(SCOFFS) THERE ARE A MILLION
CUTE BLONDES
WHO CAN HIT ALL THE NOTES.
YOU NEED A HOOK!
A SECRET SHAME.
WHAT MAKES JENNA SPECIAL?
COME ON,
THERE'S GOTTA BE SOMETHING!
NO?
FINE. UM, IS THERE A FRIEND
WE CAN INTERVIEW?
UM, SURE.
UH... OH! CHANTAY!
CAN YOU COME TELL THE CAMERA
SOMETHING ABOUT ME?
UH... HMM!
YOU BET I CAN!
JENNA: PERFECT.
CHANTAY: YOU ROLLING?
JENNA'S ALWAYS SPARKLY
AND HAPPY,
SHE NEVER HAS ANY PROBLEMS,
SHE'S THE PEPPIEST ONE
ON THE POWER SQUAD.
THAT'S...GREAT.
UH, DON'T YOU WANT
TO ASK MORE?
WE'VE GOT EVERYTHING
WE NEED.
WE'LL SEE WHAT THE VOTERS
THINK TONIGHT!
ALLI:
ANIMALIA, PROTISTA,
ARCHAEA, FUNGI,
PLANTAE,
AND BACTERIA.
THAT'S RIGHT.
PERFECT ROUND!
GUYS, WE STILL HAVE
TO FIGURE OUT WHO'S CAPTAIN.
ADAM:
HEY, DON'T LOOK AT ME.
I DON'T NEED MORE EYES ON ME
THAN NECESSARY.
I DON'T LIKE ATTENTION,
SO, UM...
IT HAS TO BE ALLI.
(GASPS) THANKS, GUYS.
I WILL NOT LET YOU DOWN.
WE ARE SO GOING
TO CREAM BARDELL!
CONNOR AND WESLEY:
YES!
GOOD WORK.
DREW WAS RIGHT.
YOU ARE AWESOME.
(GASPS)
MAJOR FAUX PAS -
MENTIONING HE WHO
SHOULD NOT BE NAMED.
I KNOW WHAT HAPPENED
IN THE BOILER ROOM.
NOTHING!
I MEANT WITH DREW
AND BIANCA.
ALL BREAK I LISTENED
TO HIM CRY
ABOUT HOW HE MESSED UP
THE BEST RELATIONSHIP
HE EVER HAD.
HE CRIED?
ADAM:
NEVER SEEN HIM
SO MESSED UP ABOUT A GIRL.
HE MADE US WALK BY YOUR HOUSE
LIKE A MILLION TIMES.
HE DID?
BUT DON'T WORRY,
I WON'T MENTION HIM AGAIN.
WELL, GOOD.
BECAUSE WHAT YOUR BROTHER
DID WAS WRONG.
REALLY WRONG.
MY LIPS ARE SEALED.
(RELIEVED SIGH)
(CROWD CHEERS)
(APPLAUSE)
HOST:
YES, YES!
WE'VE SEEN VIDEO
OF OUR CONTESTANTS' HOME LIVES.
WE'VE SEEN GREGOR,
WHOSE SINGING HAS HELPED
SUPPORT HIS FAMILY,
HAYLEY, WHO'S DETERMINED
TO HELP HER VERY ILL BROTHER,
AND JENNA,
WHO'S ALWAYS LOOKING
ON THE BRIGHT SIDE.
BUT WE NEVER STAY HAPPY
FOR LONG,
HERE ON "NEXT TEEN STAR."
IT'S TIME TO NAME
OUR BOTTOM TWO!
(DRUM ROLL)
(CONTESTANT SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
JENNA,
ANNIE,
PLEASE COME AND JOIN ME.
AUDIENCE MEMBERS:
OH, NO! BOO!
WOMAN:
WE LOVE YOU, JENNA!
WE LOVE YOU!
LADIES.
ANNIE, YOU'VE TOUCHED
OUR HEARTS
WHEN YOU SHARED YOUR STRUGGLES
WITH EPILEPSY.
JENNA,
ANY WORDS FOR THE VOTERS?
I JUST SANG MY HEART OUT.
I HOPE THAT'S ENOUGH.
AND YET IT ALL COMES DOWN
TO THIS...
AND OUR CLOSEST VOTE EVER!
JENNA,
YOU...
WILL HAVE TO WORK HARD
TO IMPRESS THE JUDGES TOMORROW,
YOU'RE SAFE FOR ANOTHER DAY!
ANNIE, I'M SORRY.
(CROWD CHEERS)
CATCH ALL THE ACTION TOMORROW
ON "NEXT TEEN STAR"!
(CROWD CHEERS)
YOU'RE GONE AT THE NEXT VOTE.
NOT IF I CAN HELP IT.
(LAUGHS ARTIFICIALLY)
(BELL RINGS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
ALLI:
THEN ADAM TOLD ME DREW SPENT
THE WHOLE BREAK IN TEARS.
SERVES HIM RIGHT!
YEAH, TOTALLY.
(SIGHS)
NO! DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE
GIVING HIM ANOTHER CHANCE!
WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR FRESH START?
(SIGHS) WELL, CAN'T I STILL
HAVE THAT WITH DREW?
I MEAN, YOUR BOYFRIEND
GOT INTO A KNIFE FIGHT
AND YOU'RE STILL WITH HIM.
IT WASN'T ELI'S FAULT;
FITZ STARTED IT.
AND DREW WOULDN'T
HAVE CHEATED,
IF BIANCA HADN'T
PROPOSITIONED HIM!
NOT SURE THAT'S
THE SAME THING.
(SCOFFS) DREW AND I HAD
A GOOD THING
BEFORE BIANCA RUINED IT
AND I WANT IT BACK!
I GOT YOUR TEXT.
YOU WANTED TO TALK?
MR. SIMPSON: (ON PA)
ALLI BHANDARI, PLEASE REPORT
TO THE PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE.
I GUESS
IT'LL HAVE TO WAIT.
IS THIS ABOUT
THE SCIENCE OLYMPICS?
ACTUALLY, NO.
UM, YOU HAVE BEEN SELECTED
FOR A SELF-ESTEEM SEMINAR.
WHY?
SOME STUDENTS HAVE BEEN
IDENTIFIED IN NEED
OF SELF-ESTEEM BUILDING.
THIS IS NOT A PUNISHMENT,
IT IS IF I DON'T KNOW
WHY I'M GOING.
WELL, APPARENTLY,
DURING VEGAS NIGHT,
SOME STUDENTS WERE ENGAGED
IN SEX ACTS.
YOUR NAME WAS MENTIONED.
WE HAVE NO PROOF-
I DIDN'T DO THAT, SIR,
I SWEAR!
THE DETAILS ARE IRRELEVANT.
THE POINT IS THAT WE HELP
THOSE WHO NEED THE SUPPORT.
MM, LOOK AT IT AS A CHANCE
TO START OVER.
SEE IF YOU CAN LEARN SOMETHING.
I DON'T BELONG IN THAT GROUP!
I ALREADY KNOW THAT!
(EXASPERATED SIGH)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
I SPENT ALL NIGHT
THINKING ABOUT YOU.
I WISH I COULD'VE
CALLED.
CAN YOU IMAGINE?
(IMITATING HER MOTHER)
ALLIA, WHO IS THIS DREW BOY
THAT IS CALLING YOU?
HE WILL ONLY WANT
TO BE TAKING ADVANTAGE!
(LAUGHS)
SO, DOES THIS MEAN
I'M FORGIVEN?
LET'S SAY
YOU'RE ON PROBATION.
BUT IF I CATCH YOU FLIRTING
WITH ANOTHER GIRL,
EVEN A LITTLE-
AND RISK LOSING YOU
AGAIN?
NEVER.
SO DOES THAT GUY
ON PROBATION
GET TO TAKE
A GIRLFRIEND OUT TONIGHT?
MAYBE WE CAN CATCH A MOVIE
AFTER THAT SELF-ESTEEM SEMINAR.
WHAT SELF-ESTEEM SEMINAR?
YOU KNOW,
THE ONE FOR ALL THE KIDS
ASSOCIATED WITH "BOILER-GATE"?
OH, COME ON, DON'T TELL ME
YOU ESCAPED THE LIST!
BIANCA:
ACTUALLY, THE EVENT'S
FOR LADIES ONLY.
NICE TO SEE YOU TWO
PATCHED THINGS UP.
MUST BE TRUE LOVE.
HMPH!
ALLI, DON'T LET HER
GET TO YOU!
SHE'S DONE ENOUGH TO US.
HOLLY J: (ON PA)
RUNNING OUT OF CLEAN
GOLF SHIRTS?
IT'S NOT TOO LATE
TO BUY EXTRAS!
PICK THEM UP
IN THE ADMIN. OFFICE.
DO YOU WANT TO BORROW
MY HOODIE?
OH! IT SAYS DEGRASSI,
RIGHT?
YEAH, CLOSE ENOUGH
TO DRESS CODE.
OH, THANKS.
I'M GETTING WAY BIGGER.
YOU HID IT OKAY
BEHIND YOUR GUITAR
ON TV LAST NIGHT.
YOU SAW THE SHOW?
THAT'S NICE.
MY MOM WATCHES.
SHE'S PROUD OF YOU.
(LAUGHS UNEASILY)
'TIL SHE FINDS OUT I'M PREGNANT.
YEAH.
IT'S GETTING HARDER
TO KEEP IT A SECRET,
AS YOU CAN SEE.
JUST LET ME TELL MY MOM FIRST,
OKAY?
WELL, WERE YOU PLANNING ON IT
THIS YEAR?
I'LL DO IT WHEN I DO IT.
YOU'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME,
KC!
(SCOFFS)
CLARE:
SO BOYS DON'T HAVE TO GO
TO THE SELF-ESTEEM SEMINAR?
ALLI:
NO, IT'S JUST FOR STUPID GIRLS
LIKE BIANCA,
WHO DON'T LIKE THEMSELVES!
THAT IS SUCH
A DOUBLE STANDARD!
TELL ME ABOUT IT!
HOW COULD SIMPSON LUMP ME
INTO THAT GROUP OF SKANKS,
WHEN I DIDN'T EVEN
DO ANYTHING?
IT DOESN'T BOTHER YOU
THAT BOYS DON'T HAVE TO GO?
YEAH, SURE, WHATEVER.
MAYBE I'LL JUST SKIP
THE SEMINAR.
I MEAN,
I DON'T EVEN BELONG THERE!
NO, THAT'LL ONLY MAKE
THINGS WORSE.
JUST GO. IT'S THE PATH
OF LEAST RESISTANCE.
AND IN A WEEK,
THIS ALL BLOWS OVER.
CHANTAY:
APPARENTLY I HAVE
BOILER ROOM BHANDARI TO THANK
FOR MY HIDEOUS
NOT-MY-COLOUR SHIRT.
THEY JUST NEED SOMEONE
TO BLAME.
(SIGHS)
CHANTAY:
GOOD! YOU'RE BY YOURSELF.
SO, TALK TO ME
ABOUT THE SHOW!
UH, BOTTOM TWO,
REMEMBER?
BUT YOU'RE NOT OUT YET,
THOUGH.
YOU WANT TO WIN,
DON'T YOU?
OF COURSE!
(SCOFFS)
IT JUST SEEMS HOPELESS.
KNOW WHAT'S NOT GONNA WORK?
THE ATTITUDE.
WHERE'S SUNNY JENNA?
SHE'S THE ONE
WHO ALMOST GOT VOTED OUT!
I WAS UP ALL NIGHT
PRACTICING MY SONG,
BUT IT'S NOT GOOD ENOUGH!
HONESTLY, I TOTALLY WANT YOU
TO WIN,
BUT YOU COME OFF
A LITTLE BLAND.
BLAND?
I'M JUST BEING MYSELF!
EVEN THE GIRL WHO LOST
LAST NIGHT
HAD THE EPILEPSY STORY!
YOU MUST HAVE SOME SORT
OF DRAMA
TO GET PEOPLE INTERESTED.
(SIGHS)
BUT HOW WOULD DRAMA HELP?
GOSSIP IS GOSSIP!
PEOPLE WANT TO SEE
HOW IT GOES,
GOOD OR BAD!
(BELL RINGS)
MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT.
HAVE I EVER BEEN WRONG?
(LAUGHS)
ALLI:
ALL RIGHT!
LET'S GET DOWN TO SCIENCE!
WHAT'S WRONG?
DID YOU REALLY DO THOSE THINGS
IN THE BOILER ROOM?
YOU KNOW ABOUT THAT?
E-EVERYONE DOES.
HOW DOES EVERYONE KNOW?
I'VE GOT TO CLEAR MY NAME!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(PHONE BUTTONS BEEP)
(CLEARS THROAT)
HI, MEG?
UM...I HAVE SOMETHING
I THINK
OUR VIEWERS WILL WANT TO KNOW.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
YEAH.
RACHEL:
I'M SURE YOU'VE ALL HEARD
THAT BUILDING SELF-ESTEEM
IS THE KEY TO A HAPPY
AND SUCCESSFUL LIFE.
BUT STUDY AFTER STUDY SHOWS
THAT MANY GIRLS
ARE AT CRISIS LEVELS.
BIANCA:
RACHEL?
THAT'S GREAT,
BUT WHY ARE WE HERE?
SOMETIMES GIRLS TURN BOYS
AND SEX
INTO A COMPETITION,
AND RUMOURS CAN TAKE OVER
GIRLS' LIVES.
I WANT YOU TO RISE
ABOVE THOSE RUMOURS.
IF YOU COULD DO ONE THING
IN YOUR LIVES,
WHEN YOU GROW UP,
WHAT WOULD IT BE?
BIANCA?
ALLI:
STEAL HUSBANDS?
YOU KNOW, ONCE SHE GRADUATES
FROM STEALING BOYFRIENDS!
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO TOOK BACK A CHEATER.
MISS, IF YOU WANNA TALK
LOW SELF-ESTEEM,
ALLI'S YOUR GIRL.
YEAH, WELL,
I'M NOT THE ONE
HOOKING UP WITH RANDOM GUYS
JUST TO MAKE MYSELF
FEEL VALUABLE!
WHATEVER.
GIRLS, REMEMBER,
IT'S A SAFE SPACE.
(SIGHS ANGRILY)
OKAY. NOW, BIANCA?
WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE TO DO
WHEN YOU GROW UP?
I DON'T KNOW,
LIKE...
DESIGN JEWELRY.
(SNORTS)
AND WHAT'S YOUR DREAM?
TO GET OUT OF HERE.
RACHEL: HIGH SCHOOL?
ALLI: NO, THIS LECTURE!
I DON'T BELONG HERE!
TELL ME WHAT YOU'RE FEELING.
NOTHING'S OFF LIMITS.
WELL, FOR STARTERS,
I AM NOT A SLUT!
IT'S ALL HER FAULT
THAT I'M HERE!
NO, WAY!
SHE TOOK MY BOYFRIEND
TO THE BOILER ROOM!
I JUST TRIED
TO MAKE HIM JEALOUS
AND NOW I'M IN SOME
SKANK SEMINAR?!
IF I COULD SMACK YOU
IN THE MOUTH RIGHT NOW,
I WOULD, BHANDARI!
IF I DIDN'T THINK
IT WOULD RISK YOUR INCOME,
I'D SMACK YOU IN YOURS!
I HAVE NEVER ACCEPTED MONEY
FOR MY SERVICES.
(LAUGHS DISBELIEVINGLY)
RACHEL:
THIS IS EXACTLY THE PROBLEM.
WE CAN'T BUILD RESPECT
UNTIL WE STOP DEGRADING
EACH OTHER.
I KNOW YOU DON'T BELIEVE ME,
BUT WE'RE GOING TO FIND
SOME COMMON GROUND.
WHY DON'T WE... (SIGHS)
TAKE FIVE AND REGROUP.
BIANCA:
FINE!
(RUMMAGING)
BULL'S EYE!
WHY DO PEOPLE INSIST
ON TAKING
NAKED PHOTOS OF THEMSELVES?
(LAUGHS HUMOURLESSLY)
FORWARD TO...
(PHONE CHIMES)
EVERYONE!
(LAUGHS)
(JENNA PLAYS GUITAR)
JENNA: (SINGING)
♪ OOH... ♪
♪ DREAM BIG ♪
♪ AND LIVE YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ EVERYTHING'S NOT
WHAT IT SEEMS ♪
♪ THIS IS JUST WHERE
YOU'RE AT NOW ♪
♪ DREAM BIG ♪
♪ BELIEVE AND TRY ♪
♪ YOU'VE FAILED IN LIFE ♪
♪ AND WITH THAT GUY ♪
♪ WHO MADE YOU FEEL ♪
♪ ON TOP OF THE WORLD ♪
♪ AND IF HE CHANGED HIS MIND ♪
♪ LIKE THE BLINK OF AN EYE ♪
♪ YOU'LL STILL BE ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ BUT IT TAKES TIME... ♪
♪ OH, OH... ♪
OH MAN,
PEPPER-FRIED STEAKBURGERS!
ARE YOU SURE
WE CAN AFFORD THIS?
WELL, WE SAVED HARD
ALL WEEK,
AND, UH,
YOU DIDN'T GET MAD AT ME
WHEN I BURNT THE SPAGHETTI
ON MONDAY.
AND TUESDAY.
(SIGHS)
DEFINITELY NOT A CHEF
IN MY FORMER LIFE.
AHH!
THERE'S JENNA!
(JENNA SINGING)
WHY DID YOU GUYS
BREAK UP AGAIN?
YOU KNOW, STUFF.
OH RIGHT, STUFF.
(TEASINGLY) YES.
STUFF CAN REALLY...
CAUSE PROBLEMS.
OKAY, I GET IT.
I'M YOUR MOM,
NOT YOUR BUD.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO TELL ME.
THERE WAS JUST THIS...
THIS SITUATION
AND WE DIDN'T AGREE
ON HOW TO HANDLE IT.
OH.
WELL,
IT MUST'VE BEEN BAD
'CAUSE SHE LOOKS GREAT
UP THERE.
HOST:
WHOO!
VERY NICE!
GIVE IT UP FOR JENNA!
FABULOUS!
YOU'VE HAD A LOT ON YOUR MIND
THIS PAST WEEK,
AND I HEAR THERE'S SOMETHING
YOU'D LIKE TO SHARE.
JENNA:
YEAH. UH...
I'VE BEEN KEEPING A SECRET.
HOST:
A SECRET!
LIKE A LONG-LOST SISTER?
JENNA:
UH, NOT EXACTLY.
HOST:
WELL, COME ON,
WE'RE ALL WAITING
ON PINS AND NEEDLES!
MAN IN TV AUDIENCE:
COME ON, JENNA!
HOST:
WELL, GO AHEAD.
TELL THE WORLD!
OKAY. UH...
I'M GOING TO HAVE A BABY.
(TV AUDIENCE GASPS)
SHE'S PREGNANT?
HOST:
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
JENNA IS GONNA HAVE A BABY!
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDS)
LISA:
OH MY GOD!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
IT'S YOURS, ISN'T IT?
KC?
YEAH. I GUESS.
YOU GUESS?
IT'S MINE!
(SIGHS)
SO WHY AM I FINDING OUT
ABOUT THIS ON TV?
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
I WAS GOING TO...
BUT?
I DON'T WANT IT!
HOST:
THAT WAS EXTREMELY BRAVE OF YOU
TO TELL THE WORLD LIKE THAT.
EXTREMELY BRAVE.
WELL, I HOPE EVERYONE ELSE
THINKS SO TOO.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDS)