♪♪♪
♪ I guess I'll confide now ♪
♪ Too tired to hide how hard
I fell for you ♪
(CELL PHONE KEYS BEEP)
HEY, ROCK STAR.
WALK ME TO CLASS?
TINSLEY.
I'VE HEARD ABOUT YOU.
WOW, I'M FAMOUS.
AND YET YOU'RE HERE
LOOKING FOR A FRIEND.
(DISMISSIVE LAUGH)
YOU'RE FRESH MEAT.
EVERYONE'S TALKING
ABOUT THE COYNES.
I JUST WANTED TO SEE WHAT
ALL THE FUSS WAS ABOUT.
WELL, WE COYNES AREN'T
AS INTERESTING AS YOU THINK.
REALLY?
THEN WHAT'S YOUR SISTER
DOING UP ON THE ROOF?
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(CELL PHONE BEEPS ON)
DECLAN:
UP ON THE ROOF AGAIN, FI?
I THOUGHT WE WERE DONE
WITH THE THEATRICS.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
IT'S BOBBY.
HE'S NOT VERY NICE.
I TOLD YOU
HE WAS A PLAYER.
FIONA:
WELL, IT'S NOT JUST THAT.
HE HURT ME.
ON THE STAIRS.
ARE YOU SURE?
WHAT, YOU THINK
I'D LIE ABOUT THAT?
OF COURSE NOT.
FIONA:
ALL I WANTED WAS
A NORMAL YEAR.
DECLAN:
YOU WANT ME TO TALK TO HIM?
WE CAN'T LET HIM GET
AWAY WITH THIS, FIONA.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
NO, I'LL DEAL WITH IT.
OKAY.
I JUST NEED YOU TO DO
ONE THING FIRST.
WHAT?
DECLAN:
GET OFF THE ROOF.
(SIGHS)
(CELL PHONE BEEPS OFF)
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, whatever ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(CELL PHONE KEYS BEEP)
♪ I know it's not
your fight to win ♪
♪ It's mine to lose
or watch unfold ♪
♪ It's all I can do to keep
my head on straight ♪
♪ Why is it me
against the world? ♪
(CELL PHONE KEYS BEEP)
(CAMERA CLICKS)
♪ Why do you feel the need
to help me ♪
♪ When you know
I'm better off alone? ♪
♪ I didn't know what
I was thinking... ♪
BOBBY:
HEY!
YOU SEE THIS CRAP?
DID YOU DO THIS
TO MY SISTER?
YOUR SISTER IS A NUTJOB!
THIS IS ALL OVER TWITTER!
IT'S FAKE!
WHY SHOULD I BELIEVE YOU,
HUH?!
LOOK, SHE SAW TINSLEY
FLIRTING WITH ME,
AND YOU KNOW WHAT
TINSLEY'S LIKE,
AND SHE LOST IT!
(CELL PHONE KEYS BEEP)
YOU OF ALL PEOPLE
SHOULD KNOW
SHE'D DO ANYTHING
TO GET HER WAY.
TELL HER SHE GOT
HER WISH.
WE'RE DONE!
(CAR DOOR OPENING)
(CAR DOOR CLOSING)
(CAR ACCELERATING AWAY)
FIONA:
OH, HE WAS PISSED!
WHERE'S YOUR BLACK EYE?
LOOK.
IS THAT THE SAME EYE
AS IN THE PICTURE?
THERE'S HARDLY A BRUISE.
SO I ENHANCED
IT A TEENY BIT.
THE MAGIC OF HOLLYWOOD.
YOU JUST TRASHED A GUY'S
REPUTATION, FIONA!
I JUST SHOWED EVERYONE WHO
THE REAL BOBBY BECKONRIDGE IS!
WHAT?
YOU THINK I'M LYING?!
HOW MANY SCHOOLS ARE YOU GONNA
TURN INTO NIGHTMARES FOR US
BEFORE YOU LEARN?
DECLAN!
TAKE THE PICTURES DOWN!
CLARE:
SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
THAT IF SAV WINS
THE PRESIDENCY,
MY PARENTS WILL EXPECT
ME TO SOLVE WORLD HUNGER!
NO PRESSURE.
UH, NO, I MEANT OF ME,
SANS GLASSES.
OKAY WOW!
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN HIDING
THOSE BIG BLUE EYES?
RIGHT? NOW EVERYONE'S GONNA
GET TO SEE THEM ALL THE TIME!
WELL, IT'S ABOUT TIME
YOU GOT CONTACTS.
EVEN BETTER?
TOMORROW I'M GETTING SURGERY.
ALLI:
REALLY? AREN'T YOU
TOO YOUNG FOR THAT?
WELL, I'M GONNA BE PART
OF A STUDY.
THEY HAVEN'T CHANGED
IN TWO YEARS,
SO THEY CAN MAKE
AN EXCEPTION.
THAT'S AMAZING!
YOU'RE GONNA BE
A WHOLE NEW CLARE.
MY PARENTS THINK IT'LL HELP
WITH MY CONFIDENCE,
LIKE I NEED THE HELP.
WILL IT HURT?
UH, THEY'LL BE SORE,
BUT I'LL BE BACK HERE
THE NEXT DAY.
WELL, BETWEEN THAT
AND YOUR NEW HAIR,
YOU'LL HAVE GUYS
FIGHTING OVER YOU.
ALLI AND CLARE:
(LAUGH)
SAV:
HEY, COME BACK TOMORROW.
I'M UNLEASHING
THE HOLOGRAPHIC BUTTONS,
LIMITED EDITION.
THANK YOU.
DREW:
HEY, MAN, NEED ANY HELP?
SAV:
YEAH, YEAH, SURE!
GRAB A SHIRT.
OH, AND HEY,
I STILL OWE YOU THAT COFFEE.
AW, FORGET IT.
ANYTHING FOR THE NEXT PREZ.
IS IT MY POLICY
ON TACO TUESDAYS OR-?
DUDE, I LOVE TACOS.
YOU KNOW, A LOT OF TEEN DADS
WOULD JUST BOLT,
BUT NOT YOU.
HOW DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT THE BABY?
SOME DORKS IN THE COMPUTER LAB
HAD IT UP ON SOME BLOG.
I-I THOUGHT-
I THOUGHT EVERYONE KNEW.
YEAH, THEY DO NOW.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
HEY, UH, THE BURNOUTS
WANT MORE BUTTONS.
BIGGER PROBLEMS.
EVERYONE KNOWS
YOU'RE PREGNANT.
OH, IS THAT ALL?
I MEAN, UM,
THAT'S HORRIBLE.
WE NEED TO DO SOME
MAJOR DAMAGE CONTROL.
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
I AM SO SORRY THAT
I PUT YOU THROUGH THIS.
UM...
HOLLY J:
AND THAT SHOULD TAKE
SAV OUT OF THE RACE.
NEXT STOP PRESIDENT,
THEN SCHOLARSHIPS,
THEN YOU AND I MAKING OUT
IN THE STUDENT LOUNGE AT YALE.
(SIGHING)
AGREED.
I CAN'T WAIT TILL WE BOTH
ESCAPE HIGH SCHOOL DRAMA.
HOLLY J:
FIONA, AGAIN?
SHE TOLD EVERYONE THAT
BOBBY BEAT HER UP.
WHY?!
'CAUSE THE SKY
WAS BLUE TODAY?
I'M SO SICK OF HER LIES.
HOLLY J:
WHAT IF SHE WASN'T LYING?
SHE SEEMED PRETTY UNHINGED
WHEN WE SKYPED YESTERDAY.
AND THOSE PICTURES...
YEAH, IT PROVES SHE'S A GREAT
MAKE-UP ARTIST.
HOLLY J:
I KNOW SHE DOES CRAZY STUFF,
BUT MAYBE THIS
IS A CRY FOR HELP.
DECLAN:
OR A CRY FOR ATTENTION.
EITHER WAY,
SHE'S YOUR SISTER
AND YOU SHOULD
BE THERE FOR HER.
YEAH.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS OFF)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
ANYA:
MAYBE YOUR PARENTS
WON'T FIND OUT?
UM, IT'S ON A BLOG.
AND THOSE THREE W'S?
THEY STAND FOR WORLD WIDE WEB!
MEANING THAT AS IN EVERYONE
IN THE WORLD CAN READ IT!
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S THINK, UM...
OKAY, WE'LL, UH...
WE'LL TELL YOUR PARENTS
FIRST, THEN MINE,
AND IF WE SURVIVE THAT,
WE'LL FIND A PLACE TO LIVE,
PLAN THE WEDDING...
THE WEDDING?
YEAH, I JUST THOUGHT
YOU MIGHT LIKE THAT,
A NICE WEDDING,
SHARE SOME VOWS.
YOU DESERVE IT.
SAV...
RIGHT, SORRY.
UH, FOCUS.
OKAY, THEY'LL-
THEY'LL BE HOME ANY MINUTE.
WHAT DO WE SAY?
THAT IT'S A LIE.
THE WHOLE PREGNANCY,
IT'S A LIE.
W-WHA...
REALLY?
HOW COULD YOU-?
IT WAS HOLLY J'S IDEA.
IT WAS SUPPOSED TO STOP
YOU FROM RUNNING.
WHY WOULD YOU GO ALONG
WITH SOMETHING LIKE THAT?!
BECAUSE YOU DUMPED
ME AFTER PROM
AND I SPENT ALL SUMMER
CRYING OVER IT.
SO I WAS CRAPPING MY PANTS
FOR NOTHING?
I WANTED TO COME CLEAN,
BUT I WAS WORRIED THAT
YOU WOULD HATE ME.
AND I REALLY DON'T WANT
YOU TO HATE ME.
NOT AGAIN.
(SIGHING HEAVILY)
I GUESS THAT'S
KIND OF SWEET.
(SMALL LAUGH)
YEAH, JUST LIKE YOU.
YOU'RE A GOOD GUY
AND A GREAT LEADER,
WHICH IS WHY YOU SHOULD
BE DEGRASSI'S PRESIDENT.
BUT PEOPLE THINK
I'M GONNA BE A DAD.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO WIN NOW?
♪♪♪
(CITY TRAFFIC NOISE)
DECLAN:
(DOOR OPENING) FIONA!
(PAPERS CLATTER)
GOOD, YOU'RE HERE.
FIONA: (CRYING)
GO AWAY, DECLAN.
DECLAN:
NO, I'M SORRY I GOT MAD.
JUST TELL ME WHAT HAPPENED
AND I'LL BELIEVE YOU.
THE STAIRS?
HE GRABBED ME,
PULLED ME DOWN.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE
DOUBTED YOU.
CAN I BLAME YOU?
CAN I BLAME ANYONE?
I JUST WANTED TO START
FRESH THIS YEAR, BE HAPPY,
BUT I GUESS I'M NOT THE KIND
OF PERSON WHO CAN BE HAPPY.
WELL, I'VE SEEN YOU HAPPY.
NOT SINCE DEGRASSI.
I JUST NEEDED SOMEONE
TO LISTEN TO ME.
HOLLY J WAS ASKING
ABOUT YOU.
SHE DID?
I TOLD HER YOU WERE
HAVING A HARD TIME
ADJUSTING TO VANDERBILT.
WHAT DID SHE SAY?
SHE SAID I SHOULD
BE THERE FOR YOU.
SHE'S ALWAYS SO GOOD ABOUT
THESE KIND OF THINGS.
(SIGHS EMOTIONALLY)
I MISS HER.
LISTEN,
WE SHOULD MOBILIZE
AND TELL MOM AND DAD
AND PRESS CHARGES.
YOU MEAN INVOLVE
THE COPS?
NO, PAGE SIX'LL
BE ALL OVER IT.
I GUESS WE CAN KISS THAT
DRAMA-FREE YEAR GOODBYE, HUH?
CAN WE GIVE IT SOME TIME?
A DAY?
SURE.
WE'LL TELL MOM AND DAD
TOMORROW.
(SNIFFING)
(EXHALING NERVOUSLY)
(SIGHING)
(SNIFFING)
(CELL PHONE KEYS CLICK)
HI, I'D LIKE TO BOOK
A FLIGHT.
JENNA:
SO, GOOD OLD RELIABLE
HOLLY J?
KC:
I DON'T KNOW.
CHANGE IS ALWAYS GOOD.
MIGHT HAVE TO GO WITH SAV.
JENNA:
SPEAKING OF CHANGE,
WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF CLARE'S NEW HAIR?
WHATEVER SHE WANTS TO CHANGE
IS NO CONCERN OF MINE.
WELL, THAT'S NOT
ALL SHE'S CHANGING.
OH YEAH?
TRUST ME.
SHE'S GOING FROM 2D TO 3D.
KC, SHE'S GETTING
A BOOB JOB.
(SNORTS)
NO WAY.
I HEARD HER BRAGGING
TO ALLI.
WOW.
I MEAN SHE LOOKS GOOD
THE WAY SHE IS.
I THOUGHT IT WAS
NO CONCERN OF YOURS.
YOU HAVE BEEN
LOOKING AT HER!
NOT LIKE THAT, JENNA,
BUT STILL...
I WONDER WHAT
THEY'LL BE LIKE?
I GOTTA TELL THE GUYS.
JENNA:
KC!
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
ASSAULT?
(SIGHING)
OVER THERE.
OH, SAV GOT ANYA PREGNANT
AND NOW HE'S SOME TYPE
OF HERO OR SOMETHING.
THAT DOESN'T MAKE
ANY SENSE!
YOU HAVE TO TELL
EVERYONE THE TRUTH.
SAV'S SCORING
THE SYMPATHY VOTE.
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
(LAUGHS)
BENEDICT ARNOLD!
YOU'VE SWITCHED SIDES!
IF YOU DON'T COME CLEAN,
I WILL.
AND THEN I'LL TELL EVERYONE
IT WAS YOUR IDEA
AND SAV KNEW NOTHING
ABOUT IT.
YOU WOULDN'T DARE.
I NEED TO PROTECT
MY FAMILY.
YOU DON'T HAVE
A FAMILY!
IF ANYBODY FINDS THAT OUT
YOU'LL BE IN BIG TROUBLE.
(COACHES' WHISTLE BLOWS)
(BOUNCING BALL)
DAVE:
HEY, WHAT'S THAT?
WESLEY:
OH, I'M TRYING TO DECIDE
WHETHER THESE GIRLS
ARE HOT OR NOT.
DAVE:
LET ME SEE.
YOU DO REALIZE THOSE IMAGES
MAKE GIRLS FEEL INSECURE
WITH THE BODIES
THEY WERE GIVEN,
SO THEY GO OUT AND SPEND MONEY
ON USELESS SOLUTIONS.
(DISMISSIVE SNORT)
YOU'RE ONE TO TALK.
CLARE:
AND WHAT IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
YOU'RE GETTING SURGERY
TO CHANGE YOUR LOOKS,
AREN'T YOU, CLARE BEAR?
ARMSTRONG:
OKAY...
WHO'S FOR DODGEBALL?
(STUDENTS GROAN)
GREAT, I'LL PROBABLY LOSE
ANOTHER CONTACT.
CLARE:
JENNA, YOU CAN HAVE
YOURS DONE TOO.
JENNA:
I'M SORRY, CLARE.
I'M HAPPY WITH WHAT
GOD GAVE ME.
P.A. ANNOUNCER:
ARE YOU TEAM SINCLAIR
OR TEAM BHANDARI?
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATES
HOLLY J AND SAV
WILL DUKE IT OUT FOR YOU VOTES
TODAY IN THE CAF.
DON'T MISS THE DEBATE.
(CLEARS THROAT)
FIONA?!
SURPRISE!
(SURPRISED GASP)
HOLLY J:
SO YOU JUST HOPPED
ON A PLANE?
FIONA:
IT WASN'T HARD.
AREN'T YOU HAPPY
TO SEE ME?
YEAH, OF COURSE.
IT'S JUST SURPRISING.
WHERE ARE YOU STAYING?
HOTEL ROOM DOWNTOWN.
MOM'S ACCOUNT.
AND SHE'S COOL
WITH THAT?
LET'S JUST SAY I KNOW
HOW TO GET MY WAY.
YOU MEAN BY NOT
TELLING HER.
WELL, IT'S NOT EXACTLY
RUNNING AWAY
IF YOU TELL YOUR MOM
WHERE YOU'RE GOING.
OKAY, I'LL TELL DECLAN.
SO YOU ARE RUNNING AWAY
FROM SOMETHING.
DECLAN TOLD ME HE WAS
WAITING FOR THE WORD
TO TEAR BOBBY'S HEAD OFF.
LET'S TALK ABOUT SOMETHING
MORE INTERESTING,
LIKE WHY YOUR HEAD'S
PLASTERED EVERYWHERE.
(SIGHING)
YEAH, I'M IN THE MIDDLE
OF A LOSING BID
FOR STUDENT COUNCIL
PRESIDENT.
LOSING? HOW?
YOU'RE CLEARLY THE BEST.
RIGHT, AND IF THE STUDENT BODY
WEREN'T ALL MORONS
THEY'D RECOGNIZE THAT.
SO LONG SCHOLARSHIPS,
SO LONG LIFE WITH DECLAN.
SO YOU'RE GIVING UP?
IT DOESN'T SOUND LIKE
THE HOLLY J SINCLAIR I KNOW.
COME ON,
LET'S POUND THE PAVEMENT,
SHAKE HANDS, KISS BABIES.
ALL THAT'S LEFT
IS THE DEBATE.
I'M SO SCREWED.
NOT YET.
LET'S GO PREP.
(SIGHING)
YOU SURE?
IT'LL BE THE PERFECT
DISTRACTION.
PLUS, YOU CAN'T GO DOWN
WITHOUT A FIGHT.
♪ I want to run,
but I don't know where ♪
♪ I want to fly... ♪
SAV:
SO, IF YOU VOTE FOR SAV
YOUR YEAR WILL BE FAB!
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
YOU ARE IN SO MUCH
TROUBLE.
NOT NOW.
WHEN MOM AND DAD FIND OUT
THAT YOU KNOCKED UP ANYA,
I'LL BE ABLE TO GET
AWAY WITH ANYTHING.
LIFE IS GONNA
BE AWESOME.
BEST NEWS EVER!
YOU TOLD EVERYONE THAT
YOU'RE NOT PREGNANT?
BETTER! THANKS TO FAKE
BABY BHANDARI
WE'RE UP IN THE POLLS.
IT'S FAKE?
YOU GUYS ARE SO WEIRD.
(STUNNED LAUGH)
ANYA,
THERE IS NO BABY.
NO ONE NEEDS
TO KNOW THAT.
SO I SHOULD LIE?
NO, YOU JUST DON'T...
TELL THE TRUTH.
I WANT TO WIN THE ELECTION
BECAUSE I DESERVE IT.
THIS IS HOLLY J'S LIE.
IF IT HELPS YOU BEAT HER,
ISN'T THAT FAIR?
CLARE!
THE SURGERY,
YOU DON'T NEED TO DO IT.
IT'S REALLY NONE
OF YOUR BUSINESS.
YOU'RE SO YOUNG.
MAYBE THEY'LL IMPROVE
ON THEIR OWN.
JUST GIVE IT
A FEW YEARS.
THEY'RE NOT GONNA CHANGE
ANYMORE, JENNA.
SURGERY'S THE ONLY
OPTION.
CLARE!
PLEASE LISTEN!
YOU DON'T NEED
TO ALTER YOUR BODY
JUST TO GET ATTENTION.
OKAY, YOU KNOW,
YOU LOST YOUR CHANCE TO TELL
ME WHAT TO DO WITH MY BODY
WHEN YOU STOLE
MY BOYFRIEND.
I AM GETTING
THE PROCEDURE,
AND I HOPE ALL THE GUYS
LOVE IT.
(SIGHS DEFEATEDLY)
LET THE DEBATE BEGIN!
STUDENTS:
(CHEER AND CLAP WILDLY)
SIMPSON:
AND HERE ARE YOUR
TWO CANDIDATES:
HOLLY J SINCLAIR...
STUDENTS:
(CLAP)
AND SAV BHANDARI!
STUDENTS:
(CLAP AND CHEER LOUDER)
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
SIMPSON:
ALL RIGHT,
YOUR FIRST QUESTION IS:
WHAT PART OF SCHOOL DO YOU FEEL
IS THE MOST IMPORTANT?
STUDENT:
OH YEAH.
FUN.
WHICH I PLAN TO PROVIDE
LIKE, ALL THE TIME.
HOLLY J:
ACADEMICS.
WE'RE HERE TO LEARN.
A SINCLAIR STUDENT COUNCIL
WILL OFFER...
A BATTLE OF THE BANDS,
HUGE PEP RALLIES,
A SENIOR SLEEP-OVER.
COMMUNITY MENTORS.
YOU'D BE CONNECTED TO PEOPLE
CURRENTLY DOING YOUR DREAM JOB
TO ASK FOR ADVICE...
A SCHOOL CHANNEL ON "YOUTUBE".
HOLLY J:
I'VE DONE THIS BEFORE.
I KNOW WHAT IT TAKES.
SAV?
I'M SORRY,
BUT HE'S JUST NOT READY.
A FEW STUDENTS:
(SNICKER)
MALE STUDENT:
YEAH, HOLLY! YEAH!
FEMALE STUDENT:
OH, COME ON.
WELL, HAVE EXPERIENCE BALANCING
A LOT OF THINGS.
UH, JUST THIS WEEK
I BALANCED SCHOOL WORK
WITH MY CAMPAIGN.
MID-WIFE APPOINTMENTS,
BABY BOOKS,
AND MY CAMPAIGN NEVER
MISSED A BEAT.
SO, YEAH, I THINK I CAN
HANDLE BEING PRESIDENT.
A FEW STUDENTS:
ALL RIGHT! YEAH!
VOTE SAV!
STUDENTS:
(CHEER AND CLAP WILDLY)
MS. OH:
EVERYBODY INTO THE GYM
TO CAST YOUR BALLOTS.
FIONA:
YOU WERE AMAZING!
UGH! WHY DIDN'T I JUST FAKE
MY OWN PREGNANCY?
YOU COULD HAVE
HAD TWINS.
BOTH:
(CHUCKLE)
HEY, I APPRECIATE
THE SUPPORT,
BUT MAYBE IT'S TIME
TO TALK ABOUT
WHY YOU'RE REALLY
AT DEGRASSI.
(NERVOUS CHUCKLE)
I TOLD YOU.
I JUST...
NEEDED A BREAK
FROM THE CITY.
THAT'S NOT WHAT
DECLAN SAID.
FIONA:
YOU TOLD HIM I WAS HERE?
HOLLY J:
YOU SAID HE ALREADY KNEW.
(SIGH WITH RELIEF)
OH, THANK GOD!
SO YOU RATTED ME OUT?!
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
MY FRIEND.
I AM.
(SIGHS EMOTIONALLY)
WE HAVE TO TALK.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
MS. OH:
AS SOCIETY BECOMES
MORE CONNECTED
I'M SURE YOU ALL TAKE
IT FOR GRANTED.
MEDIA IS EVERYWHERE.
MR. SIMPSON:
ATTENTION STUDENTS!
MS. OH:
OH, AND SO IS THE PRINCIPAL.
MR. SIMPSON:
I HAVE THE RESULTS
OF THE ELECTION.
STUDENTS:
(MURMUR IN ANTICIPATION)
MR. SIMPSON:
AND YOUR NEW STUDENT
PRESIDENT IS...
WOW, SURPRISE.
(UNEASY CHUCKLE)
UH, BY ONLY 17 VOTES,
SAV BHANDARI.
(CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY)
CONGRATULATIONS!
GOOD JOB! GOOD JOB!
(EXCITED CLAPS)
YES, WE DID IT!
♪♪♪
I AM SO PROUD OF YOU!
(LAUGHING HAPPILY)
SAV:
I COULDN'T HAVE DONE
IT WITHOUT YOU.
MR. SIMPSON:
LOTS OF WORK TO DO, SAV,
STARTING WITH THE PROCEDURES
AND PRACTICES.
SAV: (CHUCKLING)
OKAY, I'LL SEE YOU LATER!
HOLLY J:
WELL,
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT.
SAV DIDN'T WIN
THE ELECTION
BECAUSE PEOPLE THINK
I'M PREGNANT.
HE WON BECAUSE YOU THINK
YOU'RE BETTER THAN EVERYONE.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
OKAY, PEOPLE LIKE ME.
THEN WHY DIDN'T
THEY VOTE FOR YOU?
(SURPRISED GASP)
LARA:
THESE ARE VERY SERIOUS
ACCUSATIONS.
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
I TRIED.
I JUST DIDN'T WANT
TO DISAPPOINT YOU AGAIN.
(SIGHING HEAVILY)
SWEETHEART.
THERE'S SOMETHING WRONG
WITH ME, MOM.
EVERYONE KNOWS IT.
AND NO AMOUNT OF THERAPY
IS GONNA CHANGE THAT.
THERAPY IS SUPPOSED
TO HELP YOU.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO PROVE
ANYTHING TO ANYONE ELSE.
I'LL JUST NEVER BE THE NORMAL
DAUGHTER THAT YOU WANT.
OH, FIFI.
WE LOVE YOU JUST
THE WAY YOU ARE!
WHAT?
A HIGH-MAINTENANCE DRAMA QUEEN?
A SENSITIVE, PASSIONATE,
SOMETIMES MISUNDERSTOOD
YOUNG WOMAN
WITH A LOT OF PRESSURES
IN HER LIFE.
YOU MUST HAVE BEEN WORRIED.
FORTUNATELY,
YOU DIDN'T COVER
YOUR TRACKS VERY WELL.
(SMALL CHUCKLE)
WELL, I GUESS ON SOME LEVEL
I WANTED YOU TO COME FOR ME.
THANKS.
NEXT TIME LET'S HAVE
THIS CONVERSATION
BEFORE WE GET ON A PLANE.
NOW... WHAT ARE WE GONNA
DO ABOUT BOBBY?
WHAT? NO, MOM,
I DON'T WANNA.
I MEAN, BOBBY'S-
A BECKONRIDGE?
I DON'T CARE.
NOBODY HURTS MY DAUGHTER.
WHEN WE GET BACK TO NEW YORK
WE'RE GONNA TALK TO A LAWYER.
A LAWYER? WHY?!
TO PRESS CHARGES.
WE...
WE CAN'T LET THAT BASTARD
GET AWAY WITH IT, CAN WE?
(EMOTIONAL EXHALE)
MOM, PLEASE DON'T MAKE
ME GO BACK THERE.
♪ It the last day on earth ♪
♪ In my dreams ♪