MRS. EDWARDS:
I CALLED THE REAL ESTATE AGENT.
SHE'LL BE HERE AT 4:00
FOR THE APPRAISAL.
MR. EDWARDS:
WELL, WE SHOULD
PROBABLY PAINT
BEFORE WE PUT THE HOUSE
ON THE MARKET.
AND HIRE ONE
OF THOSE STAGERS.
Y-YOU'RE SELLING OUR HOUSE?
DID I MISS THE MEMO?
MRS. EDWARDS:
WE WERE GOING
TO TELL YOU TONIGHT,
WE WANTED TO IRON OUT
SOME DETAILS FIRST.
BUT...
BUT I LOVE THIS HOUSE!
IT'S LIKE,
PART OF OUR FAMILY!
IT'S TIME TO MOVE ON.
SO, WHAT ARE THESE DETAILS?
WELL, WE THOUGHT UH...
YOU'D UM, SPEND WEEKENDS
WITH ME AT MY CONDO,
AND WEEKDAYS WITH YOUR MOM.
WE'LL FIND A PLACE
NEARBY THE SCHOOL.
WE CAN PICK IT OUT TOGETHER.
(SARCASTICALLY)
GREAT.
YOU'VE GOT IT ALL FIGURED OUT.
SHOULD I START
PACKING UP MY ROOM?
MRS. EDWARDS:
UM... WELL,
THAT MIGHT NOT BE A BAD IDEA.
YOUR DAD BROUGHT A VAN
TO MOVE SOME STUFF
OVER TO HIS PLACE.
THIS IS REALLY HAPPENING,
ISN'T IT?
MRS. EDWARDS:
AFRAID SO.
YOU'RE THROWING THIS OUT?
WE'VE GOT SO MUCH STUFF
IN THIS HOUSE.
CLARE:
YOU TAUGHT ME TO TELL
TIME ON THIS.
MR. EDWARDS:
WE CAN'T TAKE EVERYTHING,
CLARE BEAR.
SOMETIMES CHANGE IS GOOD.
(SIGHS)
♪♪♪
♪ You don't have to try
to be my friend ♪
♪ You don't have to tell me ♪
♪ That you're better
off alone... ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, whatever ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
LUKE:
YEAH. UH-HUH.
CLARE: HEY.
LUKE: OH HEY, CLARE!
UH, DIDN'T SEE YOU
AT CHURCH THIS WEEKEND.
IT'S FAMILY STUFF.
YEAH,
I HEARD ABOUT THAT.
BUT WE SAID A BIG
PRAYER FOR YOU.
THAT'S UH,
THAT'S-THAT'S VERY NICE,
THANK YOU.
IT MUST BE HARD WATCHING
YOUR FAMILY CRUMBLE AROUND YOU.
ANY TIME YOU WANT TO TALK.
(LAUGHS UNCOMFORTABLY)
OKAY.
GOTTA LOVE JESUS CLUB!
SIX MONTHS AGO, I WOULD'VE
SAID THE SAME THING.
AND NOW?
THE WORLD IS A LITTLE
LESS BLACK AND WHITE.
MY MOM AND DAD
ARE SELLING THE HOUSE,
AND SEPARATING.
WHY DO I HAVE TO SUFFER
BECAUSE THEY FELL OUT OF LOVE?
MAYBE YOU WON'T HAVE TO.
THERE'S THIS KID
I KNEW GROWING UP.
HIS PARENTS GOT DIVORCED,
MOVED TO SEPARATE APARTMENTS,
BUT...
HE STAYED IN THE HOUSE.
HIS PARENTS WENT
BACK AND FORTH.
SO, HE HAD ONE BEDROOM.
ONE SET OF STUFF?
THINK YOUR PARENTS
WOULD GO FOR IT?
THEY ARE FEELING
PRETTY GUILTY
FOR PUTTING ME THROUGH THIS.
THANKS.
I CAN ALWAYS COUNT ON YOU.
THAT'S ME,
YOUR ROCK.
(LAUGHS)
I BROUGHT SOMETHING
YOU MIGHT LIKE.
ELI:
VINTAGE.
COOL.
(LOCK CLANGS)
(STUFF CLATTERS)
CLARE:
MAYBE JESUS CLUB
CAN TAKE ON YOUR LOCKER
AS A HUMANITARIAN DISASTER.
HAH!
OKAY? BYE.
(BELL RINGS)
DREW:
HOW LONG IS MOM MAKING US
RUN A FOOD DRIVE?
ADAM:
UNTIL WE REHABILITATE
THIS SCHOOL'S IMAGE
WITHIN THE COMMUNITY.
SO LIKE, TWELVE YEARS, HUH?
WE'D BETTER FIND
SOME MORE VOLUNTEERS.
WHERE ARE WE GOING
TO FIND MORE VOLUNTEERS?
GIRLS GYM CLASS
IS ABOUT TO START.
YOU COULD CANVAS
THE LOCKER ROOM.
VERY FUNNY.
♪♪♪
WHOA!
HAVE YOU SEEN MRS. HOLLAND?
ADAM:
SORRY, NOPE.
BUT SINCE YOU'RE HERE,
YOU SHOULD SIGN UP
TO WORK FOR THE FOOD DRIVE.
I DON'T DRIVE.
DREW:
YOU DO KNOW YOU NEED
40 HOURS OF COMMUNITY SERVICE
IN ORDER TO GRADUATE, RIGHT?
YEAH, WHY NOT GET THEM
HERE AND NOW?
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE
TO LEAVE CAMPUS.
OR WEAR A HAIRNET.
OR CHANGE SOME
OLD DUDE'S DIAPER.
OH MY GOD,
I CAN'T WEAR A HAIRNET!
OR...
WHAT WAS THE OTHER THING?
DREW:
NURSING HOME DUTY.
IT'S LEGENDARY.
FINE.
I CAN BE CHARITABLE.
BINGO!
(LAUGHS)
♪♪♪
WESLEY:
HEY, DAVE!
I GUESS IF WE HAVE TO HAVE
COPS IN THE SCHOOL,
AT LEAST ONE OF THEM
GIVES YOU LUNCH MONEY.
YEAH, KIDS COME TO SCHOOL
TO GET AWAY FROM THEIR PARENTS,
JUST 'CAUSE HE'S
STATIONED HERE,
DOESN'T MEAN I GOTTA
TALK TO HIM.
SO, YOU HAVE NO PARENTS.
LIKE A CHANGELING.
COOL!
YOU DO REALIZE WHAT
PEOPLE WOULD THINK
IF THEY FOUND OUT
MY DAD WAS A COP, RIGHT?
OOH, BIG SECRET!
OH MY GOSH.
WAIT,
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
DAVE:
TO PLAY BALL, WES.
WESLEY:
CAN I PLAY?
DAVE?
ONE MORE,
AND IT'S THREE ON THREE.
WHAT ARE YOU, LITTLE MAN?
GRADE 10?
JULIAN: WHOA!
DAVE: WE GONNA DO THIS?
(ASTONISHED SIGH)
(CLAPS)
ALL RIGHT, SHRIMP.
♪♪♪
♪ So Crown me
I'm about to take the throne ♪
♪ Crown me
Crown me, dawg ♪
♪ It's me, DC's own ♪
♪ Crown me
Crown me, dawg ♪
♪ And watch me do my thing ♪
♪ You should be crowning me ♪
♪ Like you were crowning
a king ♪
♪ So crown me
Crown me dawg ♪
♪ About to take the throne ♪
♪ Crown me
Crown me dawg ♪
♪ It's me, DC's own ♪
♪ Crown me
Crown me dawg ♪
♪ I'm about to do my thing... ♪
(SIGHS)
NICE THERMOMETER.
YOU KNOW,
IT'S IRONIC THAT UH,
YOU'RE MAKING SOMETHING
THAT MEASURES HEAT.
IT'S A DRAWING,
IT MEASURES CANS.
AND AN EXCELLENT
ONE AT THAT.
WOW,
THAT'S A LOT OF FLIRT.
(SIGHS)
OUCH.
AH, SHE'S JUST PLAYING
HARD TO GET.
OR, SHE'S NOT
INTERESTED IN YOU.
GIVE HER TIME,
I'LL MAKE HER INTERESTED.
(SIGHS)
(DOOR BANGS SHUT)
CLARE:
I HAVE A PROPOSAL.
MR. EDWARDS:
UH-OH.
THAT'S WHAT DARCE SAID WHEN
SHE WANTED TO GO TO AFRICA.
DON'T WORRY,
I DON'T WANT TO GO ANYWHERE.
MR. EDWARDS: PHEW!
CLARE: I WANT TO STAY HERE.
IN THIS HOUSE.
AND...
WHICH ONE OF US
WOULD STAY WITH YOU?
CLARE: BOTH!
MRS. EDWARDS: (SIGHS) CLARE!
CLARE:
NO, NOT LIKE THAT!
YOU TWO WOULD BE THE ONES
TO GO BACK AND FORTH.
ONE WEEK ON,
ONE WEEK OFF.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
OTHER FAMILIES DO THIS!
I JUST DON'T THINK
IT WOULD WORK, CLARE.
THIS PLACE HAS
TOO MANY MEMORIES.
SO YOU WON'T EVEN CONSIDER IT?
CLARE!
YOUR MOTHER AND I,
WE NEED A FRESH START.
CLARE:
SO WHAT I NEED DOESN'T MATTER?
MRS. EDWARDS:
HONEY, WE'RE JUST
TRYING TO DO
WHAT'S BEST
FOR OUR FAMILY.
WHAT FAMILY?
DARCY IS GONE,
YOU TWO ARE SEPARATING,
THE HOUSE IS THE ONLY
FAMILY I HAVE LEFT!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
CLARE,
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
WHERE SOMEONE ACTUALLY
CARES ABOUT MY OPINION!
(DOOR SLAMS)
(TRAFFIC RUMBLES)
BULLFROG:
YOU CRIED SO HARD
WE NEARLY HAD TO LEAVE,
YOU LITTLE BRAT!
(LAUGHS)
YEAH, 'CAUSE MOST
SIX MONTH OLDS
LOVE METALLICA CONCERTS.
YEAH, BUT WHEN
THE MUSIC STARTED,
YOUR TANTRUM STARTED
TO LOOK LIKE HEAD BANGING.
CECE:
ALL THE METAL HEADS AROUND YOU
STARTED IMITATING YOU.
IT WAS YOUR FIRST
MOSH PIT, BABY!
(LAUGHS)
(BULLFROG LAUGHS)
HEY.
I-I'M CLARE,
BY THE WAY.
THIS IS CLARE!
WELL, WELCOME!
THEY CALL ME THE BULLFROG.
(CROAKS)
BULLFROG: THIS IS CECE.
CECE: OH, WE'VE HEARD
ALL ABOUT YOU,
CECE: PLEASE, SIT.
CLARE: OKAY.
I HOPE YOU DON'T MIND ME
INTERRUPTING YOUR
FAMILY DINNER.
CECE AND BULLFROG:
NO!
WE WERE TELLING THE STORY
ABOUT HOW ELI
WRECKED LOLLAPALOOZA.
(LAUGHS)
(LAUGHS HUMOURLESSLY)
SO, WHAT BRINGS YOU
TO THE STEAKHOUSE?
(SIGHS)
WELL, I JUST...
I COULDN'T HANDLE
BEING AROUND MY PARENTS.
BULLFROG:
HEY, IT'S NONE OF OUR BUSINESS,
BUT IF YOU NEED A PLACE
TO CRASH,
OUR HOUSE IS YOUR HOUSE.
ANY TIME.
WOW, THANK YOU.
IT'S NICE TO KNOW
THERE'S A GUEST ROOM
WITH MY NAME ON IT.
YEAH,
NO GUEST ROOM.
EXCUSE ME?
DAD.
WE'VE BEEN TRYING TO GET
A GIRL INTO ELI'S ROOM
FOR A WHILE NOW.
DAD!
HE EVEN HAS A DOUBLE BED
IN THERE!
HEY! MOM?
COULD YOU GIVE ME AND CLARE
A MOMENT ALONE?
YOUNG LOVE!
(BOTH LAUGH)
(BIRDS CHIRP, CAR RUMBLES)
YOUR RIDE DIDN'T SHOW?
"PROMPT TAXI" MIGHT WANT
TO CHANGE THEIR NAME.
(ADAM LAUGHS)
I THOUGHT YOU'D HAVE
A PRINCESS CARRIAGE WAITING.
YOU KNOW,
WITH FIVE HORSES,
AND A CHARMING PRINCE
TO SWEEP YOU OFF YOUR FEET.
A PRINCE?
YEAH, I TRIED THAT.
NEW YORK CITY ROYALTY, ANYWAY.
CHARMING ON THE OUTSIDE,
VILE ON THE INSIDE.
RIGHT.
PRINCES ARE SO OVERRATED.
(LAUGHS)
SO MANY GUYS
ARE JUST PRETENDING
TO BE SOMETHING THEY'RE NOT.
...RIGHT.
BUT YOU SEEM HONEST.
I MEAN, I CAN TALK TO YOU
LIKE A NORMAL PERSON.
REALLY?
I TRY.
THANKS.
(TIRES SCREECH)
BUT HISTORICALLY
I HAVE TERRIBLE INSTINCTS
WHEN IT COMES TO GUYS.
♪♪♪
(LAUGHS)
FIONA:
UH, 139 HUNTINGDON, PLEASE?
♪ You see her face everywhere ♪
♪ Doesn't help
that you stop and stare ♪
♪ Contact makes me shiver ♪
(CECE AND BULLFROG LAUGH)
ELI:
SORRY ABOUT CECE AND BULLFROG.
WELL, THEY SURE
ARE INTERESTING.
WERE YOUR PARENTS SERIOUS
ABOUT ME STAYING IN YOUR ROOM?
WELL, UM...
THEY JUST ASSUMED
SINCE WE'VE BEEN DATING,
THAT WE HAVE SEX?
WHY WOULD THEY THINK THAT?
IT'S JUST THAT UM,
WELL, JULIA...
YOUR OLD GIRLFRIEND?
YEAH. SHE-SHE UH,
SHE HAD A LOT OF UH,
PROBLEMS WITH HER STEPMOM.
SO...
SHE STAYED WITH US.
LIKE...
WITH YOU, WITH YOU?
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
YOU EXISTED YET!
YOU KNOW I'M NOT
HAVING SEX
UNTIL I GET MARRIED.
I GOT THE MEMO.
DOES IT BOTHER YOU?
YEAH, IT'S NOT
MY FAVOURITE THING,
BUT THAT'S THE WAY
IT'S GOTTA BE.
WE'RE REALLY DIFFERENT,
AREN'T WE?
OPPOSITES ATTRACT.
AND GET MARRIED,
AND HAVE KIDS,
AND GET DIVORCED.
CLARE,
WE'RE NOT YOUR PARENTS!
I'LL CALL YOU LATER.
DREW:
A LIST OF THE FOOD BANK'S
MOST NEEDED ITEMS
IS ON THE CLUBS'
BULLETIN BOARD.
HOLLY J:
THANKS.
FINALLY, A WORD TO THOSE
OF YOU WHO INSIST...
HOW EXACTLY IS THAT
SUIT DRESS CODE?
COLLAR, NO JEANS.
SO...
I DID A LITTLE RESEARCH
INTO FIONA LAST NIGHT.
IF YOU SPENT HALF AS MUCH
TIME DOING HOMEWORK...
SHE'S LIVED ALL
OVER THE WORLD.
USED TO DATE SOME CLASSY,
PREP SCHOOL BIG SHOT
IN NEW YORK.
LUCKY BIG SHOT.
SHE LIKES CLASSY GUYS.
SO THAT'S THE GAME?
PRETENDING YOU'RE ALL,
MR. CLASSY?
I'VE GOT THE LOOKS,
THE MOVES.
ALL I NEED TO DO
IS ACT THE PART.
GOOD LUCK WITH THAT!
WHAT DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT GIRLS, ANYHOW?
(HUFFS)
YEAH WELL,
I KNOW PLENTY TOO.
(LAUGHS)
SO, YOU DIDN'T REALLY
MISS ANYTHING AT LUNCH.
JUST MYSTERY MEAT!
THERE'S A RUMOUR THEY'RE
TAKING AWAY ALL THE POP,
AND CANDY, THOUGH.
AND WE SHOULD ALL CUT DOWN
ON OUR INTAKE
OF SIMPLE CARBOHYDRATES.
WES, WOULD YOU STOP TALKING
LIKE A NERD,
YOU'RE GONNA GET BEAT UP!
WELL, THAT'S NOT ALLOWED.
AND WITH YOUR DAD
PATROLLING THE HALLS,
I'VE GOT NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
WOULD YOU SHUT UP
ABOUT THAT?
DID THE BASKETBALL GUYS
FIND OUT?
NO!
AND THEY WON'T!
OKAY. WELL SO,
WHEN DO I GET TO MEET THEM?
I LOVE MEETING
NEW FRIENDS!
DAVE:
YEAH I KNOW, BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
THEY'RE NOT YOUR STYLE.
I HAVE A STYLE?
WHAT IS IT?
LOOK, THEY'RE JUST
INTO DIFFERENT STUFF,
AND I DON'T THINK
YOU'D HAVE MUCH FUN.
YEAH I GET IT, YOU DON'T
THINK I'M COOL ENOUGH
TO HANG OUT WITH
YOUR NEW FRIENDS!
YOU KNOW WHAT, WES?
I KNOW YOU'RE NOT.
WHATEVER, MAN.
I DON'T NEED THIS.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
(DISHES CLATTER)
HEY, BEAUTIFUL.
ENJOYING YOUR LUNCH?
YOU SHOULD ASK
BEFORE YOU SIT.
WHAT IF MY IMAGINARY FRIEND
WAS SITTING IN THAT CHAIR?
OH, I'M SORRY.
IS YOUR LAP TAKEN?
SHE'S NOT THAT KIND OF GIRL.
(LAUGHS)
SO, WHAT ARE YOU READING?
"SCARVES: TIE ONE ON,
WITHOUT LOOKING
LIKE YOUR NANA".
TELL ME WHAT IT SAYS.
IT SAYS YOU DON'T REALLY CARE
HOW TO EXECUTE A FRENCH TWIST.
IF YOU'RE INTERESTED,
I'M INTERESTED.
DREW, I'M NOT INTERESTED.
SO, YOU CAN STOP TRYING.
PLEASE.
(SIGHS)
HEY, WAIT, WAIT! AREN'T YOU
FORGETTING SOMETHING?
YOUR IMAGINARY FRIEND.
WELL, IF YOU WANNA ASK
HER ON A DATE,
BE MY GUEST.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
LUKE:
"HE LEADS ME BESIDE
STILL WATERS;
HE RESTORES MY SOUL.
HE LEADS ME IN PATHS
OF RIGHTEOUSNESS
FOR HIS NAME'S SAKE.
AMEN."
OTHER STUDENTS:
AMEN.
LUKE:
OKAY, SO WHO WANTS
TO RAP FIRST?
(GROUP MEMBERS MURMUR)
CLARE.
WHAT'S ON YOUR MIND?
MY PARENTS.
I USED TO COUNT ON THEM
FOR EVERYTHING.
THEY TAUGHT ME RIGHT
FROM WRONG.
TOLD ME DIVORCE WAS BAD.
SEX BEFORE MARRIAGE
WAS A SIN.
BUT...
NOW THEY'RE GETTING DIVORCED.
(SIGHS SYMPATHETICALLY)
THEY SAY THEY'RE TOO DIFFERENT.
AND I ASKED,
WERE THEY ALWAYS DIFFERENT,
OR DID SOMETHING CHANGE?
AND THEY SAID,
THAT THEY WERE...
ALWAYS DIFFERENT,
BUT HOPED THAT THEY
WOULD GROW TOGETHER.
JESUS IS ALWAYS THERE
FOR YOU.
CLARE:
IF JESUS LOVES ME SO MUCH,
WHY DOES HE WANT ME
TO GO THROUGH THIS?
IT'S ALL PART OF HIS PLAN.
ELI: HIS PLAN SUCKS.
LUKE: EXCUSE ME, WHO ARE YOU?
ELI:
JUST A GUY TRYING TO HAVE
A RATIONAL DISCUSSION.
HE'S JUST TRYING TO HELP ME
FIGURE THINGS OUT.
HAVE A NICE LUNCH.
(SOBS)
CLARE, WAIT!
(CRYING)
I BET YOU LOVED THAT!
ST. CLARE HAS A CRISIS
OF FAITH.
I'M LOSING EVERYTHING
I LOVE!
NOT ME.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
(SHUDDERING SIGH)
(CRYING)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(BELL RINGS)
ADAM:
IT CAN'T HAVE BEEN THAT BAD.
DREW:
OH YEAH, THEY HAVE A NEW TERM
FOR WHEN A GIRL DISSES YOU.
"DREWED OFF."
TODAY YOU'RE EMBARRASSED,
TOMORROW EVERYBODY'LL BE
TELLING JOKES
ABOUT VIRGIL GILL'S
BAD HAIRCUT.
I NEEDED THIS, ADAM.
AFTER ALLI,
AFTER THE BOILER ROOM.
MY STOCK IS GETTING HAMMERED.
MAYBE YOU JUST NEED
TO AIM LOWER.
YOU KNOW,
WORK YOUR WAY UP TO FIONA?
YOU JUST NEED HELP.
(SIGHS)
YOU?
YOU'VE HELPED ME
WITH MY DEAL.
I PROBABLY KINDA OWE YOU.
(BELL RINGS)
OFFICER TURNER:
HI, BOYS.
I'M OFFICER TURNER.
WHAT, THEY GOT A COP
WATCHING US NOW?
I'M JUST HERE TO MAKE
YOU FEEL SAFE.
NOW, IT'S TIME
TO GET TO CLASS, OKAY?
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
DAVE: (MOCKING)
"IT'S TIME TO GET
TO CLASS, OKAY?"
(SCOFFS) WHAT'S WITH THE MAN
CRUISING OUR HALLWAYS, HUH?
HE'S JUST WAITING
TO BUST SOMEONE.
FOR REAL.
YOU GUYS READY?
WESLEY:
HEY! I'M WESLEY.
I'M DAVE'S FRIEND.
WESLEY?
WHY WOULD YOUR PARENTS
DO THAT TO YOU?
WESLEY:
I KNOW.
LAME, RIGHT?
I WAS JUST TELLING
DAVE'S DAD,
HE'S SO COOL
FOR NAMING HIM DAVE.
WES, SERIOUSLY.
WE WERE TALKING,
AND HE SHOWED ME HIS BADGE.
IT'S SO GREAT
HE'S PATROLLING HERE NOW!
JULIAN:
WHAT, YOUR DAD?
WESLEY:
(LAUGHS)
YOU GUYS DIDN'T KNOW?
DAVE'S DAD IS OFFICER TURNER!
WESLEY: COOL, HUH?
JULIAN: SO YOU'RE WHAT,
LIKE A NARC?
NO, NO!
NOT AT ALL, NO.
HE, UH...
WES, HE'S-HE'S CRAZY.
SEE 'YA, NARC.
♪♪♪
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHOOPS!
MUST'VE SLIPPED OUT, DAVE.
WHAT IS WRONG WITH ME?
♪ Crown me
Crown me dawg ♪
♪ It's me, DC's own ♪
♪ Crown me
Crown me dawg ♪
♪ And watch me do my thing... ♪
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(DOOR LATCH CLICKS)
MRS. EDWARDS:
OH GOOD, YOU'RE HOME.
YEAH... HOME.
MRS. EDWARDS:
I NEED YOU TO SORT
THROUGH THIS.
CLARE:
WHY, WHAT'S THE POINT?
OH COME ON, CLARE.
WE NEED TO DECIDE
WHAT TO HOLD ON TO.
WHY DON'T WE GO
THROUGH IT TOGETHER?
AH WELL,
THIS ONE'S DEFINITELY
A KEEPER.
YEAH, I'LL PUT IT
ON MY NEW TROPHY SHELF.
MRS. EDWARDS:
OH, WE'LL FIND A NICE PLACE
FOR THESE THINGS,
I PROMISE.
OH, LIKE THIS ONE.
THE WEEK DAD TOOK ME
AND DARCE SKIING IN MAINE.
IT WAS SO FUN,
YOU SHOULD'VE BEEN THERE.
MRS. EDWARDS:
I DON'T SKI.
IT WOULD'VE BEEN SILLY.
CLARE:
YOU COULD'VE TAKEN LESSONS.
(LAUGHS)
THAT'S WHAT YOUR DAD
ALWAYS USED TO SAY.
HE DID EVERYTHING HE COULD
TO GET ME ON THE HILL.
WELL, YOU COULD STILL
TAKE LESSONS.
EVEN IF I DID,
WE'D BE GOING DOWN
DIFFERENT HILLS.
(SIGHS)
I WISH I HADN'T BEEN
SO AFRAID TO TAKE A RISK.
WELL, IT'S TOO LATE
FOR REGRETS.
I HAVE TO GO MOM,
RIGHT NOW.
CLARE!
(DOOR SLAMS)
(KNOCKS)
CLARE?
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
I WANT TO SPEND
THE NIGHT WITH YOU.
♪♪♪
ADAM:
PRINCESS FIONA!
WAIT.
THERE'S ALREADY
A PRINCESS FIONA,
AND I'M NOT GREEN.
QUICK!
IT'S DREW.
MY BROTHER'S A GOOD GUY,
YOU JUST MAKE HIM NERVOUS.
THEN WHY WOULD HE WANT
TO BE AROUND SOMEONE
WHO MAKES HIM NERVOUS?
BECAUSE HE THINKS
YOU'RE GREAT.
WE BOTH DO!
THAT'S WHY I'M HELPING HIM.
WELL, HE HAS GOOD TASTE.
(LAUGHS)
AND IF HE'S YOUR BROTHER,
THEN MAYBE HE'S NOT SO BAD.
GIVE HIM ANOTHER CHANCE?
HE DESERVES IT.
(DOOR SLAMS)
I'M NOT LOOKING
FOR ANYTHING SERIOUS,
OR ANYTHING PHYSICAL.
REALLY?
(CLEARS THROAT)
NOTHING... SEXUAL?
(LAUGHS)
NOT ANY TIME SOON.
SO YOU CAN LET
YOUR BROTHER KNOW THAT.
COOL. THANKS.
ONLY BECAUSE YOU ASKED.
LET'S GO.
(CAR RUMBLES)
♪♪♪
WE'LL THROW YOUR BIKE
IN THE HEARSE.
WHY?
I'LL DRIVE YOU HOME.
BUT I DON'T WANT
TO GO HOME!
I WANNA BE WITH YOU.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THIS.
I WANT TO.
DON'T YOU?
YOU HAVE BELIEFS.
THIS ISN'T WHO YOU ARE.
I DON'T KNOW WHO I AM!
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
BUT I KNOW THAT
I WANNA BE WITH YOU.
WHAT IS THIS?
NOTHING,
I'LL DRIVE YOU HOME.
NO, NO!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I GET IT ELI,
DON'T BOTHER.
♪ This life is carved in you ♪
♪ Your beauty lies ♪
♪ In these eyes ♪
♪ 'Cause I can see
the truth ♪
♪♪♪