♪♪♪
(LOCKERS CLANG)
I SPENT MY NIGHT
DIVIDING MY STUFF
INTO "MOM'S PLACE"
AND "DAD'S PLACE."
I DON'T REALLY NEED
A LOCKER STALKER RIGHT NOW.
YOU WOULDN'T ANSWER
MY CALLS,
TEXTS.
I THOUGHT ABOUT
SMOKE SIGNALS-
WHAT DO YOU EXPECT,
AFTER REJECTING ME
LIKE THAT?
OR WAS YOUR EX-GIRLFRIEND
TURNED ON BY REJECTION?
I KNOW YOU'RE GOING
THROUGH STUFF
BECAUSE OF YOUR PARENTS'
DIVORCE,
BUT YOUR FAITH-
OH, YOU THINK MY FAITH
IS BOGUS,
AND WE BOTH KNOW IT!
SO, WHAT'S REALLY
GOING ON HERE?
I CARE ABOUT YOU,
THAT'S ALL.
AND IT HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH JULIA?
JULIA'S DEAD, CLARE!
SO, MAYBE I'D BE RUINING
YOUR MEMORIES
BY TAKING HER PLACE
IN YOUR BED.
(SCOFFS) WHERE DO YOU EVEN
COME UP WITH THIS STUFF?
THEN TELL ME WHY!
FOR REAL.
UNLESS EVERYTHING'S FINE
AND I CAN COME OVER
TONIGHT.
NO. I CAN'T.
YOU CAN'T.
THEN I WANT MY DAD'S
WATCH BACK.
I BROUGHT IT HOME.
IT'S MY FATHER'S WATCH!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
LET IT GO!
(SIGHS)
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever! Woo-hoo!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
DREW:
YOU'VE GOTTA DO
THE ANNOUNCEMENT TODAY
FOR THE FOOD DRIVE DONATIONS.
I DID IT
THE LAST TWO DAYS!
YOU OWE ME!
NO, YOU OWE ME.
FIONA COYNE'S GONNA GIVE YOU
A SECOND CHANCE.
YEAH, YOU TALKED TO HER?
YESTERDAY AFTER SCHOOL,
WE HAD A NICE CHAT.
SO, UH, WHAT SHOULD I DO?
CALL, TEXT,
WAIT BY HER LOCKER?
LET HER COME TO YOU.
PLAY IT COOL.
I CAN DO THAT.
THANKS, BRO.
I'LL DO THAT ANNOUNCEMENT.
(LOCKER SLAMS)
YOU LOOK LIKE I FEEL.
THANKS?
WHERE'S YOUR OTHER HALF?
PROBABLY THINKING
OF FRESH NEW WAYS
TO REJECT ME.
JUICY!
DETAILS, PLEASE.
I WENT OVER TO HIS HOUSE
LAST NIGHT,
BASICALLY THREW MYSELF
AT HIM.
HUH! NEVER A DULL MOMENT
WITH YOU TWO LOVEBIRDS.
HIS PARENTS SAID THAT
I COULD STAY IN HIS ROOM
WHEN THINGS GOT CRAZY
AT HOME,
BUT HE WOULDN'T
LET ME IN.
BUMMER. SORRY.
I'D RATHER FIND OUT
THINGS DON'T WORK
SOONER THAN LATER.
PROBLEM IS,
HE HAS MY DAD'S WATCH.
IT'S AT HIS HOUSE,
AND I WANT IT BACK!
WELL, WHAT CAN YOU DO?
I'M PLANNING A LUNCH HOUR
RESCUE MISSION.
INTENSE!
IS THERE ANYWHERE IN HIS ROOM
HE MIGHT BE HIDING IT?
I'VE NEVER BEEN IN THERE.
DON'T YOU PLAY VIDEO GAMES
AT HIS PLACE?
YEAH,
BUT HE'S KINDA WEIRD
ABOUT LETTING PEOPLE
IN HIS ROOM.
HE HAS A LOCK ON HIS DOOR.
MY CHILDHOOD IS DISAPPEARING,
BIT BY BIT.
BUT I'M GETTING THIS BIT BACK.
OKAY.
DAVE:
BET YOU GUYS MISSED ME
LAST NIGHT.
DID MARCUS EVEN MAKE A SHOT?
GUYS, COME ON,
SO WHAT, MY DAD'S A COP.
THE NARC IS TALKING TO US.
YOU GUYS STILL ON THAT?
LOOK, JUST 'CAUSE
MY DAD'S A COP,
DOESN'T MEAN
I'M GONNA SQUEAL TO HIM.
THEN PROVE IT.
SURE. HOW?
GRAB SOMETHING
FROM HIS CAR.
SOMETHING COOL.
ALL RIGHT,
I'LL DO IT.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
SURPRISE ME.
SURPRISE YOU.
♪♪♪
♪ I couldn't be here
if I tried ♪
♪ Couldn't get my body
and my mind ♪
♪ Together at the same time ♪
♪ I... ♪
♪ Don't know what's going on ♪
♪ I'm so far gone ♪
♪ I can barely write a song ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Got me daydreaming ♪
♪ And you got me... ♪
(DOORBELL RINGS)
(BIRDS CHIRP)
ADAM:
HEY.
CLARE:
I THOUGHT YOU HAD
FOOD DRIVE ALL LUNCH.
THIS SUDDENLY SEEMED A LOT
MORE INTERESTING, IS ALL.
(KNOCKS LOUDLY)
CLARABELLE!
(LAUGHS)
VIDEO-GAME KID!
YEAH... WAIT,
DON'T TELL ME YOUR NAME.
IT'S ADAM.
BULLFROG: OH.
CLARE: AND I'M JUST CLARE.
OH, I'M SORRY, GUYS,
I'VE BEEN UP SINCE THREE
DOING THE RADIO SHOW
AND IT ALL GETS
A LITTLE VERKAKTE UP HERE
IN THE BRAINPAN,
YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
CLARE:
ACTUALLY, ELI JUST SENT US
TO PICK UP HIS ENGLISH HOMEWORK.
NOBODY'S ALLOWED
INTO ELI'S ROOM.
HE GAVE US THE COMBINATION.
YEAH.
O-OKAY. WELL, GOOD!
(CLARE SIGHS)
(DOOR BANGS SHUT)
CLARE:
43...
36...
THAT'S HIS LOCKER COMBO.
(SIGHS)
IT DOESN'T WORK!
WELL, WE TRIED.
WAIT,
YOU'RE BAILING ON ME?
ELI'S MY FRIEND, TOO,
AND IF HE DOESN'T WANT US
IN HIS ROOM,
MAYBE HE'S GOT A GOOD REASON
FOR IT.
YOU WANT TO GO?
LEAVE.
I NEED TO GET MY WATCH BACK.
AND THEN,
I CAN FINALLY PUT ELI
AND HIS STUPID, STUPID PAST
BEHIND ME FOREVER.
TRY 22-04-09.
WHAT'S THAT?
THE DATE JULIA DIED.
SURE, WHY NOT.
(LOCK RASPS)
(LOCK CLICKS)
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
(LATCH CLICKS)
OH MY GOD.
WHAT A PIGSTY.
CLARE:
SO THIS IS WHY
HE WOULDN'T LET ME IN?
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER,
TRAFFIC RUMBLES IN THE DISTANCE)
GIRL:
GOODBYE!
WESLEY:
DAVE!
DIDN'T YOU HEAR ME
CALLING YOU?
DAVE:
DIDN'T YOU HEAR ME
IGNORING YOU?
WESLEY:
YOU'RE MAD AT ME?
YEAH, GOSH,
I WONDER WHY THAT COULD BE?
BECAUSE I TOLD
YOUR NEW COOL FRIENDS
YOUR DAD'S A COP.
YOU KNEW I DIDN'T WANT THEM
TO KNOW.
YEAH, YOU DIDN'T WANNA KNOW
WHO YOUR FRIENDS ARE, EITHER!
LOOK, MAN,
THIS IS MY CHANCE, ALL RIGHT?
NO OFFENCE, BRO,
BUT...
I DON'T WANT TO BE ONE
OF THE THREE TENNERS FOREVER.
OFFENCE TAKEN.
SEE 'YA.
BINGO.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
DREW:
WELL, THERE'S FIVE MINUTES
LEFT IN LUNCH.
THANKS FOR COMING OUT.
JUST PICKING UP A DONATION.
OKAY, I NEED YOUR ADVICE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT
TAKING HER TO A MOVIE?
AFTERWARDS,
THERE'S THAT PARK.
REFRIED BEANS -
DO THEY GO WITH THE REGULAR
BEANS OR SOMEWHERE ELSE?
DREW:
YOU KNOW, THE ONE WITH THE WOODS
AND THE PRIVATE BENCHES.
ADAM:
HELLO, REFRIED BEANS?
DREW:
WHEN WE'RE ALONE,
IT'S DARK,
AND THERE'S THE SOUND
OF WATER...
I SWEAR TO GOD,
IF YOU DON'T TELL ME
WHERE TO PUT THESE...
ALL THE BEANS GO OVER THERE.
SEE, FI IS THE TYPE
OF GIRL
WHO NEEDS
THE RIGHT ATMOSPHERE.
"FI"?
YOU'RE NOT GOING THERE,
OKAY?
SO PUT A SOCK IN IT!
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
YOU KNOW,
IF I DIDN'T KNOW ANY BETTER,
I MIGHT THINK
YOU'RE JEALOUS.
SHE DOESN'T WANT
ANYTHING PHYSICAL.
SO?
SO MAYBE I SHOULD
GO OUT WITH HER.
YOU'RE KIDDING,
RIGHT?
YOU LIKE HER?
YOU LIKE HER!
WHY IS IT SO CRAZY
IF I LIKE HER TOO?
DUDE, YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
HELPING ME!
AND BESIDES,
DON'T YOU THINK...
SHE'D FIGURE YOU OUT?
MAYBE IT'S NOT A PROBLEM.
ADAM, LET'S BE SERIOUS!
FIONA IS THE HOTTEST GIRL
IN SCHOOL.
WHY WOULD SHE GO
FOR A GUY LIKE YOU?
YEAH? WHY NOT?
(SIGHS)
YOU KNOW WHY.
TELL ME WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
GO AHEAD,
SAY WHY A GIRL LIKE FIONA
WOULD NEVER GO OUT
WITH A GUY LIKE ME!
ADAM...
GO AHEAD, SAY IT!
BECAUSE, PHYSICALLY,
YOU'RE NOT A GUY!
YOU HAPPY?
YEAH, JUST GREAT.
THANKS.
ADAM, YOU KNOW IT'S TRUE.
I'M JUST LOOKING OUT
FOR YOU!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(LOCKER CLANGS)
CLARE?
CLARE:
ELI, I UNDERSTAND WHY YOU WERE
SO WEIRD LAST NIGHT.
YOU'RE AT MY LOCKER.
CAN I TAKE THIS
AS A GOOD SIGN?
I KNOW SENDING ME HOME
WASN'T A REJECTION.
IT'S BECAUSE...
YOU'RE MESSY.
I'M MESSY?
CLARE:
BUT DON'T WORRY,
BECAUSE I'M GOOD AT DEALING
WITH JUNK, SEE?
SO MUCH BETTER, RIGHT?
WHAT DID YOU DO?
I JUST THOUGHT
YOU COULD SEE
HOW NICE IT IS,
AND THEN I CAN HELP YOU
WITH YOUR ROOM.
MY, MY ROOM?
WAIT, HOW DID YOU?
CLARE:
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
ELI:
THIS IS SO WRONG.
CLARE:
ELI, ELI!
DON'T BE EMBARRASSED!
IT'S JUST ME.
WE CAN DEAL.
NO, I CAN'T!
I-I-I... I CAN'T.
DO YOU KNOW
WHAT THIS MEANS?
SOMEONE'S GETTING HURT!
YOU'RE NOT MAKING
ANY SENSE!
OH! KILL ME,
PLEASE, JUST...
NO, ELI!
ELI, YOU HAVE
TO CALM DOWN.
NO, G-GET AWAY.
JUST LOOK AT ME!
CALM DOWN, CALM-
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS!
GO AWAY!
JUST...
JUST, JUST... JUST GO.
GO. I'LL BE FINE.
NO ONE WILL GET HURT.
THAT'S, THAT'S IT.
IT'S OKAY.
FIONA:
HEY! PRINCE ADAM!
WHERE WERE YOU
THIS AFTERNOON?
STUFF TO DO.
OKAY. WELL, SOMEONE DONATED
A TIN OF CAVIAR,
AND DON'T TELL ANYONE,
BUT DREW STOLE IT
FOR ME
AND WE HAD A LITTLE SNACK.
(LAUGHS) AWESOME.
YOU GUYS ARE REALLY
HITTING IT OFF.
I GOTTA GO.
UH, ARE YOU MAD AT ME?
I DIDN'T TELL YOU
TO FLIRT WITH HIM!
WELL THEN, WHY WERE YOU
PLAYING MATCHMAKER?
FORGET IT,
I HOPE YOU TWO LIVE
HAPPILY EVER AFTER.
JUST DON'T COMPLAIN TO ME
WHEN HE TRIES TO JUMP YOU.
UGH! OKAY!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I AM TIRED OF BEING
IN THE MIDDLE
OF THIS LITTLE
SIBLING RIVALRY.
SO ONCE THE CANNED
FOOD DRIVE IS OVER,
I'M DONE...
WITH BOTH OF YOU.
FIONA...
(JULIAN AND FRIENDS LAUGH)
(DAVE WHISTLES)
HEY, NARC!
COME ON,
WHAT DO YOU GOT FOR ME?
HUH?
A TAZER?
OH, NO WAY!
DAVE: IT'S COOL, EH?
JULIAN:
YEAH!
WE HAVE GOT TO TEST THIS
ON SOMEONE!
NO! NO. YOU CRAZY?
IT'S DANGEROUS.
HEY, NERDLINGER!
(GUYS LAUGH)
(GUYS SNICKER)
COME ON, NARC.
DO IT.
DAVE:
ALL RIGHT.
HEY, WES,
YOU REMEMBER THE GUYS.
YEAH. THEY'RE THE KINGS
AND YOU'RE LIKE THEIR JESTER,
RIGHT?
(GUYS LAUGH)
DAVE:
OH.
WELL, HERE'S A JOKE.
THINK FAST!
AAHHHHHHHHHHH!
(TAZER CLICKS,
GUYS GASP AND LAUGH)
(GROANS PAINFULLY)
AGGGGHHHHHH!
GUYS:
WHOA! (GASPING AND LAUGHING)
GUY:
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
(GROANS PAINFULLY)
JULIAN:
BOOM!
THAT WAS HILARIOUS,
NARC!
YO, LET'S GO GET
SOME FRIES!
(GUYS LAUGH)
GUY:
DUDE, THAT WAS AWESOME!
WESLEY: (GROANS)
DAVE: YO, WES, YOU OKAY?
NO!
THAT-THAT REALLY HURT!
HEY, WES,
I'M SORRY, MAN.
LOOK, JUST...
STOP TALKING TO ME!
(SIGHS ANGRILY)
(GROANS)
UH, YOU DON'T NEED
TO DO THAT.
THAT'S OKAY.
I HAVE TO PACK UP
SOMETIME.
ACTUALLY, YOU DON'T.
BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT
GETTING DIVORCED?
NO, WE ARE.
THEN WHY WOULDN'T
I HAVE TO PACK?
WE'RE GONNA KEEP
THE HOUSE.
YOU CAN STAY HERE.
I CAN?
YEAH, WE'LL SHARE
THE CONDO.
REALLY?
WE KNOW THIS DIVORCE
HASN'T BEEN EASY ON YOU,
SO, WHATEVER WE CAN DO
TO MAKE IT EASIER.
(RELIEVED SIGH)
EVERYTHING OKAY,
CLARE BEAR?
NO, IT'S JUST,
IT'S NICE TO HAVE ONE THING
IN MY LIFE WORKING OUT.
(CUSTOMERS CHATTER)
(DISHES CLINK)
DREW:
CAN I SIT, OR DID YOU BRING
YOUR IMAGINARY FRIEND?
(HALF LAUGHS)
ADAM TOLD ME
HE AND I ARE IN THE DOGHOUSE.
WHAT IS YOUR BROTHER'S
MALFUNCTION?
DEPENDS WHO YOU ASK.
I THOUGHT YOU TWO
WERE GETTING ALONG.
WE WERE,
AND THEN THE SECOND I GIVE YOU
THE TIME OF DAY,
HE FLIPPED.
YEAH,
JEALOUSY'S A BITCH.
HE'S JEALOUS?
GOD, HE SURE HAS A DIFFERENT WAY
OF SHOWING IT.
HE'S NOT LIKE MOST GUYS,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU DON'T KNOW?
WHAT?
SOME BIG SECRET?
(HALF LAUGHS)
HE'S THE BEST BROTHER
IN THE WORLD.
HE'D GIVE UP ANYTHING
TO MAKE SOMEONE ELSE HAPPY.
SO, THAT'S THE BIG MYSTERY?
THAT HE'S SUPER NICE?
(SLIGHT CHUCKLE)
WOW,
YOU GUYS ARE SO WEIRD!
(LAUGHS)
FIONA:
BUT YOU'RE RIGHT.
I GUESS HE'S NOT
LIKE MOST GUYS.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(RAIN PATTERS)
CECE:
OH, WOW!
IT IS COMING DOWN
IN BUCKETS!
BETTER COME INSIDE
BEFORE IT GETS WORSE.
I WAS THINKING OF MAKING
GRILLED TEMPEH FOR DINNER,
THOUGHT MAYBE YOU'D LIKE
TO CALL CLARE
AND INVITE HER OVER?
I'M NOT SURE
THAT WOULD WORK.
ARE YOU GONNA TELL ME
WHAT HAPPENED BETWEEN YOU TWO?
CLARE AND I,
WE'RE...
WE'RE JUST NOT GOING
TO WORK OUT.
YOU SEEMED SO HAPPY
WITH HER!
I WAS.
BUT NOW SHE KNOWS
THE REAL ME.
YOUR DAD TOLD ME
SHE CAME OVER.
IT SUCKS LIVING LIKE ME, MOM.
IT'S HELL.
WE TRIED TO HELP YOU,
BABY BOY.
I GUESS SOMEHOW,
WE JUST LET YOU GET
A LITTLE BIT...
LOST.
LOST IN MY OWN ROOM.
CECE:
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE WE LOST JULIA.
EVER THINK
YOU COULD CHANGE?
WHAT IF I FORGET HER?
OH, ELI,
THAT STUFF IN YOUR ROOM,
THAT'S NOT JULIA.
JULIA'S IN HERE,
AND SHE WOULD WANT YOU
TO BE HAPPY.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(BIRDS CHIRP)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
(DOOR LATCH CLICKS)
(SIGHS SCORNFULLY)
DAVE: WES! WES!
COME ON, WES!
ALL RIGHT,
LOOK, MAN, LOOK.
WHAT I DID WAS REALLY STUPID
AND I'M REALLY SORRY, MAN.
THEN PROVE IT.
HAND IT OVER,
IT'S MY TURN.
WHOA, I-I GOTTA PUT IT BACK
IN THE CAR.
THEN I GUESS
I'LL STAY MAD AT YOU.
(SIGHS)
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY,
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
HERE.
HMM?
JUST DON'T TAZE ME, BRO.
YOU LEAVE ME NO CHOICE.
(DAVE GROANS)
OKAY, LOOK,
MAKE IT QUICK.
OKAY, HERE WE GO.
IT ONLY HURTS A LOT!
WHENEVER YOU'RE READY.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
AHHHHHH!
(LAUGHS)
OH! OW!
AH! PURPLE NURPLE!
OH! (LAUGHS)
OH, MAN.
YOU KNOW, WES?
YOU'RE A GOOD GUY,
YOU KNOW THAT?
(LAUGHS)
I THINK
I'D CALL US EVEN.
YEAH.
YOU'RE A GOOD GUY.
OKAY. ALL RIGHT,
MY TURN.
(BOTH LAUGH)
WESLEY:
NO, GET OFF!
NO FAIR!
(KNOCKING)
CLARE:
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
ELI:
IT STARTED AFTER JULIA DIED -
THE... THE NOT
THROWING STUFF OUT.
EVERY TIME I TRY
TO THROW OUT SOMETHING,
I FEEL LIKE I'M GONNA DIE,
OR, OR SOMEONE ELSE
IS GOING TO,
SOMEONE I LOVE.
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD
OF HOARDING?
YEAH, MY MOM SAID SHE'D
TAKE ME TO TALK TO SOMEONE -
A... A THERAPIST
OR SOMETHING.
I WANT TO CHANGE.
THAT'S GOOD, ELI.
THAT'S REALLY,
REALLY GOOD.
IF YOU NEED ANYTHING,
JUST ASK ME, OKAY?
HERE'S WHAT I WANT,
CLARE.
I WANT YOU NOT
TO GIVE UP ON ME.
YOU'RE THE ONLY THING
THAT MAKES ME FEEL LIKE...
I COULD EVER GET BETTER.
THEN I GUESS
YOU'RE STUCK WITH ME,
JUST LIKE YOU SAID
I WAS STUCK WITH YOU.
♪♪♪
(MARKER RUSTLES)
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
SOMEONE MAY HAVE
TALKED TO FIONA.
AND I DON'T KNOW WHY,
BUT SHE LIKES YOU.
SHE SAID THAT?
WELL, SHE MADE IT
PRETTY OBVIOUS.
SO, IF YOU LIKE HER,
GO FOR IT.
BUT, WHAT ABOUT... ME?
DID YOU TELL HER?
YOU SAID SHE WASN'T INTERESTED
IN ANYTHING SEXUAL.
OH, WELL, NOT NOW,
BUT ONE DAY.
AND WHEN THAT DAY COMES,
YOU'LL FIND OUT
HOW SHE FEELS ABOUT IT.
YOU'LL NEVER KNOW
'TIL YOU TRY.
(LAUGHS)
WE MAKE A PRETTY GOOD TEAM.
LET'S GO HOME.
ADAM:
HEY. THANKS, BIG BRO.
YOU HAVE NEW BINDERS.
BUT MAYBE I NEED
ANOTHER ONE.
I'M PRETTY SURE YOUR PARENTS
WOULD BUY ONE FOR YOU.
MAYBE SOMEONE ELSE
COULD USE IT.
IT'S JUST STUFF, ELI.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
SAYS THE GIRL THAT BROKE
INTO MY ROOM
TO GET A BUSTED WATCH.
IF IT MEANS SOMETHING,
KEEP IT.
THEN I THINK YOU SHOULD
KEEP THIS.
I WANT YOU TO HAVE IT.
I NEED TO LET GO
OF SOME STUFF, TOO.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
THIS IS GONNA TAKE
FOREVER.
I'M HERE,
AS LONG AS YOU NEED ME.
YOU COULDN'T WORK
HARD ENOUGH
TO EARN A WHOLE YEAR
OF FREE STAYS
AT THE... "HOTEL ELI."
(LAUGHS) WHAT IS IT,
FOUR STARS?
(SIGHS)
ONCE IT'S READY...
AND YOU ARE.
MAYBE SOME DAY.
♪♪♪
♪ So... ♪
♪ I wanna see where this,
where this goes ♪
♪ I'll be yours ♪
♪ I'd give you today,
but it's not mine yet ♪
♪ I'll ask you
to stay here with me ♪
♪ 'Til then ♪
♪ I think I'm falling for you ♪