WE DON'T WANNA BE LATE,
OUR FLIGHT LEAVES SOON!
PRESTO!
(FIONA SIGHS)
YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
THIS IS GONNA BE
THE MOST AMAZING FASHION SHOW.
HOLLY J:
IT'S MY FIRST TIME
FLYING FIRST CLASS,
AND TO MILAN!
IT'S ALL THANKS TO
YOUR BOBBY TRIAL VICTORY MONEY.
YOU ARE AMAZING.
IT'S THE LEAST
I COULD DO, HOLLY J.
YOU NEED TO ZIP ME UP.
YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL.
YOU...
YOU'RE LUMINOUS.
BUT YOU'RE GONNA NEED
SOME SPARKLE
IF WE'RE FRONT ROW
AT KARL LAGERFELD.
♪♪♪
♪ Be my girl ♪
PERFECT.
I LOVE YOU,
HOLLY J.
FIONA.
♪♪♪
(ALARM BUZZES)
(SIGHS)
(ALARM STOPS BUZZING)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever, Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
ALLI:
IF YOU EMAIL, THEY WILL COME.
CLARE:
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU TOLD THEM
THEY'VE WON A PRIZE.
ALLI:
WELL, CLARE,
THEY DO NEED TUTORING.
BOY:
HEY.
DREW,
GLAD YOU COULD JOIN US.
SO, WHERE ARE THE PRIZES?
ALLI:
YOU'RE PROBABLY ALL WONDERING
WHY YOU'RE HERE.
WELL, YOU ARE
THE LUCKY RECIPIENTS
OF FREE MATH TUTORING
BEFORE THE STANDARDIZED TESTING!
(STUDENTS GROAN)
DREW:
(SCOFFS)
AH, WHAT A SCAM.
I'M OUT OF HERE!
WAIT, NO!
DEGRASSI COULD BE IN TROUBLE;
WE NEED TO ACE THIS TEST!
WHY? IT'S NOT GOING
TO AFFECT US.
WELL, INDIRECTLY,
IF THE TEACHERS GET FIRED.
WHO CARES?
THEY SHOULD'VE DONE
A BETTER JOB.
WHAT'S IN IT FOR US?
(STUDENTS TALK QUIETLY)
WELL, THAT WAS A BUST.
NO, DREW HAS A POINT.
WE NEED A REASON
FOR THEM TO CARE.
YOU'RE LUMINOUS.
(BOTH LAUGH)
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HOW HAPPY I AM!
THE UNIFORMS LOOK CHEERY,
THE SCHOOL...
(TAKES A DEEP BREATH)
SMELLS LIKE LEARNING.
WELL, SOMEONE'S LETTING
THE SUNSHINE IN.
SO, WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
IS THERE A DANCE TO PLAN,
OR A PLAY TO STAGE?
ANYTHING!
LET'S DO IT!
WELL, SAV AND I
WERE GONNA...
OH. SAV STUFF.
IF I DON'T HANG OUT
WITH HIM SOON,
HE'S GONNA GO EMO ON ME.
WORSE, HE MIGHT MAKE ME
A MIX CD.
SHUDDER.
GO HANG OUT WITH HIM, PLEASE!
WELL, I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
SLEEPOVER TOMORROW NIGHT,
YOU AND ME?
YOU STILL HAVEN'T TALKED
TO HIM?
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO EXPECT.
WELL DO YOU WANT ME TO STAY,
BE A BUFFER?
NO, GO HANG OUT
WITH YOUR BOY TOY.
(HOLLY J LAUGHS)
ADAM!
HEY!
HEY.
UH, YOU'RE BACK.
DID YOU GET MY LETTER?
I WAS AWFUL TO YOU.
BUT GETTING ME HELP,
TO REHAB,
IT WAS AN INCREDIBLE THING
YOU DID.
WELL, YOU WERE
PSYCHOTICALLY MAD.
I WAS.
WELL, I WAS DRUNK.
BUT I MISSED YOU.
WELL, THAT'S GOOD.
UH, SO I'LL CATCH YOU
IN THE CAF, I GUESS.
WAIT! UH...
DO YOU WANT
TO COME OVER LATER,
WATCH A MOVIE?
YEAH, SURE.
I-I LIKE MOVIES.
WELL,
I'LL SEE YOU LATER!
ALLI:
HEY, DEGRASSI,
HAVE YOU NOTICED
ANYTHING MISSING
FROM YOUR FRIDAY NIGHTS?
THAT'S RIGHT,
I'M TALKING ABOUT DANCES.
REAL ONES, AT NIGHT,
WITH ACTUAL MUSIC!
REMEMBER THOSE?
WELL, GRADE TENS,
YOU HAVE THE POWER.
STUDY HARD FOR YOUR STANDARDIZED
MATH TEST FRIDAY.
IF YOU NAIL IT,
WE GET TO SHAKE IT!
(STUDENTS CHEER AND CLAP)
AND FOR THOSE OF YOU
WHO NEED EXTRA TUTORING,
WE'LL BE CRUNCHING NUMBERS
AFTER SCHOOL.
WE CAN DO THIS,
YOU GUYS!
(STUDENTS CHEER AND CLAP)
CLARE:
PROMISING A DANCE?
ALLI, WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO SAY TO SIMPSON?
HE'S GOT TO SEE
THAT I'M AT LEAST TRYING
TO HELP, RIGHT?
MR. SIMPSON: (OVER PA)
ALLI BHANDARI TO MR. SIMPSON'S
OFFICE IMMEDIATELY.
ALLI BHANDARI.
(NERVOUS LAUGH)
ONE. DAY.
YOU'VE BEEN BACK ONE DAY.
AND I'M RIGHT BACK
IN THE SWING OF THINGS.
RIGHT, SIR?
OH, ALLI,
WHY DID YOU TELL EVERYONE
WE WERE HAVING A DANCE?
BECAUSE!
WHEN I TRIED TO GET THEM
TO STUDY
FOR THE GOOD OF THE SCHOOL,
NONE OF THEM CARED.
THEY NEEDED MOTIVATION.
OH, WELL THAT WOULD EXPLAIN
THE STUDENTS
IN THE CAFETERIA
THIS MORNING
WHO HEARD THEY WERE
"GETTING A PRIZE."
I DON'T KNOW,
HOW DO YOU TRICK KIDS
INTO STUDYING?
YOU DON'T TRICK THEM!
YOU JUST HOPE THEY'RE GOING
TO DO IT ON THEIR OWN ACCORD.
(SIGHS) YOU ALWAYS HOPE.
WELL, MR. SIMPSON,
I DID THIS ALL FOR YOU,
TO THANK YOU
FOR THE SECOND CHANCE.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
THANK YOU, ALLI,
BUT I CAN'T PROMISE A DANCE.
I THINK I ALREADY DID.
BUT PLEASE, SIR,
JUST GIVE IT A CHANCE.
YOU'LL BE SURPRISED
AT HOW HARD
KIDS'LL ACTUALLY WORK.
IF THE SCHOOL DOES WELL...
OF COURSE! PERFECT!
THANK YOU!
ALLI...
ARE YOU SURE YOU CAN GET
EVERYONE ON BOARD?
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
HOW HARD I'LL TRY.
THIS COULD BE A BIG WIN
FOR US.
LARA COYNE:
ADAM, WOULD YOU PREFER
KETTLE CHIPS
OR COUNTRY PRETZELS?
OR I COULD JUST LEAVE THEM BOTH.
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
FIONA:
THANKS, MOM.
ENJOY THE MOVIE,
I'LL BE BACK IN AN HOUR.
(LOW MURMURS COME FROM THE TV)
SHE'S A LITTLE HOVERCRAFT-Y.
SORRY.
SO HOW DID I SCORE
A PRIMO COUCH SEAT?
HOLLY J WON'T BE JEALOUS?
SHE'S WITH HER BOYFRIEND.
WHICH IS WHY I NEED TO BROADEN
MY FRIENDSHIP HORIZONS.
I KNOW THE FEELING.
MY TWO BEST FRIENDS
ARE ATTACHED AT THE HIP.
I THINK I WAS EMBARRASSING
WITH THEM, WASN'T I?
WELL, MAYBE YOU WERE JUST...
A LITTLE TIPSY.
(GROANS AND LAUGHS)
(SIGHS)
DON'T MAKE FUN OF ME.
IT WAS A DARK PERIOD.
SO DOES THAT MEAN
YOU DIDN'T REALLY LIKE
ALL THE CHAMPAGNE?
NO, I-I DID.
TOO MUCH.
IT MASKED SOME BAD FEELINGS.
WHAT'D YOU FEEL
BAD ABOUT?
MY HORRIBLE EX-BOYFRIEND,
RUNNING AWAY TO DEGRASSI,
STRESSING OUT MY FAMILY.
BEING WITH ME.
WHAT? ADAM, NO!
YOU KISSED A FEMALE TO MALE
TRANS KID;
THAT'S WHY YOU FREAKED OUT.
BEING CLOSE MADE ME
FREAK OUT
BECAUSE I THOUGHT YOU'D SEE
THE REAL ME.
ADAM, IT HAD NOTHING
TO DO WITH YOU.
I LIKE YOU.
YOU LIKE ME?
STOP IT.
WE'RE MISSING THE MOVIE.
(SIGHS)
NON-FAT HAZELNUT LATTE,
MY DEAR.
DID I GET IT WRONG?
YOU KNOW, SOME PEOPLE
JUST ASK FOR A COFFEE.
OH, IT'S GREAT.
SORRY.
I WAS JUST...
THINKING ABOUT OWEN.
NOW WHAT DID HE DO?
NOTHING!
HE APOLOGIZED,
AND HE WAS REALLY SWEET.
HE BUGGED YOU,
YOU TOLD THE TEACHER,
AND HE'S SUFFERING
THE CONSEQUENCES.
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
MAYBE I OVERREACTED
BECAUSE OF THE WAY
THAT HE TREATED RILEY
AND ZANE,
AND I WAS CARRYING
A GRUDGE.
I TALKED TO HIM,
WE CLEARED THE AIR.
AND HE SAYS
THAT HE LIKES ME.
SO WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO?
THERE'S NO REASON
THAT WE CAN'T COEXIST
IN CPR CLASS, RIGHT?
♪♪♪
♪ Yeah it seemed like
you wanted to talk ♪
♪ With your eyes
for a moment ♪
♪ In time ♪
SEE?
I KNEW WE COULD PICK UP
WHERE WE LEFT OFF.
I MISSED YOU.
YEAH?
WHAT DO YOU MISS?
MY SENSE OF HUMOUR?
MY GOOD LOOKS
AND CHARM?
(LAUGHS)
THE WAY WE'RE
SO COMFORTABLE.
♪♪♪
♪ But I... ♪
♪ I will hold on to you ♪
YOU'RE SO SOFT.
I LIKE THIS.
I'M GONNA GET A SIX PACK
SOMEDAY SOON.
FIONA:
DON'T!
IT'S SO MUCH BETTER
THAT YOU'RE BOTH.
BOTH WHAT?
I TOLD YOU,
IT DOESN'T BOTHER ME.
I LIKE THAT YOU'RE
THE BEST OF BOTH WORLDS.
BOYISH AND GIRLISH.
NO, I'M-I'M NOT,
FIONA!
I'M A GUY!
I KNOW!
THEN WHY WOULD YOU SAY
SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
I'M TRYING TO TELL YOU
THAT I LIKE YOU!
ME? OR THAT I'M STUCK
IN A STUPID GIRL'S BODY?
WHY CAN'T IT BE BOTH?
BECAUSE YOU'RE USING ME.
I'M NOT!
I WANNA BE WITH YOU.
NO.
YOU DON'T WANT ME.
FACE IT, FIONA,
YOU WANT A GIRL.
(DOOR SLAMS)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(BELL RINGS,
LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
ALLI:
DID YOU GET MY EMAIL?
ARE YOU GONNA MEET US LATER
FOR TUTORING?
LAY OFF.
DREW!
THIS IS IMPORTANT.
CAN'T WE PUT ASIDE
OUR STUPID DIFFERENCES
TO GET THE WHOLE SCHOOL
A DANCE?
CAN YOU TEACH
EVERYONE ELSE, OKAY?
WHY DO YOU HAVE
TO BOTHER ME?
I DON'T EVEN CARE
ABOUT A STUPID DANCE.
I WAS GONNA SAY
YOU'RE AN ATHLETE,
A LEADER,
PEOPLE WILL DO
WHAT YOU DO.
BUT I GUESS YOU ARE KINDA
ON THE OUTSIDE THESE DAYS, HUH?
WHATEVER.
JUST THINK ABOUT IT, OKAY?
BIANCA:
DID YOU GET US THE DANCE YET
OR WHAT?
NOT UNLESS HE STUDIES
FOR THE TEST.
DREW,
MAKE THE DANCE HAPPEN!
(SIGHS)
SO I'LL SEE YOU LATER,
I GUESS?
YEAH, I GUESS.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
FIONA:
YOU LOOK SO BUSY!
HEY.
IF YOU CAN'T MAKE
THE SLEEPOVER TONIGHT,
I GET IT.
I WOULDN'T MISS IT.
I'LL BE DONE ALL THIS STUFF
IN NO TIME!
BUT MAYBE IT'S NOT
A GOOD IDEA.
OH! IF YOU WANT
SOME ADAM TIME...
HE CAME OVER LAST NIGHT,
BUT IT WAS DIFFERENT.
I WAS SOBER.
POOR ADAM.
I THOUGHT I LIKED HIM.
I WISH I DID.
WHY CAN'T YOU JUST LIKE
WHO YOU LIKE?
WEIRD, DRAMATIC ME?
THAT'S MY FAVOURITE KIND
OF FIONA COYNE.
SO I'LL MEET YOU AT YOUR LOCKER
AFTER SCHOOL.
WE CAN WATCH A MOVIE,
HOP IN BED,
GOSSIP ALL NIGHT.
THAT SOUNDS FANTASTIC.
OKAY.
♪♪♪
♪ I'm on a mission ♪
♪ To see what's been missin' ♪
♪ My favourite song
is on repeat ♪
♪ But it's just not helping me ♪
♪ My eyes have been wider ♪
♪ But never been brighter ♪
♪ Something else is going on ♪
♪ I need a reminder ♪
♪ Of why I feel this way ♪
♪ There's a fine line ♪
♪ Between living a lie
and feeling alive ♪
♪ There are times
that I've been ♪
♪ Looking from the outside in ♪
♪ And here I go again ♪
♪ Falling behind
losing my mind ♪
(SIGHS)
THERE'S SOMETHING
SO SATISFYING
ABOUT A MOVIE ENDING
LIKE THAT.
"THE NOTEBOOK"
IS A TRUE CLASSIC.
IS THAT WHAT
IT'S REALLY LIKE?
FALLING IN LOVE?
WHY, ARE YOU IN LOVE?
JUST ANSWER THE QUESTION.
WITH DECLAN,
WAS IT LIKE THAT?
WITH DECLAN, I FELT LIKE
WE COULD DO...
ANYTHING TOGETHER.
BEING IN LOVE MAKES YOU FEEL
LIKE YOU HAVE SUPERPOWERS.
SAME FOR YOU AND SAV?
SAV'S SO GREAT.
HE'S SWEET.
BUT WHEN I FOUND OUT
I WAS SICK,
IT WAS SO HARD
TO NOT CALL DECLAN.
SO THAT'S HOW YOU KNOW
YOU'RE IN LOVE?
WHEN YOU'RE IN LOVE,
IT JUST FEELS LIKE
ALL THE STUFF
YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH
IS GONNA BE OKAY...
BECAUSE YOU FOUND
THAT PERSON.
IT'LL HAPPEN FOR YOU,
FI.
IT WILL.
LISTEN,
I'M REALLY SORRY,
BUT I THINK I HAVE
TO GO TO BED.
9 P.M. IS KINDA MY LIMIT
THESE DAYS.
OKAY.
I'LL COME TO BED IN A BIT.
♪♪♪
♪ Everything changes ♪
♪ Nothing has changed today ♪
♪ Baby I need you ♪
(SIGHS HEAVILY,
SNIFFLING)
OWEN:
THERE YOU ARE!
ARE YOU STALKING ME
AGAIN?
LOOK, WE HAVE
TO EXCHANGE NUMBERS.
I JUST REALLY WANT
TO THANK YOU;
ARMSTRONG'S LETTING ME
BACK INTO CPR.
THEN IT'S WATER
UNDER THE BRIDGE.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
WHAT?
YOU SMELL NICE.
AFTER WHAT WE JUST
WENT THROUGH?
COME ON,
WE'RE BUDS NOW, RIGHT?
CAN WE-
NO, OWEN!
LEAVE ME ALONE!
JEEZ! TAKE IT EASY!
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
OVER YOURSELF!
OKAY, WHY ARE THERE ONLY
TWO OPTIONS FOR GIRLS:
EITHER SHE LIKES YOU
OR SHE'S A BITCH?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
ALL THESE GIRLS WISH
I'D FLIRT WITH THEM.
REALLY?
GIRLS?
THIS BOY THINKS YOU WANT HIM
TO HARASS,
GROPE, AND FLIRT WITH YOU.
CAN I SEE A SHOW OF HANDS?
THAT'S A "NO."
SO YOU DON'T GET
TO COP A FEEL
AND THEN TELL US
THAT WE'RE TOO SENSITIVE.
WORD!
FINE! I GET IT.
I'LL FIND SOMEONE ELSE.
YOU TOLD HIM.
MAYBE ONE DAY
HE'LL GET IT.
(DOOR SLAMS)
(DOOR LATCH CLICKS)
LARA COYNE:
HOW WAS THE MOVIE?
GOOD?
FIONA?
WHERE DID YOU GET THAT?
I HID IT BEFORE REHAB.
I DID MY TECHNIQUES.
I DON'T WANT TO DRINK IT,
MOM,
I REALLY DON'T.
IT'S OKAY.
YOU DIDN'T DO IT.
WHERE'S HOLLY J?
SHE WENT TO BED.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
YEAH, SHE'S GREAT.
SHE'S BEING SO BRAVE
THROUGH ALL HER HEALTH ISSUES,
BUT...
I WORRY ABOUT HER.
LARA COYNE:
WELL, YOU'RE HER FRIEND,
OF COURSE YOU'RE CONCERNED.
WELL,
IT'S MORE THAN THAT.
(DOOR RUMBLES SHUT)
I LOVE HER, MOM,
MORE THAN ANYONE
IN THE WORLD,
AND SHE'S SLEEPING IN MY ROOM.
OH, HONEY.
FIONA:
MOM...
I'M IN LOVE WITH HER,
AND SHE'S A GIRL.
OH.
OH! OKAY.
I'VE NEVER FELT LIKE THIS
ABOUT A GUY -
ANY GUY... EVER -
AND I KNOW NOW
THAT I NEVER WILL.
ARE YOU SHOCKED?
ARE YOU DISAPPOINTED
IN ME?
OH, FIONA CELESTINE
ARABELLA COYNE!
ALL I WANT FOR YOU
IS TO BE HAPPY,
NO MATTER WHO YOU LOVE!
WHY DO I HAVE TO LOVE HER?
I MEAN,
IT CAN'T GO ANYWHERE.
OH, SWEETHEART,
LOVE IS NEVER EASY.
I JUST DON'T WANNA GO BACK
TO HOW I WAS:
ANGRY, LONELY,
DRINKY.
THIS WEEK I LEARNED
THAT YOU ARE STRONGER
THAN YOU OR I EVER
GAVE YOU CREDIT FOR.
JUST BECAUSE I SAT
IN A COURT CASE?
YOU CAN HANDLE THIS.
♪♪♪
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
MS. OH:
OKAY, STANDARDIZED TEST WHIZZES!
WORK OUT PROBLEMS
IN YOUR BOOKS,
AND THEN SUBMIT YOUR ANSWERS
INTO THE DATABASE.
READY?
ON YOUR MARKS,
GET SET, GO!
♪♪♪
♪ Ooooh... ♪
♪ Have you met
the inventor of it? ♪
♪ Ooooh... ♪
♪ Have you met
the inventor of it? ♪
ALLI:
(GASPS) MS. OH!
ANY WORD?
NOT YET.
BUT WE'VE BEEN WAITING
ALL DAY!
SHOULDN'T THE RESULTS
BE IN BY NOW?
I MEAN, IT'S DIGITAL,
FOR GOODNESS SAKES!
JUST RELAX, ALLI.
THE RESULTS WILL BE IN
WHEN THEY'RE READY.
MR. SIMPSON:
(SHOUTING) YESSS!
ALLI, I DON'T KNOW
HOW YOU DID IT,
BUT YOU RAISED OUR SCORE
ELEVEN POINTS!
THAT'S INCREDIBLE!
HIGH-FIVE!
NEVER MIND.
SO, DO WE GET THE DANCE?
WELL, UM...
THERE'S A LOT TO CONSIDER...
ARCHIE!
MR. SIMPSON!
GOTCHA!
OF COURSE YOU CAN
HAVE YOUR DANCE!
ALLI: WE DID IT!
DREW: DID WHAT?
ALLI:
WE GOT THE DANCE!
DREW: ARE YOU SERIOUS?
ALLI: YES!
DID YOU HEAR?
WE GOT A DANCE!
NICE WORK.
BHANDARI GOT US A DANCE.
♪ Of my love ♪
♪ Ooooh... ♪
♪ Have you met
the inventor of it? ♪
♪ Of my love ♪
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
COME IN.
(LOW MURMUR OVER HOSPITAL PA)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
(LAUGHS)
J'AI QUITTEZ
LA LECON FRANCAISE.
YOU'RE SKIPPING FRENCH?
LUCKY ME!
I HAVE SOMETHING
TO TELL YOU.
HOLLY J:
WELL, THAT SOUNDS DRAMATIC.
WHICH I GUESS IS THE POINT.
FIONA?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
I DON'T WANNA DATE
ANY MORE BOYS.
AS IN...?
I LIKE GIRLS.
I GUESS I'M GAY,
OR LESBIAN.
I HAVEN'T CHOSEN
NOMENCLATURE YET.
DID YOU ALWAYS KNOW THIS?
I ALWAYS THOUGHT
I'D MEET A GUY
AND UNDERSTAND
HOW OTHER GIRLS FELT,
BUT IT'S JUST NOT
GONNA HAPPEN.
I'M-I'M GLAD YOU'VE TOLD ME.
DID YOU TALK TO YOUR MOM
OR DECLAN?
MOM WAS GREAT -
NOT THAT I THOUGHT
SHE WOULDN'T BE,
BUT IT'S A RELIEF.
I DOUBT DECLAN
WILL BE SURPRISED.
OKAY, SO IS THIS WHY
YOU WERE WITH ADAM,
SINCE HE'S KIND OF A GIRL?
I MEAN, PHYSICALLY.
DON'T SAY THAT TO HIM.
I SHOULD'VE REALIZED
WHAT I WAS DOING -
USING HIM.
THIS STUFF TAKES TIME
TO FIGURE OUT.
DON'T BEAT YOURSELF UP.
I GUESS MAMA COYNE
WON'T BE FIXING YOU UP
WITH ANY MORE LOVELY
PREP SCHOOL BOYS?
(LAUGHS AND SIGHS)
I'M SO GLAD WE COULD TALK
ABOUT IT.
THIS WON'T CHANGE ANYTHING,
RIGHT?
ARE YOU KIDDING?
I LOVE YOU, FIONA,
NO MATTER WHAT.
HOLD UP!
IS THIS JUST GENERAL
CONVERSATION,
OR IS THERE AN ACTUAL
LOVE INTEREST HERE?
RIGHT NOW, I'M JUST HAPPY
TO HAVE MY FRIEND.
(BOTH LAUGH)