I'M FIONA,
AND I'M AN ALCOHOLIC.
I'VE BEEN SOBER 28 DAYS NOW,
AND I'VE LEARNED SO MUCH HERE,
IT'S CRAZY.
I LEARNED THAT...
MY ADDICTION TO DRINKING
WAS JUST A SYMPTOM
FOR MY UNDERLYING PROBLEMS,
AND I'M TRYING TO BECOME
MORE SELF-AWARE.
LIKE I HAVE TROUBLE
WITH RELATIONSHIPS;
MY EX-BOYFRIEND...
HE WAS ABUSIVE
AND THAT'S ONE OF THE REASONS
WHY I DRANK.
I'M AN ADDICT
AND I PLEDGE TO WORK AT IT
EVERY DAY.
COUNSELLOR:
GOOD FOR YOU.
WELL DONE, FIONA.
I'M HAPPY TO SAY
YOU ARE NO LONGER
AN INPATIENT.
(APPLAUSE)
(SIGHS HAPPILY)
CONGRATS!
THANKS FOR COMING!
I RAN HERE
STRAIGHT AFTER DIALYSIS!
I-I WOULDN'T MISS THIS
FOR THE WORLD.
ARE YOU OKAY?
WHAT CAN I DO?
WHAT DO YOU NEED?
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO TAKE CARE OF ME!
WELL, THE DAYS OF YOU
TAKING CARE OF ME ARE OVER.
I'M A REHAB GRAD.
I'M STRONG NOW.
LARA COYNE:
(LAUGHS)
OH, I AM SO PROUD OF YOU,
SWEETHEART.
AND SO WELL SPOKEN!
GOOD. I'M GONNA NEED
ALL THE PUBLIC SPEAKING PRACTICE
I CAN GET
BEFORE MY COURT APPEARANCE
THIS WEEK.
THE BOBBY TRIAL'S
THIS WEEK?
(SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
MOM, WHAT'S WRONG?
ABOUT THAT...
WE NEED TO TALK.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever, Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR THE SECOND CHANCE,
MR. SIMPSON.
WELL, I'M GLAD
TO HAVE YOU BACK, ALLI.
AND I TRUST THIS MEANS
THAT WE WON'T HAVE
ANY MORE...ISSUES?
I'M TURNING OVER
A NEW LEAF.
MR. BHANDARI:
AND WE ARE DETERMINED
TO SUPPORT HER.
OUR FAMILY IS WORKING TOWARDS
UNDERSTANDING EACH OTHER.
MR. SIMPSON:
WELL, THAT'S GREAT.
AND I HAVE TO ADMIT
I'M GLAD TO HAVE YOU BACK
FOR THE STANDARDIZED MATH TESTS
THAT ARE GOING ON THIS WEEK.
WELCOME BACK MATH TEST?
(UNENTHUSIASTICALLY)
YIPPEE.
I KNOW YOU WILL DO WELL,
ALLIA.
(SIGHS HAPPILY)
(STREETCAR RUMBLES)
FIONA:
MOM!
THE SUSPENSE IS MAKING ME
PERSPIRE!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
SIT WITH ME.
(SIGHS)
"IF THIS FINANCIAL COMPENSATION
IS NOT ACCEPTED,
TRIAL PROCEEDS AS SCHEDULED."
FINANCIAL COMPENSATION?
BOBBY'S OFFERING US
A SETTLEMENT.
HE PAYS US
A HUNDRED THOUSAND DOLLARS,
WE DROP THE CHARGES.
FORGET IT!
HE'S GUILTY.
AND WE DON'T EXACTLY
NEED THE MONEY.
FIONA, YOU KNOW I AM
THE FIRST PERSON TO SUPPORT YOU.
SO THEN?
LARA COYNE:
LAST TIME, WITH YOUR DEPOSITION,
IT TRIGGERED YOUR DRINKING.
I'M BETTER!
(TAKES A DEEP BREATH)
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
I HAVE COPING TECHNIQUES.
IF I EVER FEEL LIKE
I'M GONNA DRINK,
I DESCRIBE THE ROOM.
LIKE RIGHT NOW,
I'M WITH MY MOM,
IN A LOFT CONVERSION
WITH EXPOSED BRICK,
AND AN ANTHROPOLOGIE THROW.
BUT, FIONA, A TRIAL -
ESPECIALLY THIS WEEK -
WOULD BE OVERWHELMING
FOR YOU!
AND DO YOU REALLY WANNA BE
IN THE SAME ROOM
WITH BOBBY RIGHT NOW?
YOU WERE THE ONE WHO SAID
WE CAN'T LET BOBBY
GET AWAY WITH IT!
WELL, THINGS HAVE CHANGED
SINCE THEN.
I ONLY WANT WHAT'S BEST
FOR YOU.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
I UNDERSTAND!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
ALLI!
YOU'RE HERE!
I TOLD YOU I'D BE BACK.
CLARE:
WELL, I GUESS AFTER YOU
RAN AWAY,
I NEEDED TO SEE IT
TO BELIEVE IT.
AH WELL,
IT'S ME, BABY!
NEW AND IMPROVED.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE READY?
THINGS CAN CATCH UP WITH YOU
IN A HURRY.
THANK YOU,
MS. OPTIMISM.
SORRY.
IT'S OKAY,
IT'S ALL BEHIND ME,
WHATEVER THEY GET UP TO
IS THEIR BUSINESS.
DREW:
HEY.
LOCK UP THE BOYS!
BOILER ROOM BHANDARI'S
BACK ON THE SCENE.
MS. OH:
BIANCA? DON'T YOU HAVE
SOMEWHERE TO BE?
COME ON IN, ALLI.
WE MISSED YOU.
ALLI:
THANK YOU, MS. OH.
(BELL RINGS)
(STUDENTS TALK QUIETLY)
I'M SO EXCITED FOR CPR!
YOU WANNA TO MAKE OUT
WITH A PLASTIC DUMMY?
YOUR LOVE LIFE
MUST SUCK.
YEAH, VERY FUNNY.
I'M APPLYING TO BE
A LIFEGUARD THIS YEAR,
AND I NEED CPR
TO QUALIFY.
COACH ARMSTRONG:
OKAY.
YOU FOUR, YOU FOUR,
AND YOU FOUR.
FIND YOUR DUMMIES.
UM, OKAY,
CAN YOU SWITCH WITH ME
SO THAT I DON'T HAVE TO BE
IN A GROUP WITH OWEN?
WHY? WHAT'D HE DO?
HE'S JUST GROSS.
SO YOU WANT ME TO PAIR UP
WITH THE GROSS GUY?
NICE SALES PITCH.
CHANTAY-
JUST BITE THE BULLET.
(SIGHS)
BOBBY:
HOW CUTE IS SHE?
BOBBY: LOOK AT THAT FACE.
TINSLEY: YOU'RE CUTE!
BOBBY:
YOU ARE!
UGH! WHAT A CREEP.
AND TINSLEY'S NO BETTER.
THEY DESERVE EACH OTHER.
I WAS TALKING ABOUT TINSLEY.
WHY ARE YOU WATCHING THAT?
TESTING MYSELF,
I GUESS.
MY MOM THINKS
I'M NOT STRONG ENOUGH
TO GO TO TRIAL.
SHE THINKS I SHOULD
TAKE THE SETTLEMENT.
BUT YOU'RE STRONG.
YOU CAN DO THIS!
YOU GOT THROUGH REHAB,
AND ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS TELL THE TRUTH.
AND IF HE'S OFFERING
A SETTLEMENT,
THAT MEANS HE'S SCARED.
YOU MUST'VE MADE
A GREAT DEPOSITION.
(FIONA SIGHS)
HOLLY J:
HAVE YOU TALKED TO ADAM
SINCE REHAB?
NO.
I WANT TO, I...
I JUST HOPE HE DOESN'T THINK
MY DRINKING WAS BECAUSE HE'S...
TRANSGENDER?
IT CAN'T BE EASY
BEING DIFFERENT.
SO, WANNA HELP ME
CONVINCE MY MOM
ATTENDING THE TRIAL'S
A GOOD IDEA?
OF COURSE!
(BELL RINGS)
OWEN:
CPR EQUALS LIFEGUARD TRAINING,
WHICH EQUALS HOT CHICKS
IN BIKINIS.
IT'S A CLICHE,
BUT IT IS A TRUE CLICHE.
OKAY,
NOW LET'S TRY THRUSTS.
THIRTY COMPRESSIONS,
TWO BREATHS.
OWEN:
NO, NO, NO.
ARMS STRAIGHTER.
LIKE THIS.
ANYA:
I GOT IT.
THANKS.
NO PROBLEM,
JUST TRYING TO HELP.
OF COURSE,
IF YOU NEED MORE HELP...
UM, I'M GOOD.
I'D PAY GOOD MONEY
TO BE THAT DUMMY.
(SIGHS)
(HORN HONKS)
LARA COYNE:
FIONA, ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS SIGN THE SETTLEMENT PAPER
AND IT'S OVER.
I'M NOT GONNA SIGN THAT.
LARA COYNE:
(FRUSTRATED SIGH)
WHAT IF YOU LOSE?
HOW IS THAT
GONNA MAKE YOU FEEL?
MOM, PLEASE!
WHAT DID SHERM SAY?
(SIGHS)
HE HAS EVERYTHING SET TO GO
IN NEW YORK.
ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS SHOW UP.
BUT IT'S JUST THE TWO OF US;
DADDY'S AWAY,
AND DECLAN'S ON HIS SCHOOL TRIP.
WHAT IF HOLLY J CAME?
JUST FOR MORAL SUPPORT.
HOLLY J,
WHAT ABOUT YOUR HEALTH?
I HAVE DIALYSIS
EVERY OTHER DAY,
BUT IF IT'S ONLY
FOR ONE DAY,
I COULD ASK MY MOM.
WELL, YOU AND FIONA
DO MAKE A GREAT TEAM.
OH! THANK YOU!
I CAN DO ANYTHING WITH MY MOM
AND MY GIRLFRIEND BY MY SIDE.
I'M GONNA WIN THIS CASE.
(LAUGHS)
(BELL RINGS,
STUDENTS CHATTER)
MS. OH:
GETTING A JUMP
ON YOUR HOMEWORK?
ALLI:
I'M JUST KEEPING TO MYSELF.
BEATS HANGING OUT
IN THOSE CORRIDORS,
WATCHING MY EX-BOYFRIEND
AND HIS NEW GIRLFRIEND.
IT SUCKS,
DOESN'T IT?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
EVERYWHERE I LOOK,
THEY'RE THERE.
DON'T LET A GUY
DEFINE YOUR WHOLE
GRADE TEN YEAR.
GO MAKE YOUR MARK
LIKE ON THE STANDARDIZED
MATH TEST.
WHY? I THOUGHT
WE DON'T GET GRADED?
YOU DON'T.
THESE TESTS JUDGE TEACHERS
AND PRINCIPALS.
SO IF LITTLE OL' ME
DOES BADLY,
MR. SIMPSON GETS FIRED?
THAT'S NOT WHAT I SAID.
BUT-
YOU KNOW WHAT,
FORGET IT.
JUST, PLEASE,
DO WELL ON THE TEST.
(SIGHS)
♪♪♪
(SIREN WAILS IN THE DISTANCE)
(DOOR CLICKS OPEN)
SHERM:
AH.
LARA, FIONA.
LARA COYNE:
HOW ARE YOU?
SHERM:
HI.
HOW'S MY FAVOURITE LAWYER?
OH, WELL THE QUESTION IS
HOW'S MY CLIENT?
TOUGH AND READY?
(SIGHS)
I THINK SO.
GOOD. COME.
HOLLY J: HEY.
SHERM: HOW ARE YOU?
(WHISPERING)
WE'RE IN SESSION.
COUNSELLOR, ONCE YOUR CLIENT
GIVES HER STATEMENTS,
SHE WILL BE CROSS-EXAMINED
BY THE DEFENSE.
(LAUGHS)
CPR RULES!
IT'S KIND OF COOL
TO KNOW THAT YOU CAN SAVE
SOMEONE'S LIFE.
THEN WHY DO I FEEL
LIKE I'M DROWNING?
WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU SAW HOW OWEN
WAS ALL OVER ME,
TRYING TO PRETEND
THAT HE WAS HELPING.
I WAS WATCHING
LIKE A HAWK,
BUT YOU DIDN'T SEEM
TO MIND.
ANYA:
OOH! THAT'S WHY I FEEL
SO GROSS!
I JUST LET HIM TREAT ME
LIKE AN OBJECT.
IF IT CREEPED YOU OUT,
WHY DIDN'T YOU
SAY ANYTHING?
IN FRONT OF EVERYONE?
'CAUSE THAT'S NOT
EMBARRASSING AT ALL.
SO WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO?
I DON'T KNOW,
MAYBE I'LL DROP OUT.
THAT'LL TEACH HIM.
I KNOW!
I WILL JUST TALK
TO COACH ARMSTRONG,
AND TELL HIM TO PUT OWEN
IN ANOTHER GROUP!
AS LONG AS IT'S NOT MINE.
YEP, PROMISE.
(BELL RINGS)
WE STARTED DATING
IN THE SUMMER,
IN THE HAMPTONS.
BUT AFTER WE GOT BACK,
BOBBY GOT VIOLENT WITH ME.
CAN YOU BE
A BIT MORE SPECIFIC?
GRABBING AT FIRST,
OR SHOVING.
AND THEN HE HIT ME.
TONI STARK:
SO YOU ALLEGE.
MS. COYNE, YOU WERE IN REHAB
UNTIL JUST DAYS AGO,
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
FOR ALCOHOL ADDICTION?
YES, BUT I-
YOU'RE AN ADDICT.
(SIGHS)
REHAB TAUGHT ME
THAT I USED ALCOHOL
TO MASK MY PROBLEMS.
LIKE MY HURT
FROM BEING ABUSED BY BOBBY.
NO GIRL DESERVES
TO BE ABUSED.
TONI STARK:
MS. COYNE,
WOULD YOU LIKE TO TELL US...
HOW YOU GOT THIS BRUISE?
I GOT IT
WHEN BOBBY HIT ME.
TONI STARK:
WHICH YOU ALLEGE
WAS ON AUGUST 28TH.
YET WITNESSES SAW YOU
AFTER THAT
WITH NO BRUISE,
AND THIS PICTURE WAS TAKEN
SEPTEMBER FIRST.
WELL, I COVERED IT UP
AT FIRST.
I DIDN'T WANT IT
TO CAUSE PROBLEMS.
BUT THEN I REALIZED
I SHOULD TAKE A PICTURE.
DID YOU EMBELLISH IT
WITH MAKEUP,
MAKE IT LOOK WORSE
THAN IT WAS?
MS. COYNE?
FOR THE RECORD?
I GUESS SO.
TONI STARK:
HMM.
SO YOU LIED,
MADE UP A BRUISE,
BUT YOU WANT US TO BELIEVE
THAT YOU WERE ABUSED.
INTERESTING.
OH! ONE FINAL QUESTION.
HAVE YOU EVER HAD A SUCCESSFUL
ROMANTIC RELATIONSHIP?
SHERM: OBJECTION!
JUDGE: SUSTAINED.
NO FURTHER QUESTIONS,
YOUR HONOUR.
MR. SIMPSON: (OVER PA)
PLEASE BE RESPECTFUL
OF STUDENTS WRITING TESTS.
KEEP NOISE LEVELS IN THE HALLS
TO A MINIMUM.
ANYA:
UM...
EXCUSE ME.
I THINK WE NEED
TO TALK.
NOPE.
YOU GOT ME KICKED
OUT OF CPR.
I DID?
ARMSTRONG SAYS
I'M MAKING
CERTAIN GIRLS
FEEL THREATENED.
OKAY, WELL, I DIDN'T MEAN
TO GET YOU KICKED OUT,
BUT NOW YOU CAN'T HARASS
ANY MORE GIRLS.
OH WELL,
TOUGH BREAK.
OKAY, SERIOUSLY?
WHAT DID I DO
THAT WAS SO WRONG?
YOU TOUCHED ME
AND I DIDN'T LIKE IT!
I GUESS I SHOULDN'T
BE SURPRISED.
WHAT IS THAT SUPPOSED
TO MEAN?
YOU THREW ZANE
IN A DUMPSTER,
YOU HARASSED RILEY,
AND YOU'RE A CREEPY
HOMOPHOBE...
WHO LIKES TO UPSET
PEOPLE.
WHY NOT GROPE A GIRL?
OVERREACT MUCH?
WHY DIDN'T YOU
JUST SAY SOMETHING?
LIKE YOU WOULD'VE
LISTENED!
RIGHT. SO INSTEAD
YOU RUN TO THE TEACHER.
HMM.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO BE
A LIFEGUARD NOW?
CAN YOU DESCRIBE
YOUR RELATIONSHIP
WITH MS. COYNE?
SHE WAS ONE OF THOSE
FRAGILE FLOWERS, YOU KNOW,
AND I WANTED TO PROTECT HER.
BUT I SHOULD'VE BEEN
MORE CAREFUL.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I JUST FELT BAD FOR HER,
YOU KNOW?
I MEAN,
SHE WAS SO CONFUSED.
I WANTED TO HELP.
BUT I JUST SHOULDN'T
HAVE GOTTEN SO CLOSE.
AND HOW DO YOU FEEL
ABOUT MS. COYNE NOW,
AFTER ALL HER ALLEGATIONS?
(SIGHS)
I JUST WANNA CLEAR
MY NAME.
YOU KNOW,
I DON'T WISH FIONA ILL,
I...
I HOPE SHE FEELS BETTER SOMEDAY.
JUDGE:
IF THERE ARE
NO FURTHER QUESTIONS,
WE'LL ADJOURN FOR LUNCH.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
OKAY.
(SIGHS)
THIS WAS A BAD IDEA.
(HORNS HONK,
PEOPLE SHOUT)
HOLLY J:
YOU REALLY WERE GREAT
ON THE STAND.
FIONA:
BOBBY'S TESTIMONY MADE ME LOOK
LIKE A CRAZY PERSON.
MAYBE WE SHOULD'VE JUST TAKEN
THE STUPID SETTLEMENT
AFTER ALL.
I HAVE TO EXCUSE MYSELF.
KIDNEYS.
(SIREN WAILS NEARBY)
HONEY, ARE YOU FEELING
INSECURE?
NO, I'M-I'M FINE,
MOM.
I HAVE MY FLASHCARDS.
HMM.
I HAVE TO GET BACK
TO THE LAWYERS.
BUT YOU TWO SHOULDN'T
HAVE TO RUSH.
I'M REALLY PROUD OF YOU,
DARLING.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
♪♪♪
CLARE:
THERE YOU ARE!
STUDY EMERGENCY?
CLARE, WE HAVE TO ACE
THIS MATH TEST.
THE STANDARDIZED ONE?
GRADES DON'T COUNT
ON THAT, ALLI.
YOU CAN RELAX.
IT DOES FOR PRINCIPALS.
IF THE SCHOOL DOES BADLY,
MR. SIMPSON
COULD GET FIRED.
OKAY, THAT'S AWFUL,
BUT WHAT ARE WE
SUPPOSED TO DO?
STUDY?
GET THE OTHER KIDS TO?
I DON'T KNOW, SOMETHING!
IT'S BEEN A HARD YEAR,
CLARE,
I JUST...
I NEED A WIN.
PLEASE HELP ME?
WHAT'S YOUR PLAN?
THE GRADE TENS ARE GOING
TO ACE THIS TEST
AND SHOW EVERYONE
JUST HOW SMART WE ALL ARE.
MINOR DETAIL.
SOME OF THE GRADE TENS
AREN'T ALL THAT SMART.
WELL, THAT'S WHERE
I COME IN.
(HORNS HONK,
CARS RUMBLE)
FIONA:
WHERE AM I?
A NEW YORK BISTRO,
STARING AT A GLASS OF WINE.
"WHAT DO I HEAR?"
TRAFFIC.
LOTS OF SOOTHING TRAFFIC.
WERE YOU TALKING
TO YOURSELF?
IT'S A COPING TECHNIQUE.
WHAT IF I LOSE?
FIONA...
YOU'RE WINNING
JUST BY DOING THIS.
DO NOT LET HIM
BREAK YOU.
OKAY?
WHAT WOULD I DO
WITHOUT YOU?
WE'RE GONNA COME BACK
TO NEW YORK SOMETIME
TO CELEBRATE YOU BEING
THE BEST FRIEND
IN THE WHOLE WORLD,
OKAY?
ABSOLUTELY.
(LAUGHS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
UH, ARE YOU STALKING ME?
LOOK,
I JUST WANNA TALK.
OF COURSE YOU DO.
WELL, I AM NOT SORRY
FOR TELLING COACH ARMSTRONG
HOW YOU MADE ME FEEL
IN CPR CLASS.
OWEN:
I KNOW.
I DID WHAT I DID
AND HE KICKED ME OUT.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO APOLOGIZE,
I DO.
OKAY.
THANKS.
BUT DID IT EVER
OCCUR TO YOU
THAT I WASN'T TRYING
TO MAKE YOU FEEL UNCOMFORTABLE?
LOOK, I LIKE YOU, ANYA.
YOU'RE A SERIOUS CATCH.
OKAY.
WELL, AS LONG AS
WE'RE TALKING,
I'M GONNA BE HONEST,
OKAY?
I DON'T LIKE YOU
LIKE THAT
AND I PROBABLY
NEVER WILL.
PROBABLY?
DEFINITELY.
OKAY.
WELL, I'M SORRY
I MADE YOU FEEL BAD.
TRUCE?
SURE.
OKAY.
TINSLEY:
LIKE I SAID,
BOBBY'S A GREAT GUY.
TONI STARK:
THANK YOU, TINSLEY.
WE'LL GET TO THAT.
DO YOU HAVE A RELATIONSHIP
WITH MS. COYNE?
I MET HER LIKE ONCE,
AND THEN SHE TOOK OFF.
TONI STARK:
SO YOU'RE NOT FRIENDS?
NO.
SHE'S KIND OF A LONER.
TONI STARK:
WHAT ABOUT YOUR RELATIONSHIP
WITH MR. BECKONRIDGE?
ARE YOU FRIENDS?
MORE THAN FRIENDS?
WELL, WE HAVEN'T EXACTLY
LABELLED IT.
(LAUGHS)
BUT YOU WERE INVOLVED?
MM-HMM.
AND WHAT WAS THAT LIKE?
IS BOBBY USUALLY FUN, OUTGOING?
TINSLEY:
YEAH.
YEAH, IT WAS DRAMATIC,
DATING BOBBY.
TONI STARK:
ALL YOUNG RELATIONSHIPS ARE.
BUT I'M SURE BOBBY NEVER SEEMED
VIOLENT TO YOU, RIGHT?
HMM?
TINSLEY,
FOR THE RECORD?
SO THAT'S A NO THEN?
NO.
TONI STARK:
THANK YOU. THAT'LL BE ALL.
SHERM:
WHEN THE UH...
DEFENSE ATTORNEY ASKED YOU
IF BOBBY WAS EVER VIOLENT,
YOU HESITATED.
IS THERE SOMETHING YOU'D LIKE
TO SHARE WITH THE COURT?
I DON'T KNOW.
UNDER OATH?
WE WERE AT THIS PARTY.
BOBBY CAUGHT ME TALKING
TO THIS GUY.
HE DIDN'T LIKE THAT
VERY MUCH.
HE PULLED ME AWAY,
AND UH...
HE SLAPPED ME.
JUST A LITTLE BIT!
TONI STARK:
OBJECTION! THIS WAS NOT
IN THE DEPOSITION.
TINSLEY:
IT WAS ONLY ONE TIME!
SHERM:
UH, THAT'LL BE ALL.
THANK YOU.
♪♪♪
MS. OH:
HELLO, LADIES.
ALLI:
HEY, MS. OH,
WE'RE JUST STUDYING SOME MATH.
MS. OH:
GOOD FOR YOU.
I THOUGHT OF SOME KIDS
THAT MIGHT WANNA JOIN
YOUR UM...YOUR CLUB.
OUR CLUB?
WHAT DID I MISS?
MS. OH:
CHECK YOUR EMAIL,
THEN DELETE IT.
THEN EMPTY YOUR TRASH BIN.
MS. OH SENT ME
AN EMAIL.
"HERE ARE SOME STUDENTS
WHO MIGHT BENEFIT
FROM A LITTLE HELP."
IT'S A LIST OF ALL
THE BOTTOM FEEDERS
IN GRADE TEN MATH!
AND ONE GRADE 11.
UGH!
DREW'S ON HERE?
WELL,
HE'S NOT EXACTLY SMART.
WHICH IS WHY HE'S STILL
IN GRADE TEN MATH.
(BIRDS CHIRP,
SIRENS WAIL IN THE DISTANCE)
I'M SO NERVOUS.
IT'S OVER NOW
AND YOU DID GREAT.
JUDGE:
I HAVE A VERDICT.
AFTER CONSIDERING THE EVIDENCE,
WE HAVE FOUND SUFFICIENT PROOF
TO FIND IN FAVOUR
OF THE PLAINTIFF,
MS. FIONA COYNE,
IN THE AMOUNT OF $250,000
DOLLARS.
I'M GOING TO RECOMMEND
ANGER MANAGEMENT THERAPY
FOR MR. BECKONRIDGE.
ADJOURNED.
(SIGHS)
CONGRATULATIONS.
(BOBBY'S FAMILY WHISPERS)
(MOUTHS "THANK YOU")
LARA COYNE:
OH CONGRATULATIONS, SWEETHEART!
OH, THANKS!
YOU DID IT!
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU!
(FIONA SIGHS HAPPILY)
WHOA!
IT'S BECAUSE OF YOU,
HOLLY J!
YOU HELPED ME
THROUGH THIS.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH!
(SIGHS HAPPILY)