♪♪♪
♪ Sammy Dector ♪
♪ Are you listening
to your records ♪
♪ Are you dreaming of tomorrow ♪
♪ Again... ♪
♪ The world could be yours ♪
♪ If you dream
of something more ♪
♪ You will sail
across the seas ♪
♪ My friend... ♪
♪♪♪
DECLAN:
MORNING, SUNSHINE!
I WAS JUST GONNA CHECK
IF YOU WERE ONLINE.
OH, YOU WERE THINKING ABOUT ME?
AS ALWAYS.
HOLLY J:
I LOVE SEEING YOUR FACE...
AND YOUR BEDHEAD.
(LAUGHS)
HEY, DON'T MAKE FUN OF THE GUY
WHO HAS THE CURE
FOR PINING FROM AFAR.
GO-SEE WEEKEND -
A BUNCH OF VANDERBILT
GUYS AND GALS
ARE GOING ON A ROAD TRIP,
AND UH, YOU'RE COMING!
THIS WEEKEND?
YEAH, IT'LL BE A CHANCE
TO SEE THE PLACE
WE'RE GONNA BE SPENDING
THE NEXT FOUR YEARS TOGETHER.
I HAVE ASSIGNMENTS,
NOT TO MENTION THIS EXAM
ON SATURDAY,
AND ONE MINOR DETAIL -
THE LAST MINUTE AIR FARE?
HOW MUCH COULD IT BE?
HOLLY J:
MORE THAN I HAVE.
GUESS I'M JUST GONNA BE STUCK
WITH THE SINGLE CHICKS, HUH?
NOBODY SAID IT WOULD BE EASY.
GO.
SEND ME THE FULL REPORT,
JUST TRY NOT TO HAVE
TOO MUCH FUN!
I'LL TRY NOT TO.
BYE.
OKAY, BYE.
LOVE YOU.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever, Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
MARY KATE:
SO HOW'S YOUR JOB SEARCH GOING?
YOU KNOW,
BEFORE I COMMIT TO ANYTHING,
I SHOULD PROBABLY
SQUEEZE IN
A QUICK TRIP TO NEW YORK.
(CHOKES) NEW YORK?
WHAT,
YOU GONNA HITCHHIKE?
(SCOFFS)
LOOK, IF YOUR YALE PLAN
WORKS OUT,
YOU AND MR. MONEYBAGS
WILL HAVE LOTS OF TIME
TO SPEND TOGETHER
NEXT YEAR.
IT'S JUST...
IT'S A LONG TIME
TO BE AWAY.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT'S
A GREAT DISTRACTION?
A JOB.
HOLLY J:
YEAH, OKAY,
I GET IT, MOM!
I'VE ALREADY SAID GOODBYE
TO MY ALLOWANCE.
THAT NEW STEAKHOUSE
IS HAVING A JOB FAIR.
(SIGHS)
AND I THOUGHT MY DAYS
OF SCRAPING FOOD SCRAPS
WERE OVER!
I FINISH AT THE CALL CENTRE
AT FOUR.
I'LL GIVE YOU
A RIDE THEN.
FINE.
WESLEY:
HEY, TENNERS!
DAVE:
WOULD YOU STOP WITH THAT?!
WESLEY:
WE'RE IN GRADE TEN,
THEREFORE WE'RE TENNERS!
CONNOR:
IT'S LOGICAL.
WESLEY:
SO WHAT ARE WE UP TO
THIS WEEKEND?
WELL, WHAT WE'RE NOT DOING
IS MAKING OUT IN THE BACK ROW
WITH OUR GIRLFRIENDS.
UM, WE DON'T-
WE DON'T HAVE GIRLFRIENDS.
THAT'S MY POINT,
CONNOR.
WELL, THEN LET'S GET
SOME GIRLFRIENDS!
YEAH, AND HOW DO YOU
PROPOSE THAT?
I READ SOMEWHERE THAT WOMEN
ARE SIMPLE CREATURES,
LIKE, LIKE HAMSTERS.
YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
WELL, THINK ABOUT IT.
HAMSTERS JUST WANNA BE FED,
AND CUDDLED,
AND SHOWERED
WITH COMPLIMENTS.
I MEAN...
ISN'T THAT WHAT GIRLS WANT?
YOU COMPLIMENT HAMSTERS?
WELL, THEY'RE VERY CUTE.
HOW HARD COULD IT BE?
REALLY HARD!
LOOK, I'VE TRIED.
MANY, MANY TIMES.
(SCOFFS) IT'S JUST...
NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
SO I'M DONE TRYING.
YOU'RE JUST GONNA
GIVE UP?
I'M A LOSER.
WHY FIGHT IT?
YOU'RE A WINNER, DAVE!
A WINNER!
♪♪♪
♪ Ten years through ♪
♪ Throw it away ♪
♪ For the greater good
of a (unclear) ♪
(HORN HONKS REPEATEDLY)
(MUSIC SHUTS OFF)
YEAH, EXCUSE ME!
FITZ'S FRIEND:
(CLEARS THROAT)
(GUYS SNICKER)
ELI:
HEY, WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
YEAH!
YOU DESTROY MY CAR OVER
A FREAKING PARKING SPOT?
FITZ:
AW, YOU WANT A TISSUE?
GIVE ME THAT.
FITZ:
OOPS!
GO GET IT.
IS THAT THE BEST YOU GOT?
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU LOOKING AT?
TRYING TO FIGURE THAT OUT.
(MUFFLED LAUGHTER)
SAV:
CALLING ALL MUSICIANS!
THIS WEEKEND WE'RE HOLDING
OPEN AUDITIONS
FOR THE DEGRASSI BAND SLAM.
IF YOU THINK
YOU CAN ROCK OUT,
COME PROVE IT.
PEACE! SAV OUT.
CONNOR!
YOU, ME, AND DAVE -
LET'S TRY OUT!
YEAH,
BUT WE'RE NOT A BAND.
SAYS WHO?
BANDS PLAY INSTRUMENTS.
WE COULD PLAY INSTRUMENTS.
BANDS WRITE SONGS.
WESLEY: WE COULD WRITE SONGS!
STUDENT: SSSHHHH!
WHAT'S YOUR FAVOURITE BAND?
I-I DON'T HAVE ONE.
EVERYONE HAS A FAVOURITE BAND.
WAIT, IF...
IF WE WRITE A SONG
AND PLAYED SOME INSTRUMENTS,
WE COULD BE
MY FAVOURITE BAND!
YEAH, THAT'S THE SPIRIT!
(GASPS EXCITEDLY)
GIRL: (ON PA)
HEY DEGRASSI,
THE DEBATE CLUB IS MEETING
AFTER SCHOOL IN THE CAF.
TONIGHT'S TOPIC:
THE WAR IN AFGHANISTAN.
HOLLY J: (READING)
IF EIGHTY-ONE DOLLARS
IS TO BE DIVIDED
AMONG N PEOPLE,
WHERE N IS GREATER
THAN ONE,
SO EACH GETS X DOLLARS
WHERE X IS A WHOLE NUMBER
GREATER THAN ONE,
HOW MANY VALUES COULD THERE BE
FOR N?
FIONA?
SORRY, WHAT?
WERE YOU EVEN
PAYING ATTENTION?
I'M BUYING A BIRDCAGE.
YOU'RE BUYING A BIRDCAGE?
AN ANTIQUE,
FOR MY CONDO.
SO YOU'RE GETTING
A BIRD NOW?
NOT A REAL ONE!
(SIGHS)
IT MUST BE REALLY NICE
TO JUST BUY WHATEVER YOU WANT,
WHENEVER YOU WANT.
OH HOLLY J,
ONCE YOU MARRY DECLAN
AND POP OUT
A FEW NIECES FOR ME,
YOU WON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT BORING THINGS LIKE MONEY.
WHAT ABOUT THE PART WHERE
I BECOME AN ENTREPRENEUR?
OR A SENATOR?
THAT TOO.
(SIGHS)
COME SHOPPING WITH ME
AFTER SCHOOL?
SORRY, I'M BORING,
I HAVE A...THING.
A "THING"?
YEAH.
A JOB INTERVIEW.
OH, RIGHT.
YOUR SITUATION.
UNLESS YOU WANT ME
TO NOT GO TO YALE,
NOT MARRY DECLAN,
AND END UP LIVING IN A VAN
DOWN BY THE RIVER,
JUST... PICK UP YOUR PENCIL,
AND HELP ME FIGURE OUT
THE VALUES FOR N.
(SIGHS) YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU ARE BORING.
(BELL RINGS)
CLARE:
SO HE JUST BROKE YOUR CAR?
SNAPPED MORTY'S
HOOD ORNAMENT OFF.
WHAT'S THE WORLD
COMING TO?
ADAM:
(CRASH) OH!
YOU FIGURE OUT
WHAT YOU WERE LOOKING AT YET?
STILL TRYING TO PROCESS
THE SMELL.
HARD TO DO WITH A BROKEN NOSE.
UH, WHOA!
TELL ME SOMETHING:
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING
WHEN YOU GOT THAT HAIRCUT?
NO, NO, NO, SERIOUSLY,
WERE THERE AUDITIONS
FOR THE "PLANET OF THE APES"
REMAKE
THAT I DIDN'T HEAR ABOUT?
ADAM:
HE'S GOT THE ODOUR
PART DOWN.
GUYS, TEACHER.
(DOOR CLICKS SHUT)
THIS ISN'T OVER.
YOU OKAY?
WE FIND OURSELVES
IN THE CLASSIC STRUGGLE
BETWEEN BULLY AND BULLIED.
THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
TO PLAY THAT GAME.
BY IGNORING THEM?
BY REFUSING
TO BE THE VICTIM.
I KEEP TELLING YOU,
HE'S NOT GONNA GO FOR IT.
THAT'S WHY WE'RE NOT
GIVING HIM THE CHOICE.
THERE.
ALL SIGNED UP.
ALL RIGHT,
FIRST ONES ON THE LIST!
WHAT DO YOU GUYS PLAY?
I PLAY THE FLUTE
AND CONNOR'S TAKEN SOME PIANO.
I WANT TO DJ!
AND DAVE'LL BE
THE FRONTMAN,
ROCKIN' DA MIC.
SAV:
I MEAN LIKE WHAT KIND OF MUSIC
DO YOU GUYS PLAY?
OH, RIGHT.
UM...FUSION?
DAVE'S GONNA KILL US.
(SIGHS)
GIRLS LOVE GUYS IN BANDS,
RIGHT?
OKAY, LOOK, I-I USED TO BE
A DORKY LOSER LIKE YOU GUYS.
BUT, UH,
IF DAVE NEEDS CONVINCING,
TELL HIM IT'S TRUE:
JOINING A BAND
EQUALS INSTANT CRED,
AND THEN COME THE HONEYS.
(LAUGHS)
ALL RIGHT!
SAV:
OH, MAN!
(COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYS)
HOLLY J:
CLEANING TOILETS?
JUAN:
ONLY IF THERE'S A REAL PROBLEM.
OKAY, WAIT.
YOU DO KNOW I'VE BEEN
A SERVER BEFORE, RIGHT?
I ALSO RAN MY OWN
BABYSITTING AGENCY...
IMPRESSIVE.
I'LL PUT YOU UP FOR SERVER.
WHO KNOWS?
THIS COULD EVEN BE A CAREER.
ACTUALLY, THIS IS JUST-
JUAN: COME TO THINK OF IT,
MY WIFE WAS A LOT LIKE YOU
WHEN WE FIRST MET.
NOW SHE'S CO-MANAGER.
GOOD GOD.
THANKS.
(SIGHS)
WE'LL GET BACK TO YOU.
OKAY.
(PHONE BUTTONS BEEP)
FIONA: HELLO?
HOLLY J: FIONA,
IS IT TOO LATE FOR ME
TO COME SHOPPING?
FIONA:
(SQUEALS EXCITEDLY)
I KNEW YOU'D CHANGE YOUR MIND!
OKAY, I WAS THINKING WE'D GO
TO QUEEN STREET,
HIT A COUPLE
OF VINTAGE BOUTIQUES...
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
FIONA:
(LAUGHS)
I AM A BAD INFLUENCE!
YEAH, MY MOM'S GONNA
LOSE HER MIND!
THE CREDIT CARD WAS SUPPOSED
TO BE FOR EMERGENCIES.
WELL, THIS WAS AN EMERGENCY,
HOLLY J.
WAIT HERE,
I'LL GET CHANGED.
CAN I USE YOUR LAPTOP?
TELL DECLAN I SAY HI!
(KEYS CLACK)
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
TOO PATTERN-Y?
WHO'S TINSLEY?
(SIGHS)
A SLUT!
THE ONE I CAUGHT
WITH BOBBY.
WELL, HER STATUS
SAYS SHE'S SINGLE.
YEAH, WELL,
GIVE IT FIVE SECONDS.
AND SHE'S GOING ON
THE YALE TRIP.
OOH... WITH DECLAN?
AND OTHERS.
WHAT, SHOULD I BE WORRIED?
WELL, I CAN'T SAY
SHE WON'T TRY SOMETHING.
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE
SHE ALREADY HAS.
BUT YOU TRUST DECLAN,
RIGHT?
OF COURSE!
I MEAN, HE'S NEVER CHEATED.
NOT ON YOU, HOLLY J.
(SIGHS)
I'M GOING ON THAT TRIP.
(BAGS RUSTLE)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
HMM...
WHAT ARE THOSE?
UH...FANTASY SHOES?
YOU WENT SHOPPING?
I WASN'T GONNA BUY ANYTHING,
BUT...THEN FIONA-
MARY KATE:
AM I GOING TO HAVE TO TAKE
THE CREDIT CARD AWAY?
HOLLY J:
NO!
IT'S ALL GOING BACK.
MARY KATE:
YEAH, IT SURE IS.
WELL, ON THE BRIGHT SIDE,
IT'S LESS STUFF TO PACK.
DAD'S RENTING THE TRUCK
ON SUNDAY.
THIS SUNDAY?
FILL THOSE BOXES!
(SIGHS)
♪ You are my only escape ♪
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
♪ You are the reason
that I wait ♪
♪ On the corner
of this empty street ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ I just can't wait to meet ♪
(KEYS CLACK)
♪ Any fool would do the same ♪
(SIGHS)
ELI:
HEY, CLARE!
SO I'VE CONSIDERED YOUR
"IGNORE THE BULLY" THEORY,
AND IT'S JUST SO...
UNSATISFYING.
NOT LIKE, SAY,
OH, I DON'T KNOW,
A PUNCH IN THE FACE.
I THOUGHT VIOLENCE
WASN'T YOUR STYLE.
OR ARE THE RUMOURS TRUE?
WELL, WHAT ARE THESE
SUPPOSED RUMOURS?
I DON'T KNOW.
PEOPLE SAY YOU'RE OBSESSED
WITH DEATH,
WHICH MIGHT HAVE SOMETHING
TO DO WITH THE HEARSE.
PEOPLE CAN SAY
WHAT THEY WANT.
MY STYLE IS NOT LETTING JERKS
GET AWAY WITH...
BEING JERKS.
I JUST DON'T SEE THE POINT
IN GETTING CAUGHT UP
IN A CYCLE OF VIOLENCE.
TURN THE OTHER CHEEK,
RIGHT?
IT WORKED FOR JESUS.
REALLY,
THAT'S A MATTER OF OPINION.
DO WHAT YOU WANT,
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE
TO IMPRESS ME, OKAY?
ELI:
CLARE!
WHO SAYS I'M TRYING
TO IMPRESS YOU?
FINE! I'LL CALL OFF THE DOGS,
SMOOTH THINGS OVER.
I KNEW YOU WERE SMART!
FITZ:
EEEEEE-LIIIII!
MM! TWO SYLLABLES! GOOD.
GOOD FOR YOU.
YOU JUST CAN'T KEEP
YOUR MOUTH SHUT, CAN YOU?
ELI:
YOU BROKE MY CAR.
JUST APOLOGIZE
AND WE CAN BOTH GO BACK
TO IGNORING
EACH OTHERS' EXISTENCE.
SURE, NO PROBLEM.
I'M SORRY.
ABOUT YOUR NARDS.
ABOUT MY WHA-?
UGH!
I APOLOGIZED.
CLARE: WHAT CAN I DO?
ELI: DON'T. TOUCH. ANYTHING.
AGH! STILL THINK
I SHOULDN'T PUNCH HIM?
I THINK IT ONLY MAKES
THINGS WORSE.
OH!
AGH!
JUAN:
YOU WERE OUR TOP CHOICE.
I APPRECIATE IT,
I JUST...
CAN'T START THIS WEEKEND.
JUAN:
THEN WE'LL HAVE TO HIRE
SOMEBODY ELSE.
OH.
WELL, I GUESS YOU'LL DO
WHAT YOU HAVE TO DO.
JUAN:
I'M SORRY.
(PHONE BEEPS)
HOLLY J:
(SIGHS)
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
DECLAN:
HEY, MILADY.
WHAT'S UP WITH YOU?
I'M JUST BROWSING FOR FLIGHTS!
DECLAN:
YEAH, I UH...
I GOT YOUR EMAIL,
IT'S KINDA WHY I'M CALLING YOU.
YEAH, SO?
SO ARE YOU EXCITED I'M COMING?
YEAH, I'M HAPPY.
KINDA.
YOU'RE "SORT OF" HAPPY
I'M COMING ON THE YALE TRIP?
YEAH, I MEAN...
I'M JUST THINKIN'
MAYBE IT'S NOT A GOOD IDEA.
WHAT?
HOW COULD YOU SAY THAT?
DECLAN:
I JUST KNOW HOW YOU GET AROUND,
YOU KNOW,
LARGE GROUPS OF ROWDY CO-EDS,
AND WE CAN GO SEE YALE
SOME OTHER TIME.
BUT I'M COMING TO SEE YOU.
DECLAN:
YEAH, WELL,
WHAT ABOUT YOUR SATS?
AND YOU SHOULDN'T WASTE
THE MONEY, RIGHT?
YOU REALLY KNOW HOW TO MAKE
A GIRL FEEL WANTED.
HOLLY J, COME ON-
HEY!
TINSLEY:
TOUCHEE! COMING TO PRACTICE?
DECLAN:
OH YEAH, IN A SEC.
TINSLEY:
WELL, DON'T BE LATE!
IS THAT TINSLEY?
WHAT? YEAH.
UM... I GOTTA GO.
UH, JUST PROMISE ME
YOU'LL STAY PUT, OKAY?
ANYTHING YOU SAY.
BYE.
OH MY GOD.
HE'S CHEATING ON ME.
WHAT'S ALL THIS?
WESLEY:
OH, YOU GOT THE LOCKER NOTE.
UH, WE NEED TO PRACTICE.
DAVE:
PRACTICE?
PRACTICE FOR WHAT?
UM, FOR THE BAND SLAM AUDITION!
YOU'RE THE SINGING RAPPER GUY.
GUYS, THIS IS LAME!
YOU SAID YOU WERE SICK
OF BEING A LOSER,
WELL,
I'M TRYING TO HELP YOU.
AND US.
UH, WHAT DID SAV SAY?
BAND EQUALS CRED
EQUALS GIRLS!
SEE? IT WORKED FOR HIM;
IT'LL WORK FOR US.
ALL RIGHT,
THEN I'M IN.
(LAUGHS)
I'LL TRY AND KEEP YOU GUYS
FROM EMBARRASSING YOURSELVES.
I WROTE SOME LYRICS.
AWESOME!
LET'S HEAR IT FOR
THE THREE TENNERS!
SERIOUSLY?
WELL,
WELL THERE'S THREE OF US,
AND...WE'RE IN GRADE TEN?
DAVE:
YEAH. WHATEVER. LET'S GO.
ALL RIGHT, IT STARTS
WITH THE SINGING PART.
(COMPUTERIZED DRUM BEATS PLAY)
(PLAYING FLUTE)
DAVE: (SINGING OUT OF TUNE)
♪ YOU WERE ALWAYS ONLINE ♪
♪ ALWAYS ON MY MIND ♪
♪ I'D NEVER EVEN... SEEN YOU ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY LOVE IS BLIND ♪
MARY KATE:
YOU'RE AWFULLY QUIET.
LET ME GUESS.
FRIENDS?
SCHOOL?
THE ECONOMY?
BOYS?
I REALLY DON'T WANT
TO TALK ABOUT IT.
OKAY.
I'M JUST SO STUPID!
OH, I KNOW
THAT'S NOT TRUE!
HE'S CHEATING ON ME, MOM.
OH, HONEY.
OH, I AM SO SORRY.
(SIGHS)
DECLAN'S NOT PERFECT,
BUT I NEVER THOUGHT
HE WOULD ACTUALLY DO THIS.
HE'S A SPOILED RICH KID.
THINKS HE CAN LIVE
BY DIFFERENT RULES.
(SIGHS)
I KNOW THIS HURTS NOW,
BUT YOU ARE BETTER OFF.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
SCREW THE IVY LEAGUE.
YOU WERE RIGHT ALL ALONG;
I WAS KIDDING MYSELF
FOR AIMING THAT HIGH.
I NEVER SAID THAT!
NO, I JUST WANTED
TO MAKE SURE
YOU WERE DOING IT
FOR ALL THE RIGHT REASONS.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL,
DO YOU WANNA GO TO YALE
TO GET A GOOD EDUCATION,
OR TO LIVE OUT SOME FAIRY-TALE
WITH A PRINCE?
(SIGHS)
(MUSIC PLAYS IN THE DOT)
(CUSTOMERS CHATTER)
GOT A SEC?
I THINK IT'S TIME
TO TAKE DOWN FITZ.
WHAT HAPPENED?
I TRIED TO TALK TO HIM
AND IT GOT PERSONAL.
AS IN, MY PERSONAL AREA.
YOUR LOCKER?
HELP ME OUT HERE.
THE GUY KNEED ME.
LOW BLOW.
AW, MAN!
I... I HATE IT
WHEN THAT HAPPENS.
HURTS SO BAD!
UH...YOU WITH ME?
HEY FITZ.
FITZ:
BACK ON YOUR FEET!
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
FOR ME AND MY FRIENDS
NOT TO BE IN A COLD WAR
WITH YOU AND YOURS.
A PEACE TREATY.
AND I'D GO FOR THAT
BECAUSE?
TAKE A LOOK.
YOU'RE 22?
NOPE.
NICE FAKE.
CAN YOU GET SMOKES?
EVEN BETTER,
I CAN GET YOU
ONE OF THOSE
IF YOU AGREE TO LEAVE ME
AND MY FRIENDS ALONE.
DEAL.
(SIGHS)
THAT'S IT?
I THOUGHT TAKING FITZ DOWN
WOULD BE MORE...
YOU KNOW, AWESOME.
TRUST ME,
I HAVE A PLAN.
FIONA:
SO, YOU'RE SURE?
HOLLY J:
AGAIN, YEAH.
FIONA:
COFFEE TOMORROW?
BEFORE SCHOOL AT THE DOT.
FIONA: OKAY.
HOLLY J: I'LL SEE YOU THERE.
HEY, FIONA?
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS,
I'M...
REALLY GLAD WE'RE FRIENDS.
FIONA:
ME TOO, HOLLY J.
NOTHING COULD CHANGE THAT.
(LAUGHS) YEAH.
OKAY.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
FIONA:
BYE.
(DIALLING BEEPS)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(PHONE RINGS)
BE THERE...
OPERATOR:
THE CUSTOMER YOU ARE TRYING
TO REACH IS UNAVAILABLE.
UGH!
YEAH, ROBOT LADY,
I KNOW HOW TO LEAVE A MESSAGE!
(VOICEMAIL BEEPS)
HEY, IT'S ME.
I REALLY DIDN'T WANT TO DO THIS
OVER THE PHONE.
THIS... LONG DISTANCE THING,
IT'S DRIVING ME INSANE.
AND UM,
IT MADE ME REALIZE THAT...
I SORTA HITCHED MY WAGON TO YOU,
INSTEAD OF MAKING MY OWN WAY.
AND IF YOU'RE HOOKING UP
WITH SOME...
HIGH-CLASS SKANK
RIGHT NOW?
I REALLY HOPE
SHE'S WORTH IT.
YOU'RE NOT THE GUY
I THOUGHT YOU WERE, DECLAN.
SO, WE'RE DONE.
GOODBYE.
♪♪♪
ELI: WHAT ABOUT THIS GUY?
ADAM: MMM...
TOO MUCH UNIBROW.
ELI:
OKAY...
THIS ONE.
NAH, THE CHEEKBONES
ARE TOO HIGH.
PLUS THE LIPS ARE FULLER.
WOW, YOU'RE REALLY GOOD
AT THIS.
NO, I'M NOT.
UM...
WHAT ABOUT THAT GUY,
WITH THE FRECKLES
AND SQUINTY EYES?
I THINK WE HAVE OUR MAN.
TAKE FITZ'S PHOTO,
PUT IT WITH MR. ESCAPED
CONVICT'S VITAL STATS,
AND...BINGO!
EVERY COP IN THE COUNTRY
WILL WANT FITZ'S HEAD
IN THEIR TROPHY CASE.
ALL WE HAVE TO DO IS POINT THEM
IN THE RIGHT DIRECTION.
YEAH, BUT-
ADAM!
MY FRIEND,
OUR BULLY CROSSED THE LINE.
WE HAVE TO SHOW FITZY-BOY
WHO NOT TO MESS WITH.
(KEYS CLACK)
HAVE YOU SEEN FIONA?
SHE TOLD ME TO MEET HER HERE.
PETER:
NOPE.
SHE'S NOT GONNA
MAKE IT.
(LAUGHS)
THOUGHT I'D COME INSTEAD.
COFFEE?
(LAUGHS)