(STUDENTS CHATTER)
YOU HAD BETTER SIGN UP
FOR THE BACHELOR AUCTION,
WE'D MAKE A FORTUNE
ON YOU ALONE.
WHO'D BID ON ME?
LOADS OF GIRLS!
AND GUYS,
IF YOU WERE OUT OF THE BIGGEST,
LONGEST,
WALK-IN CLOSET IN THE WORLD!
(LAUGHS)
WHAT'S THE PROGRESS REPORT
ON ZANE?
WELL YOU GOT US TALKING,
BUT ONLY ABOUT MATH.
THE MATH RUSE WAS REALLY
ONLY SUPPOSED TO BE
A TEMPORARY SOLUTION.
COME ON,
STEP UP, QB!
I'M TRYING!
YOU'RE NOT TRYING
HARD ENOUGH
IF YOU WANNA GET BACK
TOGETHER.
I'LL TALK TO HIM TOMORROW.
MM-MM.
THE PRESENT IS A GIFT, GO.
GIVE HIM YOUR GIFT.
(GUYS TALKING AND LAUGHING)
FLIRT WITH HIM!
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever! Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
SO, WANNA GRAB A MATH-LESS
COFFEE LATER?
YOU DON'T WASTE ANY TIME,
DO YOU?
THE PRESENT'S A GIFT!
SOMEONE'S BEEN TALKING TO ANYA.
MY TREAT.
YOU CAN HAVE ANY MOCHA
CARAMEL COMBINATION
IN THE LARGEST SIZE
YOU CAN IMAGINE.
RILEY STAVROS IS OFFERING
TO PAY?
HOW COULD I POSSIBLY SAY NO?
OWEN: (MOCKINGLY IMITATING)
"HOW COULD I POSSIBLY SAY NO?"
(SMATTERING OF LAUGHTER)
THIS AIN'T DRAMA CLASS,
BUDDY,
TONE IT DOWN.
WHY, OWEN?
DOES IT MAKE YOU
UNCOMFORTABLE?
HIDING SOMETHING?
YEAH, I'M...
I'M SO INTO YOU!
(SCOFFS)
GET YOUR CLEAN PRACTICE
SHIRTS HERE, LADIES.
GUY:
THANKS.
OH. WHAT'S THIS?
SEEMS LIKE A RED SOCK
MUSTA SNUCK IN THE WASH!
OH! THE SHIRT!
IT'S MAKING ME...
TOTALLY GAY!
I MUST GET IT OFF
BEFORE IT WINS!
UNH!
SOMEONE'S BECOMING FABULOUS!
(GUYS LAUGH)
WHAT?
IT WAS A JOKE.
THEN WHY ISN'T IT FUNNY?
(GUYS LAUGH)
SO MUCH FOR TRYING.
HEY, COME ON.
WE WERE KIDDING!
MS. DAWES:
GREAT WORK ON THE POEMS,
EVERYONE.
LOTS OF LOVELY BALLADS.
A MINUS? REALLY?
(LAUGHS)
YOU SHOULD'VE TAKEN MY NOTES.
AND RISK HAVING MY POETRY
SOUND LIKE REJECTED
"ALEXISONFIRE" LYRICS?
NO THANK YOU!
OUCH, LADY,
YOU'RE HITTING ME
WHERE I LIVE!
ADAM:
LET'S ALL CALM DOWN,
SHALL WE?
MS. DAWES:
OKAY, GENTLEPEOPLE!
FOR OUR NEXT ASSIGNMENT,
WE WILL BE FILMING
MODERNIZED SCENES
FROM SHAKESPEARE.
I WANT YOU TO BREAK
INTO GROUPS OF THREE,
AND THEN SEND A LIAISON
TO THE FRONT
TO PICK UP YOUR FILM PACKAGE.
HEY, DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT.
I GOT THIS ONE.
OKAY, CAN WE TALK ABOUT
THE ELEPHANT IN THE ROOM?
HE WANTS TO...
I WANT TO...
WE JUST NEED TO TAKE
THE NEXT STEP.
IT'S SLOWLY DRIVING ME
INSANE.
WELL, THAT MAKES TWO OF US.
IT'S LIKE WE'RE PLAYING
ROMANTIC RUSSIAN ROULETTE
AND WE KEEP SHOOTING BLANKS.
IT NEEDS TO BECOME REAL.
THEN MAKE A MOVE ALREADY!
IT'S NOT THAT SIMPLE.
I-IT'S LIKE WE NEED
THE RIGHT SETTING.
HEY GUYS,
CHECK IT OUT.
WE GET TO ACT OUT
ROMEO AND JULIET.
HOW COOL IS THAT?
(BELL RINGS)
KEEP UP WITH YOUR MARXIST
LENINIST READINGS, PEOPLE.
SPEAKING OF KEEPING UP,
HOW'S THE ZANE
FLIRTATION GOING?
I ALREADY MESSED UP.
OH! WHAT HAPPENED?
(SIGHS)
STUPID LOCKER ROOM JOKES.
I DON'T GET WHY
HE'S SO SENSITIVE!
RILEY!
I HAD TO JOKE WITH OWEN
TO FIT IN,
AND ZANE KNOWS I'M NOT
COMING OUT
'TIL FOOTBALL SEASON'S OVER.
WELL, MAYBE YOU COULD'VE DEALT
WITH IT BETTER.
FOR YEARS, I'VE BEEN
DEALING WITH IT.
EITHER WITH FISTS
OR WITH JOKES.
I THINK I CHOSE
THE BETTER OPTION.
WHATEVER.
YOU'RE STILL IN
THE DOG HOUSE.
RILEY:
SEE? HE DOESN'T WANT TO TALK!
WELL,
WHAT DO YOU EXPECT?
YOU'RE NOT MAKING YOURSELF
A VIABLE OPTION.
YOU'RE JUST...
OKAY, HERE.
LGBT COMMUNITY ROUNDTABLE:
"HOMOPHOBIA IN OUR HALLWAYS."
TONIGHT, AT 8 P.M.
SOUNDS INTENSE.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD GO.
SHOW HIM YOU'RE NOT LIKE
THE OTHER GUYS.
(SIGHS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
STUDENT:
HEY!
HI, ANYA.
HI...
I WAS WONDERING,
MAYBE IF YOU COULD ADD ME?
TO THE-
TO THE BACHELOR AUCTION LIST?
YEAH, SURE, WESLEY.
ARE YOU CRAZY?
WELL...
I DON'T THINK SO.
WHY WOULD YOU SIGN UP
FOR THE BACHELOR AUCTION?
WELL, WHY WOULDN'T I?
I MEAN,
OUR CRED SKYROCKETED
SINCE OUR HOT THREE TENNER
TRACK WENT...
WENT VIRAL!
WES, THAT SONG GOT 50 HITS.
MOST OF WHICH WERE YOU.
MM-HMM, BUT...
WELL, MAYBE ANYA
WILL BID ON ME.
DID YOU HEAR?
SHE KNOWS MY NAME!
(EXASPERATED SIGH, SNAPS)
WAKE UP, MAN.
ANYA DOESN'T GO FOR GUYS
LIKE YOU.
ANYA GOES FOR GUYS LIKE...
LIKE DREW.
LOOK AT HIM.
HE'S GOT ALL THE MOVES.
LISTEN, MAN, I JUST DON'T WANT
TO SEE YOU GET ON THAT STAGE,
AND, YOU KNOW...
WES?
(DREW AND ALLI LAUGH)
WESLEY!
HUH.
CAN'T BE THAT HARD.
ARE YOU EVEN
LISTENING TO ME?
CONNOR'S BEING MAULED
BY GRIZZLIES.
I'LL OBSERVE AND LEARN.
LIKE DIANE FOSSEY
AND HER GORILLAS IN THE MIST.
(SCOFFS)
IT'S PERFECT!
OBSERVE?
I THINK YOU MEAN STALK.
OH! YEAH.
GOOD CALL, DAVE.
THANKS.
OH, PLEASE.
CLARE:
SO,
OBVIOUSLY, I'LL PLAY JULIET.
WHICH ONE OF YOU
WANTS TO BE ROMEO?
I WILL!
ON ACCOUNT THAT
I'M PRETTY FAMILIAR
WITH THE MATERIAL,
AND ALL.
YEAH, WHAT ARE YOU NOT
THE EXPERT ON?
SHALL WE REHEARSE?
OH.
OKAY, SO...
UH, WHEN ROMEO FINDS JULIET
PRETENDING TO BE DEAD,
HE CAN'T WAIT TO START
HIS NEW LIFE WITH HER.
AND WHEN IT LOOKS LIKE
SHE'S REALLY DEAD,
HE CAN'T GO ON ANY MORE,
SO HE DRINKS THE POISON.
BUT THEN JULIET WAKES UP,
FINDS ROMEO DEAD,
AND... KILLS HERSELF.
YOU'D THINK THAT ROMEO
WOULD REQUIRE A FEW MINUTES
BEFORE THE POISON KICKED IN.
Y-YOU MAKE A VALID POINT.
UH, HE DOES DIE
PRETTY HASTILY.
WHAT IF...
JULIET WERE TO WAKE UP,
AND FIND HIM ALIVE
FOR A BRIEF MOMENT?
THEY COULD SHARE
A FINAL KISS.
(EXASPERATED SIGH)
YEAH.
YEAH, I THINK THAT
COULD WORK.
THAT'S CUTE.
OOOH!
NEW CLOTHES?
HAS SOMEONE GOT A DATE TONIGHT?
JUST HANGING OUT
WITH A FRIEND,
BUT WHO KNOWS?
MAYBE SOMETHING COULD HAPPEN.
RILEY!
NO NEED TO GET EXCITED, MA.
MRS. STAVROS:
SHE MUST BE SPECIAL.
WHEN DO I GET TO MEET HER?
IT COULD BE A WHILE,
I SPENT THE YEAR
SCREWING IT UP.
OH HONEY,
I'M SURE IT'S NOT SO BAD.
OH, BELIEVE ME, IT IS.
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING.
IF YOU WORK HARD ENOUGH,
YOU'LL GET A SECOND CHANCE.
JUST MAKE IT COUNT.
MA?
THANKS.
ANY TIME.
OH, ONE MORE THING.
GO WITH THE GREY SHIRT.
THE OTHER ONE'S A BIT...
ZESTY.
JULIET,
I WILL JOIN YOU
IN THE AFTERLIFE!
(SIGHS DRAMATICALLY)
DEATH COME QUICKLY,
SO I CAN BE WITH HER ASAP.
ROMEO! YOU DRANK THE POISONOUS
HIGH-FRUCTOSE COLA BEVERAGE?
NO!
CLARE:
STAR CROSSED?
NOT FOR LONG.
I WILL SEE YOU
IN THE AFTERLIFE, ROMEO.
(TOY GUN PINGS)
ADAM:
AND...CUT.
SHOULD WE DO ANOTHER TAKE?
UH...
I THINK WE GOT IT.
(SIGHS HAPPILY)
(STREETCAR RUMBLES)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
THIS SEAT TAKEN?
COME HERE OFTEN?
IF YOU'RE JUST HERE
TO MAKE FUN-
I'M NOT!
I'M HERE 'CAUSE
I WANNA LIKE...
UNDERSTAND.
SPEAKER:
I'M GLAD YOU ALL MADE IT.
TONIGHT IS ABOUT SHARING.
HARD TIMES, GOOD TIMES.
YOUR ENCOUNTERS
WITH HOMOPHOBIA,
AND HOW YOU THINK
THEY'VE AFFECTED YOU.
HOW MANY OF US
HAVE HAD TO DEAL
WITH "HARMLESS" GAY JOKES
FROM OUR FRIENDS?
EVEN HE SAID IT.
HARMLESS.
HE'S BEING FACETIOUS.
HE'S BEING WHAT?
GIRL:
SSHHHHH!
SPEAKER:
ANYONE WANNA START?
YEAH.
(CLEARS THROAT)
HI. I'M ZANE.
I'M ON THE FOOTBALL TEAM HERE,
AND SOMETIMES THE GUYS
MAKE GAY JOKES
IN THE LOCKER ROOM.
SOME OF THEM
DIRECTED AT ME,
OTHERS NOT.
I KNOW THEY'RE JOKING,
BUT IT MAKES ME FEEL...
DIFFERENT.
LIKE YOU'RE NOT PART
OF THE TEAM.
EXACTLY.
USUALLY I JUST LET IT GO,
BUT THERE'S A GUY
ON THE TEAM
THAT'S IN THE CLOSET
AND HE JOINS IN
ON THE TEASING.
AND FOR SOME REASON,
YOU KNOW,
THAT HURTS THE MOST.
SPEAKER:
INTERNALIZED HOMOPHOBIA.
IT'S WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN A PERSON BECOMES CONVINCED
BY FRIENDS, OR FAMILY,
OR SOCIETY,
THAT THEY'RE DISGUSTING
OR WRONG.
THESE PEOPLE...
OFTEN HATE THEMSELVES,
AND CONSEQUENTLY,
THEY TAKE IT OUT ON PEOPLE
WHO ARE LIKE THEM.
I'M A HOMOPHOBE.
SPEAKER:
IT STARTS WITH EACH ONE OF US
IN THIS ROOM.
♪ The only one that hurts me
more than a little bit ♪
♪ More than all the ones
before ♪
♪ I will always love you more ♪
(BUS RUMBLES AWAY)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
HEY.
HI.
YOU LEFT QUICKLY
LAST NIGHT.
YOU OKAY?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
YEAH.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO PUT YOU
ON THE SPOT,
IT'S JUST...
IT'S SOMETHING
I NEEDED TO GET OUT.
IT'S OKAY.
I'M GLAD YOU DID.
SO YOU'RE DONE MAKING
GAY JOKES?
YEAH.
AND I'M DONE PUTTING UP
WITH THEM.
I DIDN'T KNOW HOW MUCH
IT HURT YOU...
AND ME.
ONE DAY I'LL SERENADE ANYA
WITH A SONG SO SWEET,
MAYHAP SHE THINK
IT'D BE ANGELS.
BRO, THAT IS SO GAY.
HEY!
"SO GAY?"
THAT'S HOMOPHOBIC, MAN.
N-N-NO, NO,
I JUST MEANT LIKE IT WAS LAME.
RILEY:
EXACTLY. IT MAKES IT SOUND
LIKE IT'S BAD TO BE GAY.
UH, I-I DIDN'T THINK OF IT
THAT WAY.
OKAY, LOOK.
I-IT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
I PROMISE.
(LAUGHS)
NEXT TIME, TRY AND LAY OFF
THE SHOVING?
I JUST WANNA MAKE THINGS
RIGHT.
FRANKLY, YOUR TEST WAS
A DISASTER, MR. TORRES.
ROUGH.
IS THERE ANYTHING I CAN DO
TO BRING UP MY GRADE?
UH, I SUPPOSE YOU COULD
RETAKE THE TEST,
MAYBE GET A TUTOR.
I'LL TUTE YOU, DREW!
I MEAN, I'LL BE YOUR TUTOR!
THANKS, BUT, UM, ALLI BHANDARI
USUALLY HELPS ME
WITH THIS STUFF.
WELL, I MAY NOT BE
AS PRETTY AS HER,
BUT YOU WON'T FIND
A BETTER TUTOR THAN ME.
WAIT, DO YOU EVEN KNOW
THIS STUFF?
I LOVE SCIENCE.
I LARVAE IT.
(LAUGHS)
HAH!
AND LIKE MY UNCLE
ALWAYS SAYS,
"WITH A LITTLE EFFORT,
YOU CAN DO ANYTHING!"
I AM ALWAYS SAYING THAT,
AREN'T I?
HMM.
UH, ALL RIGHT.
YOU'VE GOT YOURSELF A DEAL.
COOL!
OH!
OUCH.
HEY!
SOMEONE'S HAPPY TODAY.
WELL, THE SUN IS SHINING,
THE BIRDS ARE SINGING.
YOU WERE THERE,
ELI AND I FINALLY TOOK
THAT NEXT STEP!
IT'S OFFICIAL.
I'M A THIRD WHEEL.
OH, PISH POSH, ADAM!
THAT'S JUST SILLY.
MORNING, ELI.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
NEVER BETTER.
ONCE WE'RE DONE
EDITING TOMORROW,
LA STRADA'S SHOWING
AT THE SELECT.
FELLINI'S FINEST.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
MS. DAWES:
GOOD MORNING, MY FRIENDS.
DO I SMELL OR SOMETHING?
(INHALES DEEPLY)
NO, YOU'RE GOOD.
WHAT HAPPENED?
I DON'T KNOW.
A PH METER MEASURES WHAT?
UM...
THE-THE KELVIN SCALE?
SO CLOSE!
IT MEASURES THE ACIDITY
OF A SUBSTANCE.
IN CHEMISTRY,
THE PREFIX "MEGA"
IS EQUAL TO TEN
TO WHAT POWER?
UM...
WAIT, WAIT,
I-I KNOW THIS.
UM...THE MILLIONTH?
ALMOST!
IT'S THE SIXTH.
UH, OKAY.
OKAY, STOP.
WHA-WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
(LAUGHS AWKWARDLY)
WHAT?
ARE YOU MAKING FUN OF ME?
(SIGHS) OKAY.
DON'T TAKE THIS
THE WRONG WAY,
BUT I, WELL,
I KINDA SIGNED UP
FOR THE BACHELOR AUCTION.
YOU'RE BARKING UP
THE WRONG TREE, WES.
NO, NO, NO!
I JUST FIGURED IF WE HUNG OUT,
I COULD LEARN TO BE COOL
LIKE YOU,
AND WELL,
THEN SOMEONE MIGHT ACTUALLY
BID ON ME.
WHO'D YOU HAVE IN MIND?
ANYA.
(LAUGHS)
(SIGHS)
YOU'RE IN DOUBLE ARM CASTS.
IT'S GONNA TAKE A LITTLE BIT
MORE THAN A POPPED COLLAR,
MY FRIEND.
PLEASE? COME ON,
I REALLY NEED YOUR HELP!
OKAY, FINE. I'LL TEACH YOU
EVERYTHING I KNOW,
IF I GET AT LEAST A B
ON TOMORROW'S TEST.
OKAY. OKAY, COOL.
THEN LET'S GET B-USY!
(SIGHS) I...
LAUNDRY DAY?
MY TURN TO WASH
THE PRACTICE SHIRTS.
IS THAT LIKE A TURN ON
OR SOMETHING?
(CHUCKLES)
I'M JUST ASKING!
(LAUGHS)
SO?
HOW DID IT GO,
THE WHOLE HOMOPHOBIA THING
WITH ZANE?
REALLY GOOD.
THE GAY JOKES
IN THE LOCKER ROOM?
THEY'RE NOT JUST JOKES.
THEY MESS PEOPLE UP.
ZANE'S PUT UP WITH IT
ALL YEAR.
I WISH I COULD DO
SOMETHING TO STOP IT!
WELL, YOU ARE
TEAM CAPTAIN.
WAIT!
MY DAD'S FAVOURITE MOVIE!
WHAT?
HAVE YOU EVER SEEN
SPARTACUS?
WELL, I'M GREEK.
IT'S REQUIRED VIEWING.
OKAY, THERE'S THAT SCENE
WHERE THE ROMAN SOLDIERS
ARE LOOKING THROUGH HUNDREDS
OF SLAVES FOR SPARTACUS,
AND TO PROTECT HIM,
ALL THE SLAVES GET UP AND SAY,
"I'M SPARTACUS!"
SO THE WHOLE TEAM'S
GONNA SAY THEY'RE GAY?
YOU'RE DREAMING.
BUT, IF YOU COULD GET
THE TEAM ON BOARD...
THEN I CAN GET
THE POINT ACROSS
WITHOUT HAVING
TO COME OUT!
BUT, REMEMBER HOW
THE MOVIE ENDS?
THE SOLDIERS COULDN'T FIND
SPARTACUS,
SO THEY CRUCIFIED EVERYBODY.
COME ON,
TIMES HAVE CHANGED!
(LAUGHS)
I HOPE YOU'RE RIGHT.
♪ Right about now... ♪
♪ Wan big up
the (unclear) crew ♪
♪ Rock City
and the Beach Girl 5 ♪
♪ Live life and love life ♪
♪ I've been lying to myself ♪
♪ Hanging out without you ♪
♪ Saying I'm all right
with that ♪
♪ To all my friends ♪
♪ But when I'm here alone ♪
♪ I can't stand the silence ♪
♪ Can you stop the rain
for one minute ♪
♪ Lay a little sunshine on me ♪
♪ It's been a little cloudy
lately ♪
♪ Hey! Hey! ♪
♪ The sound
of your voice beats ♪
♪ Textin' you miss me ♪
♪ Your conversation beats
the hell outta me wishin' ♪
♪ Lay a little sunshine on me ♪
♪ You said if I need somebody ♪
♪ So get up off the couch,
jump in your car ♪
♪ Oh-oh oh-oh ♪
♪ Come and get me ♪
MISS EDWARDS!
IT'S LATE.
YOU STICKING AROUND
FOR SENIOR'S POTTERY?
(LAUGHS)
EVENING, LADIES.
NO, I WAS JUST
FINISHING SOMETHING.
ACTUALLY,
I'M A LITTLE STUCK.
WELL, MAYBE I CAN HELP.
IT'S ABOUT
THE FILM PROJECT.
I'M HAVING TROUBLE WITH
THE CHARACTERS' MOTIVATIONS.
IT JUST, IT SEEMS LIKE
JULIET'S BEING STUPID.
I MEAN, SHE TAKES THIS HUGE
LEAP OF FAITH ON ROMEO,
PRETENDING TO BE DEAD.
OH, TEEN LOVE.
EXACTLY.
HE'S AN IRRESPONSIBLE
TEEN BOY!
HOT ONE DAY,
COLD THE NEXT.
WHAT IF HE CHANGED HIS MIND
AND BAILED ON THE PLAN?
SHE'D GET BURNED!
IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
HOW IS SHE SUPPOSED TO KNOW
HOW HE REALLY FEELS?
UH... WELL,
JULIET KNEW DEEP DOWN
THAT ROMEO LOVED HER,
AND I GUESS SHE JUST
HAD FAITH
THAT THINGS WOULD WORK OUT.
YOU KNOW WHAT THEIR BIGGEST
PROBLEM WAS?
LACK OF COMMUNICATION?
YES! AH, IF ONLY ROMEO
AND JULIET HAD SMARTPHONES!
GOOD NIGHT!
NIGHT.
(SIGHS)
(STREETCAR RUMBLES)
(BUS RUMBLES AWAY)
GUYS:
YEAH, WHOO!
(TEAM CHATTERS)
(CLAPPING HANDS)
LISTEN UP!
GUYS, I'VE GOT SOME NEWS.
GUY:
UH-OH.
OWEN:
OOOH! PINK SHIRT GOT YOU TOO,
HUH?
RILEY:
NOT JUST ME, IT GOT EVERYBODY!
TODAY, WE'RE ALL WEARING PINK.
OH YEAH, RIGHT.
YOU TRYING TO MAKE US
ALL FLAMERS?
HOW DO YOU THINK A GAY PERSON
FEELS WHEN YOU SAY THAT?
RILEY:
THE LOCKER ROOM IS NO LONGER
A PLACE FOR HOMOPHOBIA.
NO MORE COMMENTS.
(OWEN GROAN)
NO MORE JOKES.
GUY: WHAT?!
RILEY: CLEAR?
I REMEMBER YOU JOKING TOO.
I WAS BEING A BAD CAPTAIN.
NOW PUT IT ON,
UNLESS YOU WANNA GO SHIRTS
VERSUS SKINS TODAY.
BUT I DOUBT YOU'LL LIKE
THOSE ODDS.
(GUYS LAUGH, WHISTLE)
GUYS:
GOOD POINT. MM-HMM.
(HELMET CLATTERS)
GUY:
WHERE YOU GOING?
YOU CAN'T REACH EVERYONE.
♪ I don't care about anything ♪
♪ I don't care,
I don't care about anything ♪
♪ I don't care about you ♪
(SARCASTICALLY)
THANKS FOR RETURNING MY CALLS!
ELI: (SIGHS)
CLARE: CAN WE TALK?
NO THANK YOU.
WELL, IT'S HAPPENING.
OKAY, THE OTHER DAY,
THAT WASN'T JUST A KISS
FOR THE FILM.
THERE'S SOMETHING BETWEEN US,
ELI,
AND YOU KNOW IT.
YOU'RE WRONG.
I'M NOT STUPID!
OKAY,
EITHER YOU LIKE ME,
OR YOU'RE A SOCIOPATH
WHO LIKES TO JERK
PEOPLE AROUND
AND HURT THEM,
AND I KNOW IT'S NOT
THE LATTER.
(SIGHS)
OR IS IT?
I'M SORRY I LED YOU ON.
WOW.
("All the World is All That
is the Case" by Parlovr plays)
♪♪♪
ZANE:
SPARTACUS! GENIUS!
WHY DIDN'T I THINK
OF THAT?
I MAY NOT BE "EINSTEEN,"
BUT I HAVE MY MOMENTS.
(BOTH LAUGH)
NICE TO SEE OWEN
THE HOMOPHOBE
FEELING LIKE
THE ODD MAN OUT
FOR A CHANGE.
YEAH, IT FEELS SO GOOD.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
♪♪♪