HEY.
SO,
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
PREGNANT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT, ALLI.
I'M PREGNANT.
AND I'M A TEENAGER.
I'M ONE OF THOSE...
PREGNANT TEENAGERS?
WELL, I MEAN,
LOOK ON THE BRIGHT SIDE.
THERE'S A BRIGHT SIDE?
I CAN'T WAIT
TO HEAR THIS.
AT LEAST NOW YOU KNOW WHY,
YOU KNOW,
THE BOOB ENLARGEMENT.
OKAY,
YOU'RE NOT HELPING, ALLI.
I'M SORRY,
I'M TRYING!
HAVE YOU TOLD YOUR BROTHER?
NOT YET.
WELL, WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO TELL KC?
NOTHING.
HELLO! YOU'VE BEEN DOING
A WHOLE LOT OF NOTHING.
ISN'T IT TIME
YOU DO SOMETHING?
YOU KNOW, DISCUSS OPTIONS
WITH BABY DADDY?
I'M IN THE TOP 24
OF NEXT TEEN STAR!
DO YOU KNOW HOW MAJOR
THAT IS?
YOU'RE STILL DOING THAT?
UH, YEAH!
I'VE WORKED HARD
FOR THIS,
AND NOTHING IS GONNA STOP
MY DREAM.
NOT EVEN A PREGNANCY?
(SIGHS)
NOT EVEN A PREGNANCY.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever, whatever ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
KC:
THE WHOLE SCHOOL IS TALKING
ABOUT YOU, MS. MIDDLETON.
UH, TALKING?
ABOUT WHAT?
RIGHT, LIKE YOU DON'T
ALREADY KNOW.
MY GIRL MADE NEXT TEEN STAR!
TOP 24, BABY!
YEAH!
JENNA:
UH, I FEEL SO LUCKY.
(LAUGHS)
UM...
WHAT IF I TOLD YOU EVERYTHING
WAS ABOUT TO CHANGE?
YOU'RE NOT GONNA GET FAMOUS
AND LEAVE ME, ARE YOU?
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I-I'D NEVER LEAVE YOU.
YEAH THAT'S WHAT YOU SAY NOW,
BUT SOON YOU'LL BE ON TOUR,
DATING SOME SORT OF BIEBER.
THEN YOU DON'T KNOW ME AT ALL.
I'M MORE OF A R PATZ
KIND OF GIRL.
WHY?
WOULD YOU EVER LEAVE ME?
YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN MY LIFE,
I'M NORMAL.
MY MOM'S DOING GREAT,
I'M ON THE FOOTBALL TEAM,
AND I'M DATING
THE HOTTEST CHEERLEADER.
(LAUGHS UNCOMFORTABLY)
I GUESS WE'RE BOTH
PRETTY LUCKY.
WE'VE GOT A GOOD THING.
WHY IN THE WORLD
WOULD I WANT TO MESS THAT UP?
(SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
MR. SIMPSON:
CONNOR, YOU'RE LUCKY YOU HAVE
FRIENDS LIKE DAVE AND WESLEY.
NO, I'M NOT.
MR. SIMPSON:
THEY'RE JUST WORRIED ABOUT YOU!
YEAH. WELL, IT'S NONE
OF THEIR BUSINESS.
AND IT'S NONE OF YOURS.
HEY!
AS YOUR GUARDIAN,
YOU SNEAKING AROUND TO MEET
AN OLDER WOMAN
YOU MET ONLINE,
IS MY CONCERN.
I'M GOING TO THE M.I. LAB.
RIGHT NOW I CAN'T TRUST YOU
AROUND COMPUTERS.
WHAT!?
I TALKED TO YOUR OTHER
TEACHERS, AND THEY AGREED.
WE HAVE TO REVOKE YOUR COMPUTER
PRIVILEGES FOR NOW.
YOU CAN'T DO THAT!
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO,
WITHOUT MY COMPUTER?
WHAT AM I GONNA DO WITH THIS?
IN MY DAY,
NOTEBOOKS WERE OUR COMPUTERS.
(SIGHS)
WOULD YOU JUST GIVE IT TRY,
PLEASE?
WHO KNOWS,
YOU MIGHT ENJOY IT.
I HIGHLY DOUBT THAT.
OKEY DOKEY, EVERYONE.
WORK WITH YOUR PARTNERS
ON YOUR GENETICS LAB,
AND WE'LL TAKE UP THE RESULTS
AT THE END OF CLASS.
"GENETICALLY SPEAKING,
ATTACHED EARLOBES
ARE A RECESSIVE TRAIT."
JENNA:
OW!
ATTACHED.
HMM, IF WE KNEW WHAT KIND
OF EARLOBES KC HAD,
WE COULD PROBABLY DETERMINE...
LET IT GO, BHANDARI.
STILL HAVEN'T TOLD HIM, HUH?
THE TIMING WAS ALL WRONG.
HE WAS SO HAPPY, AND...
I DIDN'T WANT TO BURST
HIS BUBBLE.
RIGHT. UNPLANNED PREGNANCIES
CAN BE SUCH A BRING DOWN!
WE'RE FINALLY
IN A GOOD PLACE.
YOU SHOULD'VE SEEN HIM
WHEN HE CAME TO MY AUDITION.
HE WAS SO SUPPORTIVE
AND GREAT.
WOW.
SUPPORTIVE AND GREAT?
I KNOW, RIGHT?
GREAT TRAITS TO HAVE
IN THE POTENTIAL FATHER
TO YOUR POTENTIAL CHILD,
DON'T YA THINK?
MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT'S JUST THAT
WE'RE SO IN TUNE RIGHT NOW.
WE ALWAYS TALK
THROUGH OUR PROBLEMS.
LIKE MATURE ADULTS?
YEAH!
AND MATURITY'S ANOTHER
GREAT QUALITY TO HAVE
IN A POTENTIAL FATHER.
ALLI, I GET IT.
GREAT.
NOW LET'S SEE IF THIS KID
WILL HAVE MID-DIGITAL HAIR.
MM... RIGHT.
VERY HAIRY KNUCKLES.
(DAVE AND WESLEY CHUCKLE)
OH COME ON, CONNOR.
WESLEY:
WE'RE TRYING TO REACH OUT
TO YOU.
GET IT?
CONNOR:
LEAVE ME ALONE.
DAVE:
LOOK CONNOR,
LOOK I KNOW YOU'RE MAD,
WE WERE JUST TRYING
TO LOOK OUT FOR YOU.
WESLEY:
YEAH, WE LOVE YOU MAN.
OKAY LOOK,
MAYBE YOU AND LOVEQUEEN16
WERE MEANT TO BE TOGETHER
AND WE WERE WRONG,
AND WE SHOULDN'T HAVE RATTED
YOU OUT TO SIMPSON.
WE'RE REALLY SORRY.
CAN WE STILL BE FRIENDS?
WHY DO YOU EVEN WANT
TO BE MY FRIEND?
WELL, RISK IS MORE FUN
WITH THREE PEOPLE.
CONNOR:
THEN FIND ANOTHER GAME.
SO WHAT, THAT'S IT?
YOU'RE JUST NOT GONNA HAVE
ANY FRIENDS?
I HAVE A FRIEND.
I'M JUST NOT ALLOWED
TO TALK TO HER.
ANYA:
(LAUGHS)
IT'S NOT GONNA WORK!
HE'S TOO BUSY.
RILEY:
IT'LL TOTALLY WORK,
WHO WOULDN'T TAKE A FEW MINUTES
TO HELP SOMEONE
WITH A SCHOOL ASSIGNMENT?
THAT'S YOUR COVER?
WHATEVER, 'CAUSE MY MOM'S CANCER
DOCTOR'S TOTALLY NOT GAY.
I'VE ONLY HAD FOUR CRUSHES
IN MY LIFE.
THREE OF THEM TURNED OUT
TO BE GAY,
AND... JURY'S STILL OUT
ON PETER.
SO?
SO, MY GAYDAR HAS AT LEAST
A 75 PERCENT SUCCESS RATE.
I'M TELLING YOU,
DR. CHRIS IS GAY.
(SCOFFS)
WHY DON'T YOU JUST ASK HIM?
YOU CAN'T JUST ASK,
YOU HAVE TO LURE IT OUT OF HIM.
SO, WHAT IF HE IS?
WE'LL SEE.
THIS'LL BE FUN!
THERE YOU ARE!
CONNOR:
HEY. I'M SORRY
I WASN'T ON CHAT LAST NIGHT.
LOVEQUEEN16:
THAT'S OKAY,
WHAT HAPPENED?
CONNOR:
MY GODFATHER TOOK AWAY
MY COMPUTER.
EVERYONE'S AFRAID OF ME
SEEING YOU.
AND YESTERDAY...
LOVEQUEEN16:
OH, I'M SORRY I LEFT.
I-I DIDN'T WANT TO GET YOU
IN TROUBLE.
I KNOW.
LOVEQUEEN16:
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY EVERYONE'S SO AFRAID
IF WE TALK TO EACH OTHER!
CONNOR:
WE'RE NOT DOING ANYTHING WRONG.
THEY OBVIOUSLY CAN'T UNDERSTAND
OUR...
RELATIONSHIP.
(LAUGHS)
I'M SORRY IF YOU'VE HAD
A ROUGH DAY,
DO YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT?
CONNOR:
UM, CAN YOU PICK ME UP
AT SCHOOL?
WOW, UM... SURE!
UH, I HAVE A COUPLE OF THINGS
I HAVE TO TAKE CARE OF FIRST,
WILL YOU STILL BE THERE
IN AN HOUR OR SO?
UM, I'LL PLAY BASKETBALL
UNTIL I SEE YOU.
LOVEQUEEN16:
WE'LL UH, GET SOME FOOD,
AND GO TO MY PLACE.
AND FINALLY TEST OUT
THAT EXPANSION PACK.
CONNOR:
THAT'D BE GREAT!
BYE.
UH, SO UH,
DOCTORS WORK REALLY LONG HOURS.
SO WHAT EFFECT DOES YOUR JOB
HAVE ON PERSONAL RELATIONSHIPS?
WELL, RIGHT NOW,
I'M NOT IN A RELATIONSHIP,
SO THAT'S THE EFFECT.
OH, THAT'S TOO BAD.
RILEY:
WHAT HAPPENED?
I MEAN,
WERE YOU TOO BUSY?
WELL, ERIN HAD THE SAME AMOUNT
OF DEDICATION TO WORK AS I DID.
WE WERE BOTH TOO BUSY.
AND AARON WAS?
SORRY, MY FORMER PARTNER.
RILEY:
AND HOW DO YOU SPELL THAT?
WAS IT A MRS., A MR.?
DOCTOR!
DR. ERIN DANSON.
WHAT COURSE IS THIS FOR AGAIN?
UM, RELATIONSHIPS AND SOCIETY.
REALLY?
I'VE NEVER HEARD OF THAT.
RILEY:
WELL, IT MUST'VE BEEN
A WHILE
SINCE YOU WERE AT UNIVERSITY,
RIGHT?
YOU'RE IN UNIVERSITY?
I THOUGHT-
YEP! UH,
UNIVERSITY.
SE-SECOND YEAR.
WHAT ARE YOU MAJORING IN?
ANYA:
THIS AND THAT.
LIBERAL ARTS...?
YEAH, EXACTLY!
YEAH.
OKAY. WELL, I WISH THEY'D
HAD A COURSE
LIKE THE ONE YOU'RE TAKING
WHEN I WAS THERE.
WHY'S THAT?
WELL, MAYBE THEN I WOULDN'T
HAVE HAD TO WAIT
'TIL MED SCHOOL
TO GET A GIRLFRIEND!
ANYA:
A GIRLFRIEND! HUH!
INTERESTING.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(KNOCKS)
KC:
WHAT'S UP, SUPERSTAR?
GOT YOUR TEXT.
WHAT'S WRONG?
UH... KC,
WE NEED TO TALK.
KC:
UH OH. IS SOMETHING WRONG?
MAYBE.
OKAY,
YOU'RE FREAKING ME OUT.
I'M REALLY SCARED.
WHATEVER IT IS,
WE CAN GET THROUGH IT.
WHAT IS IT?
YOU'RE GONNA BE A DAD.
YOU'RE PREGNANT?
ARE YOU SURE?
PRETTY SURE.
I-I STILL HAVE TO GO
SEE A DOCTOR.
BUT WE USED BIRTH CONTROL.
NOT ALWAYS.
THAT ONE TIME?
WE GOT CAUGHT UP IN THE MOMENT.
THIS IS INSANE!
HEY.
(SNIFFLES)
DON'T CRY.
I JUST, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO.
WE'LL FIGURE OUT.
SO YOU'RE NOT MAD AT ME?
MAD AT YOU?
WHY WOULD I BE
MAD AT YOU, JENNA?
THIS MISTAKE IS BOTH
OUR FAULTS.
WE'RE IN THIS TOGETHER.
I'M SO GLAD TO HEAR
YOU SAY THAT.
I CAN'T GO THROUGH
THIS ALONE.
AND YOU WON'T HAVE TO.
I'LL BE WITH YOU
EVERY STEP OF THE WAY.
(RELIEVED SIGH)
AND ONCE YOU GET
THE ABORTION,
IT'LL ALL BE OVER.
(SIGHS)
I CAN'T HAVE
AN ABORTION, KC!
SERIOUSLY?
WHAT ABOUT SCHOOL,
AND FOOTBALL,
AND CHEERLEADING?
WHO'S GOING TO TAKE
CARE OF IT?
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS HAPPENING.
WHAT ABOUT NEXT TEEN STAR?
WE CAN'T BE PARENTS RIGHT NOW.
I KNOW!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
MY DAD'S IN JAIL, JENNA.
I CAN'T BE ONE.
I NEED TO THINK ABOUT IT,
OKAY?
ANYA:
COSMO AND VOGUE?
OKAY, MOM.
GIFT SHOP. MAGAZINE RUN.
COMING?
I MIGHT JUST GO HOME.
OH...
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
IT'S STUPID.
TELL ME.
YOUR MOM'S IN THERE
WITH CANCER,
AND I'M UPSET
OVER DR. CHRIS.
YOU HAVE A CRUSH
ON DR. CHRIS?
WELL, HE DOESN'T GO
TO OUR SCHOOL,
SO I THOUGHT
IT MIGHT BE EASIER.
RILEY,
RELATIONSHIPS ARE NEVER EASY.
BUT, WHEN YOU FIND
THE RIGHT PERSON,
IT'LL BE WORTH IT.
(HALF LAUGHS)
SO,
WHAT'S YOUR DREAM GUY LIKE?
WELL, SMART,
I GUESS.
UH...
FUNNY AND KIND,
AND HE'S GOTTA LOVE SPORTS.
AND BE SUPER CUTE?
WELL, THAT COULDN'T HURT.
HE SOUNDS LIKE
SOMEONE WE KNOW.
ZANE'S NOT GONNA GIVE ME
ANOTHER CHANCE.
MAYBE...
MAYBE NOT?
SO YOU'RE OVER DR. CHRIS?
NO POINT CRUSHING
ON A STRAIGHT GUY.
GOOD. BECAUSE HE DOESN'T
SEEM LIKE YOUR TYPE.
'CAUSE HE'S YOURS?
WELL, HE DID MENTION
HE WAS SINGLE.
(SCOFFS)
AS IF.
WHAT?
(LAUGHS)
YOU KNOW,
THANKS TO YOU,
HE THINKS I'M IN UNIVERSITY!
MEG:
WAIVERS, POR FAVOR!
IN MY HANDS,
SIGNED BY BOTH YOU
AND YOUR PARENT OR GUARDIAN!
STAT!
ALL SET?
JENNA:
UH, I THINK SO.
THERE WAS A LOT TO TAKE IN.
ACTUALLY MEG,
UM, THERE WAS ONE PART
THAT I DIDN'T QUITE UNDERSTAND.
WHAT ARE YOU,
HER LEGAL COUNSEL?
AND PART TIME THERAPIST.
NOW IT SAYS HERE
THAT CONTESTANTS
"MUST MAKE ANY PREEXISTING
CONDITIONS KNOWN
TO THE PRODUCERS".
SO WHAT DOES THIS MEAN,
LIKE ASTHMA,
OR LIKE,
SAY... PREGNANCY?
SOMETHING I NEED TO KNOW?
UM...
NO, IT'S JUST THAT
I REALLY WANTED TO TRY OUT
FOR NEXT TEEN STAR,
BUT I'M YOU KNOW,
WITH CHILD.
NEAT.
NO,
CONTESTANTS CAN BE PREGGARS.
HELL, YOU'D BE THE FACE
OF THE SHOW FOR A WHILE.
SHE WOULD?
MEG:
YEAH! WHO DOESN'T LOVE
THE POOR PREGNANT TEENAGER
WHO'S TRYING TO BE A STAR?
BUT IN REALITY?
(SCOFFS) NIGHTMARE!
BETWEEN THE SHOOTING SKED,
PUBLICITY EVENTS,
TEETH WHITENING,
SUMMER CONCERT TOUR?
YOU DO NOT WANNA BE CARRYING
A BABY KANGAROO
IN THAT POUCH.
WAIVERS, PEOPLE!
NOW!
(HORN HONKS)
(ENGINE RUMBLES)
CAN WE JUST GO?
LOVEQUEEN16:
IT SOUNDS LIKE YOU HAD
A BAD DAY.
THEY TOOK ALL MY STUFF.
IT'S NOT FAIR,
THERE'S A ROUTINE,
AN ORDER, YOU CAN'T JUST
CHANGE SOMETHING LIKE THAT
FOR SOMEONE WITH ASPERGER'S!
I DON'T WANT THIS!
(SIGHS)
I HATE THEM SO MUCH.
LOOKS LIKE IT'S ME AND YOU
AGAINST THE WORLD.
W-WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
LOVEQUEEN16:
DON'T BE NERVOUS,
WE'RE FRIENDS, RIGHT?
CONNOR:
(GASPS)
I'M-I'M NOT COMFORTABLE.
LOVEQUEEN16:
WE'LL GO BACK TO MY PLACE,
WE CAN BE ALONE.
MORE... INTIMATE.
CONNOR:
I JUST WANT TO PLAY
"REALM OF DOOM".
REALLY?
THAT'S ALL?
CONNOR: STOP!
LOVEQUEEN16: WHAT?
CONNOR: STOP IT!
LOVEQUEEN16:
CONNOR!
I'M-I'M SORRY!
CONNOR:
GO AWAY!
(CAR RUMBLES AWAY)
(TIRES SQUEAL)
HOW WAS THE ULTRASOUND?
UM...
KIND OF COLD,
BUT OKAY.
HOW ARE YOU?
UH, I AM STILL TRYING
TO PROCESS
THAT MY BABY SISTER'S PREGNANT.
WELL,
THE PRENATAL SCREENING
SHOWS THE BABY'S HEALTHY.
ALL THE PARTS
ARE IN THE RIGHT PLACE.
TAKE A LOOK.
ARE YOU THE BABY'S FATHER?
KYLE:
OH, NO,
I'M HER BROTHER.
UH, CAN HE STAY?
DOCTOR:
SURE.
YOU'RE FURTHER ALONG
THAN YOU THOUGHT.
THE BABY'S ABOUT...
20 WEEKS.
(SIGHS)
WOW.
DOCTOR:
DID YOU NOTICE YOU WERE
MISSING YOUR PERIODS?
HAVE ANY OF THE OTHER
SYMPTOMS?
YEAH.
BUT YOU DIDN'T SPEAK
TO A PHYSICIAN?
(SIGHS) I...
I HOPED I WAS IMAGINING IT.
THEN I JUST GOT SCARED.
DOCTOR:
WELL SCARED OR NOT,
YOU PUT YOUR HEALTH,
AND YOUR BABY'S HEALTH
AT RISK.
UH...
OH, NO!
I-I TOOK SOME DIET PILLS.
DOCTOR:
WERE THEY PRESCRIBED?
JENNA:
NO. I ONLY TOOK THEM
A COUPLE OF TIMES.
NEVER AGAIN, OKAY?
HAVE YOU TAKEN FOLIC ACID?
DONE ANYTHING TO OPTIMIZE
YOUR BABY'S HEALTH?
I...
GUESS I WAS JUST HOPING
IT WOULD JUST GO AWAY.
WHAT IF,
WHAT IF THAT HAPPENED?
ARE WE TALKING ABOUT ABORTION?
BECAUSE THIS WOULD BE
A LATE-TERM ABORTION.
AND USUALLY
THOSE ARE RESERVED
FOR WOMEN WHOSE HEALTH
IS THREATENED.
SO...
IS IT TOO LATE?
IT DEFINITELY POSES
GREATER RISKS,
AND COMPLICATIONS.
IF YOU WERE TO KEEP
THE BABY,
WHAT SUPPORT MECHANISMS
WOULD YOU HAVE IN PLACE?
UM, JUST ME.
UM, OUR DAD'S WORKING
OUT WEST,
AND... HER MOM'S NOT
IN THE PICTURE.
HMM.
WILL THE BABY'S FATHER
BE INVOLVED?
OH...
UH, I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, ADOPTION
IS ANOTHER OPTION.
NONE OF THEM'S EASY,
I'M AFRAID.
IF YOU NEED ANY INFORMATION,
I CAN DIRECT YOU
TO AN AGENCY.
SEE YOU IN A MONTH!
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SIGHS)
ANYA:
SO IF WE INCREASE
THE VALUE OF Y,
TO GREATER X...
Y MINUS ONE IS...
ZANE!
WHAT DO I DO?
ZANE?
UM, WE'RE HAVING SOME TROUBLE
WITH ALGEBRA,
CAN WE PICK YOUR BRAIN?
I GUESS, I COULD TAKE A LOOK.
WITH ALL THESE VARIABLES,
I'M LOST.
YEAH, IT LOOKS LIKE
YOU'VE GOT SOME FACTORIZATION
OF POLYNOMIALS THERE.
CAN YOU WORK THIS EQUATION
WITH ME?
SURE.
SO THAT'S ALL THAT HAPPENED?
NOTHING ELSE?
SHE JUST TOUCHED MY LEG.
I'M SORRY.
DO YOU KNOW HER NAME?
WHERE SHE LIVES?
NO.
WELL, I'M GLAD
YOU TOLD US, CONNOR.
WE'LL FIND HER,
SOMEHOW, OKAY?
I GOT HER LICENSE PLATE.
PHOTOGRAPHIC MEMORY.
WELL THEN,
WRITE IT DOWN!
WE'LL CALL THE POLICE.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
I HAVE NO FRIENDS,
AND NO COMPUTER.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE TAKEN AWAY
YOUR STUFF.
I KNOW THAT...
THAT KIND OF CHANGE
CAN BE DISRUPTIVE.
WE... OVERREACTED.
SO DOES THAT MEAN
I CAN USE MY COMPUTER AGAIN?
YES,
BUT WITH NEW GUIDELINES!
YOU CAN ONLY PLAY
VIDEO GAMES WITH ME.
HEY, I WAS A FROGGER EXPERT
BACK IN THE DAY.
(LAUGHS)
DO YOU KNOW FROGGER?
CONNOR: FROGGER?!
MR. SIMPSON: YEAH.
OKAY.
YOU KNOW,
DAVE AND WESLEY,
THEY ONLY WANTED TO DO
WHAT WAS BEST FOR YOU,
YOU KNOW THAT, RIGHT?
YEAH, I KNOW.
THANKS.
I-I THOUGHT YOU SAID
WE'D GET THROUGH THIS TOGETHER.
THAT'S WHEN I THOUGHT
WE WERE GETTING THROUGH
THE SAME THING!
I-I-I DIDN'T THINK
FOR ONE SECOND
YOU'D ACTUALLY CONSIDER
HAVING THE BABY!
THE DOCTOR SAID AN ABORTION
WOULD BE RISKY!
HOW FAR ALONG ARE YOU?
FAR.
ALMOST FIVE MONTHS.
OKAY. GREAT,
SO YOUR STUPID DENIAL
TOOK AWAY OUR OPTIONS.
I'M SORRY,
BUT IT'S TOO LATE!
SO THAT'S IT?
I DON'T EVEN GET A SAY
ANYMORE?!
MAYBE IT'S FOR THE BEST, KC!
MAYBE THIS IS HOW
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE!
HOW IS IT FOR THE BEST
IN ANY POSSIBLE WAY, JENNA?
DO YOU EVEN HEAR YOURSELF?
(SIGHS ANGRILY)
IF YOU WANT TO KEEP IT,
I CAN'T STOP YOU.
DOES THAT MEAN...
WE'RE GONNA BE PARENTS?
YOU DO WHATEVER YOU WANT.
I CAN'T BE INVOLVED.
WHAT?
YOU'RE GONNA MAKE ME
GO THROUGH THIS ALONE?
JENNA, MY LIFE IS BEING HELD
TOGETHER BY TAPE RIGHT NOW.
I DON'T NEED THIS.
I'M SORRY.
(CRYING)
(SIGHS)
(BUTTONS CLICK)
WOO-HOO-HOO!
WHO OWNS YOU? WHO?
DAVE.
WHAT'S UP?
I JUST WANNA SAY SOMETHING.
I, UH...
AH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT,
MY MAN.
WE FEEL THE LOVE.
MR. SIMPSON:
OH-HO-HO-HO-HO!
ALL RIGHT,
NOW I NEED A REMATCH.
I'M GETTING IN THIS.
EXHAUSTED!
♪♪♪
♪ Mistakes that I've made ♪
♪ I've gotta take it ♪
♪ One day at a time ♪
HEY.
SO HOW'D IT GO WITH KC?
I GUESS I'M A SINGLE
PARENT NOW.
THIS IS GOING TO MEAN
BIG CHANGES FOR BOTH OF US.
KYLE, I-I'M SO SORRY.
THAT'S THE DEAL.
YOUR LIFE IS MY LIFE.
THE BABY'S TOO, I GUESS.
IT'S NOT GONNA BE EASY
FOR THE LITTLE SQUIRT,
BUT...
AT LEAST HE'LL HAVE A COOL
UNCLE TO TAKE HIM MUDDING.
SHE IS NEVER GOING MUDDING!
(LAUGHS)
SO, YOU'RE NOT MAD AT ME?
IS IT MY FAVOURITE THING
THAT'S EVER HAPPENED?
NO.
IS IT GONNA SUCK
BIG TIME SOMETIMES?
YES.
BUT, HAVE WE BEEN
THROUGH WORSE?
YEAH.
THE MIDDLETONS DON'T GIVE UP.
SO, WHAT NOW?
(SIGHS)
I NEED A RIDE.
WHERE TO, DOCTOR?
NEXT TEEN STAR.
WARDROBE FITTING.
THE MIDDLETONS DON'T GIVE UP.