DREW:
OKAY, IF YOU WERE TO WRITE
AN ESSAY ON THE VICTORIAN ERA,
WHERE WOULD YOU START?
UH, WHEN WAS IT?
THE VICTORIAN ERA?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD HAVE SAID
THE ESSAY ALLI WROTE FOR YOU
WAS YOUR OWN.
I'M TRYING TO FORGET
ABOUT THAT.
SO I'M GUESSING
YOU TWO ARE OVER?
I DON'T APPRECIATE
BEING CALLED STUPID.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
I'M A NEW GUY
AT A NEW SCHOOL.
I DON'T SEE WHY
I SHOULD BE TIED DOWN.
I SUCK AT SCHOOLWORK,
BUT I RULE AT GIRLS.
GIRL:
HI.
DREW:
HEY.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
STEP RIGHT UP,
IT'S EGO TIME.
WATCH ANDREW TORRES DOWN
TWELVE RAW EGGS.
HA HA. MAKE FUN.
BUT YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO HAVE THE HOTNESS
THROWN AT YOU
LEFT, RIGHT AND CENTRE.
SO WITH ALL YOUR OPTIONS,
WHO'RE YOU GONNA PICK?
I DON'T KNOW.
SOMEONE SIMPLE.
OKAY.
ONTO BIGGER AND BETTER THINGS.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Ooh-oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh! ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(Whatever! Woo-ooh!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
(Whatever!)
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
OKAY, HERE'S WHAT
I'M LOOKING FOR:
CUTE, FUN,
ATTRACTED TO SHINY OBJECTS.
WHERE SHOULD I LOOK?
THE PET STORE?
NO, SERIOUSLY, MAN.
HELP ME NAVIGATE.
AN ARTSY GIRL
COULD BE COOL.
MIGHT INVOLVE
NUDE PORTRAITURE?
AND UNDERARM HAIR.
AH, WHAT ABOUT
THE THEATRE CHICKS?
SURE,
IF YOU WANT DRAMA 24/7.
OH.
OOH.
CAN'T GO WRONG
WITH A CHEERLEADER.
CUTE, PEPPY,
AND THEY CAN DO NO WRONG
IN THOSE SKIRTS.
(CHUCKLES)
I HEAR MARISOL'S
SINGLE.
OH YEAH?
HMM...
HEY, MARISOL,
AS A POWER SQUADDER
AND A HOTTIE,
I'M CONCERNED ABOUT
YOUR CURRENT STATUS AS SINGLE.
OH, THE RIGHT GUY
HASN'T COME ALONG, I GUESS.
OH, WHAT'S TAKING HIM
SO LONG?
I DON'T KNOW.
I COULDN'T BE MORE AVAILABLE
RIGHT NOW.
WELL, SOMEBODY HAS
TO ASK YOU OUT.
IT'D BE A SIN NOT TO.
YEAH, BUT WHO?
I HEARD YOU'RE WITH ALLI.
I DON'T SEE HER AROUND,
DO YOU?
NO.
WELL THEN,
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
VITE! VITE!
WE CAN'T BE EN RETARD
FOR FRENCH AGAIN.
HEELS!
WHAT'S THE RUSH?
SAV:
HEY, HOT STUFF!
HOLLY J:
HEY.
(LAUGHING)
UM, HOT STUFF?
WHAT AM I MISSING HERE?
MILD FLIRTATION.
NOTHING SERIOUS.
I EXPECTED YOU TO ACT WEIRD
POST BREAK-UP,
BUT SAV?
WHAT'S SO WRONG
WITH SAV?
YOU LIKE HIM!
NO!
NO. OF COURSE NOT.
HMM, WHAT WOULD
DECLAN SAY?
FIONA.
BUT YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
MY SISTER-IN-LAW SOME DAY.
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
GONNA HAPPEN IN THE FUTURE,
BUT I DO KNOW THAT THE THOUGHT
OF SAV AND I TOGETHER IS...
WRONG.
SO VERY...
RIGHT.
AND SO, SO HOT.
SO YOU KISSED?!
AND HER LIPS WEREN'T ALL LIKE
TIGHT AND ANGRY AND HARD?
NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
MAYBE SHE WAS A BIT
SURPRISED.
AND SHE DIDN'T SLAP YOU?
NO.
THAT'S GOOD, RIGHT?
DUDE, SHE WAS LIKE BEST FRIENDS
WITH YOUR EX GIRLFRIEND.
NO, MAN,
ANYA DOESN'T NEED TO KNOW.
FUN SECRET TIMES
IN THE STUDENT COUNCIL ROOM
AWAIT.
OKAY, MR. COMMITMENT,
DON'T GO BUYING
ANY ENGAGEMENT RINGS JUST YET.
OF COURSE NOT.
NOT UNTIL I'M FINISHED
MY LUNCH.
DAVE:
HEY, CON-MAN.
SO, I WAS THINKING,
IT'S COOL THAT YOU HAVE A GIRL,
EVEN IF SHE ONLY EXISTS
IN AN ONLINE RPG.
THANK YOU.
I APPRECIATE YOUR APPROVAL.
BUT KNOW WHAT'S EVEN BETTER
THAN A VIRTUAL GIRLFRIEND?
A REAL ONE.
THAT'S NOT NECESSARILY
ACCURATE.
OKAY, COME ON,
CAN YOU MAKE OUT
WITH AN AVATAR?
THAT'S NOT IMPORTANT TO US.
CAN SHE BUY YOU
COOL GIFTS?
HER GREATEST GIFT TO ME
IS HER ADVANCED
MAGIC SKILL LEVEL.
OKAY, OKAY,
SO CAN YOU TAKE HER
TO THE DANCE AS A DATE?
DIDN'T THINK SO.
CONNOR:
BUT WE AREN'T SUPPOSED TO MEET
STRANGERS OFF THE INTERNET.
OKAY, SO ME AND WES
WILL COME CHECK IT OUT
AND MAKE SURE IT'S SAFE.
IN PUBLIC,
SO NO WORRIES, HUH?
OKAY, YEAH.
SO, DO YOU JUST WANT ME
TO GO ON A DATE
SO YOU KNOW WHAT
IT'S LIKE?
(SNORTED LAUGH)
BOOM! DISSED!
CONNOR!
(LAUGHING)
SHEESH.
JENNA:
YOU USUALLY FINISH
ALL THE CHEESE CURDS
BEFORE I CAN GET ONE.
YOU THINKING ABOUT DREW?
I ADMIT DOING HIS ESSAY
WAS STUPID, BUT...
I SAW A SIDE OF HIM
AND IT WAS REALLY MEAN.
SO, ARE YOU OVER HIM?
(SIGHING)
MARISOL:
I MEAN I WAS SO NERVOUS...
I'M PRETTY SURE
HE'S OVER ME.
MARISOL:
I MEAN, LIKE YOU'RE
A QUARTERBACK
AND I'M CHEERLEADER SO...
CAN WE GO?
MARISOL:
LIKE I SAID,
ALL THE GIRLS THINK
YOU'RE THE HOTTEST GUY
ON THE TEAM.
THEN KC,
THEN RILEY,
THEN ZANE, THEN OWEN.
GLAD TO HEAR
I'M ON TOP.
HI.
WANNA ORDER SOMETHING?
UM, LADIES FIRST.
WHAT'RE YOU GETTING?
A LARGE ICE TEA FOR ME.
ME TOO.
(GIGGLING)
I LOVE ICE TEA.
ME TOO.
HEY, HAVE YOU HEARD
OF THE BAND "HOT CHIP"?
OH MY GOD,
THEY ARE LIKE THE BEST!
YEAH?
WHAT'S YOUR FAVOURITE SONG
BY THEM?
PETER:
(CLEARS THROAT)
SO TWO ICE TEAS.
ANYTHING ELSE?
DREW:
GO AHEAD.
WHAT'RE YOU GETTING?
I'M GONNA GET A TUNA WRAP,
WITH A SCOOP OF STRAWBERRY
ICE CREAM ON TOP
AND... GARLIC SALT.
REALLY?
YES, THAT'S WHAT I WANT.
OKAY, YOU'RE THE BOSS.
AND FOR THE LADY?
I'LL GET THE SAME.
OKAY, WEIRDOS.
YOU SURE YOU DON'T WANT
SOMETHING ELSE?
IT'S EASIER IF I DON'T HAVE
TO THINK FOR MYSELF.
(GIGGLING)
♪♪♪
CONNOR:
SHE SAID SHE'D BE WEARING
A REALM OF DOOM SHIRT.
DO YOU SEE HER?
WESLEY:
NO.
(GAGS)
WHY CAN I TASTE YOU?
DAVE:
(SNIFFING)
HE OVERDID THE COLOGNE.
YOU NERVOUS?
YOU LOOK NERVOUS.
YEAH, MY STOMACH'S PRODUCING
NERVOUS ENZYMES.
I JUST HOPE IT DOESN'T
TURN INTO GAS.
REAL CLASSY, HOMES.
(WHISPERING)
GUYS, THERE'S A REALM
OF DOOM SHIRT!
EXCUSE ME.
THAT'S HER!
UM, OLD!
WESLEY:
SHE'S A WOMAN.
I THOUGHT SHE WAS SUPPOSED
TO BE SIXTEEN?
MAYBE IT'S NOT HER.
OH, THAT'S DEFINITELY HER.
OKAY,
LET ME GO CHECK.
DAVE:
NO, NO. WE'RE LEAVING, STAT.
BUT SHE'S WAITING
FOR ME.
DAVE:
(LAUGHING) NO!
♪ She sure looks good,
good, good ♪
♪ Good on you! ♪
♪ Kiss me quick... ♪
DREW:
HEY!
CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
ALLI:
MAKE IT QUICK.
DREW:
OKAY, YOU WIN.
I'LL GO TO THE DANCE WITH YOU.
ALL BETTER?
THAT'S IT?
THAT'S ALL YOU HAVE?
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE HAPPY.
YOU MADE A MISTAKE;
I MADE A MISTAKE -
CAN PLEASE MOVE ON
ALREADY?
YOU'RE MY MISTAKE, DREW.
WHAT'RE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WE HAVE ONE FIGHT
AND YOU RUN OFF
TO MARISOL?!
MARISOL'S BORING!
SHE MADE ME REALIZE THAT...
I WANNA HANG OUT WITH YOU.
SO, YOU LIKE ME
BECAUSE I'M LESS BORING
THAN SOMEONE ELSE.
WOW, THAT'S ROMANTIC.
I'M SURPRISED I HAVEN'T
SEEN THAT ONE
ON A GREETING CARD.
I COULD, UH,
I COULD MAKE ONE FOR YOU.
UGH!
SO, THE DANCE.
DOES "UGH" MEAN "YES"
IN HINDI?
IT MEANS "GO AWAY"
IN CAVEMAN!
I'M SURPRISED
YOU DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
(DEJECTED SIGH)
(DOOR OPENS)
HOLLY J:
THANK YOU.
PETER.
HOLLY J!
HOW'S IT GOING?
GOOD.
JUST SKIPPING WORK
AND DROPPING OFF DECOR
FOR THE DANCE.
IS SAV UPSTAIRS?
YEAH. WHY?
I'M JUST WONDERING.
OH GOD,
WHAT DID HE SAY?
WELL, YOU DIDN'T HEAR
IT FROM ME,
BUT MY MAN LIKES YOU.
HE SAID THAT?
I'M GUESSING IT GOES
BOTH WAYS?
NO, IT DOESN'T.
BUT YOU KISSED!
SAV TOLD YOU THAT?
WE SHOULDN'T HAVE.
IT WAS A BIG MISTAKE.
WELL, YOU BETTER
TELL HIM THAT THEN.
(DOOR SHUTS LOUDLY)
(APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS)
(IMPRESSED GASP)
LOOKING GOOD!
THANKS. IT'S NEW.
OH, UM...
I WAS ACTUALLY TALKING
ABOUT THE DECORATIONS.
YEAH, YEAH, NO.
AND I THINK THEY'LL BE READY
FOR TOMORROW NIGHT.
SO, UH...
DO YOU FEEL AS WEIRD
AS I DO?
TOTALLY.
WHEN WE KISSED,
IT WAS...
STUPID.
SO STUPID.
YEAH.
AND, AND IT WOULD BE...
SO STUPID IF WE...
DID IT AGAIN,
RIGHT?
WOW.
WE ARE SUCH IDIOTS.
ADAM:
YOU'RE GONNA GIVE YOURSELF
BLISTERS.
STUPID KNOT!
UGH!
EASY, CAVEMAN.
SERIOUSLY?
I CAN'T WIN.
IT'S LIKE WITH OTHER GIRLS,
I DON'T CARE AND IT'S EASY.
BUT WITH ALLI
IT'S LIKE I GET NERVOUS.
THAT'S 'CAUSE YOU ACTUALLY
LIKE HER.
YEAH, I TRIED TO TELL HER THAT,
BUT NOTHING I SAY WORKS.
HAVEN'T YOU EVER SEEN
AN '80S MOVIE?
NO. NOT ON PURPOSE.
THE GIRL WHO'S WORTH IT
REQUIRES AN EFFORT,
LIKE A GESTURE
OR SOMETHING.
NOT THE SAME OLD
DREW TRICKS.
(MOUSE CLICKS)
(SIGHING CONTENTEDLY)
I KNOW A PATHETIC LOVE SIGH
WHEN I HEAR ONE.
YOU LIAR!
YOU DO LIKE HIM.
FINE.
I LIKE BEING AROUND HIM.
IS... IS THAT SO WRONG?
HELLO, REBOUNDAGE!
CAN YOU REALLY TRUST
YOUR FEELINGS RIGHT NOW?
I MEAN, YOU JUST BROKE IT OFF
WITH DECLAN.
YOU'RE USING SAV.
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
WHAT'S IT LIKE, THEN?
GIRL GETS HER HEART BROKEN,
GIRL FINDS NEW GUY
TO FILL ATTENTION VOID.
CLASSIC STORY
THAT ENDS IN "OUCH."
THERE WON'T BE ANY OUCH.
WHATEVER.
(MOUSE CLICK)
I THOUGHT YOU DELETED
ALL YOUR DECLAN PICS.
I GUESS I FORGOT ONE.
JENNA:
UM, SHOULD WE TAKE
A DIFFERENT ROUTE?
ALLI:
(SIGHING HEAVILY)
CAN'T AVOID HIM FOREVER.
DREW:
OH, HERE SHE COMES.
YOU GUYS REMEMBER YOUR LINES?
OWEN:
THIS IS SO STUPID.
DREW:
SHUT UP.
THIS IS GOING TO WORK.
BREAK, READY, DOWN,
SET, HUT!
HIS KILLER SMILE MAKES
LADIES SCREAM!
HE'S THE BEST QB
IN THE ENTIRE LEAGUE.
OWEN:
EVERY GIRL IN SCHOOL
WANTS TO BE HIS MATCH
AND THAT'S WHY
HE IS THE PERFECT...
(BALL THUMPS)
CATCH.
(CLAPPING SLOWLY)
WOW. UM, I DON'T EVEN
KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
SAY YOU'LL GO
TO THE DANCE WITH ME.
(SIGHING HEAVILY)
COME ON,
WHY NOT?
LOOK, I'M NOT GOING TO GO
TO THE DANCE WITH YOU
'CAUSE YOU THINK
YOU'RE GREAT.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD TAKE A MIRROR
TO THE DANCE.
DREW:
COME ON, ALLI, I LIKE YOU.
REALLY?
YOU NEVER TELL ME WHY.
OWEN:
(EXHALES LOUDLY)
TOLD YOU THAT WAS
A STUPID IDEA.
GUYS:
(LAUGHING)
♪♪♪
♪ (Unclear lyric) ♪
♪ If we could just take
some time ♪
♪ Oh, and drift away, yeah ♪
♪ Ooh wouldn't it be good ♪
♪ To slow down these rains... ♪
WELL HOWDY, PARTNER!
(CHUCKLING)
(SAD SIGH)
OH, THAT'S
A "WE NEED TO TALK" LOOK
IF I'VE EVER SEEN ONE.
(SIGHING HEAVILY)
YOU'RE A GREAT GUY, SAV.
I JUST...
I CAN'T DO THIS.
WHY?
I'M NOT TOTALLY OVER
DECLAN.
I SHOULDN'T BE SURPRISED.
SORRY I KISSED YOU.
IT'S OKAY.
WE JUST GOT CARRIED AWAY
FOR A FEW MINUTES.
YEAH, IT WAS...
IT WAS A FUN FEW MINUTES.
SO, NO HARD FEELINGS?
SAV:
YEAH, NO, I MEAN,
WHO WANTS TO BE
A REBOUND ANYWAYS, RIGHT?
UM, SO IF, YOU KNOW,
IF WE'RE GOING BACK
TO BEING COLLEAGUES, UM...
DO YOU WANT TO HELP ME STACK
SOME DRINKS?
DAVE:
(LAUGHING)
LOVEQUEEN16?
MORE LIKE LOSERQUEEN42.
THAT'S JUST WRONG.
CONNOR:
I DON'T GET WHY I COULDN'T
JUST TALK TO HER.
I MEAN, WE LEFT HER ALONE.
THAT'S JUST RUDE.
DAVE:
SHE'S TOO OLD FOR YOU, CONNOR.
CONNOR:
YEAH, WELL MS. OH'S OLD
AND WE LIKE HER.
DAVE:
YEAH, THAT'S 'CAUSE
SHE'S A TEACHER.
OKAY? A HOT, SUPPLE TEACHER
THAT I'LL NEVER DATE.
NOT SOME AN ONLINE RANDOM.
BESIDES YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHO THAT WOMAN IS.
SHE COULD BE A SERIAL KILLER.
CONNOR:
SHE'S NOT A SERIAL KILLER!
(BASKETBALL HITS RIM)
I MISS TALKING TO HER.
DAVE:
WHEN EVERYTHING'S ALL RIGHT,
THERE WON'T BE ANY RESTRICTIONS
IN THE WAY.
I PROMISE.
(BALL CLANKS ON RIM)
ARE YHOU READY TO GET SET
FOR THIS DANCE?
IS IT OKAY IF WE DON'T GO?
I'M NOT REALLY IN THE MOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
SHOOT SOME HOOPS THEN?
YEAH, SURE, ONE SECOND.
(KEYS CLICK)
(DANCE MUSIC SWELLS)
♪♪♪
♪ Hey, baby,
I love the way you move ♪
AS CHEERLEADER,
I'M CONCERNED
WITH OUR QUARTERBACK
STANDING ALONE
ON THE SIDELINES.
COME DANCE!
NOT RIGHT NOW.
♪ Hey, baby,
I love when you bruise ♪
WAITING FOR SOMEONE ELSE?
IS IT WEIRD IF I ASK
YOU GIRL ADVICE?
YES. VERY.
GOOD LUCK WAITING AROUND.
♪ And your body's like
a furnace ♪
♪ And you're fueled
to the furthest ♪
♪ You got me fevered, fevered ♪
♪ Fevered, yeah ♪
♪ Hey, baby,
I love the way you... ♪
SAV:
(OVER MIC)
HAVIN' A GOOD TIME, DEGRASSI?!
STUDENTS:
(CHEERING AND CLAPPING LOUDLY)
SAV:
ALL RIGHT, VERY GOOD.
I JUST WANT TO THANK
THE LOVELY HOLLY J SINCLAIR
FOR MAKING TONIGHT HAPPEN.
STUDENTS:
(CHEERING AND WHISTLING)
SAV:
WE'RE ALL VERY LUCKY TO HAVE HER
AS OUR VICE PRESIDENT,
AND I'M VERY LUCKY TO HAVE HER
AS A FRIEND.
I'D ALSO ADD THAT
IN THAT GET-UP,
SHE LOOKS AWESOME!
STUDENTS:
(CLAPPING AND CHEERING)
SAV:
SO LET'S THANK HER BY HAVING
THE BEST DEGRASSI DANCE EVER!
STUDENTS:
(CHEERING AND CLAPPING LOUDLY)
SAV:
RIGHT ON!
♪ Where did you come from,
baby ♪
♪ Your eyes are like the sky ♪
♪ How did I find you ♪
♪ I can't believe you're mine ♪
ADAM:
JENNA WANTS TO SEE YOU
IN THE PHOTO BOOTH.
JENNA? WHY?
JUST GO!
OKAY.
NICE SPEECH, DJ.
WELL, I HAD TO GIVE A SHOUT OUT
TO MY VICE PRESIDENT.
WAS IT TOO MUCH?
I REALLY LIKE YOU,
SAV.
(RAISING HIS VOICE)
WHAT?
(RAISING HER VOICE)
I SAID REALLY LIKE YOU,
SAV!
RIGHT.
AS A FRIEND.
YOU DON'T NEED
TO EXPLAIN ANY MORE.
IT'S MORE THAN THAT.
ANYTHING YOU AND I START
COULD HAVE
AN EXPIRATION DATE.
SO IT'S ROMANTIC LIMBO
FOR BOTH OF US
UNTIL THE FUTURE
COMES CALLING.
YEAH.
SO I MEAN...
WE COULD PUT
OUR HEADS DOWN
AND LIVE OUT
THE NEXT SIX MONTHS
LIKE A COUPLE
OF HEARTLESS ZOMBIES...
OR?
OR WE COULD FILL THAT TIME
WITH EACH OTHER.
NO PRESSURE, NO PARENTS,
JUST...
YOU AND I
MAKING EACH OTHER
FEEL GOOD.
WHY SHOULDN'T WE HAVE FUN,
RIGHT?
JUST UNTIL GRAD.
THEN WE SHAKE HANDS,
WE GO OUR SEPARATE WAYS.
I KNOW.
IT'S A CRAZY THEORY.
WELL, I GUESS WE'LL JUST HAVE
TO PUT IT TO THE TEST.
YES!
THAT IS PANDEMIC!
STUDENTS:
(CHEERING AND CLAPPING LOUDLY)
HOLLY J:
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE
IT'S BECOMING A THING!
SAV:
DEGRASSI, ANOTHER PANDEMIC TRACK
COMING RIGHT UP!
STUDENTS:
(CHEERING AND CLAPPING WILDLY)
(ROCK SONG STARTS UP)
YOU'RE NOT JENNA.
I ASKED ADAM
TO GET YOU.
ALLI, HOLD UP!
THERE HAVE BEEN OTHER GIRLS
IN MY LIFE,
BUT THEY'RE NOT LIKE YOU.
YOU'RE SMART,
YOU LIKE SCHOOL,
YOU CAN BANG OFF
AN ENTIRE ESSAY IN A NIGHT.
YEAH, AND?
I LIKE THAT.
I LIKE NEVER KNOWING
WHAT YOU'RE GONNA SAY NEXT.
YOU DO?
I'M NOT SMART LIKE YOU,
AND IF WE DATED
IT WOULD JUST BE
A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE YOU DUMPED ME.
(SIGHING)
SO WHEN I DID THE ESSAY
FOR YOU,
YOU THOUGHT
I WAS CALLING YOU DUMB.
PEOPLE HAVE BEEN
TELLING ME THAT
MY ENTIRE LIFE.
MY MOM, DAD, BROTHER,
PERINO,
AND EVERY OTHER TEACHER
I'VE EVER HAD.
THERE ARE TWO TYPES
OF SMARTS:
BOOK SMARTS AND PEOPLE SMARTS.
I'VE DATED
THE BOOK SMART GUY BEFORE
AND TRUST ME,
IT'S OVERRATED.
PEOPLE MEET YOU
AND THEY LOVE YOU RIGHT AWAY.
I JUST WISH I WOULD HAVE
BEEN MORE PEOPLE SMART
WHEN IT CAME TO YOU.
WELL, SINCE WE'RE ALONE
IN HERE...
MIGHT AS WELL.
ALLI:
(HAPPY HUM)
(RAPID CAMERA SNAPS)
SAV:
YOU KNOW, IF THIS WAS
A LAS VEGAS GANGSTER MOVIE,
WE'D BE MAKING OUT
ON TOP OF THE MONEY.
HMM...
FIONA:
HOLLY J!
IT'S FIONA. SHOOT!
UH...
IN HERE, FI!
OW, MY FEEBLE WRIST.
I WAS LOOKING FOR YOU.
OH.
HEY, WEIRDOS.
ANYA:
WHAT, ARE YOU LIKE
PLAYING STATUES?
BOTH:
(GIGGLING)
(NERVOUS CHUCKLE)
ANYA:
UM... I NEED MY HISTORY NOTES
BACK.
HOLLY J:
OH, THEY'RE IN MY LOCKER.
UM, I CAN BRING THEM
TO CLASS.
(QUIETLY)
OKAY.
OKAY, WELL, UM,
WE HAVE A BUCKET
OF CHANGE TO COUNT.
YOU'RE WELCOME TO STAY
AND HELP OUT IF YOU LIKE.
OH, THAT'S OKAY.
FIONA:
I DON'T REALLY LIKE
TOUCHING COINS, SO...
YOU KNOW,
ANYA MIGHT FREAK
IF SHE EVER FOUND OUT
ABOUT US.
YEAH, SHE CAN'T KNOW.
NOR CAN FIONA.
KEEPING THIS A SECRET
MIGHT BE HARDER THAN IT LOOKS.
IT MIGHT BE FUN TO TRY.
♪♪♪
♪ I like the way
that you look at me ♪
♪ And your smile turns me... ♪
EXCUSE ME.
I'M LOOKING FOR
MY GIRLFRIEND -
CUTE, SMART,
AND KINDA SEXY?
KINDA? YOU MEAN VERY,
AND THAT MUST BE ME.
NOW,
WHERE IS MY BOYFRIEND?
OH WAIT,
IS THAT WHAT I AM?
WELL, I MEAN,
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH
SO MANY PERMUTATIONS,
I BARELY KNOW WHAT BOYFRIEND
AND GIRLFRIEND MEANS RIGHT NOW.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
PERMUTATIONS MEANS,
BUT I DO KNOW
THIS IS SIMPLE.
I'M YOURS;
YOU'RE MINE.
AND NOW,
TO MAKE IT OFFICIAL...
DREW'S GIRLFRIEND.
♪ When I'm a clown
you'll always laugh at me ♪
♪ No matter how bad... ♪
WHAT'S WRONG?
NOTHING.
IT'S JUST,
FOR THE FIRST TIME,
I FEEL LIKE
I'M IN SOMETHING GOOD.
ME TOO.
♪ Don't you change for me ♪