♪♪♪
EYOU THINK THAT'S FUNNY,
BUELLER?
YOU THINK THAT'S FUNNY?
IT'S NOT FUNNY.
NO. NO IT'S NOT.
SEE YOU TONIGHT,
LITTLE "B"!
BUELLER?
LITTLE "B"?
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
MR. MARTIN.
FRIDAY'S END OF THE MONTH,
ELLIE.
I NEED A CHEQUE.
I'M GETTING IT TONIGHT
FROM MY MOM.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY, SIR.
JUST LIKE I DIDN'T HAVE
TO WORRY LAST MONTH.
WHEN YOU WERE LATE
WITH THE RENT?
SEE I HAD THE RENT,
I JUST DIDN'T KNOW
HOW TO GET IT TO YOU.
SEAN ALWAYS DID THAT.
IS HE BACK YET?
SEAN'S NOT COMING BACK,
SIR.
(ELECTRIC CRACKLING)
MR. MARTIN:
YOU FORGET TO PAY
THE ELECTRIC BILL, TOO?
ELLIE:
SOMETIMES MY FERRET, I-
YOU GOT A FERRET HERE?
ELLIE:
I CATCH HIM CHEWING
ON ELECTRICAL CORDS AND...
BUELLER!
OH BUELLER.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
FERRET BUELLER IS DEAD?
CRAIG:
THAT'S AWFUL.
IT'S TERRIBLE.
YOU NAMED YOUR FERRET,
"BUELLER"?
ALEX, A HEART.
TRY TO FIND ONE.
BEULLER WAS SEAN'S BABY
AND SINCE HE'S BEEN GONE,
THINGS HAVEN'T EXACTLY BEEN
"FUN" AROUND THE APARTMENT.
MARCO? PARTNER?
THE GAME IS EUCHRE.
SPADES IS UP.
I'LL COME OVER AFTER SCHOOL.
WE'LL HAVE A CEREMONY,
A FERRET FUNERAL.
I'M MEETING MOM
FOR DINNER.
AN EVENT PROMISING
TO BE AS MUCH FUN
AS A FERRET FUNERAL.
CRAIG:
YOU CAN'T POSTPONE?
DEATH IN THE FAMILY.
IT'S A GOOD EXCUSE.
DINNER PLUS MOM
EQUALS RENT MONEY.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
I'LL COME OVER AFTER.
MATT:
I'M LOOKING FOR EXAMPLES
OF MEDIA MANIPULATION
IN SAY... TELEVISION.
HAZEL?
WELL THERE'S VIDEO NEWS
RELEASES.
COMPANIES CREATE UM,
STORIES ON THEIR PRODUCT,
WHICH ARE THEN SHOWN
AS LOCAL NEWS PROGRAMS
AND THE PEOPLE WATCHING HAVE
NO IDEA WHERE THEY CAME FROM.
MR. O.
IS THERE A REASON YOU'RE SHY
TO CALL ON ME IN CLASS?
HEY, I GIVE EQUAL TIME
TO EVERY STUDENT.
IN THE CLASSROOM ANYWAY.
GOOD CLASS,
MR. OLEANDER.
NEW RULE?
SUGGESTIVE COMMENTS
ONLY TO BE DELIVERED
APRES DEGRASSI.
SAY AT THE CINESQUARE?
TONIGHT?
BACK ROW?
GOT FREE PASSES.
ISN'T IT
A SCHOOL NIGHT?
YEAH, I LIKE SCHOOL NIGHTS.
THERE'S LESS CHANCE OF RUNNING
INTO SOMEONE FROM SCHOOL.
PAIGE.
OH NEW UNIFORMS FINALLY.
YEAH, THERE'S THREE BOXES
IN THE OFFICE
WE HAVE TO PICK UP.
LISTEN, PAIGE,
THANKS FOR HELPING ME
WITH THE UM,
BULLETIN BOARD.
AND MR. OLEANDER,
THANK YOU FOR OFFERING
ME HELP WITH THAT ESSAY.
SO OBVIOUS.
OH...
IT'S $500, RIGHT?
RENT'S $540.
MOM.
YOU COULD GIVE ME
A FEW CHEQUES POST-DATED.
AND MISS MY MONTHLY DINNER
WITH MY DAUGHTER?
HOW ARE YOU?
LIVING ALONE.
GOOD.
I'M PROUD OF YOU
BEING SO INDEPENDENT.
LIVING ALL BY YOURSELF.
I'VE BEEN IN GROUP
FOR THREE MONTHS.
(CHUCKLES)
I'VE BEEN THERAPY'D OUT
THE WAAZOO.
(FORCED LAUGH)
SINCE YOU LEFT
I HAVEN'T HAD A DRINK.
IF YOU WANT TO MOVE BACK
I PROMISE TO KEEP IT UP.
(LAUGHS)
SIT!
I MISS YOU ALL THE TIME.
I WANT TO TALK ABOUT THIS.
YEAH, I TOLD MARCO
I'D MEET HIM.
I'M DIFFERENT.
UNDERSTAND WHY I DON'T
TRUST YOU ON THAT ONE, MOM.
MRS. NASH:
ELLIE-
IF YOU'RE PROUD OF ME BEING
INDEPENDENT,
WATCH ME GO ONE STEP FURTHER.
AFTER THIS MONTH,
I WON'T TAKE ANY MORE
OF YOUR MONEY.
I WON'T NEED YOU, MOM.
NOT ANYMORE.
(CLATTER OF STONE)
ELLIE:
HERE LIES BUELLER NASH.
I'M SORRY I COULDN'T
TAKE CARE OF YOU BETTER.
OR LONGER.
I'M JUST REALLY SORRY
YOU'RE GONE.
I KNOW THIS WAS MY IDEA
BUT WE HAVE TO GO NOW.
I THOUGHT YOU WANTED
TO SIT IN A DARK THEATRE.
TWO HOURS
PLUS PREVIEWS.
MEERI:
PAIGE!
YOU DON'T RETURN PHONE CALLS?
THE REJECT TWINS
CALLED IN SICK.
YOU'RE BEHIND THE COUNTER.
BUT I'M OFF SHIFT.
WANT TO MAKE THAT
PERMANENT?
NO, SHE DOESN'T.
MATT!
PAIGE.
YOUR BOSS COULD HAVE JUST
AS EASILY BEEN SIMPSON.
AND WE COULD HAVE JUST
AS EASILY BEEN CAUGHT.
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
(KISS)
(SIGHS)
MARCO:
NO SEAN.
NO BUELLER.
YOU SURE YOU'RE OKAY
TO STAY ALONE?
SAY YOU'RE OFFERING.
PLEASE.
THE ONLY OTHER PERSON
WHO WANTS TO BE
WITH ME RIGHT NOW -
MY MOTHER.
I'M OFFERING.
NO WORRIES.
I WON'T-
LEAST NOT ABOUT WAKING UP
TO FIND YOU PASSED OUT
WITH THE HOUSE ON FIRE.
MOM FLASHBACK.
SORRY.
HEY.
WORRY INSTEAD...
ABOUT PLAYING EUCHRE,
ELLIE NASH.
YOU WANT TO PLAY CARDS?
DYLAN'S HOCKEY TEAM
PLAYS THURSDAYS FOR MONEY,
A LOT OF MONEY.
MY ALLOWANCE ONLY LASTS
LIKE THREE HANDS.
AND YOU PLAY WHY?
MARCO:
I REPEAT.
DYLAN'S HOCKEY TEAM.
(LAUGHS) OKAY.
MARCO:
NOW.
YOU DEAL OUT
FIVE CARDS EACH.
WHAT'S LEFT OVER GOES IN A PILE
WITH THE TOP CARD TURNED UP.
THAT CARD'S "TRUMP".
NOW THE JACK OF THAT SUIT
IS THE HIGHEST.
IF YOU HAVE
AN AMAZING HAND
YOU CAN GO ALONE,
PLAY WITHOUT YOUR PARTNER.
WORTH TWO POINTS.
SO...
JIMMY:
LET'S GO, DEL ROSSI.
DEALER'S DEALT.
HEARTS ARE TRUMP.
MEANING THE
JACK OF HEARTS
IS THE HIGHEST CARD
IN THE WORLD.
ELLIE SPEAKS
EUCHRE NOW.
CRAIG:
HEY MARCO?
WITH YOUR HAIR
ALL BIG LIKE THAT?
YOU KINDA LOOK
LIKE ASHLEY.
(LAUGHTER)
I WAS SANS PRODUCT
THIS MORNING, CRAIG.
AND YOU SAID
IT LOOKED FINE.
MARCO, BEGONE.
ELLIE, YOU'RE IN.
I CAN'T TAKE
MARCO'S PLACE.
NO, IT'S OKAY.
SIT.
DYLAN'S ENTIRE HOCKEY TEAM
COMBINED
IS LESS COMPETITIVE
THAN HER.
ALEX:
THE ACE OF SPADES IS DOWN.
MEANING IT'S THEIR TRICK
SO FAR?
CRAIG:
THAT'S THE QUEEN.
OF HEARTS.
YOU SURE YOU WANT
TO LEAD TRUMP?
WELL, I DON'T HAVE NO SPADES
AND THAT'S MY LOWEST HEART.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
I GET A SCATTER-PROOF PARTNER
ONLY TO STOP FOR FRENCH CLASS?
OH WELL,
JE SUIS UP FOR SKIPPING.
(LAUGHS)
WHERE TO?
MATT:
TODAY I THOUGHT WE'D TALK ABOUT
BIAS IN THE MEDIA -
HOW THE NEWS SOMETIMES
TWISTS THE FACTS.
YOU'RE DOING THE NOD OF SLEEP?
IT'S NOT ATTRACTIVE.
AVERT YOUR EYES.
EVIL MEERI KEPT ME
FOR THE LATE SHIFT.
MATT:
PAIGE.
CAN YOU TELL ME HOW THAT'S
DIFFERENT FROM OUTRIGHT LYING?
TO LIE IS TO PRESENT
A FALSEHOOD.
BIAS IS TELLING
THE TRUTH JUST...
A VERSION OF THE TRUTH.
GOOD.
OKAY, SO BACK TO WHY
POP STARS MARRY
ONCE THEY RELEASE A NEW CD.
I'VE NEVER HAD A TEACHER
PASS ME A NOTE BEFORE.
LOOK I KNOW THIS PLACE
ISN'T EXACTLY ROMANTIC,
BUT IT SEEMS LIKE
EVERY TIME
WE TRY TO GET TOGETHER-
(DOOR RATTLES)
-THERE'S SOMETHING.
ELLIE:
THERE'S ALWAYS THE BASEMENT?
(RELIEVED SIGH)
MATT, THAT'S IT.
TONIGHT AFTER WORK
I COME OVER.
WHERE? AT MY PLACE?
YEAH, I WANT TO SEE YOUR
PRIVATE BOHEMIAN MAN-LAIR.
PAIGE, YOU CAN'T.
I'M FAMILIAR WITH
THE STUDENT LIFESTYLE.
MY BROTHER?
HE SHARES ONE BATHROOM
WITH TWELVE GUYS.
AT LEAST YOU HAVE
A PLACE OF YOUR OWN.
WITH WHAT?
A COMFY COUCH, TV, DVD.
AWAY FROM DISTRACTIONS.
NO.
IT'S GOT TO BE SOMETHING,
OR SOMEPLACE ELSE.
LOOK, I'LL POP BY
THE THEATRE
AND WE'LL GO OUT
FOR COFFEE AFTER WORK.
MATT.
WAIT A BIT BEFORE YOU LEAVE.
(BLOWS HER A KISS)
(ANNOYED SIGH)
ALEX:
(LAUGHS) YES!
OKAY, OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, REMATCH.
OKAY? RIGHT NOW.
ELLIE:
UM, THAT WAS THE REMATCH.
ALEX:
UNLESS YOU WANT TO MAKE IT
MORE INTERESTING.
AS IN UH, "STRIP EUCHRE"?
CRAIG:
(LAUGHS)
ALEX:
AS IN MONEY.
AS IN TWENTY DOLLARS?
OKAY.
AND IT'S CLUBS.
ELLIE:
OH.
UM, ONE QUESTION -
WHY DO THEY CALL THESE
"BOWERS"?
(LAUGHS)
WE SKIPPED FRENCH CLASS
FOR THIS?
COME ON.
ALEX:
TEN BUCKS EACH.
NOT REAL MONEY,
BUT IT'LL BUY
A CAFETERIA LUNCH.
WAIT.
TODAY'S THURSDAY,
RIGHT?
I THINK I KNOW WHERE
REAL MONEY'S GONNA BE.
ALEX AND I WOULD LIKE
TO PLAY EUCHRE
WITH YOU AND DYLAN
AND DYLAN'S HOCKEY TEAM.
IF...
IF I HOOK YOU UP,
NEW PLAYERS HAVE TO HOST
THE EVENING.
I CAN HOST,
HOSTESS WHATEVER.
WHICH MEANS BUYING PIZZA,
PLAYING 50, 60 DOLLAR HANDS,
AND LOSING THE LITTLE MONEY
THAT YOU MIGHT HAVE.
WE HAVE MONEY.
WE DO.
JUST NOT ANY MONEY
WE PLAN TO LOSE.
(SIGHS)
SO MR. O -
HE'S CUTE.
AND SMART AND...
FUNNY WITH
A TIGHT LITTLE YOGA BODY
THROWN IN FOR FUN.
BUT...
THE "BIG SECRET".
THE ONLY PLACE
WE CAN ESCAPE TO
WHERE HE AND ME
CAN BE A "WE"
IS HIS.
HE DOESN'T WANT ME
GOING THERE.
IT SOUNDS TO ME THEN
THERE'S NOT A LOT
OF HONESTY GOING AROUND.
NOBODY CAN KNOW ABOUT THIS,
MANNY.
NO NOT AROUND THE SCHOOL.
I MEAN BETWEEN YOU AND HIM.
A GUY LIKE THAT,
I'M SURPRISED HE DOESN'T HAVE
A GIRLFRIEND.
HE DID HAVE ONE
BUT THEY SPLIT.
AND THAT'S WHAT HE TOLD YOU?
THAT'S MY WHOLE
LAST PAYCHECK.
PLUS TEN DOLLARS
FROM THIS MORNING.
IT ISN'T ENOUGH, IS IT?
ELLIE:
$540.
OTHERWISE KNOWN AS MY RENT.
LET'S NOT USE
ALL OF IT.
I LIKE THIS,
PLAYING THIS.
THE "PARTNER" THING
WORKS FOR ME.
ELLIE?
THE HOCKEY TEAM JUST GOT HERE
AND WE'VE ALREADY GONE THROUGH
THE PIZZETTES.
LET ME INTRODUCE YOU
TO THE TEAM.
THEY WANT TO GET STARTED.
I'M ALEX.
THIS IS ELLIE,
MY FRIEND.
WE'RE HERE
TO DEFEAT YOU.
♪ Tracing my steps
that I take. ♪
♪ Feeling mistakes
that I fake. ♪
♪ Making excuses like
imaginary friends. ♪
♪ Run away to where
I've already been. ♪
♪ To where I already am. ♪
♪ So tell me, tell me
it'll work out ♪
♪ So I'll be wrong again. ♪
♪ I look inside I'm surprised
of what I see in my eyes. ♪
♪ So tell me, tell me,
was I there ♪
♪ When I was taught
how to lie. ♪
♪ I thought I'd chase paradise
but I'll just settle for life. ♪
♪ So tell me, tell me, ♪
♪ Did I die when I was taught
how to lie. ♪
WE'RE BEHIND BY A POINT.
WE HAVE TO TAKE
THE NEXT HAND.
AND IF WE LOSE IT?
LET ME BE THE NEGATIVE ONE,
OKAY?
IT'S A BIGGER GAMBLE
BUT JAMES WANTS
TO PUT MORE MONEY DOWN.
YOU ALL RIGHT
WITH THAT?
MOVE IN!
SURE I'LL GO GET
MY THINGS.
I'M SERIOUS.
MOVE IN.
IT'D BE COOL.
COOL?
SURE NO MOM,
NO MOM'S BOYFRIEND
OF THE WEEK,
BUT THERE'S THIS THING
CALLED RENT.
ONLY $270 A MONTH EACH.
I CAN'T AFFORD
$2 A MONTH.
SO I'LL PAY MORE,
OR I WON'T TELL MY MOM
YOU'RE LIVING HERE.
IT'S NOT LIKE
SHE COMES AROUND.
AND THIS IS THE
HORRIBLE WOMAN YOU HATE?
IT'D BE GREAT, OKAY?
IT'D BE FUN.
RIGHT NOW I NEED FUN.
MOVE TO WASAGA WITH SEAN
IF YOU'RE LONELY
OR SUCK IT UP
AND GO HOME.
MY MOM WAS DRUNK...
ALWAYS DRUNK.
RIGHT UP TO THE NIGHT
SHE LIT THE HOUSE ON FIRE.
BUT SHE'S SOBER NOW.
AND PAYING YOUR RENT.
ALL THE TIME TRYING TO MAKE
THINGS RIGHT WITH YOU.
WOW, WHAT A MONSTER.
THE HOCKEY BOYS
ARE WAITING.
WHEN YOU COME BACK
TO THE TABLE
LEAVE THE SUCKY GIRL BEHIND.
HI, CUSTOMER SERVICE?
YES, UM, I JUST WANTED TO MAKE
SURE MY PHONE'S WORKING.
YEAH, I KNOW I'M CALLING
YOU ON IT
SO IT MUST BE...
OKAY, THANKS. BYE.
FIVE MORE SECONDS.
PLEASE, MEERI.
HE STOOD YOU UP,
DIDN'T HE?
HE'S NOT CHEATING ON ME
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK.
MEERI:
I THINK?
THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK.
(SIGHS)
ALEX:
SPADES IS TRUMP.
PICK IT UP.
I'M GOING ALONE.
WHAT?!
YOU KNOW YOU'RE A POINT AWAY
FROM LOSING
AND US FROM WINNING?
UM ALEX, CAN I TALK TO YOU?
WE'VE BEEN OVER THE CONCEPT
OF "GOING ALONE" BEFORE.
TALK TO MARCO.
I'M SURE HE'LL CLARIFY THINGS
AGAIN.
ARE YOU A 100% SURE OF YOUR
HAND, ALEX?
THOUSAND.
RELAX HERE,
LOOK AT THE PRETTY CARDS.
IT'S UH, MY LEAD, RIGHT?
ELLIE:
WAIT.
THAT'S MY RENT MONEY.
YOU'RE BUGGING ME, ELLIE.
YOU KNOW,
WE'LL JUST FORGET THIS HAND.
CAN I HAVE THE CARDS?
SIT DOWN!
I LEAD WITH
THE ACE OF HEARTS.
KEEP IT.
DON'T BOTHER.
FOUR POINTS.
WE WIN.
YOU REALLY OUGHT
TO BELIEVE IN PEOPLE MORE.
(KNOCKS ON DOOR)
WHY AREN'T YOU ANSWERING
YOUR PHONE?
WHO'S IS IN THERE
WITH YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE,
PAIGE?
DON'T- PAIGE!
(WATER DRIPS)
GUY UPSTAIRS
FLUSHED HIS TOILET
THROUGH MY CEILING...
FOR THE THIRD TIME
THIS YEAR.
I WOULD'VE CALLED
BUT THEY'VE CUTOFF MY SERVICE.
THIS IS YOUR APARTMENT?
YUP.
YOU WANT THE TOUR?
WE CAN BEGIN AND END
IN THE FOYER.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
WITH SOMEONE?
IS THAT THE KIND OF GUY
YOU THINK I AM?
I DON'T KNOW, MATT.
I SEE YOU IN CLASS
OR AT THE WATER FOUNTAIN
OR AT YOGA,
BUT BEYOND THAT-
THAT'S WET.
THE TOILET'S ABOVE IT.
LOOK BEYOND THAT
I'M A STUDENT LIKE YOU.
EXCEPT I LIVE
IN A PIT-HOLE APARTMENT.
THERE...
ALL THE GLAMOUR THIS
RELATIONSHIP EVER HAD -
GONE.
YOU SAID "RELATIONSHIP",
WHICH MEANS...
I GET TO STAY.
(KISS)
(KNOCK AT THE DOOR)
IT'S OPEN.
(DOOR OPENS)
IT'S THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT,
ELLIE.
THERE'S NO EMERGENCY?
I HAD TO BE SURE
OF SOMETHING.
SURE OF WHAT?
THAT YOU COULD COME OVER.
THAT YOU WERE SOBER,
YOU WEREN'T DRUNK.
YOU WOKE ME AS A TEST?
I WROTE A LETTER
TO MR. MARTIN.
IT SAYS I'M GIVING
TWO MONTHS NOTICE.
OH SO YOU'RE COMING HOME!
I...
I SAID I WROTE IT.
MOM, I-
I HAVEN'T GIVEN IT TO HIM.
NOT YET.
BUT YOU'RE GOING TO?
NO MORE DRINKING?
THE BEST I CAN DO IS TRY.
DAY BY DAY - TRY.
THEN PROMISE ME THAT YOU'LL
TRY AND MAKE IT EASY FOR ME
TO TRUST YOU AGAIN.
COME HOME, ELLIE.
I'M TIRED OF BEING ALONE.
YEAH.
ME TOO.