(SOMEONE KNOCKS ON DOOR)
JUST TELL THEM TO GO,
MA!
HOW HARD IS IT?
UH, WAS I SUPPOSED
TO HEAR THAT?
(LAUGHS)
DO YOU KNOW
I HAVE ZERO STYLE?
I HATE EVERYTHING
I OWN.
SO LEAVE IT.
COME TO DYLAN'S.
(SNORTS) YEAH.
BECAUSE EVERYONE
LOVES PARTYING
WITH A WRETCHED,
BADLY-DRESSED
RAPE-VICTIM LOSER.
PAIGE,
YOU'RE NOT A LOSER,
OKAY?
BESIDES,
WE WEREN'T EVEN THINKING THAT.
HEY, WELL, I AM.
ALONG WITH UM...
WHAT'S THE POINT?
WHY BOTHER?
LOOK...
I FELT THE EXACT
SAME WAY
WHEN I GOT BASHED.
I JUST...
WANTED TO CHANGE MY SKIN,
JUST STOP BEING.
THE FACT THAT THOSE GUYS
NEVER EVEN GOT CAUGHT...
OF COURSE NOT.
WHAT A JOKE.
LOOK, GRADE ELEVEN'S YOUR YEAR,
REMEMBER?
YOU CAN'T LET HIM
CONTROL YOU.
MARCO...
I JUST LOST MY CASE
THREE HOURS AGO.
DEAN WAS FOUND NOT GUILTY
OF RAPING ME.
I KNOW.
PAIGE,
I'M SORRY, OKAY?
JUST-
WHAT?
YOU'RE JUST WHAT,
MARCO?
I'LL BE DOWN
IN A MINUTE.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best that I can be ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(LOUD MUSIC BLARES)
(GASPS)
(MUFFLED) WHAT?!
(MUSIC BLARES)
(MUFFLED) PAIGE!
HEY, BOYS!
WHAT'S UP?
(MUSIC BLARES)
YO!
SORRY,
HE GETS JEALOUS.
SO I DID MAKE
YOU JEALOUS.
OKAY,
PUT ME IN TRACTION
FOR ASKING, WHATEVER,
BUT WHAT THE HELL
IS GOING ON WITH YOU?
WOW, YOU'RE SO TOUGH.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
PAIGE!
WHAT?
I'M EASY.
EVERYONE KNOWS IT.
THE JUDGE,
MY MOTHER...
NOW YOU.
LIKE DEAN,
YOU JUST...
GET ME ALONE
AND...
DO WHATEVER
YOU WANT.
NO ONE'LL STOP YOU.
WHAT?
YOU DON'T WANT ME?
NOT RIGHT NOW,
NO.
'CAUSE DEAN
GOT THERE FIRST?
YOU HAVE TO LET
THAT GO.
YOU WANT ME
TO JUST "LET IT GO"?
LIKE SOMEONE
WAS RUDE OR...
OR STOLE MY SEAT
AT LUNCH?
NO!
THAT'S NOT WHAT I-
I JUST...
I WANT MY GIRLFRIEND BACK,
OKAY?
I WANT PAIGE BACK.
YOU DON'T EVEN
KNOW HER.
SPINNER:
THAT'S STUPID.
THE TRUTH?
PAIGE WENT UPSTAIRS
THAT NIGHT.
SHE NEVER CAME BACK.
YOU KNOW WHAT
I WOULD REALLY LIKE?
IF I NEVER HAD
TO SEE
YOUR IDIOTIC FACE
AGAIN.
OKAY?
HOW ABOUT THAT!
(MUSIC BLARES)
(DOOR BANGS SHUT)
(DOOR CLICKS OPEN)
HEY, HEY GUYS,
KEEP IT DOWN.
ANGIE'S SLEEPING.
OH. JOEY,
YOU REMEMBER ASHLEY?
THE BAD INFLUENCE?
IT WAS BURNING
A HOLE IN YOUR POCKET.
I WAS TRYING TO HELP!
ALL RIGHT,
WELL, UH...
SHE MADE ME DO THIS.
DID NOT!
WOW!
IS THAT A FENDER STRAT?
YUP.
EXACTLY LIKE
HENDRIX HAD.
AND IT'S ALL MINE!
(GASPS) WOW.
WHAT DID THIS SET
YOU BACK?
FOUR HUNDRED?
(SNORT OF LAUGHTER)
WHAT, SIX?
SIX-FIFTY?
UH...
FOUR GRAND.
IT'S THE REAL THING.
IT'S A PIECE OF HISTORY.
WOW.
ENJOY IT.
(LAUGHS)
(PLAYING SOME FUNK MUSIC)
HEY.
GOT A LITTLE WAYS TO GO
'TIL I SOUND LIKE UH,
FOUR GRAND, HUH?
A LITTLE BIT.
CRAIG.
HMM?
I WAS THINKING MAYBE
YOU COULD UH...
HELP OUT
WITH A LITTLE RENT?
FOR THE MORTGAGE?
(STRUMS GUITAR ABSENTLY)
MY DAD'S ESTATE
GIVES YOU MONEY.
YEAH,
LIKE $250 A MONTH,
AND THAT BARELY
KEEPS YOU IN PIZZA.
YOU GO THROUGH SHOES
LIKE NO ONE I'VE EVER SEEN.
I-I...
CRAIG.
CRAIG!
I HEAT THIS GARAGE FOR YOU.
I MEAN, WITH THE PRICE
OF HYDRO...?
WOULD YOU ASK ANGIE THIS?
FOR ONE THING SHE'S SEVEN,
I MEAN,
SHE EATS LIKE A BIRD.
SHE DIDN'T JUST BUY HERSELF
A $4, 000 GUITAR.
AND THAT'S THE ONLY REASON
IT'S DIFFERENT?
OF COURSE.
YEAH WELL,
I'M NOT SO SURE.
THE NORTH CAROLINA
SCOUT?
HE'S COMING BACK DOWN
IN DECEMBER.
WANTS TO SEE ME
PLAY BALL AGAIN.
VINCE CARTER
WAS AN NC TAR HEEL.
I MEAN,
THAT COULD BE ME NEXT.
IMAGINE!
HAVE YOU SEEN PAIGE?
NOPE.
AND I'M SURE SHE'S HAPPY
ABOUT THAT.
SPINNER, I'M WORRIED.
(MUSIC BLARES FROM HOUSE)
OH. HI.
UM, I'M HERE TO SEE STEVE?
STEVE...?
STEVE, THE CUTE ONE?
SECOND YEAR?
HE TOTALLY
INVITED ME TODAY
IN LINE
AT THE BOOKSTORE,
AND I WAS LIKE,
"SURE, I'LL COME BY."
ARE YOU NINETEEN?
TWENTY, ACTUALLY.
UH, JUST... SHORT.
(MUSIC BLARES)
(PEOPLE LAUGHING AND CHATTING)
I HAVE TO TALK TO YOU.
NO YOU DON'T.
NOT NOW.
I HAVE SOMETHING TO SAY.
ACTUALLY,
EVERYONE SHOULD HEAR IT.
"NOT GUILTY."
NOTHING ELSE TO SAY.
HEY, SCARECROW!
MORE JUICE?
YOU HAVE TO LISTEN TO ME!
WANT TO GRAB US
A FRESH KEGS?
PLEDGE:
YEAH, OF COURSE.
DO ANY OF YOU HERE KNOW
WHAT YOUR "BUDDY" IS?
DO YOU KNOW WHAT HE DOES?
SHUT UP!
HE IS A LIAR!
OKAY?
A LIAR AND A RAPIST.
AN EX-GIRLFRIEND,
YOU KNOW.
OUTSIDE, NOW!
PLEDGE:
HEY! WANT ME TO RUN
THE BAR FOR YOU?
YOU DON'T GET IT!
I WAS FIFTEEN!
I DON'T RECOMMEND
YOU DO THAT AGAIN.
I AM TRYING TO GET IN
TO THAT FRATERNITY.
THIS WAS MY LIFE!
YOU RAPED ME!
YEAH.
(GASPS)
YOU ADMIT IT?
JUST LIKE THAT?
I FIGURE I MUST'VE DONE
SOMETHING WRONG
IF YOU KEEP
PUNISHING ME.
YOU DIDN'T SAY
THAT IN COURT.
WELL,
I MUST'VE DONE
SOMETHING RIGHT TOO,
IF YOU KEEP COMING
BACK LIKE THIS.
I'M NOT COMING BACK.
I CAN'T BLAME YOU
FOR WANTING
SOME MORE OF THIS.
EXCUSE ME?
LISTEN, SWEETHEART?
GO HOME,
CALL YOUR SAD
LITTLE BOYFRIEND,
ALL RIGHT?
YOU WANT TO HAVE FUN
SOME TIME?
CALL ME.
YOU WERE GOOD.
(ENGINE ROARS TO LIFE)
PAIGE!
(TIRES SQUEAL)
(SMASH)
(ENGINE WHEEZES)
SPINNER:
STOP IT!
STOP!
SPINNER.
SPINNER:
GET OUT.
GET OUT!
(SHOCKED LAUGHTER)
SPINNER... WOW!
GO HOME.
I DIDN'T-
JUST GET IN A CAB
AND GO HOME!
GO!
♪ COME ON DOWN,
SLOW DOWN ♪
♪ YOU WORKED SO HARD
TO BE WHERE YOU ARE ♪
♪ SO YOU SHOULD SLOW,
SLOW DOWN ♪
♪ YOU KNOW THIS CITY'S FINE ♪
♪ ONCE YOU'VE FOUND OUT HOW ♪
♪ YOU CAN SPREAD
YOUR TIME AROUND ♪
♪ COME ON DOWN,
SLOW DOWN ♪
♪ YOU'VE GOT SO MUCH TIME
TO FIND YOUR MIND ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE
THE WAITIN' KIND ♪
♪ YOU SHOULD SLOW,
SLOW DOWN ♪
♪ USED UP ALL YOUR AIR
BEING EVERYWHERE ♪
♪ TRYING TO PROVE YOUR WORTH
TO THE TOWN ♪
♪ SO CATCH YOUR BREATH ♪
♪ AND SLOW DOWN ♪
HI, PAIGE.
IT'S CHANTEL SAUVE.
WE HAD AN 8:45-
WHOOPS.
DON'T WORRY.
HAVE A SEAT.
WOW!
THIS ISN'T THE PAIGE
I EXPECTED TO SEE
THIS MORNING.
I'VE GOT MULTIPLE
PERSONALITIES?
THAT EXPLAINS A LOT.
SAUVE:
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
I WANT
TO CONGRATULATE YOU
ON YESTERDAY.
I KNOW THINGS
DIDN'T TURN OUT
THE WAY YOU WANTED
THEM TO,
BUT THE OUTCOME'S
GOING TO BE GOOD
FOR YOU
IN THE FUTURE,
BECAUSE YOU DID
THE RIGHT THING -
THE ONLY THING -
BY GOING TO COURT.
THE JUSTICE SYSTEM
ISN'T PERFECT.
BUT I'VE WATCHED IT
HELP YOU
TO FIND YOUR
VOICE AGAIN
AND TO HEAL.
YOU'VE TRIUMPHED OVER
YOUR RAPIST MORALLY
BECAUSE YOU'VE
BEEN HONEST.
SURE.
THANKS.
YOU OKAY?
HOPE IT FELT GOOD.
A LITTLE.
HOW'S THE LOVE-MOBILE?
I'LL GET A JOB,
OKAY?
I'LL GIVE YOU
THE MONEY TO FIX IT.
WHATEVER IT TAKES.
HATZILAKOS:
GAVIN?
YOU'RE WANTED OUTSIDE.
OOH, FRIES AND GRAVY!
GOOD ON A PLATE,
NOT SO GOOD
ON A KEYBOARD.
I'LL BE CAREFUL.
NO WORRIES.
YOU WANNA TELL
YOUR DAD THAT -
THE "NO WORRIES" PART?
HE CALLED ME LAST NIGHT
AND THIS MORNING.
AH...
I DON'T HAVE A DAD,
REMEMBER?
I'LL SEE YOU IN CLASS,
CRAIG.
YEAH, BYE.
IT'D BREAK JOEY'S
LITTLE HEART
IF HE HEARD YOU TALK
LIKE THAT.
WELL, THEN HE'D PROBABLY
MAKE ME PAY FOR IT.
BECAUSE APPARENTLY,
I'M THE BANK OF CRAIG.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
HELLO?
SPINNER:
PAIGE.
WHERE ARE YOU?
COP SHOP.
FIFTY-FIVE.
PAIGE:
YOU DIDN'T MAKE ME
YOUR ONE PHONE CALL, SPIN?
FAILURE TO REMAIN
AT THE SCENE OF AN ACCIDENT,
MISCHIEF
AND DANGEROUS DRIVING.
I'M SCARED.
YOU DIDN'T DO ANYTHING!
DEAN CALLED THE POLICE
WITH MY LICENCE PLATE NUMBER.
I TOLD THEM I DID IT.
NO.
SPINNER:
YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH ENOUGH,
OKAY?
I SAW YOU GO THROUGH
ENOUGH.
YOU'RE SAFE.
I JUST WANTED TO TELL YOU.
TIME'S UP.
YOUR MOTHER'S HERE.
BYE, PAIGE.
YOUR BOYFRIEND IS DEAD!
I DID IT.
YOU WRECKED MY CAR?
YOU'RE GOING TO GO DOWN
FOR THAT.
I'LL PROVE IT WAS YOU!
SORRY TO TAKE AWAY YOUR FUN,
BUT I'M ABOUT TO CONFESS.
'CAUSE THAT'S WHAT
GOOD PEOPLE DO
WHEN THEY REALIZE THEY'VE
DONE SOMETHING WRONG.
THE FRAT DIDN'T
LET ME IN
BECAUSE OF YOU
AND WHAT YOU SAID.
HEY!
I'M NOT FINISHED!
WELL,
I'M VERY FINISHED -
WITH ALL OF THIS,
OKAY?
BUT ESPECIALLY
WITH YOU.
IT'S OVER, DEAN.
I'VE GOT SOMETHING
TO DO.
SOMETHING
MORE IMPORTANT.
HI. UM...
I'M HERE ABOUT SOMETHING
THAT HAPPENED LAST NIGHT?
JOEY:
CRAIG,
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?!
I'M JUST GETTING MY GUITAR
AND SOME CLOTHES.
I WON'T-
I WANT TO TALK
TO YOU-
I WON'T USE ANY
OF YOUR FOOD OR-
I WANT-
CRAIG!
WHAT?!
I MIGHT LOSE MY BUSINESS.
WHAT?
I DIDN'T WANT
TO TELL YOU.
I-I-I DIDN'T WANT YOU
TO WORRY.
WELL, YOU SHOULD
HAVE SAID SOMETHING.
I'M TRYING TO BE
THE DAD HERE.
AND INSTEAD,
LIKE AN IDIOT,
I HIT YOU UP
FOR CASH.
IT WAS WRONG.
SO YOU ASKED ME
THIS STUPID
RENT THING INSTEAD.
JOEY:
I KNOW.
BUT MY LINE OF CREDIT
IS SHOT.
MY BILLS,
THEY'RE HUGE.
LOOK, I'LL GIVE YOU
THE MONEY, JOEY.
I'LL-I'LL TAKE
MY GUITAR BACK
AND YOU CAN
HAVE IT ALL.
NO.
I CAN'T DO THAT.
WELL, YOU HAVE TO LET ME
DO SOMETHING.
LOOK, I KNOW YOU WANT TO BE
A BIG ROCK STAR SOMEDAY,
BUT IF YOU NEEDED IT,
I'D LIKE THE DEALERSHIP
TO BE THERE FOR YOU.
HI.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WELL, I LOST MY LICENCE,
WHICH WAS EXCITING.
AND I'M PROBABLY STUCK
WITH A YEAR
OF COMMUNITY SERVICE.
TEACHING ANGER MANAGEMENT?
I THINK I'D BE GOOD
AT THAT.
I ALSO THOUGHT
I MIGHT EMBROIDER
"ON PROBATION"
ON ALL MY CLOTHES.
GIVE MYSELF THAT
"BAD GIRL" EDGE.
SO YOU CAME BY
TO MAKE JOKES?
I CAME TO SAY THAT...
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT ELSE TO SAY.
I WISH I'D NEVER HURT
YOUR CAR...
OR YOU.
OKAY.
AND I MEANT IT
WHEN I SAID I'D PAY.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO GO OUT
WITH ME?
TRIPLE-FEATURE
AT THE DRIVE-IN
THIS WEEKEND.
SOUR CANDY'S ON ME.
IF WE CAN GET THE CAR
IN DECENT SHAPE BY THEN.
WRENCH?