♪♪♪
ALL RIGHT, C'MON GUYS,
LET'S SPOT.
♪♪♪
MANNY:
WOO! GO US!
WHOOPSY DAISY.
♪♪♪
(APPLAUSE)
WOW!
WHEN EVERYONE GETS
A LOAD OF THAT
AT THE YEAR END PARTY,
WE'LL HAVE TO FORCE THEM
TO TAKE A SUMMER VACATION!
MANNY'S CHOREOGRAPHY
IS MORE FUN THAN
GOING TO THE BEACH.
OKAY,
AS CAPTAIN OF THE SQUAD,
I'D JUST LIKE TO SAY
THAT I ADORE YOU GUYS
AND I WANT TO THANK
ALL OF YOU
FOR YOUR SPECTACULAR
HARD WORK.
WELL, THE SCHOOL
APPRECIATES IT, PAIGE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
FOR BEING A BIG, FAT,
USELESS PILE OF NOTHING.
(GIRLS GIGGLE)
DID YOU WANT TO SAY SOMETHING,
MANNY?
GOSH, NO, PAIGE.
IT'S ALL YOU.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
IF I PEED
IN THE FOYER,
PAIGE WOULD CLAIM
SHE GAVE ME THE WATER.
THERE WOULDN'T BE
MUCH CREDIT THERE.
TOBY:
IF YOU BE MY PROM DATE,
I WOULDN'T LET HER TAKE
ANY CREDIT.
NOT FOR ME.
THERE REALLY
WOULDN'T BE.
SHUT UP, EMMA.
I'VE BEEN KNOCKING
MYSELF OUT.
PAIGE COMES
TO ONE PRACTICE
IN THREE MONTHS
AND ACTS LIKE
SHE OWNS IT.
TOBY:
DID YOU HEAR THE PART
WHERE I ASKED YOU TO THE PROM?
TOBY, YOU'RE A SWEET,
SWEET GUY...
MARCO:
BUT MANNY'S GOING WITH ME.
SORRY, BUT AS THE NEWLY SINGLE
HEAD OF THE DANCE COMMITTEE,
I HAD TO SCOOP UP THE CUTEST
DATE I COULD FIND.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
HOW COME THE GAY
GUYS ALWAYS WIN?
OH MY GOD,
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
YOU'LL FIND SOMETHING
CHIC TO WEAR?
OF COURSE!
WHO'S ALL GOING?
US, JIMMY, HAZEL,
AND JUST SO YOU KNOW?
I THINK PAIGE
IS BRINGING MATT.
MANNY:
MARCO IS MY DREAM DATE.
WELL, NEARLY.
BUT PAIGE WILL EAT ME ALIVE
IF I GO WITH YOU GUYS.
THAT'S BECAUSE
YOU DID
GET HER BOYFRIEND
FIRED FROM TEACHING
AND PULL HER HAIR.
WELL, MAYBE HAZEL
THE PEACEMAKER
COULD SMOOTH IT OVER
JUST A TEENSY BIT?
WE ARE GOING SHOPPING
TONIGHT
AT "PRETTY PRETTY"
AROUND SEVEN-ISH
AND SHOPPING
MAKES PAIGE EMOTIONAL.
OKAY.
YOU COULD RUN
INTO US,
ACT ALL SUBMISSIVE.
YOU MIGHT GET SOMEPLACE.
KEVIN SMITH:
UM, I DON'T KNOW,
I THINK IT JUST FELT LIKE
IT WAS TIME
TO GET OFF THE SOUND STAGES
AND KIND OF GO BACK
INTO THE REAL WORLD.
SHOOT REAL LOCATIONS,
REAL PEOPLE.
CAITLIN:
AND SO WHEN DO CAMERAS
START ROLLING ON
"JAY AND SILENT BOB
GO CANADIAN, EH?"
KEVIN SMITH:
YOU LIKE THAT TITLE?
THE "EH" MAKES IT.
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO START
SHOOTING IN A COUPLE OF WEEKS
BUT SADLY,
JUST RECENTLY,
SOME OF OUR LOCATIONS
DROPPED OUT ON US.
DROPPED OOT ON US,
AS YOU SAY.
SO IF ANYONE OUT THERE
HAS A BEER FACTORY,
OR A HOCKEY RINK,
OR A DONUT SHOP
OR A STRIP CLUB,
OR A SCHOOL,
PARTICULARLY
WE NEED A SCHOOL.
PLEASE, CALL US.
CALL ME.
CAITLIN:
PLEASE JOIN US NEXT WEEK.
I'M CAITLIN RYAN.
THAT WAS GREAT, EVERYONE.
THAT WAS GREAT.
THANK YOU.
THAT WAS REALLY FUN.
CAITLIN:
THANK YOU.
KEVIN, THIS IS CRAIG,
MY SORT OF UH...
STEPSON.
KEVIN:
RIGHT ON.
HOW ARE YOU,
SIR?
MR. SMITH?
HI.
WOW. HI.
MR. MANNING. HI.
WOW. HI, YOURSELF.
HOW DID YOU...?
LITTLE BIRD.
CRAIG GOES TO MY OLD SCHOOL.
MAYBE YOU'VE HEARD OF IT?
DEGRASSI?
WELL, IT'S A GREAT
LOOKING SCHOOL,
YOU SHOULD CHECK IT OUT.
UH, YOU SHOULD CHECK IT OUT
ON FRIDAY
BECAUSE MY GIRLFRIEND AND I
ARE PLAYING PROM.
OH, REALLY?
WHAT ARE YOU
A MUSICIAN OR SOMETHING?
FANTASTIC MUSICIAN.
FANTASTIC,
THE LADY SAYS.
THAT'S GOOD ENOUGH
FOR ME.
CAN I BORROW YOUR PEN?
OF COURSE.
I'M LOOKING FOR A FANTASTIC
MUSICIAN, SIR.
THIS IS MY MUSIC GUYS NUMBER.
YOU GIVE HIM A SHOUT.
TELL HIM I TOLD YOU
TO CALL HIM.
GIVE ME SOMETHING
HIGH SCHOOL, DUDE.
REAL HIGH SCHOOL.
NOT WEEZER
APPROXIMATING HIGH SCHOOL.
CAN YOU GIVE ME EMO?
YOU CAN GIVE ME REAL EMO?
I CAN GIVE YOU
REAL EMO?
RIGHT ON, SIR.
EXCELLENT MEETING YOU.
YOU MAY HAVE A JOB.
THE SMALL IS STILL
A BIT SQUEEZE-Y.
BETTER THAN
THE EXTRA SMALL.
OOH, I LOVE IT!
HI!
I GUESS I HAVE
GREAT TASTE!
STRAPLESS MAKE YOU
NERVOUS TOO?
IS THAT
THE EXTRA SMALL?
PFFT!
NO. NO.
LISTEN, PAIGE,
I WAS REALLY HOPING
THAT WE CAN MAKE THINGS
BETTER BETWEEN US.
TAKE OFF THE DRESS.
LISTEN, I HATE...
I HATE THAT YOU HATE ME.
PLEASE, IS THERE ANYTHING
THAT I CAN DO?
OUT OF THE DRESS
AND MY AIRSPACE.
GET BEHIND
THAT KEYBOARD!
ASHLEY:
COULD WE SIT
FOR A MINUTE FIRST?
NO SITTING.
NO TIME!
OKAY. I TOLD YOU
MY DAD GOT A TRANSFER
TO BBC WORLD
IN LONDON?
NO SMALL BOLLOCKS,
OY?!
WELL, HE GOT ME
A SUMMER JOB TOO.
BBC SIX!
THEY CALL IT "TEA GIRL",
WHICH I THINK MEANS GOPHER,
BUT...
YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO LONDON.
LOOK, CRAIG,
I KNOW,
BUT I PROMISE,
I'LL I.M. YOU EVERY DAY
AND SEND YOU TONS
OF OBSCURE BRIT-POP?
I'M AFRAID THAT WE'RE
GONNA BE TOO BUSY...
DOING MUSIC FOR
KEVIN SMITH'S SOUNDTRACK!
ASHLEY:
WHAT?!
HOW?
OH MY GOD!
I KNOW.
WE HAVE A MEETING
WITH HIS MUSIC GUY.
HOW MUCH DO YOU
LOVE ME NOW?
I BETTER GET BEHIND
THAT KEYBOARD!
SEE, I TOLD YOU
YOU WEREN'T GOING.
(SINGS WHAT SOUNDS LIKE
"SILENT BOB")
THE ONLY SUMMER JOB OUT THERE
IS IN THE YUKON?
I'M BROKE, PAIGE.
I'M LIKE SELLING-MY-STUFF-
EATING-MACARONI BROKE...
AND TREE-PLANTING PAYS.
MY PARENTS HAVE CUT OFF
MY TUITION MONEY.
IT'S FOUR HUNDRED A DAY.
FREE RENT.
IT'S LOOKING LIKE
THE ONLY WAY OUT.
I'LL BE BACK
BEFORE YOU EVEN MISS ME.
THE WHOLE SUMMER
IS FOREVER.
MARCO:
HEY, I JUST SAW YOUR OLD BOSS?
THE MERE SIGHT OF MEERI
TOOK 6 YEARS OFF MY LIFE.
I'LL GO GET US
SOME DRINKS.
DIET.
SQUEEZEY DRESS.
DID I JUST TOTALLY
WRECK A MOMENT?
HE'S LEAVING...
BEFORE THE PROM
AND HE WON'T BE BACK
FOR MONTHS.
MANNY:
WHAT?
I'M SO SORRY.
BUT PAIGE NEEDS A DATE
AND SHE'S HONESTLY
HEARTBROKEN
AND I...
MAYBE TOBY'S
STILL FREE?
DARCY:
MANNY? CAN YOU HELP US
FOR A SEC?
HEY, I'LL VOTE FOR YOU
FOR QUEEN?
A TIARA WOULD
REALLY SUIT YOU.
HAIR JEWELRY.
RIGHT.
THAT'D FIX MY TOTALLY
SUCKY LIFE FOR SURE.
DARCY:
PAIGE IS HAVING TROUBLE
WITH THE ONE-KEWPIE-TWO
GRAPEVINE-THREE COMBO.
I'M NOT HAVING
TROUBLE WITH IT,
I JUST DON'T LIKE IT.
AND I DON'T SEE WHY
IT CAN'T JUST BE
STRAIGHT GRAPEVINE.
CHANTAY:
BECAUSE THAT'S BORING.
OKAY, I'M THE CAPTAIN,
I'M NOT IN THE MOOD
FOR SASS,
AND I'M CHANGING
THE CHOREOGRAPHY.
IS THAT BORING?
MANNY:
I'LL SHOW YOU
AND I'LL TAKE IT REALLY,
REALLY SLOW, OKAY?
I'M MISSING THE MASCOT.
GO GET THE COSTUME,
I'LL TAKE YOUR PLACE.
YOU WANT ME
TO DO WHAT?
HAZEL:
WE'RE PERFORMING
IN TWO HOURS, PAIGE.
WE'VE NEVER CAUGHT YOU.
WELL, UNLESS MANNY,
DARCY, CHANTAY AND YOU
ALL WANT OFF THE SQUAD?
MANNY'S THE MASCOT.
CONSIDER MY FOOT DOWN.
DON'T THROW OUT
JUSTIN!
PURGING.
ANYTHING THAT COULD POSSIBLY
REMIND ME OF THIS YEAR MUST GO.
I WISH WE COULD
PURGE PAIGE.
IF ANYONE EVER DESERVED
TO FALL OFF HER HIGH HORSE...
IT'S HER.
WHAT?
AND SO, I'D LIKE TO DECLARE
THIS SCHOOL YEAR...
OFFICIALLY OVER!
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
KEVIN:
CHECK YOU OUT?
FREE SODA?
SWANKY SCHOOL.
CAITLIN:
ACTUALLY, WE CALL IT POP
AROUND THESE HERE PARTS.
KEVIN SMITH:
POP.
SEE? THIS IS WHY
I NEED YOU AROUND ME
WHEN WE'RE SHOOTING
THE MOVIE -
SO YOU CAN TRANSLATE
CANADIAN.
CAN YOU DO THAT
FOR ME?
STOP.
PLEASE?
SHUSH!
MS. HATZILAKOS:
TO SEND US TOWARD
THE SUMMER
WITH SMILES ON OUR FACES,
HERE'S DEGRASSI'S
SPIRIT SQUAD!
(APPLAUSE)
♪♪♪
AHHHH!
(SCREAMING IN PAIN)
PAIGE:
OW! MY LEG!
SO...
THAT'S THE GYM.
PAIGE:
PLEASE DO SOMETHING.
♪♪♪
WE WRITE
ALL OUR OWN STUFF.
SO WE CAN ADJUST IT,
IF YOU WANT.
IF I WANT?
WANT I WANT IS
HUSKER DU MEETS
THE MEAT PUPPETS
WITH MAYBE A SOUPCON
OF VAN HALEN.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT.
UM... OKAY.
IS THAT WHAT WE DID?
IS THAT WHAT YOU DID?
THIS IS A
BUDDY-SLASH-LOVE STORY,
OKAY, MAN?
IT'S NOT THE PLACE
FOR WHINY GIRLS
IMPERSONATING KATE BUSH
ACCOMPANIED BY BON JOVI
WANNABES!
HEY!
DAVE:
GET OUT OF MY OFFICE
PLEASE!
THANK YOU.
GET KEVIN FOR ME,
PLEASE.
I GUESS WE'RE NO
BEEF PUPPETS.
I GUESS WE SUCK.
DON'T LOOK SO WORRIED.
PAIGE IS FINE.
AND SO IS THE DRESS.
MANNY:
FINE. FINE. FINE.
FINE AS IN BORING.
LIKE MASS.
LATIN, WHEN THE HOLY-HOT
ALTAR BOY'S OUT WITH THE FLU.
IT KINDA LOOKS
LIKE SOMETHING
THE ALTAR BOY
WOULD WEAR.
MANNY:
THIS ONE MAKES ME
HAPPY,
BUT PAIGE...
EMMA:
SHE BROKE HER LEG YESTERDAY.
SHE'S NOT GOING
TO THE SEMI-FORMAL.
AND THIS JUST HAPPENS
TO BE
THE MANNY-EST
DRESS EVER.
YOU THINK?
EMMA:
AFTER ALL SHE PUT YOU THROUGH,
I THINK YOU DESERVE IT.
JT:
THE CHEESE BUFFET
OPENS AT 10:00 P.M.
MANNY:
MMM. TEMPTING.
LIBERTY:
WE CAME UP WITH THAT
TOGETHER.
WE SHARE A LOVE
OF CHEESE.
JT:
YES, WE DO.
ANYWAYS, YOUR BALLOTS
FOR KING AND QUEEN.
I FEEL TERRIBLE.
DO YOU FEEL TERRIBLE?
SHE'LL GET OVER IT
AND SO WILL WE.
HER LEG WAS TWISTED
LIKE SHE WAS
A CIRQUE DU SOLEIL CHICK.
SHE ISN'T.
SO WE'LL...
WE'LL VOTE FOR HER
FOR PROM QUEEN, OKAY?
AND WE'LL SEND THE TIARA
TO HER HOUSE. SEE?
NOW I'M GOING TO ASK
TOBY TO DANCE
FOR EXTRA PENANCE.
OKAY.
NINTH GRADE.
MY DATE IS ORANGE
AND I'M SPORTING
A SCREAMING SUNBURN.
TENTH GRADE.
OUR LIMO DRIVER,
JIM-BOY-JED THE CRIMINAL,
DELIVERS US
IN A COP CRUISER.
ELEVENTH GRADE,
IT GETS WORSE.
HALF-WHACKED
ON PAINKILLERS,
I ARRIVE WITH A DATE,
WHO DOESN'T LIKE GIRLS,
ON THE SPECIAL BUS.
HELLO, EVERYONE!
HAPPY PROM!
ISN'T THIS SO PERFECTLY
FESTIVE?!
JIMMY:
ARE YOU FINISHED?
NO!
MY ARMPITS HURT!
MORE THAN YOUR ARMPITS
WILL HURT
IF YOU DON'T SHUT
YOUR PIE-HOLE!
I WANTED THIS
TO BE SPECIAL FOR HIM
AND ALL YOU CAN DO
IS WHINE.
IF THE TANTRUM'S
BEEN THROWN...
ONE MORE THING.
MANNY STEPPED UP AND RAN
THE SPIRIT SQUAD FOR YOU
WHEN YOU WERE TOO
SELF-INVOLVED.
ALL SHE WANTED
WAS A THANK YOU.
BUT COULD YOU
GIVE HER THAT?
OH NO.
SHE WAS HORRIBLE TO ME.
BUT CAN YOU TELL ME
WHY YOU HAD TO BE MORE
HORRIBLE BACK?
WHY YOU ALWAYS HAVE TO BE
MORE HORRIBLE?
♪♪♪
UH, MAYBE...
MAYBE I CAN GET
A BEVERAGE NOW?
MAYBE YOU'LL
LIKE THE NEXT SONG TOO.
RIGHT.
WELL, EMMA...
EMMA... SAID,
SHE WOULD DIE IF SHE DIDN'T
GET HER HANDS ON YOU.
EMMA:
NO, I-
KEVIN:
OH MY GOD,
MS. RYAN.
IF I KNEW YOU WERE TAKING ME
TO THE PROM,
I WOULD'VE TOTALLY
GOTTEN YOU A CORSAGE.
NO, I'M HERE TO HELP YOU
CHECK THE PLACE OUT.
IT DOESN'T QUALIFY
AS A DATE.
THAT'S SO WEIRD.
MY PROM DATE SAID
THE EXACT SAME THING.
MANNY:
OH MY GOD!
YOU'RE INDESTRUCTIBLE!
I'M GLAD YOU'RE HERE,
BECAUSE-
WHAT ARE YOU
WEARING?
LIBERTY:
ONCE THE BALLOT'S FILLED OUT,
IT NEEDS TO BE
HANDED IT IN.
I CANNOT BELIEVE.
JT:
MAYBE YOU TWO CAN BE
THE WORLD'S FIRST
MATCHING PROM QUEEN SET,
HUH?
LIKE SOCKS OR MITTENS
OR BOOKENDS.
WE'RE NOT BOOKENDS.
PAIGE:
WHAT I WAS GOING
TO SAY WAS...
GOOD LUCK.
I REALLY HOPE YOU WIN.
♪♪♪
♪ THROUGH THE MUD
AND THE DIRT ♪
♪ ALL THE TEARS
AND THE HURT ♪
♪ IT SEARED
AND IT BURNED ♪
♪ AND I CRIED ♪
♪ THROUGH THE MUD
AND THE DIRT ♪
♪ ALL THE TEARS
AND THE HURT ♪
♪ IT SEARED
AND IT BURNED ♪
♪ AND I DIED ♪
CRAIG AND ASHLEY:
♪ THERE WAS NOTHING AT ALL, ♪
♪ NO NOTHING AT ALL ♪
♪ THERE WAS ONLY A DREAM
OF YOU ♪
♪ THERE WAS NOTHING AT ALL ♪
♪ NO NOTHING AT ALL ♪
♪ 'TIL YOUR PROMISE
EXPLODED THROUGH... ♪
♪ THERE WAS NOTHING AT ALL, ♪
♪ NO NOTHING AT ALL ♪
♪ THERE WAS ONLY A DREAM
OF YOU... ♪
PAIEGE:
CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOU
CENTRE STAGE
MANNY SANTOS.
OH, WE ROCKED
THE PLACE OUT!
DID YOU JUST SAY
ROCKED OUT?
HEY, NO LIP
OR I'LL SMOTHER YOU
IN SWEAT.
I'M GOING TO MISS YOU
SO MUCH.
BUT THE SHOW
WENT REALLY GREAT.
THERE WAS
A MOMENT UP THERE?
WHEN I THOUGHT
TO MYSELF
I HAVE NOTHING LEFT
TO PROVE.
NOW I'M READY
TO GO TO ENGLAND
AND TRY SOME
NEW THINGS.
RIGHT.
YOU KNOW I'VE WANTED TO GO
SINCE I WAS A KID.
SINCE YOU SAW
MARY POPPINS.
I KNOW.
IT'S GREAT.
IT'S REALLY GREAT.
COME ON, YOU.
LET'S GET
TO THE CHEESE BUFFET
BEFORE HEATHER SINCLAIR
SCARFS ALL THE HAVARTI.
UM... I'LL MEET
YOU THERE.
MARCO:
THANKS TO MY CHARMING
BUT-ODD CHEESE-LOVING
COMMITTEE,
TO ALL OF YOU,
AND OF COURSE TO OUR SPONSOR,
PANTENE.
(APPLAUSE)
ALL RIGHT.
AND NOW,
THE FATEFUL MOMENT...
(DRUM ROLL)
OUR KING: JIMMY BROOKS!
AND QUEEN: MANNY SANTOS!
(APPLAUSE)
MARCO:
OW! PAIGE,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
GIVE ME THE CROWN.
WELL-DESERVED,
MANNY.
JT:
MANNY!
YOU ALL RIGHT?
WE'RE GONNA DEFINITELY BE
SHOOTING HERE, MS. RYAN.
YOU SHOULD GO
AND PUT ON A NEW GOWN.
(LAUGHING)
KEVIN:
HEY, I KNOW THAT KID.
HEY KID! GET OFF MY SET!
SORRY.
ARE YOU WORKING HERE?
KEVIN:
NO, WE'RE NOT.
THAT'S OKAY.
DUDE, I NEVER WORK.
AND THAT THING,
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
HOW THAT OPERATES.
YOU EVER SEEN ONE
OF MY FLICKS?
KINDA SHOWS.
CRAIG:
I LIKE THE ONE
WHERE THE GUYS HANG
OUTSIDE THE 7-ELEVEN.
YEAH, THAT KINDA
NARROWS IT DOWN A BIT.
WHY AREN'T YOU INSIDE
PROMING IT UP?
YOUR MUSIC GUY
HATED US
AND NOW ASHLEY'S
GOING TO ENGLAND.
UH, WHAT I'M HEARING
IS GIRL TROUBLE, DUDE.
IT ALWAYS COMES DOWN
TO GIRL TROUBLE.
I CAN FEEL YOUR PAIN, SIR.
YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH THIS?
KEVIN:
GIRL TROUBLE?
DUDE, I'M A FAT GUY
FROM NEW JERSEY.
YEAH,
I'VE HAD GIRL TROUBLE.
EVEN WHEN I WRITE
AND DIRECT THE MOVIES,
I NEVER GET THE GIRL.
I ALWAYS WIND UP WITH JAY.
IN SOME CASES,
A MONKEY.
WELL, YOU KNOW
WHAT I'VE FOUND...
WHEN MY HEART GETS BROKEN,
JUST THROW YOURSELF
INTO WORK, MAN.
GO HOME
START WRITING A SONG.
GO WRITE A SONG
FOR A MOVIE.
A MOVIE DIRECTED BY
FAT STAR WARS NERD
WHO HANGS AROUND HIGH SCHOOLS
DURING PROM,
TALKS TO BROKEN-HEARTED
MUSICIAN TYPES...
DUDE, WHAT PART OF THIS
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
YOUR MUSIC GUY SAID
I SUCK.
UH, DUDE.
HE'S PERSONA NON-GRADA.
THAT DUDE'S GOT NO CREDIBILITY
WHATSOEVER.
THE DAY CREED BROKE UP,
I FOUND HIM
IN A BATHROOM STALL
AND HE WAS CRYING.
CRYING, DUDE!
BESIDES, IT'S MY MOVIE.
IT'S NOT HIS MOVIE.
YOU'RE LOOKING AT ME
ALL INCREDULOUS LIKE.
DUDE, DID NOT SEE ME
TEN MINUTES AGO?
I FLAT OUT CAUGHT
THE PROM QUEEN.
YOU KNOW WHAT KIND OF A HUGE
KARMIC DEBT THAT IS
TO PAY BACK?
I GOT TO PAY IF FORWARD,
MAN.
I'M GONNA PAY YOU.
I BROUGHT PINS.
IF IT WERE LEGAL
I'D OFFER YOU
PAINKILLERS TOO.
MANNY:
WHERE DO YOU GET OFF
COMING IN HERE?!
HOW CAN YOU
EVEN TALK TO ME?!
HI,
YOU BROKE MY LEG!
YOU MADE ME
BE THE MASCOT!
LOOK STUPID!
YOU TOOK CREDIT
FOR MY WORK!
YOU GOT MATT
FIRED!
YOU-
I DON'T REMEMBER,
BUT YOU STARTED IT!
I'LL KEEP GOING!
YOU STRESS ME
AT SPIRIT SQUAD,
YOU MAKE ME LOOK
LIKE A FULL-FAT SPAZ!
SHUT UP!
YOU'RE JUST JEALOUS!
YEAH, RIGHT.
DON'T DRINK ANYTHING
ELSE TONIGHT.
THE GIRLS WENT OUT
FOR LAXATIVES.
THANKS FOR THE TIP.
WELL, AT LEAST IT'S SUMMER NOW.
YEAH.
SUMMER'S GOOD.