DANNY:
16 MAY.
CASTLE DRACULA IS A VERITABLE
PRISON AND I AM ITS PRISONER.
WORSE,
I FEAR I MAY BE GOING MAD.
LAST NIGHT I WAS SITTING.
IT WAS THEN THAT I NOTICED
I WAS NOT ALONE.
YOU'RE TENSE.
I'M ALWAYS TENSE.
JAY:
SNAP IN HALF
IF YOU DON'T RELAX.
DANNY:
I THOUGHT I MUST BE DREAMING.
ALTHOUGH THE MOONLIGHT
WAS BEHIND THEM
THEY THREW NO SHADOW
ON THE FLOOR.
WHAT ARE YOU THREE BEAUTIES?
JT:
THREE BEAUTIES?
THREE BEAUTIES! EMMA!
SORRY, UH...
WE ARE RAVENOUS.
WE HUNGER.
WE LONG.
AMY:
TONIGHT WE FEAST.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
EMMA.
WOULD YOU LIKE
TO SEE A GRAPH
OF YOUR
PARTICIPATION GRADE?
I KNOW YOU WENT THROUGH A LOT
AFTER THE SHOOTING.
BUT THE GRACE PERIOD
IS COMING TO AN END.
OKAY?
P.A. ANNOUNCER:
THIS IS A REMINDER THAT
THE GYM IS CLOSED THIS WEEK
IN PREPARATION FOR THE UPCOMING
"CASTLE DRACULA" PLAY.
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE
A PICTURE;
IT'LL LAST LONGER.
YOU CAN SELL IT ONLINE
FOR BIG PORNO BUCKS.
(RATTLE OF MAGAZINE)
I HAVE TO PARADE ANOREXIC
FASHION VICTIMS
TO GET YOUR ATTENTION?
WORRYING ABOUT CRAIG
AS USUAL.
SO NOT YOUR JOB
TO WORRY.
TRUST ANOTHER
SICKO HERE.
CRAIG:
WHO'S A SICKO?
ME...
AFTER SEEING THAT COMPOST
ON YOUR TRAY.
IT'S GOULASH.
IT'S GOOD-BYE.
SO HOW WAS SHRINK-TIME?
WHAT WERE YOU GUYS
TALKING ABOUT?
I HAVEN'T TOLD ELLIE.
DON'T WORRY.
MMM, GOULASH.
I FIGURE ANY FOOD
WITH "GOO" IN THE NAME
HAS TO BE GOOD.
HAVE YOU EVER THOUGHT ABOUT
GOING TO A SUPPORT GROUP?
FOR GOULASH LOVERS?
NO, NO.
THERE'S A MENTAL HEALTH GROUP
FOR TEENS
TONIGHT AT
THE REC CENTRE.
HAVE YOU NOT NOTICED
MY DESPERATE URGE
TO TALK ABOUT
SOMETHING ELSE?
LOOK IT'S ONE NIGHT
AND IF YOU HATE IT
THEN YOU DON'T GO BACK.
PREDICTION?
I WILL HATE IT.
SO YOU'LL GO?
GOOD.
JT:
OKAY, ACT ONE, SCENE FIVE.
AND GO.
MANNY:
BUT SURELY DEAREST MINA,
I SHOULD KNOW IT
IF I WALKED IN MY SLEEP.
DARCY:
DEAREST LUCY...
LINE?
YOU AROSE FOUR TIMES
FROM BED.
DARCY:
OH RIGHT. OKAY...
YOU GOT UP
FOUR TIMES AND...
POOP.
WHAT'D SHE DO?
THIS IS MY LEADING LADY
THREE DAYS TO OPENING?
PATIENCE,
MY HOT-HEADED PARAMOUR.
BUT SHE'S PARAPHRASING
YOUR WORDS,
MY TALENTED INAMORATA.
YOU DRESSED YOURSELF
COMPLETELY.
I THINK PROMPTING
IS LIBERTY'S JOB.
KWAN:
PERHAPS WE OUGHT TO TAKE
A BREAK?
JT:
LISTEN.
I'M DIRECTING AND PLAYING
VAN HELSING
AND I KNOW MY LINES.
WELL, MAYBE IF YOU'D STOP
CHANGING THE BLOCKING
EVERY FIVE MINUTES THEN...
I KNOW.
HOW ABOUT I CHANGE
THE CASTING INSTEAD?
OKAY, ARE YOU FIRING ME?
I CAN'T IF YOU RESIGN FIRST.
DARCY:
FINE!
THEN I CURSE YOU,
MACBETH!
MANNY:
DRIVE A STAKE THROUGH
THIS PLAY'S HEART.
THEY HAVE TO CANCEL IT.
AMY:
THEY COULD LET ME PLAY MINA.
ME, THE BEAUTIFUL VIRGIN.
ALEX:
NOW THAT'S ACTING.
DEAREST LUCY, I SWEAR.
YOU AROSE FOUR TIMES FROM BED.
YOU DRESSED YOURSELF
COMPLETELY.
EM, YOU COULD DO IT!
JUST GO ASK.
I BOMBED THE AUDITION.
JUST BECAUSE DARCY QUIT
DOESN'T MEAN THEY'VE CHANGED
THEIR MINDS ABOUT ME.
WHERE ARE MY BRACELETS?
THOSE WIRE THINGS?
THEY'RE WORTH A NICKEL.
BIG WHOOP.
IT IS.
WHO TOOK THEM?
LOOK, COME OVER TONIGHT.
LIBERTY AND I ARE GIVING
EACH OTHER MANI-PEDIS
AND WE CAN DO YOURS TOO.
YOU'D PROBABLY HAVE
MORE FUN
WITHOUT MY HANDS AND FEET
TAGGING ALONG.
AMY...
GIVE ME THOSE!
NANCY:
I GAINED SO MUCH WEIGHT
I COULD HEAR MY ENTIRE BALLET
CLASS THINKING
"WHAT'S SHE BEEN EATING?"
NIGEL:
SO YOU REVEAL YOURSELF AS AN
ANOREXIC DEPRESSIVE INSTEAD?
COME ON.
DOCTOR JIM:
I THINK NANCY WAS SAYING
IT WAS A POSITIVE EXPERIENCE
FOR HER, NIGEL.
CRAIG:
I'M WITH HIM.
I WOULDN'T TELL ANYONE
I DIDN'T HAVE TO.
LET'S TALK ABOUT
WHY YOU FEEL THAT.
OKAY, UM...
ONCE PEOPLE THINK YOU'RE CRAZY,
I THINK THEY JUST THINK
ABOUT THAT.
THEY STOP TREATING YOU
LIKE YOU'RE YOU.
SORRY I'M LATE.
DOCTOR JIM:
WELCOME, ELLIE.
WE WERE TALKING ABOUT
STIGMATIZATION.
CRAIG?
THAT'S ALL I HAD TO SAY.
(CAR STEREO BLARES)
YOU KNOW MY RIDE'S GOT
16 INDEPENDENT SPEAKERS?
I DO NOW.
SOME OF US GOT PLACES TO BE.
THANKS.
UM, MY HOUSE IS-
I DROPPED YOU OFF BEFORE,
REMEMBER?
AFTER SEAN RAN HOME
TO MOMMY DEAREST.
KINDA SUCKS WITHOUT HIM.
YEAH, I MISS HIM TOO.
I DIDN'T SAY THAT.
DON'T GO GETTING ALL MUSHY
ON ME, GREENPEACE.
(CAR STEREO BLARES)
THERE.
OKAY, THANKS.
GOING TO BENNETT PARK LATER.
YEAH.
BUNCH OF US HANG OUT THERE.
SPIKE:
I'M WORRIED, SNAKE.
SIMPSON:
I'M SURE SHE'S OKAY.
SPIKE:
SHE'S STOPPED BRINGING
FRIENDS OVER.
NO DATES.
I FEEL LIKE SHE JUST DIDN'T
GET OVER THE SHOOTING.
SIMPSON:
WELL, MOST OF THE KIDS
AT SCHOOL HAVE.
BUT MOST KIDS DIDN'T WATCH
SOMEONE DIE.
SPIKE:
I KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW I GUESS
IF YOU CLUMP THAT TOGETHER
WITH BEING A TEENAGE GIRL...
HELLO?
ANYBODY HOME?
SIMPSON:
HEY! IT'S THE EMMA NELSON SHOW!
STARRING EMMA NELSON!
REHEARSAL WAS FANTASTIC!
I JUST CAN'T WAIT
'TIL YOU GUYS SEE DRACULA.
SPIKE:
ME NEITHER, HONEY.
SIMPSON:
WELL WE WAITED FOR YOU
FOR DINNER.
IT'S GARDENER'S PIE.
OOH VEGGIELICIOUS.
BUT I HAD PIZZA AFTER
REHEARSAL SO I'M STUFFED.
SPIKE:
HONEY...
ARE YOU OKAY?
MMM HMM.
I'VE GOT A TON OF WORK TO DO
ON MY LINES THOUGH SO...
GOOD NIGHT.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
EMMA:
IS THIS SEAT TAKEN?
JAY:
IT IS NOW.
EMMA:
ARE YOU SURPRISED TO SEE ME?
DO YOU THINK I'M WEIRD?
NOW THERE'S A LOADED QUESTION.
EVERYONE'S BEEN ACTING LIKE
I BELONG IN A STRAIGHTJACKET.
WELL THAT'S THEIR PROBLEM.
YOU'RE NO WEIRDER
THAN THE REST OF US.
EMMA:
WHAT'S IN THE VAN?
WHAT DO YOU THINK'S
IN THE VAN?
BEER? MORE BEER?
SMELLY SHAG CARPETING
FROM THE SEVENTIES?
(LAUGHS)
YOU WANNA SEE?
THIS IS FULLY ANTI-CLIMACTIC.
(DOOR SLIDES SHUT)
COME OUT, COME OUT,
WHEREVER YOU ARE!
JAY:
HEY...
IT'S FOR HOOKING UP.
WHAT?
YOU KNOW WHAT BLOW JOBS ARE,
DON'T YOU?
HEY...
EVERY PLAYER
GETS A PRIZE.
JT:
FORGIVE ME, LIBBY-TIBBY.
MY ICKLE NUBBY-WUBBY
PUNKINHEAD.
PWEASE?
LIBERTY:
DO I HONESTLY STRIKE YOU
AS A BABY-TALK SORT OF WOMAN?
YOU FIRED DARCY
AND NOW WE HAVE
ZIP, ZERO, ZILCH.
LET ME BE AS
YOUR LIGHTHOUSE,
A CANARY FOR
YOUR COALMINE.
LET DRACULA COME
TO MY BREAST
AND I WILL ALLOW HIM
SUSTENANCE.
HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
OH NO.
WE NEED RELIABLE,
ROCK SOLID.
I DO ROCK SOLID PRETTY WELL.
DAY BEFORE YESTERDAY
YOU MISSED YOUR CUE.
LAST NIGHT YOU DIDN'T EVEN
SHOW UP TO MANNY'S.
EVERYONE KNOWS YOU'RE OFF
OR WHATEVER.
I'M NOT OFF.
I'M YOUR MINA!
I KNOW THE BLOCKING.
SO CORSETS,
EVER WORN ONE?
SO MY DAD AND CHRIS
GOT BACK
FROM PUERTO VALLARTA
LAST NIGHT.
APPARENTLY IT'S GAY
HONEYMOONER PARADISE.
THEY ASKED ABOUT YOU.
"CRAZY CRAIG"?
WHAT DID YOU TELL THEM?
OH I BET EVERYTHING.
OKAY.
IT'S GOOD THING I KNEW
MOOD SWINGS ARE COMMON
WHEN YOU FIRST START MEDS.
YOU SENT ME
TO ELLIE'S GROUP.
WHICH SHE LOVES.
I DIDN'T THINK YOU'D MIND.
WELL THEN YOU DIDN'T THINK
AT ALL.
JT:
ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE.
PUT YOUR FANGS TOGETHER
FOR EMMA.
(MILD CLAP) YAY.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S JUMP
RIGHT INTO THE DEEP END
WITH ACT TWO,
SCENE SEVEN.
AND GO.
NATE:
WHEN MY BRAIN SAYS COME TO YOU
YOU SHALL CROSS LAND OR SEA
TO DO MY BIDDING
AND TO THAT END...
THIS.
BUT NO...
I CANNOT.
(GIGGLES)
JT:
EMMA.
THE SCRIPT SAYS
YOU KISS HIM.
SO KISS HIM!
OKAY, I'M SORRY.
IT'S JUST WEIRD DOING THIS
IN FRONT OF EVERYBODY.
JT:
IT'S NOT REAL.
THERE'S NO FOURTH WALL.
NEXT PLAY, LIBERTY?
UNIONIZED ACTORS.
SORRY, I'LL GET IT
BY TOMORROW, OKAY?
I PROMISE.
FINE, TOMORROW.
DON'T LET ME DOWN.
OKAY, SET CHANGE
FOR SCENE ONE.
GO.
ALEX:
GIVE YOU ONE MINUTE WITH NATE
YOU'D DO BETTER THAN THAT.
AMY:
I'D EAT HIM ALL UP.
YOU'D JUST SEE HIS BIG MANLY
SHOES STICKING OUT.
FOR THE SAKE OF GUYS
EVERYWHERE
I HOPE SHE BECOMES A NUN.
ONE OF THEM BIG ONES
THAT SING ALL THE TIME.
ALEX:
OH AMY, THAT'S MEAN.
THE POOR GIRL SUFFERS FROM
PENIS-A-PHOBIA.
HER MOM CAN'T EVEN BUY BANANAS.
AMY:
ONE TIME THEY GAVE HER
A HOT DOG?
SHE THREW UP FOR A WEEK.
(LAUGHS)
ALEX:
SIMPSON HAS TO KEEP
HIS JOCKEY SHORTS
LOCKED IN A SHED OUT BACK
OR SHE WON'T GO INTO THE HOUSE.
AMY:
IS THAT MINE?
NO. IT'S MINE.
WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
EMMA:
JAY! HEY.
DID YOU KNOW I'VE ONLY BEEN
IN A CAR
WITH 16 SPEAKERS TWICE?
POOR YOU.
AMY WAS BEING REALLY
MEAN ABOUT REHEARSAL
AND WHAT HAPPENED,
SO I SHOWED HER
THE BRACELET
AND SHE SHUT RIGHT UP.
IT'S AMY KRYPTONITE.
THIS ISN'T SOME
BROWNIE BADGE COMPETITION.
MAYBE YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO NEEDS TO SHUT UP.
YOU DIDN'T EARN ANYTHING.
AMY DID.
SHE EARNED THEM
FROM YOU?
THERE ARE A LOT OF GIRLS
DOWN THAT RAVINE, EMMA.
I PICKED YOU.
(KNOCKING ON A DOOR)
YOU KNOW HOW TO RE-STRING
A GUITAR?
GET ASH TO.
SHE'S GOOD AT FORCING THINGS.
LIKE FORCING ME TO COME HERE
WITH THIS PAPER-THIN
GUITAR EXCUSE?
CRAIG...
I USED TO CUT MYSELF.
I KNOW.
ELLIE:
WHAT'S BIZARRE IS THAT
I'M ALWAYS GONNA BE A CUTTER.
EVEN IF I DON'T DO IT FOR YEARS,
IT'S STILL ME.
WELL, THAT SUCKS.
IT JUST- IT JUST IS.
IT DOESN'T MATTER HOW I FEEL
OR HOW ANYONE ELSE FEELS.
I'M BI-POLAR.
AND APPARENTLY
IT DOESN'T MATTER
IF I THINK THAT SUCKS EITHER.
THEY THINK KURT COBAIN
WAS BI-POLAR.
YEAH?
ELLIE:
IF HE'D JUST ACCEPTED IT
MAYBE IT ALL
WOULD'VE BEEN DIFFERENT.
NIGEL FROM GROUP
MANAGES OKAY.
HE SEEMED COOL.
ELLIE:
HE IS.
YOU SHOULD COME BACK.
AND YOU SHOULD PROBABLY
CALL ASH.
WHY?
WHY? 'CAUSE I BIT HER HEAD OFF
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE SCHOOL?
YEAH, MAYBE 'CAUSE
OF THAT.
ALL SHE TALKS ABOUT LATELY
IS MEDICATION,
MY SHRINK AND MY MOODS.
SHE CARES ABOUT YOU.
A LOT.
I KNOW.
YOU ALREADY HAD
THE TOUR.
SHOW ME AGAIN.
SHOW ME AGAIN FOR REAL.
AFTER YOU.
ASHLEY:
I SHOULD'VE TOLD YOU SOONER
THAT IT WAS ELLIE'S GROUP.
BUT I STILL LIKED IT.
I'M GONNA GO AGAIN
NEXT WEEK.
ASHLEY:
YOU ARE?
ASH...
I WANT BE YOUR BOYFRIEND.
OF COURSE.
WE WENT THROUGH THIS
A COUPLE MONTHS AGO, REMEMBER?
I WANT BE THAT BOYFRIEND
NOT THE CRAZY GUY
YOU GOT TO SAVE ALL THE TIME.
I WANT TO TALK ABOUT MUSIC
AND MOVIES
AND, YES, GOULASH.
OKAY. GOT IT.
GOOD.
SO...
WELL?!
EMMA:
I WENT FOR A WALK.
SIMPSON:
IT'S 2:00 IN THE MORNING.
SPIKE:
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
(CHOKING UP)
I CAN'T SLEEP.
I HAVEN'T BEEN...
EVER SINCE THE SHOOTING.
I DIDN'T WANT
TO UPSET YOU GUYS BUT...
SINCE THEN
I WAS SO SCARED.
OH, HONEY.
DO YOU WANT TO GO
TO BED, EM?
THERE'S ALWAYS TOMORROW
TO TALK.
OKAY. YEAH.
YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO SLEEP?
DON'T WORRY, MOM.
NIGHTY-NIGHT.