(HONKING)
SPINNER:
YO, RICHARD.
HEY BUDDY.
HEY, MAN.
I SAID HI.
IT'S RUDE
NOT TO SAY HI BACK.
SERIOUSLY,
WHAT'S THAT?
I MEAN...
RICK:
HI, SPINNER.
HI.
RICK:
NEW HAIRCUT?
YES, IT IS.
NEW CHAPEAU?
OOH.
OH, MAN.
THIS IS NICE.
(WHISTLES)
OH! HEY, THIS IS NICE.
SO SOFT.
WHERE DID YOU GET IT?
I KNOW WHERE YOU
CAN FIND IT.
JIMMY:
(GROAN)
AW, MAN.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'LL HELP YOU.
OH, THERE.
JIMMY:
READY?
RICK:
AHHH!
(SPINNER & JIMMY LAUGH)
WELL, I HOPE
YOU FIND IT
ALONG WITH MAYBE
A LITTLE SNACK
OR SOMETHING.
YEAH.
SEE YOU TOMORROW,
FREAK!
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
(PAINED GROAN)
YOU MIGHT WANT TO WATCH
WHERE YOU'RE GOING, LOSER.
WHERE YOU'RE GOING, NEANDERTHAL.
WHAT DID YOU
JUST SAY?
MORNING, SIR.
I'VE GOT A HALL PASS.
I'M GOOD.
QUICK, WORLD'S THREE LONGEST
RIVERS, IN ORDER.
JIMMY:
UH, OKAY.
THE NILE, AMAZON
AND THE YANGTZE?
MOST NBA CHAMPIONSHIPS?
BOSTON CELTICS.
WHY?
OKAY. WE'LL WE GOT GEOGRAPHY
AND SPORTS COVERED.
RICK, MEET YOUR NEW TEAMMATE.
WHAT?!
HEATHER SINCLAIR CAME DOWN
WITH MONO.
HER LOSS IS JIMMY'S GAIN.
WELCOME TO "WHACK YOUR BRAIN".
THE DAY AFTER TOMORROW'S
THE OPEN HOUSE.
YOU'LL HAVE TO CLEAN.
OKAY.
WHAT ELSE?
YOU KNOW, DUST.
MAYBE VACUUM,
SWEEP THE FLOORS.
I MEAN,
"WHAT ELSE" ELSE?
I HAVE TO SELL MY HOME,
HELEN.
YOU GOT TO GIVE ME MORE TO DO
THAN JUST SPIT AND SHINE.
HELEN:
AND WE WILL SELL IT, JOSEPH.
WITH OUR ASKING PRICE,
THIS HOUSE WILL BE SNAPPED UP.
EXCUSE ME.
CRAIG...
(COUGHING)
WHY AREN'T YOU
DRESSED?
CLAMMY PALMS,
SCRATCHY THROAT...
YEAH WELL,
IF I DON'T SEE A FEVER,
YOU'RE OUT THE DOOR
IN TEN.
OKAY, NO TV,
NO PHONE.
JUST REST.
HELEN, I'M SORRY,
BUT THIS MEETING,
IT'S GONE ON LONGER
THEN I EXPECTED.
BUT WE STILL HAVE BUSINESS
TO FINISH.
JOEY:
WELL, I HAVE A BUSINESS
TO GET TO
OR I'M FINISHED.
SO PLEASE,
JUST SELL MY HOUSE.
HEY GUYS,
I MADE FLASHCARDS.
DO YOU WANT ME
TO QUIZ THEM BY CATEGORY
OR SHOULD I SHUFFLE.
I'M QUITTING.
RICK, THE FINALS
ARE TOMORROW.
WE HAVE
A NEW TEAMMATE -
JIMMY BROOKS
AKA,
MY DAILY TORMENTOR.
TOBY:
I TOLD YOU, MAN.
JUST GO TO SIMPSON.
JUST ASK HIM FOR
A RE-THINK ON HIS DECISION.
IF JIMMY'S BOOTED NOW,
HE'LL KNOW IT WAS ME.
JIMMY AND THEM?
THEY DON'T LIKE YOU
'CAUSE THEY DON'T KNOW YOU.
SO?
SO, YOU CAME BACK
TO DEGRASSI
TO SHOW YOU'VE CHANGED,
RIGHT?
SO WORK WITH JIMMY
ON THE TEAM.
SHOW HIM YOU'RE NOT THE GUY
HE THINKS YOU ARE.
THINK THEY WANT TO KNOW
WHO I AM?
THEY WANT TO TORTURE ME.
RICK, WE NEED YOU ON THE TEAM.
SO YOU NEED TO DO SOMETHING.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
MR. RADITCH, SIR.
I REQUIRE
A KIND OF FAVOUR.
IT'S CONCERNING
A MEMBER
OF THE "WHACK
YOUR BRAIN" TEAM.
MR. RADITCH:
DO I LOOK LIKE I HAVE
TIME FOR A CHAT, RICHARD?
YOUR POINT.
RICK:
UH, HE'S HARASSING ME, SIR.
HARASSING HOW?
WELL,
HE DOESN'T LIKE ME
AND HE HAS NO QUALMS
EXPRESSING IT.
SO, ARE YOU ASKING ME TO ORDER
THIS STUDENT TO LIKE YOU?
DO YOU REALLY THINK
THAT WILL RESOLVE MATTERS?
RICHARD, I'VE TOLD YOU
TIME AND TIME AGAIN,
IT TAKES TWO TO TANGO.
SIR-
MR. RADITCH:
YOU DON'T LIKE HIM
AND HE DOESN'T LIKE YOU.
SO I SUGGEST YOU TRY
HARDER TO GET ALONG.
COME BACK IF ANYTHING
SERIOUS HAPPENS.
THAT IS ALL.
SPINNER:
THIS CAR IS CURSED,
ALL RIGHT?
TOTALLY CURSED.
YOU TOO?
SOMEBODY PICKED
THE WRONG GUYS TO MESS WITH.
SOMEONE NAMED
RICK MURRAY.
YOU GUYS ARE GONNA
WANNA GET THIS OFF
YOUR CLEAR COAT
BEFORE IT RUINS IT.
WHAT?
SCREW THAT.
IT'S EVIDENCE.
I'M TELLING RADITCH.
I'M TELLING RADITCH!
YOU DON'T THINK
HE'S GONNA WANNA KNOW WHY
RICK TAGGED YOU?
JAY:
SEAN'S RIGHT.
LET'S KEEP RADITCH
OUTTA THIS.
BUDDY'S GOING DOWN.
HE'S TOAST.
ANNOUNCEMENT:
TODAY'S LUNCH SPECIAL
IS MACARONI AND CHEESE
WITH GARLIC BREAD,
AND THE SOUP
IS BEEF BARLEY.
SPINNER:
HEY, REJECT,
WHERE'S YOUR FRIEND?
TOBY:
AS IF I'M GOING
TO TELL YOU.
JAY:
HEY WIENER,
HE ASKED YOU A QUESTION.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
SMARTER THAN THIS.
MR. SIMPSON:
AH! OUR HI-TECH GENIUS
HAS ARRIVED!
AND HE'S BLEEDING.
SKATEBOARD ACCIDENT.
I'M FINE.
MR. SIMPSON:
I'LL GET YOU SOME ICE.
JIMMY:
SO GIVE IT UP, ISAACS.
WHO DID IT?
WISH YOU HIT HIM,
JIMMY?
MISS OUT ON
ALL THE FUN?
LOOK, RICK,
WHY DON'T YOU JUST BACK OFF?
I'VE BEEN SUFFERING
FOR WEEKS.
JUST A BIG JOKE
TO YOU AND YOUR FRIENDS.
WHY SHOULD I STOP IT?
TOBY DOESN'T DESERVE THIS.
NOBODY DOES.
JOEY:
CRAIG, I SAID NO TV.
HI, JOEY.
JOEY:
SYD?
CRAIG CALLED ME AT WORK.
HERE'S YOUR TEA.
HOW DO YOU FEEL
ABOUT YOUNGER MEN?
UH, YOU LOOK GOOD.
I'VE BEEN GOOD.
YOUR HOUSE, JOEY -
YOU SHOULD HAVE CALLED ME.
IT'S WHO I AM.
IT'S WHAT I DO.
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE-
SYD?
YOU SELL
DEPARTMENT STORES,
OFFICE TOWERS,
BANKS.
CRAIG TOLD ME, JOEY.
I DIDN'T KNOW THE BUSINESS
WAS DOING SO BADLY.
JOEY:
HOW BADLY DID HE MAKE IT OUT
TO GET YOU HERE?
ESPECIALLY AFTER THAT-
AFTER THAT WHOLE
VICIOUSLY DUMPING ME
FOR CAITLIN THING?
C'MON, JOEY,
WE'RE NOT EIGHTEEN.
THIS WAS A MISTAKE.
JOEY!
SHE'S NOT DESPERATE
FOR THE JOB.
LET HER HELP.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
BYE.
WHICH POEM ENDS WITH THE LINE,
"AND MILES TO GO
BEFORE I SLEEP?"
RICK:
STOPPING BY WOODS
ON A SNOWY EVENING.
ROBERT FROST.
CORRECT.
WHICH ELEMENT,
REPRESENTED BY TE,
HAS ALSO BEEN KNOWN
TO CAUSE GARLIC BREATH?
TELLURIUM.
MR. SIMPSON:
BINGO.
AND ONE LAST QUESTION
FROM THE WORLD OF SPORTS.
WHICH TEAM HAS SUFFERED
THE MOST CONSECUTIVE
SUPERBOWL LOSSES?
THE BUFFALO BILLS.
FOUR TIME LOSERS,
NO WINS.
FUTILITY PERFECTED.
RICK:
AMAZING TRIVIA SKILLS, JIM.
JIMMY:
THANKS. YOU WERE GOOD TOO.
YO! JIMMY.
HEY DOGMEAT.
YOU GOT SOMETHING
ON YOUR SHIRT.
JIMMY:
THAT'S JUST WEAK.
GROW UP.
OOOH!
RICKY FOUND A FRIEND!
JIMMY:
GIVE IT A REST.
IT'S BORING.
BAD MOVE,
FREAK.
RICK'S MOM:
ALL SET.
A YEAR FROM NOW YOU'LL BE
THE SAME SIZE AS YOUR FATHER.
RICK:
I DON'T WANT
A SALES JOB.
I NEVER WANT ANY JOB.
HE DOESN'T LIKE BEING
SENT OUT OF TOWN, RICKY.
(DOORBELL)
OH HEY, TOBY!
ARE YOU AS EXCITED
AS RICKY?
THE LIGHTS,
THE CAMERAS,
THE THRILL
OF PERFORMANCE.
RICKY TELLS ME THAT
YOU AND YOUR NEW FRIENDS-
JIMMY AND EMMA.
RICK'S MOM:
THAT YOU ALL HAVE BECOME
PRACTICALLY INSEPARABLE
AT SCHOOL!
UH, JIMMY?
RICK'S MOM:
AND TO THINK I WANTED YOU
TO TRANSFER TO ANOTHER SCHOOL.
YOU WORRY TOO MUCH,
MOTHER.
PRETTY SOON TOBY AND I'LL BE
RUNNING THAT PLACE.
UH... YEAH.
WE'RE THE COOLEST.
CRAIG, COME ON.
GET UP!
CRAIG:
I'M AS SICK AS YESTERDAY.
SCRATCH THAT -
SICKER.
I GOT TO GET THIS PLACE
READY FOR THE OPEN HOUSE,
SO THE DEALERSHIP IS GONNA
HAVE TO STAY CLOSED TODAY.
SO YOU'RE HERE
ALL DAY?
JOEY:
WELL, I MIGHT STEP OUT BRIEFLY.
AND WHEN I GET BACK
I DON'T WANT TO FIND
TESSA CAMPANELLI
SITTING ON MY FRONT DOORSTEP,
OKAY?
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE CALLED
SYDNEY.
HOW PATHETIC DID YOU
MAKE ME SOUND, HUH?
DID YOU TELL HER WE WERE BURNING
FURNITURE FOR HEAT?
SLEEPING ON SEWER GRATES?
EATING OUT OF-
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M GOING TO SCHOOL.
THAT'S HOW BADLY I DON'T
WANT TO BE AROUND YOU LATELY.
EXCUSE ME?
LOOK...
SORRY IF I'M THE ONLY ONE
THAT ACTUALLY CARES
ABOUT THIS PLACE.
JOEY, YOU'D SELL IT
FOR BEADS.
SYDNEY WON'T.
RICK:
HEY!
MY THOUGHTS
ARE ON SALE TODAY.
TWO FOR A PENNY.
YOU CAN PAY ME LATER.
OKAY.
THANK YOU FOR
TALKING TO ME.
YOU KNOW,
ABOUT JIMMY.
WHEN YOU SPEAK,
I LISTEN.
YOU'RE MY GUIDE.
WELL, I'M GLAD
THINGS WORKED OUT.
I KNEW YOU'D
MAKE FRIENDS.
HI JIMMY.
HEY, RICK.
SAY UH, NERVOUS?
AH, NO.
NOT REALLY.
YES.
YEAH, I AM A LITTLE BIT.
YEAH.
WELL, DON'T WORRY.
TOGETHER WE'LL LEAD THE TEAM
TO NEW HEIGHTS OF VICTORY.
OKAY.
RADITCH,
LINE ONE.
WANTS HIS SUIT BACK.
TAKE A MESSAGE.
FLOOR DIRECTOR:
FOUR, THREE...
HOST:
GOOD MORNING, FOLKS
AND WELCOME TO THE WORLDS
FAVORITE QUIZ SHOW.
WE ARE BACK TO ATTACK
YOUR CRANIUM AND...
ALL:
"WHACK YOUR BRAIN!"
YOU GOT YOUR BOY JOE.
WE GOT A GOOD GAME
FOR YOU TODAY.
NORTHERN HIGH
IS GETTING READY TO GO UP
AGAINST DEGRASSI CS.
BOTH THESE TEAMS
ARE READY,
LET'S NOT WAIST
ANY MORE TIME.
HANDS ON BUZZERS.
HERE WE GO...
IN WHAT CANADIAN CITY
WAS THE TELEPHONE INVENTED?
THAT'D BE BRANTFORD,
ONTARIO.
YOU'RE ON THE BOARD.
(APPLAUSE)
HOST:
CULTURE:
NAME THE SPICY SPANISH
VEGETABLE SOUP
USUALLY SERVED CHILLED?
TOBY:
UH, GAZPACHO.
HOST:
GOOD JOB.
SCIENCE:
WHAT SCIENTIFIC INSTRUMENT
CUTS VERY THIN SLICES
FOR EXAMINATION BY MICROSCOPE?
MICK:
A MICROTOME.
HOST:
YOU'RE ON THE BOARD.
GEOGRAPHY:
WHAT IS THE GEOGRAPHICAL TERM
FOR LAND BETWEEN AREAS
OF PERMANENT SNOW
AND THE TREE LINE
IN ARCTIC REGIONS?
TUNDRA?
HOST:
GOOD JOB.
SPORTS:
IN TENNIS,
WHAT TERM DESCRIBES THE BALL
TOUCHING THE NET
AND FALLING INTO
THE OPPONENTS COURT?
LET?
HOST:
GOOD JOB.
DEGRASSI HAS 30 POINTS.
GEOGRAPHY...
THE GREAT CIRCLE ROUTE.
FRANZ FERDINAND.
NAMIBIA.
THE PLEISTOCENE.
HOST:
GOOD JOB.
NORTHERN 180 POINTS.
DEGRASSI
RIGHT THERE WITH 170.
JUST A REMINDER.
IN CASE OF A TIE,
EACH TEAM WILL
SELECT ONE PLAYER
TO COMPETE IN THE FINAL
LIGHTNING ROUND.
HANDS ON BUZZERS, TEAMS.
YOUR LAST CATEGORY,
SPORTS.
NAME THE FIRST GOLFER TO WIN
THE BRITISH AND U.S. OPENS
IN THE SAME YEAR?
ANYONE?
(RICK DINGS BUZZER)
BOBBY JONES?
HOST:
TIE GAME!
(APPLAUSE AND CHEERING)
HOST:
A SHORT BREAK,
WHEN WE COME BACK -
THE FINAL LIGHTNING ROUND.
DON'T GO ANYWHERE!
YOU'RE GONNA TAKE THAT,
RIGHT?
YEAH.
SO, LET ME ASK YOU
A QUESTION?
HOW'D YOU BECOME
AN ENCYCLOPEDIA?
I READ A LOT.
I HAVE A LOT OF TIME
TO MYSELF.
I THOUGHT SPORTS
WAS YOUR TERRITORY.
YEAH. YEAH.
I HAD A LITTLE
BRAIN CRAMP.
AND ANYWAYS,
GOLF IS NOT A SPORT.
SPINNER:
HEY MAN, THAT WAS SO SWEET.
I MEAN, YOU'RE A KNOW-IT-ALL
TRIVIA MACHINE.
THIS COMPETITION
IS MONEY IN THE BANK
WITH MY BOY
RIGHT HERE.
NICE. ARE YOU DOING
THE LIGHTNING ROUND, BUDDY?
AFFIRMATIVE.
IT'S PROBABLY BETTER
HIM THAN ME, RIGHT?
WE'RE COOL,
MAN.
BETTER HIM THAN ME?
SPINNER:
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, YOU ARE SURE
ALEX CAN SET THIS UP?
JAY:
DUDE, THE BEST PART ABOUT
DATING THE STUDENT COUNCIL VP?
NOBODY ASKS QUESTIONS.
SYDNEY:
I'M SORRY I'M LATE.
NO PROBLEM.
YOU'RE HERE.
I... I REALLY
APPRECIATE THAT.
SAY SOMETHING ELSE
TO MAKE ME STAY.
I NEED HELP.
BADLY.
CRAIG WAS RIGHT,
YOU WERE RIGHT.
I SHOULD'VE COME TO YOU
WEEKS AGO.
I COULD SIT HERE ALL DAY
AND COME UP WITH WAYS
TO HATE YOU.
BUT YOUR FAMILY'S
IN TROUBLE.
BEING HERE ISN'T EASY FOR ME,
EITHER, JOEY.
I KNOW.
LOOK,
THE WAY WE FINISHED...
I'M NOT PROUD OF THAT.
MY ASSISTANT WILL BE HERE
WITHIN THE HOUR
AND PUT A SIGN UP
ON YOUR LAWN.
I'LL POP BY AFTER WORK,
SAY 5:30 P.M.?
SO, WE'RE GOING
WITH THE OPEN HOUSE?
THINK ABOUT CREATING
AN ATMOSPHERE.
START WITH SOME
MUSIC PLAYING.
JOEY:
MUSIC?
BUT NOT THAT DEMO TAPE
THAT YOU USED TO PLAY ME
FROM YOUR BAND.
YOUR BAND-
ZIT REMEDY.
SYDNEY:
NO "ZITS".
NO "REMEDIES".
BUT A PIE - SOMETHING
BAKING IN THE OVEN?
THAT WOULD BE NICE.
OKAY.
HOST:
THE DEEPEST PLACE ON EARTH?
MICK:
THE MARIANA TRENCH.
HOST:
TIME!
NORTHERN WITH 40 POINTS.
GOOD JOB.
DEGRASSI? WHO'S UP?
THIS IS ALL FOR YOU.
HOST:
THERE'S THE SCORE
YOU HAVE TO BEAT.
THIRTY SECONDS
ON THE CLOCK.
TIME BEGINS... NOW!
THE CONFEDERATION BRIDGE
LINKS PRINCE EDWARD ISLAND
WITH WHAT CANADIAN PROVINCE?
NEW BRUNSWICK.
A MINIMUM
OF HOW MANY GAMES
DOES IT TAKE TO WIN
A SET IN TENNIS?
SEVEN.
HOST:
WHAT WAS THE ORIGINAL HOME
VIDEO GAME CONSOLE,
INTRODUCED IN 1972?
MAGNAVOX ODYSSEY.
HOST:
SAURON REIGNS
OVER WHAT TERRITORY?
MORDOR.
WHO SPENT
27 YEARS IN PRISON
BEFORE BEING ELECTED
PRESIDENT OF SOUTH AFRICA?
NELSON MANDELA.
HOST:
IN WHAT ROBERT BOLT PLAY
DOES SIR THOMAS MORE
FACE A MORAL DILEMMA?
"A MAN FOR
ALL SEASONS."
TIME!
THAT'S IT!
50 POINTS!
DEGRASSI WINS!
(CHEERING & APPLAUSE)
(LAUGHTER)
EMMA:
RICK!
RICK, WHAT HAPPENED...
IT ONLY MAKES
THE PEOPLE WHO DID IT
LOOK TOTALLY JUVENILE.
THEY RUINED IT,
EMMA.
THEY'RE LIFE-RUINERS.
EVERYONE LAUGHING.
BUT NOBODY IS EVER
GONNA FORGET WHO WON.
WHO IS THE SMARTEST GUY
IN THE SCHOOL -
IN THE WHOLE CITY?
RICK?!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
LET GO!
I THOUGHT YOU LOVED ME.
I FELT SORRY FOR YOU.
I PITIED YOU.
GET A CLUE.
(DOORBELL)
AROUND THE WORLD
IN JUST OVER 180 DAYS...
CAITLIN!
I'M ON AN EMERGENCY
HIATUS FROM THE AIDS PIECE.
TURMOIL IN HAITI.
SO I TOOK
THE FIRST FLIGHT HOME.
WHY IS SYDNEY'S NAME
ON YOUR LAWN?
MOTHER?
FATHER?