♪♪♪
(SIGHS) 67 PATHETIC CENTS.
HEY, STOP. STOP.
YOU MAY BE POOR
BUT AT LEAST
YOU'RE PRETTY.
PLEASE JUST TELL ME
I'VE MADE A DENT
IN WHAT I OWE YOU.
A DING?
OOH! NEW SCHEDULE.
PAIGE.
CRAP.
I WORK SATURDAY?
PAIGE:
UM, I DON'T.
FRIDAY OR SUNDAY EITHER.
HELLO, DO I EVER WORK?
SORRY, PAIGE.
BUT YOU'RE FIRED.
(GASPS)
(SIGHS)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
HEY.
NICE SUNBURN.
LOOKS PRETTY OUCH.
YEAH, IT IS OUCH.
UM, WHERE'S YOURS?
IT'S CALLED SUN BLOCK
WITH A GREASE-FREE
MOISTURIZER TO FOLLOW.
OH, OKAY.
PAIGE USES MOISTURIZER
BUT HER'S IS LAVENDER.
NOT THAT I'M CLOSE ENOUGH
TO KNOW THAT YOURS ISN'T...
LAVENDER.
HEY IDIOT, NICE SUNBURN.
LIBRARY'S OUT IN THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE SCHOOL.
BYE.
SPINNER:
MAN, AM I THE ONLY ONE WHO GOT
BURNED AT THIS CAR WASH?
ARE YOU AND PAIGE
STILL TIGHT?
YEAH. YOUR POINT?
YOU AND MANNY HAVE BEEN TALKING
A LOT LATELY.
AGAIN, YOUR POINT?
HEY, LOOK,
I'M JUST WARNING YOU.
HEY, IT'S NONE
OF YOUR BUSINESS.
AND NEITHER'S MANNY.
NOT THIS YEAR.
SIMPSON:
AH WELCOME TO THE TRYOUTS
FOR DEGRASSI'S OFFICIAL
TRIVIA TEAM.
NOW I WANT YOU
TO ALL PARTNER OFF
AND WE'RE GONNA START
WITH A LITTLE WARM-UP.
PARTNERS, EMMA?
SORRY. I'M WITH HEATHER.
RICK:
HEARTBREAKING.
I MYSELF HAVE MISS NELSON
PEGGED AT NUMBER THREE.
I'VE GOT THIS LIST.
IT'S NOT SOME KIND
OF CRASS RATING SYSTEM.
IT'S A RANKING SYSTEM.
TOBY:
YOU'RE SICK.
RICK:
I'M ORGANIZED.
WRITING OUT GOALS
HELPS REALIZE THEM.
SIMPSON:
WHAT'S THE WORLD'S
LARGEST GLACIER?
UH, THE LAMBERT GLACIER?
HMM, HE'S CORRECT.
IT'S IN ANTARCTICA.
WELL I THINK YOU TWO
MIGHT MAKE A GOOD TEAM.
HAZEL:
I LOVE SOUP.
PAIGE:
OKAY, THAT WAS RANDOM.
ASHLEY:
HEY, SOUP'S GOOD.
(GIGGLES)
PAIGE:
HEY!
OH! WHOA!
PAIGE!
(LAUGHTER)
SPINNER:
"CRASH" MICHALCHUK,
WORLD CHAMPION DESTROYER!
TWO DOWN
WITH ONE TRAY!
JIMMY:
HAZEL, I'M GOING TO GET YOU
SOME NAPKINS.
SUNSTROKE GOT YOU
TOO TIRED TO MOVE?
HEY! THAT'S MY LUNCH!
(GRUNTS)
OH MORE SALT NEXT TIME.
SPINNER.
SPIN ENDURED "THE DOT"
FOR A YEAR
FOR A CAR I TOTALED
IN TWO MINUTES.
HE JOKE AND SNACK.
HE'S ALLOWED.
(KISS)
YOUR APPLICATION SAYS
YOU WORKED AT "THE DOT",
JUST NOT FOR HOW LONG.
IT'S THE OLD
"YOU CAN'T GET A JOB
WITHOUT EXPERIENCE".
"AND YOU CAN'T GET
EXPERIENCE WITHOUT A JOB."
I'M A TERRIBLE WAITRESS.
MORE THAN ONE TABLE
AND MY MIND GOES...
WHICH IS WHY THIS JOB
IS PERFECT.
ONE CUSTOMER AT A TIME.
GET THEM THEIR DRINKS,
THEIR POPCORN AND NEXT!
HOW ARE YOU AT TEAMWORK
THOUGH?
OH, I'M TEAM.
I CHEER FOR TEAM.
GO TEAM.
UH, YOU LOOK PRETTY TODAY,
EMMA.
THANKS, TOBY.
(MOCKING)
OKAY, I MADE A LIST
AND GEE, GUESS WHAT?
MY GOALS - NOT REALIZED.
RELINQUISH THE LIST,
TOBY.
IT'S IN MY HEAD.
I TOLD YOU MINE.
FINE THERE'S EMMA.
NOT ENTIRELY SURPRISING.
UH, ELLIE NASH?
OOH, GREAT ALTERNATIVE.
HAZEL.
AH, COUPLE OF VERY FINE
ATTRIBUTES ON THAT ONE.
HMM, THERE'S A SET OF ROLE
PLAYING DICE
I'VE HAD MY EYE ON
FOR OH SO LONG.
WHAT WE NEED IS COURAGE.
AND ALL I'M PROPOSING
IS A CHALLENGE.
WHAT?
WHAT KIND OF CHALLENGE?
RICK:
LOSER BUYS THE DICE,
WINNER GETS 'EM.
WHOEVER CAN MANAGE A KISS
FROM ANY GIRL ON THAT LIST
BEFORE LAST BELL.
NARROW IT DOWN TO EMMA
AND WE'RE ON.
PAIGE:
I CAN'T JUST GO IN THERE
AND TALK TO HER.
ALEX HATES ME.
I HATE ALEX.
SPINNER:
SO PERFECT CHANCE
TO MAKE A NEW FRIEND.
SPIN, PLEASE.
WE ARE TALKING
MY PRIDE HERE.
HOW MUCH IS IT WORTH?
HOW MUCH?
UM, ABOUT $1200 AND UH...
PAIGE:
(DEFEATED SIGH)
ALEX.
UM, CAN WE TALK A SEC?
YOU'RE NOT CALLING ME
"DOG-FACE"?
SIMPSON:
OKAY, INTERNET LOVERS,
TWO MINUTES TO HOMEROOM,
SO PLEASE LOG OFF.
JUST ONE SECOND,
PLEASE.
WE'VE HAD OUR ISSUES,
I KNOW,
BUT HON, YOU SEE HOW MUCH
I DO AROUND HERE.
THAT I'M EMPLOYEE MATERIAL.
I WOULDN'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I PUT IN A PERFECTLY BAD WORD
FOR YOU.
(DEPRESSED SIGH)
UH, STANDING UP FOR
RICK LIKE YOU DID,
I'VE DECIDED TO
FOLLOW YOUR LEAD.
WHAT DO YOU WANT,
TOBY?
WE'VE GOT THIS GAME
GOING.
IT'S KIND OF
SCAVENGER HUNT-ISH.
(WHISPERS)
IF I GET A KISS I WIN.
(KISS)
HA! I WIN WHICH MEANS YOU LOSE.
YOU ARE A LOSER!
NICE WAY TO FOLLOW
MY LEAD, TOBY.
JUST SO YOU'RE NOT LONELY...
(KISS)
(LAUGHS) IT'S A TIE 'CAUSE
THE GAME WAS SUPPOSED TO END
IN THREE, TWO, ONE...
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
WHICH MEANS THAT TOMORROW
TO BREAK THE TIE
WE NEED A NEW GAME.
MS HATZILAKOS:
ALL RIGHT CLASS,
PUT AWAY THE MICROSCOPES,
CLEAN UP YOUR WORK AREAS
AND I WILL SEE YOU
NEXT CLASS.
PAIGE:
MY LAST HOPE WAS A MOVIE
THEATER CONCESSION...
WITH ALEX IN A MALL.
YOU'RE SO BETTER
THAN THAT.
TELL THAT TO THE
"MOUND O' DEBT"
I OWE SPINNER.
YOU'RE ALSO BETTER
THAN HIM.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
I MISS THE OLD YOU
WITH THE OLD SPINNER
TRAILING BEHIND
OBEDIENT AND
SLIGHTLY AFRAID.
THAT WAS BEFORE
I SMASHED HIS CAR.
INTO THE CAR OF THE FREAK
WHO RAPED YOU!
GOOD BOYFRIENDS
DON'T HOLD YOU
TO THINGS LIKE THAT.
GOOD BOYFRIENDS ALSO
DON'T DO THIS.
PAIGE:
IS THAT...
SPINNER AND MANNY
ARE FRIENDS.
IT'S NOTHING.
UM, RULE IS YOU GET FIRED,
YOU DON'T POP BY.
ANOTHER RULE?
LOVE CLUTCHES ARE BANNED
WITH GIRLS WHO AREN'T ME.
IT'S A HUG.
NEARNESS COMES
IN VARYING DEGREES.
COME HERE.
COME ON.
THIS, THIS IS A HUG.
OH, SUNBURN,
PAIGE.
NOW THIS!
PAIGE!
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS TELL ME
THAT IT WAS NOTHING, BEE-BEE.
SPINNER.
I HAVE TO GET
BACK TO WORK.
PAIGE:
DID YOU HEAR ABOUT THOSE TWO?
HAZEL:
TOTALLY SHACKING UP?
I KNOW.
PAIGE:
HARD TO BELIEVE ELLIE
IS DEFEATING ME AND SPIN
IN THE "DATING OLYMPICS".
HAZEL:
AND BY MORE THAN A NOSE.
PAIGE:
I KNOW, BY A LOT.
DENY IT, CONFIRM IT.
JUST DON'T AVOID ME ALL DAY.
JAY:
SLAM.
RICK:
WHAT?
(CRASH)
I SAID SLAM.
NOW PAY ATTENTION
NEXT TIME.
TOBY:
YOU OKAY?
RICK:
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
WHY WOULDN'T I BE?
SO YESTERDAY'S CHALLENGE
WAS FAR TOO EASY.
WE'RE GOING TO,
YOU KNOW,
GO FOR QUANTITY
NOT QUALITY TODAY.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, SO NEW DAY,
NEW CHALLENGE.
WHOEVER GETS THE MOST GIRLS
TO KISS HIM
BEFORE THE END
OF THE DAY WINS.
LOSER BUYS THE DICE.
I'VE MADE UP SOME CHARTS
AND STUFF.
YOU KNOW,
NAME, AGE, LOCATION.
TOBY:
YOU SURE THAT'S A GOOD IDEA?
RICK:
YEAH. ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE NOT A BIG WUSS?
TOBY:
OKAY BUT YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO BE GOOD.
(BANG)
OW. OOH. OW.
MANNY:
AH TOBY, WHAT'S WRONG?
OH I BANGED MY ARM.
IT HURTS.
AW POOR BABY.
IS THERE ANYTHING
THAT I CAN DO TO HELP?
(KISS)
PAIGE:
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT!
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR,
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT.
HEY MANNY, LET'S TRY LISTENING
TO THE BEAT THIS TIME.
LET'S DO IT AGAIN.
FIVE, SIX,
SEVEN, EIGHT.
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR,
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, JUST WORK
ON TECHNIQUE FOR A FEW.
CAN WE TALK?
YOU MEAN INSTEAD
OF IGNORING ME?
OKAY, I ADMIT IT.
I HAD SOME
GUILTY THOUGHTS.
YOU HAVE THOUGHTS?
JUST LIKE YOU DID
LAST YEAR
WITH THAT STUPID
DRIVER'S ED GUY.
FALCONE WASN'T ALL OVER ME
HALF NAKED AT A CAR WASH.
ANYWAY WHAT I CAME HERE
TO TELL YOU IS THAT...
IN THE END...
ALL MY THOUGHTS
COME BACK TO YOU.
FLOWERS ARE NICE AND...
ESPECIALLY IF THEY'RE
NOT CARNATIONS.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
OH.
I DON'T KNOW
WHO THIS IS.
HELLO?
HI.
MEERI.
YEAH, I'M STILL INTO THE JOB.
(EXCITED GIGGLE)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
RICK:
SO ONE, YOU KNOW,
I THINK I'M DECENT LOOKING.
UM, TWO, I'LL GIVE YOU
FIVE BUCKS OR SOME-
♪ Look at all the pretty people
surrounding you. ♪
♪ They're stuck like glue
to you. ♪
♪ And look at all
the pretty faces. ♪
♪ You only think
can take you places. ♪
♪ When will you realize ♪
♪ They pulled the wool
over your eyes? ♪
It's hard to see
tangled in your misery.
DARCY:
THIS FRIEND OF YOURS
HE'S REALLY LOSING THAT BAD?
I THOUGHT HE WAS
GOING TO CRY.
OH, HERE HE COMES.
DARCY:
POOR GUY.
TOBY:
YEAH, YEAH, POOR GUY.
DARCY:
HE'S THE ONE THEY KEEP
PUSHING INTO LOCKERS.
WHY DOES EVERYONE AROUND HERE
HATE HIM SO MUCH?
SO WILL FIVE BUCKS
CHANGE YOUR MIND?
YEAH.
WHERE'D YOU GET
YOUR GLASSES?
UM, THE OPTOMETRIST?
I LIKE 'EM.
UM, MY FRIEND AND ME
WE HAVE THIS GAME GOING.
ANYTHING I CAN DO
TO HELP YOU WIN?
A KISS?
IT DOESN'T HAVE TO BE LIPS.
IT DOESN'T EVEN HAVE
TO BE IN THE-
(KISS)
HAZEL:
SO YOU'RE A COUPLE AGAIN.
UH, WE NEVER STOPPED.
(SIGHS)
THE HAZEL HEAD SHAKE.
DO NOT MAKE ME SUFFER.
YOU LET HIM TREAT
YOU LIKE GARBAGE,
HE'LL KEEP DOING IT.
THANK YOU, OPRAH,
DR. PHIL
AND EVERYONE ELSE
IN THE WORLD.
PAIGE.
JUST BACK OFF, OKAY?
UNLESS YOU'D LIKE ME
TO GIVE YOU PLAY-BY-PLAYS
ON YOUR RELATIONSHIP
WITH JIMMY.
I'M GONNA BE LATE FOR WORK.
DRINKS NEED ICE.
SORRY.
ALEX:
AND WHILE IT'S POURING...
UH POPCORN.
RIGHT. SORRY.
OH.
ALEX:
I'LL WIPE IT UP.
AND DON'T SAY SORRY.
ENJOY YOUR SHOW.
HI, CAN I INTEREST YOU IN-
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WELL, I'M HERE TO SUPPORT YOU
IN YOUR FIRST SHIFT
WEARING MAN-MADE FIBERS
AND I WANT A LARGE POPCORN.
ONLY COULD YOU STOP HALFWAY
FOR BUTTER?
LITTLE MORE.
JUST A BIT MORE.
ANY MORE AND YOU'LL GET GREASE
STAINS ON YOUR PANTS, HONEYBEE.
OKAY, SO A QUARTER MORE POPCORN.
AND A SMIDGEN MORE BUTTER.
GOOD GIRL.
THAT'S NICE.
NO.
IT'S GOOD TRAINING.
PAIGE:
OH, WANNA CHECK TO SEE
IF I CLEANED
THE NACHO-SLUDGE-THINGY RIGHT?
ALEX:
THE FACT THAT YOU, PAIGE,
DID IT AT ALL IS AMAZING.
NO WORSE THAN CLEARING
MY BROTHER'S HAIR
OUT OF THE BATHTUB.
THANKS.
I THOUGHT WE HIRED YOU
NOT YOUR BOYFRIEND.
REAL SWEET GUY.
THE JERK YOU JUST
EXPERIENCED
IS USUALLY A LITTLE
LESS OF A JERK.
NOT THAT I'D EVER ADMIT THIS
BUT I USED TO BE SCARED OF YOU.
PLEASE. I'M SO NOT SCARY.
ALEX:
NO.
YOU'RE A COWARD
AND A SUCK.
'CAUSE IF MY BOYFRIEND
SHOWED UP HERE
AND TREATED ME THAT WAY,
I'D BE SHOPPING
FOR A NEW BOYFRIEND.
CRAIG:
THAT MOVIE WAS SURREAL.
MARCO:
IT WASN'T SURREAL.
IF IT WERE REALLY SURREAL
KOVACK WOULD BE PLAYED BY,
LIKE, A GOAT.
JIMMY:
OKAY, TELL ME AGAIN,
WHY DID KOVACK KILL THAT GUY?
CRAIG:
WHY DO YOU THINK?
JEALOUSY.
SPINNER:
I KNEW KOVACK REMINDED ME
OF SOMEONE.
WHAT'S THAT?
NOTHING MAN.
JUST A JOKE. RELAX.
(SIGHS)
SPIN, COME ON,
LEAVE PAIGE ALONE.
SHE'S SO SUFFERED ENOUGH.
SO HOW'S THE REST OF YOUR SHIFT
GOING, MY BOOTIE-BLOSSOM?
YOU REALLY WANNA HELP?
GIVE THE GIRL WHO LOST
HER LICENSE A RIDE HOME.
YOU DON'T GET OFF WORK
FOR ANOTHER TWO HOURS.
AND THERE'S SO MUCH
TO BE JEALOUS ABOUT, SPIN.
I MEAN YOUR CHARM,
YOUR WAY WITH WOMEN.
YOU'RE CRAZY, MAN.
OOH.
NICE COMEBACK, GENIUS.
(SLAP)
THAT ONE BETTER FOR YOU?
HEY, BAG OF GROSSNESS
COMING THROUGH.
CRAIG:
YOU KNOW, YOU WERE ALWAYS
JEALOUS OF MANNY AND ME.
YEAH? WELL NOW YOU'RE
CROWD:
LET'S GO! LET'S GO!
HERE WE GO!
FIGHT! YEAH, YEAH, YEAH!
PAIGE:
YOU GUYS, STOP IT!
GET OFF OF EACH OTHER!
I WORK HERE!
GO!
I'VE CALLED SECURITY!
ARE YOU GONNA WAIT FOR THEM
TO ARRIVE OR...
I TOLD THEM TO LEAVE.
HAND IN YOUR UNIFORM.
NO, MEERI.
YOU'RE FIRED.
(DEJECTED SIGH)
SO THAT'S MY 11 KISSES
TO YOUR ONE?
YOU KNOW,
I ATTRIBUTE MY SUCCESS
TO MY SILKY CHEEK.
YOU ARE THE VICTOR.
I ACCEPT THAT.
BUT NONE OF YOUR KISSES
WERE EVEN CLOSE
TO THE ONE I GOT.
AND YOU STILL WON'T
TELL ME WHO.
AH LET'S JUST SAY
IN THIS CASE
IT'S ABOUT QUALITY
AND NOT QUANTITY.
THIS HAS GIVEN ME ALL
THE CONFIDENCE I NEED.
TO WHAT?
OH, SURVIVAL INSTINCT
HAS THE OLDEST
AND STRONGEST MEMBER
OF THE PACK
PROTECTING THE YOUNG
AND THE WEAK.
I'M WEAK.
I'M PRACTICALLY FEEBLE.
YEAH, WELL WORD'S OUT
THAT A NINER'S
GETTING STALKED
BY A CERTAIN...
PSYCHO.
TOBY:
LOOK RICK'S MY FRIEND.
I WAS-
I WAS JUST TRYING TO SAVE HIM
FROM HUMILIATION.
JAY:
YEAH.
TOBY:
JAY! COME ON, MAN!
LET ME OUT!
TOO BAD HE'S NOT HERE
TO SAVE YOU NOW.
TOBY:
COME ON, GET OUT!
COME ON!
AND I WAS JUST THINKING,
"GEE, I HOPE ALEX
COMES BY TO GLOAT."
YOU HAVE A SHIFT TOMORROW.
THE NEW SCAMPI MOVIE'S OUT
SO WE'LL HAVE A TON
OF OVER-SUGARED TODDLERS.
TOU'RE NOT FUNNY
AND I'M FIRED.
IT WASN'T YOUR FAULT.
I TALKED TO MEERI FOR YOU
SO BE THERE.
(SIGHS)
UM...
I'M SORRY, OKAY?
FOR GETTING ME CANNED
ON MY VERY FIRST SHIFT?
NO PROBLEM.
SPINNER:
WAIT, YOU GOT FIRED?
PAIGE:
DON'T WORRY,
YOUR PAYCHECK'S SAFE.
SPINNER:
THAT'S NOT ALL I CARE ABOUT.
RIGHT.
THERE'S ALWAYS MANNY.
SO THAT'S IT, HUH?
GOTTA MAKE ME
THE BAD GUY HERE.
PUT ME BACK IN MY PLACE?
IF ANYONE HAS BEEN
PUT IN HER PLACE LATELY,
IT'S ME.
LISTEN, I'M SORRY ABOUT
LAST NIGHT.
SPINNER, DON'T.
WHY ARE YOU SO HUNG UP ON THIS?
BECAUSE LAST NIGHT
YOU WEREN'T FIGHTING OVER ME.
LOOK...
WE'LL FIGURE OUT SOME KIND OF
PAYMENT SCHEDULE OR SOMETHING.
I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF THIS.
PAIGE!
SPIN?
I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF YOU.