(CRYING)
EMMA:
THEY CAN'T AIR THE QUIZ SHOW,
TOBY.
TOBY:
YES THEY CAN.
THEY JUST CUT BEFORE
THE PAINT POURS ON RICK.
JT:
WHICH IS OFFICIALLY MY NEW
FAVOURITE MENTAL IMAGE.
TOBY:
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU WOULDN'T THINK
IT WAS SO FUNNY
IF IT HAPPENED TO YOU.
DANNY:
(CHUCKLES) I WOULD.
AND SPEAKING
OF HYSTERICAL IMAGES...
TOBY:
WHAT'S RICK DOING BACK
AT SCHOOL?
WE SHOULD GO TALK TO HIM.
EMMA:
GO RIGHT AHEAD.
TOBY:
RICK.
RICK!
LOOK, RADITCH
IS GOING SUPERNOVA.
HE'S GONNA FIND OUT
WHO DID IT.
AND WHAT?
GIVE THEM DETENTION?
I'M JUST SAYING,
I'M SURE
HE'D BE COOL
IF YOU SKIPPED
THE REST OF THE DAY.
TOBY,
THIS IS THE ONE TIME
I ACTUALLY WANT
TO BE AT SCHOOL.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
IN TWENTY-FIVE YEARS
AS AN EDUCATOR,
I HAVE NEVER,
NEVER BEEN SO EMBARRASSED
TO BE ASSOCIATED
WITH THIS SCHOOL.
WHOMEVER WAS RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE INCIDENT THIS MORNING,
SHOULD BE ASHAMED
OF THEMSELVES.
AND LET ME ASSURE YOU
THAT THE PERPETRATOR
OR PERPETRATORS
RESPONSIBLE FOR THIS
WILL BE FOUND OUT
AND PUNISHED SEVERELY.
IF ANYONE HAS ANY INFORMATION,
PLEASE SPEAK TO ME IMMEDIATELY.
I ASSURE YOUR CONFIDENTIALITY.
THANK YOU.
SO, BACK TO 1984.
LET'S DISCUSS BIG BROTHER...
SO, HOW'S BIG
YELLOW LOSER?
THAT'S REALLY NICE,
JT.
I HOPE HE JUST GETS
THE HINT AND LEAVES.
AND YOU'LL HAVE TO FIND
A NEW GAMER-GEEK FRIEND.
AND THEN WHEN THE FEATHERS
CAME DOWN...
OH... (KISS)
LOOK, CUT THE GUY
SOME SLACK, SPIN.
HE'S NOT THAT BAD.
YEAH, OKAY.
OH, CHICKEN BOY.
I LOVE YOUR
WEALTH OF KNOWLEDGE
AND I, I LOVE YOU.
I'M GLAD YOU THINK
THIS IS FUNNY.
DID YOU SEE THE GUYS FACE?
DEFINITION OF FUNNY.
WHAT KIND OF PERSON
DOES THAT?
ONE: A GENIUS.
AND TWO:
IF YOU RAT ON ME-
WHAT?
NO, REALLY?
WHAT'RE YOU GONNA DO?
YEAH, THAT'S
WHAT I THOUGHT.
LOOK,
SAVE THE BULLY CRAP
FOR SOMEONE WHO
WON'T FIGHT BACK.
AND YOU BETTER DO SOMETHING
ABOUT IT NOW!
BEFORE I DO.
SPINNER:
WHAT?!
(PAINED GROANS)
MR. ARMSTRONG:
HEY! HEY! HEY!
SAVE IT FOR THE GAME,
GUYS.
CAITLIN:
BUT THIS IS YOUR HOME.
I MEAN, WHAT ABOUT CRAIG
AND ANGELA?
CRAIG, AND ANGELA AND I
CAN LIVE IN A SMALLER PLACE.
IT'S EITHER THAT
OR THE DEALERSHIP.
YEAH, BUT-
JOEY:
YEAH, BUT...
YOU KNOW,
IF THERE WAS A WAY
THAT I COULD KEEP BOTH,
BELIEVE ME,
I'D BE ALL FOR IT.
I GOT TO HEAD BACK
TO THE DEALERSHIP.
BUT WE'RE ON FOR COFFEE
LATER, RIGHT?
YEAH.
JOEY:
MAKE YOURSELF AT HOME.
WHILE I STILL HAVE ONE.
(LAUGHTER)
LOOK, I KNOW WE'RE
NOT EXACTLY BEST FRIENDS.
BUT I WANTED TO SAY THAT
I THOUGHT THE WHOLE PAINT
AND FEATHERS JOB WAS SICKENING.
IT WAS REALLY CHILDISH.
I'M SORRY...
FOR HURTING TERRI.
(SIGHS)
CAITLIN:
KNOCK KNOCK.
CAITLIN.
YOU'RE... HERE.
I GOT JUST BACK
THIS MORNING...
TO FIND JOEY'S HOUSE
FOR SALE
AND YOUR NAME ON THE SIGN.
LOOK, BEFORE YOU
SAY ANYTHING,
I'M JUST HELPING JOE
OUT AS A FAVOR.
NO STRINGS ATTACHED.
SO YOU DON'T NEED
TO WORRY ABOUT US.
HOW MUCH IS HE ASKING?
FOUR HUNDRED.
WHY?
HOW DOES
THREE FIFTY SOUND?
SOUNDS LIKE FIFTY THOUSAND
LESS THAN THE HOUSE IS WORTH.
ALL RIGHT,
THREE SEVENTY-FIVE.
DOES JOE KNOW ABOUT THIS?
CAITLIN:
NOT YET.
AND UNTIL IT'S A DONE DEAL,
I PREFER HE NOT.
SO... IF HE ASKS,
JUST TELL HIM ITS
AN ANONYMOUS OFFER.
SYDNEY, IT'S BEEN AN UNEXPECTED
PLEASURE.
SPINNER:
HEY, JAY, LISTEN.
RADITCH KNOWS,
MAN.
ABOUT JIMMY?
YEAH. I'M SURPRISED NOBODY'S
FIGURED IT OUT YET.
DUDE!
JIMMY SET THE WHOLE
THING UP PERFECTLY.
THE WAY HE GOT THOSE EASY
SPORTS QUESTIONS WRONG?
YEAH, AND MADE SURE
PSYCHO-BOY
WAS ALONE
IN THE FINAL ROUND.
NEVER WOULD
HAVE HAPPENED
WITHOUT A MAN
ON THE INSIDE?
HOW ARE YOU
HOLDING UP?
GOOD.
THAT'S GOOD.
KIND OF SURPRISED TO SEE YOU
HERE THIS AFTERNOON.
YEAH.
I BET YOU ARE.
JIMMY:
LOOK, I'M REALLY SORRY ABOUT
EVERYTHING, OKAY?
AND IF THOSE GUYS
GIVE YOU ANY MORE PROBLEMS,
I GOT YOUR BACK.
LIKE YOU STABBED ME
IN THE BACK.
WHAT?
YOU SET
THE WHOLE THING UP.
JIMMY:
RICK, COME ON.
I DEFENDED YOU!
IS THAT REAL?
THE WHOLE TIME
YOU PRETENDED TO BE
MY FRIEND.
YOU MADE ME DO THIS!
(GUNSHOT)
AHHH!
J-J-JIMMY!
HI EMMA.
SORRY I KISSED YOU.
SEAN:
HE GOT A GUN.
OKAY. LET'S GO.
DON'T TURN AWAY FROM ME!
I'M GLAD I FOUND YOU,
EMMA.
YOU MADE MY LIST.
TOBY:
RICK, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU FLIRTED WITH ME.
I THOUGHT YOU LIKED ME,
BUT THAT WAS SOMETHING ELSE.
SEAN:
JUST PUT THE GUN DOWN, OKAY.
ANYTHING ELSE IS JUST GOING
TO MAKE YOUR LIFE WORSE.
IT CAN'T GET ANY WORSE.
SEAN:
BELIEVE ME, IT CAN.
I KNOW.
WE'LL FIGURE IT ALL OUT, OKAY?
WE'LL FIGURE THIS ALL OUT.
IT'S TOO LATE.
NO.
I ALREADY SHOT SOMEONE.
(STRUGGLING GRUNTS)
STOP!
(GUNSHOT)
(FRIGHTENED SOB)
(SIRENS)
MR. RADITCH:
AGAIN, REMAIN IN YOUR
CLASSROOMS
UNTIL FURTHER NOTICE.
ABSOLUTELY NO ONE IS TO LEAVE,
ACCORDING TO LOCK-DOWN
PROTOCOL.
AND PLEASE REMAIN CALM.
I GOT A PHONE CALL
FROM THE POLICE.
KATE KERWIN.
I HAVE
A KATE KERWIN HERE.
MY STEPSON
TOBY IS-
OVER RADIO:
SHE'S CLEAR.
JIMMY?
JOEY:
YOU ARE NOT GOING
TO BELIEVE THIS.
BUT THERE'S ALREADY
AN OFFER ON THE HOUSE.
ALREADY?
THAT'S GREAT!
SYDNEY HAS
REALLY COME THROUGH.
AND IT'S TEN PERCENT
ABOVE MARKET VALUE.
TEN PERCENT?
WELL, GO SYDNEY.
I AM BACK IN BUSINESS
AND WITH THE EXTRA MONEY...
NAME A PART OF TORONTO
YOU'VE ALWAYS
WANTED TO LIVE IN.
JOEY.
JOEY:
DANFORTH? BEACHES?
OH WAIT.
YOU JUST BOUGHT A HOUSE
IN RIVERDALE.
I'M MAY NOT BE THE CRAFTIEST
GUY ON THE CORNER,
BUT WHEN MY HOUSE SELLS
IN LESS THEN A DAY
ON THE MARKET?
HOW CAN I LET YOU
LOSE IT?
YOU LOVE THAT HOUSE.
YEAH, I DO.
IT'S GREAT.
ENJOY IT.
CAITLIN:
JOEY... (CELL PHONE RINGS)
CAN'T YOU PUT YOUR MALE PRIDE
ASIDE FOR ONE SECOND?
THIS IS ABOUT ME
RAISING MY OWN FAMILY
AND RUNNING MY OWN BUSINESS.
CAITLIN RYAN.
OH MY GOD.
I'M ON MY WAY.
WE HAVE TO GET
TO DEGRASSI, NOW!
DETECTIVE:
TOBY, WHY DO YOU THINK
HE DID THIS?
TOBY:
I'M SUPPOSED TO KNOW?
LOOK, THE GUY IS A PSYCHO,
OKAY?
HE'S A TOTAL PSYCHO.
WAS HE BULLIED
OR TEASED?
TOBY:
ALWAYS.
EVERY DAY.
CONSTANTLY.
AND WHAT DID YOUR FRIEND DO
WHEN SOMEONE-
TOBY:
LOOK, HE'S NOT MY FRIEND!
HE'S A PSYCHO.
AND HE'S NOT MY FRIEND.
TOBY.
DETECTIVE:
I'LL GIVE YOU SOME TIME.
I'LL BE BACK
IN A FEW MINUTES.
MR. SIMPSON:
HE NEEDED HELP, EMMA.
HE POINTED THE GUN
RIGHT AT ME.
OH, HONEY.
MR. RADITCH:
ARCHIE?
NO. I AM BUSY HERE,
IF YOU HADN'T NOTICED.
MR. RADITCH:
I'M SORRY.
THEY WANT TO KNOW IF YOU CAN
GET INTO RICK'S EMAIL
TO LOOK FOR SIGNS...
WARNING SIGNS.
OF COURSE.
NOW THE GROUNDBREAKING
20/20 HINDSIGHT POLICY
KICKS INTO GEAR.
I HAVE 700 STUDENTS
AND A TEACHING STAFF
THAT I AM RESPONSIBLE
FOR EVERY DAY.
DON'T GET ON MY CASE
BECAUSE ONE KID OVERREACTED
TO SOME SPILLED PAINT.
YEAH. ONE KID WHO YOU'VE
PERSONALLY SPOKEN TO TWICE
IN THE LAST TWO DAYS.
BUT DID YOU LISTEN?
OF COURSE I DID.
I BET YOU CAN'T REMEMBER
A WORD HE SAID.
THIS TRAGEDY, DAN,
IT COULD'VE BEEN PREVENTED
IF YOU HADN'T-
ARCHIE!
CAN YOU TWO
DO THIS LATER?
EMMA, THEY'RE GONNA WANT
TO SPEAK TO ALL THE WITNESSES.
I'M SORRY.
CAITLIN:
CAITLIN RYAN, CQJH.
CAN YOU TELL US ANYTHING?
WE HAD A FIREARM
SITUATION.
AT LEAST TWO SHOTS
HAVE BEEN FIRED.
THERE IS GUNSHOTS
IN THERE?
MY KID'S IN THERE!
CAN I PLEASE JUST
MAKE SURE HE'S OKAY.
SORRY, SIR.
SCHOOL'S IN LOCK-DOWN.
PAIGE:
OKAY, I HATE NOT KNOWING
WHAT'S GOING ON.
HAZEL:
I KNOW, IT'S BEEN,
LIKE, FOREVER.
I NEED TO GO PEE.
ASHLEY:
MAYBE IT'S AN ALARM?
HAZEL:
BOMB SCARE?
NINER MIDTERM PHOBIA
STRIKES AGAIN.
GUYS...
MY MOM HEARD
THERE WAS A SHOOTING.
(KNOCKING)
HAZEL, COULD I SEE YOU
IN THE HALL?
HAZEL,
IT'S ABOUT JIMMY.
NO...
HE WAS SHOT.
HE'S ON HIS WAY
TO THE HOSPITAL.
NO.
I NEED TO GO...
NO YOU CAN'T GO.
I NEED TO GO!
THE LOCK-DOWN WILL BE
OVER SOON, OKAY?
WE'LL GET YOU THERE.
(CRYING)
MR. RADITCH:
PLEASE HEAD STRAIGHT HOME.
DO NOT STOP AT YOUR LOCKERS.
DO NOT LOITER AROUND.
WE RECOMMEND YOU NOT SPEAK
TO REPORTERS.
JAY:
JUST RELAX.
EVERYTHING IS GONNA
BE FINE.
WHY DID I GO ALONG
WITH ALL THIS?
I SAID RELAX.
YOU'RE ALIVE,
AREN'T YOU?
YO, SPIN!
I THOUGHT THAT
MIGHT HAVE BEEN YOU.
IT WAS JIMMY, MAN.
JIMMY!
THEY'RE GOING TO FIND OUT.
I HAVE TO-
NO!
LOOK, YOU HAVE
TO SHUT UP, OKAY?
HE'S MY BEST FRIEND.
EITHER OUTCOME,
I WOULD SAY HE WAS
YOUR BEST FRIEND.
WE MIGHT'VE
KILLED HIM.
WE DIDN'T
DO ANYTHING.
WE DID.
JOEY:
CRAIG!
CRAIG,
ARE YOU OKAY?
JIMMY GOT SHOT.
WHAT?
RACHEL:
DID YOU KNOW THE VICTIM?
CAITLIN:
RACHEL RHODES?
CRAIG:
DON'T CALL HIM "VICTIM".
HE HAS A NAME.
RACHEL:
WAS HE A TARGET, THOUGH?
WERE YOU?
DID YOU SEE THE SHOOTINGS?
THIS HAS TO STOP
RIGHT NOW.
SHARE, CAITLIN.
NO, I'M NOT
COVERING THIS.
WELL, THEN STEP ASIDE
AND LET ME.
CAITLIN:
HERE'S YOUR STORY FOR YOU:
LOCAL INSENSITIVE
REPORTER
PUMMELED BY
FAMOUS COLLEAGUE.
I'M SO GLAD
YOU'RE OKAY.
RACHEL:
YOU WERE THE GUNMAN'S FRIEND?
DO YOU KNOW WHO HE WAS AFTER?
WHY HE DID IT?
TOBY:
I DON'T KNOW.
RACHEL:
DID YOU TRY TO STOP HIM?
TOBY:
WHAT WAS I SUPPOSED TO DO?!
KATE:
LET'S GO.
RACHEL:
DID THE GUNMAN SAY ANYTHING
BEFORE HE DIED?
HE DIED?
SIMPSON:
COME ON, LET'S GO.
(CRYING)
RACHEL:
FOLLOWING THIS AFTERNOON'S
DOUBLE SHOOTING,
ONE STUDENT IS DEAD
AND ANOTHER REMAINS
IN SERIOUS CONDITION.
THE SUSPECT,
A 16-YEAR-OLD BOY
WHOSE NAME CANNOT
BE RELEASED,
WAS THE STUDENT FOUND DEAD
AT THE SCENE.
TOBY, MAYBE YOU SHOULD
TURN THAT OFF NOW.
SPIKE:
PEOPLE DO NOT GET SHOT
AT DEGRASSI.
THEY JUST DON'T.
YOU TALK ABOUT DEGRASSI
LIKE IT'S ACHIEVED SAINTHOOD.
IT'S A SCHOOL.
THAT'S MY POINT.
MR. SIMPSON:
LOOK, WE JUST DIDN'T...
NONE OF US TOOK RICK'S BULLYING
SERIOUSLY ENOUGH.
IT'D BE AN UNDERSTATEMENT TO SAY
THAT HE WAS UNPOPULAR.
UNPOPULAR?
HOW ABOUT "FULL-ON PSYCHO".
"CERTIFIED FREAK."
THE GUY MADE US THE LEAD STORY
ON THE 6:00 NEWS.
KATE:
ASHLEY...
ASHLEY:
HE SHOT JIMMY, MOM.
I JUST-
I WANT AN ANSWER.
WHO WAS THIS GUY WHO SHOT HIM,
IF NOT SOME PSYCHO?
(DOOR SLAMS)
HE WAS TOBY'S FRIEND.
♪ I AM PLAYING GOD ♪
NO,
THERE IS NO CHANGE.
♪ AND I AM RAISING HELL ♪
♪ AS FAR AS I CAN TELL ♪
♪ I'M ALL ALONE ♪
♪ ALONE IN THIS WORLD ♪
♪ ALONE WITH YOU ♪
RACHEL ON TV:
WE ARE TOLD HE WAS THE STAR
OF THE SHOW,
SINGLE-HANDEDLY WINNING
THE COMPETITION,
ONLY TO BE DOUSED WITH
YELLOW PAINT AND FEATHERS
BY FELLOW STUDENTS ON CAMERA.
THAT AFTERNOON,
THE SUSPECT RETURNED TO SCHOOL
WITH A HANDGUN.
THE PRINCIPAL,
DANIEL RADITCH,
A VETERAN EDUCATOR
AND TEACHER
AT DEGRASSI COMMUNITY SCHOOL
FOR MORE THAN TWENTY YEARS,
REPORTEDLY ASKED THE ACCUSED
TO TAKE THE AFTERNOON OFF.
IT WAS THEN
THAT THE RAMPAGE STARTED.
FOR CURRENTLY UNKNOWN REASONS,
THE ACCUSED HUNTED
THE HALLS FOR HIS TEAMMATES.
HE SHOT ONE IN THE BACK
AND WAS ABOUT TO FIRE
UPON ANOTHER
WHEN THE GUN WAS WRESTLED
FROM HIS HAND...
♪ I WILL FLY ♪
♪ YOU WILL SEE ♪
♪ CAUSE I AM PLAYING GOD ♪
♪ I AM RAISING HELL ♪
♪ AS FAR AS I CAN TELL ♪
♪ I AM ALL ALONE ♪
♪ ALONE IN THIS WORLD ♪
♪ ALONE... ♪