♪♪♪
OKAY. THAT SOUNDED
A BIT TIGHTER?
KEYBOARD WAS A BIT OFF
ON THE BRIDGE, THOUGH.
REALLY?
'CAUSE THE DRUMS
THREW ME OFF
ONLY IT WAS MORE
IN THE VERSE.
OKAY. IT SOUNDED LIKE THIS TAPE
OF WHALES MY AUNT PIA HAS.
WE HAVE TO DO BETTER.
SPINNER:
DUDE, WE ONLY HAVE THREE DAYS.
CRAIG:
WELL, WE AREN'T GOING TO WIN
$10, 000 WORTH
OF FREE RECORDING AGAIN.
AND WE HAVE TO USE IT NOW
AND WE HAVE TO BE BETTER.
MARCO:
YEAH AND WE COULD BE IF...
IF JIMMY COULD PLAY WITH US.
I WISH HE COULD, TOO.
WELL, WHAT IF WE TRIED
"EVERYTHING'S DUST?"
SPINNER:
SURE, THE SONG THAT JUST SO
HAPPENS TO BE ALL ABOUT YOU.
MARCO:
I THINK WHAT SPINNER MEANS
IS THAT UH...
WE'VE COME A LONG WAY
SINCE THAT SONG.
CRAIG:
BUT IT'S HOW WE WON
THE CONTEST.
I MEAN,
WE KNOW IT WORKS FOR US.
YEAH, IT WORKED FOR YOU,
ANYWAY.
WHAT?
MARCO:
LET'S JUST TRY IT.
SPINNER:
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
SO WHAT?
ONE, TWO, CRAP, FOUR...
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
PAIGE:
EW! OKAY, THERE IS GUM
ON THIS CHAIR!
EXCUSE ME, MR. SIMPSON,
BUT GUM ON CHAIRS
IS DISGROSSTING AND ILLEGAL!
SIMPSON:
JUST FIND ANOTHER SEAT, PAIGE.
IT'S NOT THE END
OF THE WORLD.
HELLO?
IT'S WATERMELON.
YEAH...
YOU DEFINITELY NEED
TO COME WITH ME TO YOGA.
THEY OFFER IT AFTER SCHOOL
IN THE GYM.
YEAH,
I PREFER RETAIL THERAPY.
HAZEL:
HONESTLY?
IT'S THE ONLY THING
KEEPING ME SANE SINCE...
WELL, YOU KNOW.
I'M SO SORRY.
I HAVEN'T EVEN ASKED
ABOUT JIMMY TODAY
OR YOU.
HE'S OKAY.
ME?
I'M JUST GLAD
THAT THE SCHOOL GAVE US
A WAY TO DE-STRESS
THAT DOESN'T INVOLVE
MORE TALKING.
DO NOT LET THE CULT OF YOGA
SUCK YOU IN.
YOU'LL END UP WEARING
BATIK AND EATING SPELT
AND I'LL HAVE TO PERFORM
AN EXORCISM
TO GET MY HAZEL BACK.
MATT:
GOING TO YOGA TODAY?
WOULDN'T MISS IT,
MR. OLEANDER.
PAIGE:
MR. O TEACHES YOGA?
WHAT WAS I THINKING?
I LOVE YOGA.
SIMPSON:
OKAY, EVERYONE.
A SPECIAL TREAT TODAY.
MR. OLEANDER,
OUR STUDENT TEACHER HERE,
IS GOING TO START
THE CLASS OFF,
WITH A DISCUSSION
ON SUBLIMINAL MESSAGES
IN MAINSTREAM MEDIA.
ALL RIGHT?
IT'S ALL YOURS.
MATT:
THANKS.
EVERYBODY. UM...
DID THAT WORK?
GOOD.
OKAY, SO.
IN THE EARLY 1950'S,
AN ADVERTISING EXPERT
BY THE NAME OF JAMES VICARY
WALKED INTO A MOVIE THEATRE...
WE CAN'T MAKE THE NEW SONG
WORK WITHOUT YOU.
I THOUGHT SPIN WAS GOING
TO WALK OUT OF REHEARSAL.
YEAH, SPINNER WALKS OUT
ON A LOT OF THINGS.
YEAH.
SO UM, ASH THINKS THAT
WE SHOULD DO THAT SONG
FROM LAST YEAR.
YOU KNOW, "DUST."
ASHLEY?
YEAH.
SHE'S BEEN COMING
TO REHEARSALS,
ADVISING AND STUFF.
OKAY.
IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE
CALLING IT THESE DAYS?
NO.
WE'RE... THERE'S NOTHING
GOING ON WITH ME AND ASH.
WE'RE FRIENDS.
OKAY, LOOK...
I MIGHT BE CRIPPLED, MAN,
BUT I'M NOT BLIND.
DON'T.
YOU'RE NOT CRIPPLED,
OKAY?
I GUESS I WON'T BE
FOR LONG.
JUST LIKE I IMAGINE
THAT YOU AND ASHLEY
WON'T JUST BE FRIENDS
FOR LONG EITHER.
WHAT, DID YOU GET
BRAIN DAMAGE, TOO?
ASHLEY AND I ARE NOT GOING
TO HAPPEN AGAIN.
WHATEVER.
MATT:
IN THE WARRIOR STANCE,
YOUR FEET ARE FIRMLY ROOTED
IN THE EARTH.
YOUR KNEE IS OVER YOUR ANKLE,
YOUR SHIN IS VERTICAL.
GOOD.
DOESN'T MR. O LOOK
O' SO FETCHING
IN HIS YOGA PANTS?
FETCHING IS FOR DOGS.
AND MR. OLEANDER
IS NOT A DOG.
SHH!
MATT:
EXCELLENT, PAIGE.
BREATHE.
HOW DOES THAT FEEL?
AMAZING.
EXTRA POINTS
FOR SMILING.
HE WAS FLIRTING WITH ME!
HE'S A TEACHER.
STUDENT TEACHER, HELLO.
CRAIG:
♪ DON'T ASK ME
WHY I COULDN'T SEE IT ♪
♪ THAT'D TAKE ME YEARS
TO FIGURE OUT. ♪
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I THINK
YOU'RE BRILLIANT.
YOUR SONG IS BRILLIANT.
UM, DOESN'T IT SOUND
KINDA PRETTY?
I MEAN, WE ARE A ROCK BAND.
HEY, HEY,
IT'S GOOD CONTRAST.
IT'S COUNTERPOINT.
WELL, MAYBE IT WOULD HELP
IF WE WORKED ON THE BASS LINE.
YOU KNOW,
MADE IT LESS SIMPLE.
HEY GUYS,
SORRY I'M LATE.
CRAIG:
SPINNER, WE'VE BEEN HERE
AN HOUR!
YOU WANNA SIT
ON THE CHAIR THING?
THANKS, STIX.
WHO'S STIX?
AND WHY IS SHE HERE?
SPINNER:
I'M STIX. OKAY?
AND I JUST THOUGHT THAT
SINCE THE BAND IS OPEN
TO ANY AND ALL CHICKS,
I BRING MY OWN AMUSE.
YOU MEAN MUSE?
(BANGS ON DRUMS)
PAIGE:
I MEAN, DO YOU THINK
IT MEANT SOMETHING?
IT MIGHT HAVE,
BUT THEN HAZEL SAID THAT-
UGH, THIS IS TORTURE.
YOU AND THE FURBY
JUST BROKE UP.
IT'S OKAY TO BE SINGLE
FOR TWENTY MINUTES.
PAIGE:
EASY FOR YOU TO SAY.
MATT:
TO SAY WHAT?
THAT UM...
I, I SO HATE POLYESTER.
OKAY.
ANYWAYS, I WAS
JUST WALKING BY
THOUGHT I'D COME SAY HI
TO MY FAVORITE YOGA STUDENT.
YOU SHOULD GO FOR IT.
WHAT?!
I HAPPENED TO SEE
MY FAVORITE YOGA STUDENT?
PLEASE.
HE LOVES YOU.
MANNY:
THERE IS NO SUCH THING
AS BAD PUBLICITY,
BUT THERE IS SUCH A THING
AS A BAD SHIRT.
I COULDN'T AGREE
WITH YOU MORE.
SPINNER:
I LIKE THIS SHIRT.
OKAY WHATEVER.
I DON'T KNOW
WHY WE BOTHER
BECAUSE IT'S OBVIOUS
WE'RE JUST THE BACK-UP BAND
FOR ASHLEY AND CRAIG'S
VARIETY HOUR.
MARCO:
SPIN, STOP BEING A DRAMA QUEEN,
OKAY?
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
IT'S LIKE...
YOU AND I
AREN'T EVEN IN THE BAND.
ASHLEY:
IT IS JUST THE SCHOOL PAPER.
CRAIG:
YOU GOTTA START SOMEWHERE.
YOU KNOW, I CAN SEE
THIS GOING REALLY FAR.
WITH THE BAND,
I MEAN.
LIBERTY:
LET'S COMMENCE.
DEADLINE LOOMING.
SO, WHERE DO YOU SEE
YOUR BAND GOING?
CRAIG:
FAR. REALLY FAR.
LIBERTY:
WHO ARE YOUR MAJOR INFLUENCES?
WE ALL LOVE DEATH CAB.
BOTH:
AND NEUTRAL MILK HOTEL.
LIBERTY:
OKAY.
UH... WHERE DO YOUR SONGS
COME FROM?
MARCO:
WE'D LIKE TO LOOK-
CRAIG:
WELL, ACTUALLY
THEY ALL COME FROM
A BUNCH OF DIFFERENT
SOURCES OF INSPIRATION.
LIBERTY:
OKAY.
ANY SOLO PROJECTS
COMING UP?
UH... YEAH.
MARCO AND I, WE HAVE A-
GOD,
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
THIS IS ONLY OUR FIRST SINGLE.
LIBERTY:
OKAY.
WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE
TO SAY TO YOUR FANS?
JUST KEEP WATCHING US
AND YOU AIN'T SEEN
NOTHIN' YET.
EVERYONE SAY
"THEMISTOCLES".
ASHLEY:
THEMISTOCLES.
LIBERTY:
FABULOUS.
ASHLEY:
THAT WAS REALLY COOL.
LIBERTY:
GOOD JOB, GUYS.
THANKS LIBERTY.
LIBERTY:
IT'S GOING TO BE
AN INTERESTING ARTICLE.
CRAIG:
HEY.
MARCO:
HEY CRAIG, UM...
WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
CRAIG:
OKAY.
SO LET'S TALK.
SPINNER:
ASH HAS GOTTA GO.
WHOA, STIX,
HEY SLOW IT DOWN.
ASH HAS GOTTA GO.
CRAIG:
HAS EVERYONE GONE NUTS?
MARCO:
SHE'S NOT IN THE BAND, CRAIG.
WE NEVER AGREED TO IT.
YES YOU DID.
SPINNER:
DUDE, IT USED TO BE OUR BAND.
REMEMBER?
IT USED TO BE ABOUT US.
IT'S STILL ABOUT US.
ASH LOST THE CONTEST,
OKAY?
TO US AND TO JIMMY.
SO WHY DOES SHE GET
TO BE ON THE RECORDING?
LOOK, RECORDING THIS SINGLE
IT MEANS EVERYTHING TO ME,
OKAY?
SPINNER:
DUDE...
EITHER SHE GOES OR WE DO,
OKAY?
'CAUSE IT'S NOT WORKING.
YOU HAVE TO FIRE HER.
(SIGHS)
REMEMBER
THE RECORDING SESSION?
UM HI.
AND YEAH,
HOW COULD I FORGET?
YEAH, UM...
I DON'T KNOW HOW
TO TELL YOU THIS-
HEY LOOK.
I'M NERVOUS, TOO.
BUT I MEAN,
YOU'LL BE THERE.
YOU KNOW, ALL I HAVE TO DO
IS LOOK OVER AT YOU,
AND I'LL BE FINE.
SO, YOU WANTED
TO TELL ME SOMETHING?
UH...
MARCO:
LOOK, YOU DID THE RIGHT THING,
OKAY?
I'M SURE IT WAS PAINFUL
FOR YOU AND ASH,
BUT HEY, AT LEAST US GUYS
CAN BE US GUYS AGAIN.
PAINFUL?
THE OPPOSITE.
ASHLEY AND I... WE'RE BACK!
WE'RE BACK TOGETHER!
OH GEE, I THOUGHT SHE
WOULD'VE BEEN ALL MAD
WHEN YOU FIRED HER.
MARCO:
UH, YEAH.
HE DIDN'T FIRE HER,
SPINNER.
CRAIG:
LIKE I COULD KISS HER
AND THEN DO IT.
COME ON.
MARCO, CUT ME SOME SLACK.
IT'S NOT THAT BIG OF A DEAL!
MATT:
EXTEND THE CROWN OF YOUR HEAD
AND BREATHE DEEPLY.
GOOD. GOOD.
YOU'RE A NATURAL,
HEATHER.
PERFECT.
PAIGE:
HE DIDN'T EVEN LOOK AT ME!
ALL HE COULD LOOK AT
WERE HEATHER SINCLAIR'S
TRASHY ROOTS
AND HER BIG,
ROUND-
NOT TO SOUND
LIKE A BROKEN RECORD,
BUT HE IS A TEACHER.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO GO FOR IT
IF HE WON'T EVEN
LOOK AT ME?
HAZEL:
MAYBE YOU SHOULDN'T GO FOR IT.
YOU AND OLDER GUYS
ARE NOT ALWAYS A GOOD MATCH.
SHH!
MATT:
HEY CHARLIE,
JUST GOT YOUR MESSAGE.
UH YEAH, 8:00 P.M.,
BAR CRAFT.
SEE YOU THEN, BYE.
WHERE'S BAR CRAFT?
SO ONE MINUTE WE'RE TALKING
FIRST RECORDING SESSION
BUTTERFLIES AND THE NEXT?
FULL ON LIP LOCK.
ELLIE:
DON'T DO IT.
ASHLEY:
YEAH, LITTLE LATE FOR THAT.
ELLIE:
NOT THE KISS. THE REST.
ASHLEY:
WELL, HE'S DIFFERENT.
I THINK.
ELLIE:
GUYS SUCK, ASHLEY.
THEY ENJOY MESSING
WITH OUR FEELINGS
AND THEN STICKING US
WITH THE RENT.
JUST DON'T COME CRYING
TO ME
WHEN HE "CRAIGS OUT"
ON YOU.
EVERYTHING OKAY?
YOUR TEXT
WAS ALL IN CAPS.
YEAH, I JUST,
I FIGURED
WE SHOULD TALK
BEFORE REHEARSAL
ABOUT YESTERDAY.
RIGHT.
OKAY.
UM... WELL, IT SORTA
TOOK ME BY SURPRISE.
YEAH, JOIN THE CLUB.
SO YOU'RE CONFUSED,
TOO?
YOU KNOW,
MAYBE WE'RE JUST UH...
REACHING FOR SOMETHING
FAMILIAR.
YOU KNOW, GIVEN JIMMY,
EVERYTHING THAT'S HAPPENED.
OH. NEVER THOUGHT
OF THAT.
WELL, YOU KNOW, WE HAVE BEEN
DOING GREAT AS FRIENDS, RIGHT?
RIGHT.
AND WHO'D WANT
TO SCREW THAT UP?
YEAH. WHO WOULD?
GOOD. GREAT. GOOD.
I'M GLAD WE GOT
THAT SETTLED.
YEAH, WELL, HEY AT LEAST
WE STILL HAVE THE BAND.
YEAH.
I HOPE THEY HAVE YOGA
IN JAIL.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO JAIL,
OKAY?
OUR I.D. IS SUPER GOOD.
I SWEAR DYLAN'S DORMMATE'S
IN THE MAFIA.
SO WE'LL BE IN JAIL
AND THE WITNESS
PROTECTION PROGRAM.
HAZEL,
BREATHE OUT TENSION,
BREATHE IN PEACE, REMEMBER?
WHEN'S YOUR BIRTHDAY?
UM... YOU KNOW...
IT'S UH...
NOVEMBER 19TH.
OF WHAT YEAR?
OH CRAP.
NINETEEN -
TOO SLOW.
YOU'RE IN JAIL.
OKAY, WHAT'S YOUR
POSTAL CODE?
BOUNCER:
(AHEM) I.D., LADIES?
CRAIG:
SO LAST PRACTICE, EH?
TOMORROW'S OUR BIG BREAK.
MARCO:
YEAH, GREAT. WHERE'S ASH?
UM... KITCHEN.
GETTING US SOME-
MANNY:
GUYS CAN'T WE GET
A PRETTIER ONE?
SPINNER:
OH YEAH...
UH BECAUSE YOU GET
TO DO WHAT YOU WANT?
I'M PUTTING MANNY
ON TAMBOURINE.
MARCO:
WHAT?
EVERY MAN FOR HIMSELF,
RIGHT CRAIG?
ASHLEY:
HEY GUYS.
DID I MISS SOMETHING?
YEAH, ACTUALLY...
CRAIG, WHY DON'T
YOU TELL ASHLEY
ABOUT THE CHANGES
WE MADE TO OUR BAND.
ASHLEY:
UH, THAT THEY INCLUDE
THE ACCORDION?
PLAYING A NICE POLKA?
OKAY, UM, WE RECORD TOMORROW.
WHY ARE WE MAKING CHANGES NOW?
TELL HER WHY, CRAIG.
NO?
ALL RIGHT.
AND-A-ONE-STILL-CRAP-FOUR.
♪♪♪
♪ I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU'LL FORGIVE ME ♪
♪ FOR BEING SO BLIND ♪
♪ TO HOW YOU FELT. ♪
♪ DON'T ASK ME WHY
YOU COULDN'T SEE IT... ♪
PAIGE:
WE DID IT! WE DID IT!
WE DID IT! (GIGGLES)
HAZEL:
PAIGE, YOU NEED
TO GET OUT MORE.
PAIGE:
OKAY.
THERE HE IS.
OH MY GOD,
HE IS DRINKING BEER.
THAT IS SO CUTE.
I COULD DIE.
MR. O?
WOW, I NEVER THOUGHT
I'D SEE YOU IN HERE.
PAIGE.
HEY, UM...
YOU KNOW THIS IS
A BAR, RIGHT?
YEAH,
I LOVE THIS PLACE.
CAN I SIT DOWN?
CAN I BUY YOU
A DRINK?
HEY MATTY.
HEY.
HEY, PAIGE,
I WANT YOU
TO MEET SOMEONE.
THIS IS CHARLIE,
MY GIRLFRIEND.
OH.
MATT:
UH, PAIGE IS A STUDENT OF MINE.
AW, THAT'S SO SWEET.
I THINK SHE'S KINDA
CRUSHIN' ON YOU, MATTY.
I'LL HAVE A RED WINE,
AND A SHIRLEY TEMPLE
FOR THE KID HERE.
IT'S A SCHOOL NIGHT.
BOUNCER:
BAD GIRLS.
PAIGE:
HEY, I AM NINETEEN.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
MARCO:
IT'S UBER-COOL.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
WE'RE RECORDING.
SPINNER:
YEAH, IT IS JUST LIKE
WE ALWAYS WANTED,
EH CRAIG?
SURE.
A GYPSY ROCK
AND ROLL ACT.
SPINNER:
HEY. IT'S YOUR CHOICE, BUDDY.
ASHLEY:
HEY, SORRY I'M LATE.
THE CAB DRIVER GOT LOST.
MY LUCK.
C'MON GUYS,
WE'RE ON THE CLOCK.
UM... I'M, I'M SORRY.
I DON'T-I DON'T MEAN
TO BE A DIVA
BUT ARE WE REALLY GOING
TO RECORD LIKE THIS?
WELL, WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
YOUR HIGHNESS?
WITH THE ACCORDION
AND THE TAMBOURINE?
CRAIG?
YEAH, OKAY GUYS.
LET'S GO GET SOME
MORE FREE FOOD, EH?
HERE, HOLD THIS.
MANNY:
DIBS ON THE CINNAMON BUNS.
SPINNER:
OOH YEAH.
UH CRAIG?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
LOOK, I'M NOT STUPID.
YOU HAVE TO TELL ME.
OKAY, UM...
YOU NEED TO LEAVE.
YOU'RE OUT OF THE BAND.
AND UM... THE WHOLE BAND
WANTS THIS?
YEAH, BUT I DON'T.
IT'S JUST-
NO, NO. IT'S...
IT'S JUST BUSINESS.
♪ I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU'LL FORGIVE ME ♪
♪ FOR BEING SO BLIND ♪
♪ TO HOW YOU FELT. ♪
♪ DON'T ASK ME WHY
YOU COULDN'T SEE IT ♪
♪ AND THAT'D TAKE ME YEARS
TO FIGURE OUT ♪
♪ AND THAT'S NOT SOMETHING
I KNOW MUCH ABOUT. ♪
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH! ♪
♪ AND WHAT I KNOW ♪
♪ IS THAT I HURT YOU,
OH... ♪
♪ AND WHAT I KNOW
IS THAT I SUCK ♪
IS THAT I'M SORRY. ♪
♪ WHAT I KNOW
IS THAT I'M A LOSER. ♪
♪ YEAH! ♪
♪ WHAT I KNOW
IS I SCREWED UP ♪
♪ AND THAT I NEVER
EARNED YOUR TRUST. ♪
♪ WHAT I KNOW
IS THAT EVERYTHING ♪
♪ EVERYTHING... ♪
UH... CRAIG?
CRAIG!
SPINNER:
UH... (AHEM) OKAY.
THAT WAS AWESOME.
LET'S JUST TAKE IT
FROM THE TOP.
I CAN'T DO IT.
MARCO:
WHAT? WHOA, CRAIG,
OF COURSE YOU CAN.
SPINNER:
NO, NO, NO.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
UM... EVERYTHING.
IT WAS ALL ABOUT ASHLEY.
IT WASN'T ABOUT A SINGLE
OR MAKING IT BIG.
IT WAS JUST ASHLEY.
SPINNER:
NO, CRAIG!
CRAIG:
ASHLEY!
ASHLEY.
HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
YOU'RE RECORDING.
I COULDN'T.
I COULDN'T DO IT.
ESPECIALLY A SONG
THAT MEANT SO MUCH TO US.
I SEE.
SO YOU JUST LEFT?
UGH.
HOW COULD YOU THROW
A CHANCE LIKE THAT AWAY?
LOOK, THE RECORDING STUDIO
WILL ALWAYS BE THERE.
BUT YOU I WASN'T,
I WASN'T SO SURE.
WHAT?
I... I... SORRY.
I UM...
I THOUGHT THAT-
OH GOD.
HEY!
IF YOU THINK YOU'RE
JUST GOING TO WALK AWAY...
SO UM...
DO YOU THINK
WE CAN UH...
YEAH.
YEAH, I DO.
SO DO I.