BYE.
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW,
RIGHT?
ONE MORE?
OKAY, MY MOM'S GONNA
BE HERE IN A SEC.
YOU'LL CALL ME,
THOUGH, RIGHT?
ASHLEY:
DAD'S WEDDING IS TAKING
OVER MY ENTIRE LIFE.
DRESS-FITTINGS, DINNERS,
THE AIRPORT TO PICK UP
CHRIS' SISTER...
I LIKE AIRPORTS.
PEOPLE SAYING HELLO'S,
GOOD-BYE'S,
I LOVE YOU'S.
DID YOU JUST-?
I ONLY SAY IT
AT AIRPORTS.
MRS. KERWIN!
IT'S BEEN A WHILE.
ASHLEY, DO YOU WANT
TO GET IN THE CAR?
I'LL CALL.
I WILL.
OR I CAN CALL YOU.
DON'T BOTHER.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
"MOM? CRAIG AND I
ARE BACK TOGETHER.
AND THAT'S IT."
SHE SAID
DON'T BOTHER.
WHAT DOES
DON'T BOTHER MEAN?
IT MEANS THAT I PROMISE
NOT TO TELL HER
EVERY DETAIL OF OUR NEXT
HORRIBLE BREAKUP.
NO "NEXT", OKAY?
PROMISE.
(THE SOUND OF ACCORDION
AND DRUMS PLAYING)
WHAT?
MARCO: (SINGING BADLY)
♪ I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU'LL FORGIVE ME ♪
♪ FOR BEING SO BLIND. ♪
CRAIG:
IS THAT WHAT
I THINK IT IS?
YEAH.
IT'S WHAT WE WERE
SUPPOSED TO RECORD
UNTIL YOU GAVE IT ALL UP
FOR MISS BAND-BREAKER-UPPER.
THAT'S PRETTY-
SPINNER:
AWFUL?
HORRIBLE?
SEIZURE-INDUCING?
OH, HOW ABOUT,
HOW ABOUT LOUSY?
OH, IT'S ALSO
THE LAST SINGLE
THAT "DOWNTOWN SASQUATCH"
WILL EVER PUT OUT.
HERE.
IF YOU THROW 'EM REAL
HARD AT THE CEILING,
SOMETIMES THEY STICK.
"CRAIG AND I
ARE BACK TOGETHER.
AND THAT'S IT.
I'M REALLY HAPPY."
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
JT:
GOT THE SCRIPTS.
LIBERTY:
WOW. THAT'S A LOT OF PAPER.
AND MUFFINS?
DRAMA CLUB GOES ALL OUT.
(GROAN) I DON'T WANT
TO DO THIS ANYMORE.
LIBERTY,
YOU WROTE THE PLAY.
YOU ADAPTED
"DRACULA".
AND NOT FROM
A MOVIE, EITHER;
FROM A BOOK.
IT'S GREAT.
LIBERTY:
BUT IT'S NOT "GREAT".
IT'S EMBARRASSING,
PEDESTRIAN,
REPUTATION-KILLER.
OKAY,
THIS SO ISN'T YOU.
YOU ARE IRRITATING,
STUBBORN...
SELF-CONFIDENT TO THE POINT
OF SOCIAL RETARDATION.
LIBERTY:
GEE, JT, THANKS.
BUT YOU'RE TALENTED,
OKAY?
BRILLIANT.
SO JUST HAVE A MUFFIN
AND CHILL.
YOUR DIRECTOR
SAYS SO.
JT JUST SAID
I'M BRILLIANT.
WHEN DID YOU
WRITE THESE?
ONLY ONE SONG'S
FINISHED.
THE OTHER THREE
ONLY KINDA.
SIMPSON:
MR. MANNING? MISS KERWIN?
YEAH, THE PAST COUPLE
NIGHTS I'VE STAYED UP.
I DON KNOW,
INSPIRATION.
ENERGY, I GUESS.
SIMPSON:
I SAID, MR. MANNING?
I MEAN I COULD'VE
SHOWN YOU LATER,
BUT THIS TEENY
PART OF ME...
THIS TEENY PART OF ME
KIND OF WONDERS
WHAT YOU MIGHT
THINK NOW-
SIMPSON:
CRAIG!
CRAIG:
WHAT?!
THE COMPUTER
IN THE CORNER,
IT'S LONELY.
GO INTRODUCE YOURSELF.
THIS IS SUPPOSED TO BE
INDEPENDENT STUDY TIME,
RIGHT?
ME?
INDEPENDENT AND WALKING.
YOU STUDY MY BUTT LEAVING.
WELL THEY CAN STUDY
YOUR BUTT AT THE OFFICE.
NOW!
SO YOU'RE CALM NOW,
RIGHT?
AT LEAST,
REASONABLY?
EVERYONE'S TRYING
TO SEPARATE US!
WE WERE PASSING NOTES
AND TALKING.
WHOSE SIDE
ARE YOU ON?
LOOK, WHEN ARE YOU
SEEING YOUR MOM?
TODAY AFTER SCHOOL.
CRAIG:
CONVINCE HER I'M NOT
SATAN'S KIN, OKAY?
THAT YOU AND I
ARE CHANGED AND RIGHT
AND GOOD.
OR ELSE THE REHEARSAL
PARTY TONIGHT'S
REALLY GONNA SUCK.
WHAT IF WE WORK ON MY PARENTS
AFTER THE WEDDING.
YOU DON'T WANT ME
THERE.
I DO, CRAIG.
EXCEPT...
CRAIG...
PROMISE,
THAT IF THE TIME COMES,
YOU WILL KILL ME.
I PROMISE.
NATE:
MINA, THE SUN'S ALMOST SET.
DRACULA'S BLOOD HAS NOT
NEARLY POISONED MINE,
BUT IT WILL.
IN KILLING ME,
DOCTOR VAN HELSING
SAVES MY LIFE.
BUT JONATHAN,
IT IS YOU WHO SAVES MY SOUL.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
(APPLAUSE)
OKAY.
WE'RE ALL MEETING
SATURDAY MORNING.
WE'LL FINISH
THE REST THEN.
MS. KWAN?
A WORD?
THAT WAS GOOD,
LIBERTY.
NO, IT WAS GREAT.
ALEX:
YEAH. A LITTLE GROSS, TOO.
YOU SEE?
RADITCH:
TODAY I HEARD
ABOUT SEVERED HEADS,
AND STAKES THROUGH
THE HEART.
WITH RECENT EVENTS,
DO YOU THINK PRESENTING
VIOLENCE IS A GOOD IDEA?
"THIS POWER OF GOOD,
YOU HAVE WON FROM
YOUR SUFFERING."
VAN HELSING SAYS IT
AT THE END.
AND EVER SINCE
RICK DIED,
WE'VE ALL BEEN
SUFFERING, SIR.
I WROTE THE PLAY TO SHOW
THE SCHOOL THERE'S HOPE.
A LIGHT AT THE END
OF THE TUNNEL.
CAN'T IT BE
SOMETHING CHEERY,
SOMETHING FUN?
YOU'D PREFER
A MUSICAL OF "DRACULA"?
A MUSICAL ABOUT
DEGRASSI
AND THE WONDERFUL
THINGS THAT HAPPEN HERE.
JT:
YEAH, BUT DRAMA CLUB MEETS
TOMORROW.
RADITCH:
WELL, YOU BETTER GET WRITING.
SEE HOW MUCH YOU CAN
GET DONE TONIGHT.
(LISTENING TO RAP MUSIC)
CRAIG:
SOON YOU'LL BE NEEDING THAT
BAR TO BEAT THE NURSES AWAY.
SHOULDN'T YOU BE
AT SCHOOL?
ASH IS THIS CLOSE
TO DUMPING ME.
IT IS HER TURN,
RIGHT?
JUST HELP ME.
TELL ME TO STAND
OUTSIDE HER WINDOW
WITH A STEREO.
OR...
SORRY, MAN.
I'M ALWAYS TALKING
ABOUT MYSELF.
I SHOULDN'T.
NO, YOU SHOULD.
YOU SHOULD.
EVERYONE ELSE
THAT COMES IN HERE
EITHER TALKS
ABOUT THE WEATHER
OR MY PROGNOSIS,
MY LEGS.
STILL?
STILL.
IT ISN'T ROCKET SCIENCE,
OKAY?
TALK TO ASHLEY.
GET HER ALONE.
WELL, HER HOUSE
IS FULL OF WEDDING.
CAITLIN'S PAINTING,
SO MY PLACE LOOKS LIKE
A DISASTER FLICK.
SO WHAT,
YOU WANT ME TO SEE
IF THEY HAVE
ANY VACANCIES HERE?
VACANCIES...
LIKE AT A HOTEL.
ANGELA:
MORE PIZZA.
JOEY:
AH CRAIG...
PIZZA FOR DINNER.
AGAIN.
NO THANKS,
BUT YOU KNOW
WHAT I COULD USE?
I HAVE NO MONEY.
BUT YOU HAVE
A CREDIT CARD.
IF YOU PAINT EVERY ROOM
IN THE HOUSE,
I'LL SIGN OVER MINE.
CRAIG:
LOOK, I HAVE THE MONEY
TO PAY YOU UP FRONT.
AND I'D ONLY BE BORROWING IT
FOR ONE NIGHT.
PLEASE.
CRAIG, YOU SKIPPED
CLASS TODAY.
SCHOOL DOES CALL.
I WENT TO VISIT JIMMY
ON A STUDY PERIOD.
WHAT DOES IT HAVE TO DO
WITH ME BORROWING YOUR CARD?
WHAT DO YOU NEED IT
SO BADLY FOR?
ARE YOU RENTING
SOMETHING?
JOEY, CAN YOU HELP WITH THIS?
JOEY:
OKAY.
CRAIG, NO.
I'M NOT LENDING YOU
MY CARD.
AND SKIPPING A STUDY PERIOD
IS STILL SKIPPING.
DON'T DO IT AGAIN.
I DIDN'T EVEN
SEE THAT!
PIZZA!
SALLY:
TALL, DARK AND HOPELESSLY LOST?
YOU MUST BE CRAIG.
I'M SALLY.
ASHLEY'S AUNT.
MY BROTHER'S GONNA BE
MARRYING HER DAD.
COME BACK LATER,
I'LL HAVE CHARTS.
HAVE YOU SEEN ASHLEY?
SALLY:
YOU KNOW,
CHRISTOPHER TOLD ME
ALL ABOUT YOU.
WHICH VERSION?
DID I HAVE HORNS
IN THAT ONE?
MAYBE A LONG,
POINTY TAIL?
YOU MEAN
YOU'RE DIFFERENT NOW?
DARN.
LOOK, I HURT ASHLEY.
AND THE FACT SHE'S EVEN
WILLING TO EVEN LOOK AT ME?
I'M NOT SCREWING
THAT UP AGAIN.
SO YOU CAN FLIRT WITH ME,
AND PEOPLE CAN SAY
WHATEVER,
BUT THAT FACT IS
I LOVE YOUR NIECE.
ASHLEY:
THOUGHT YOU ONLY SAID
THAT AT AIRPORTS?
I'M NOT STAYING
HERE LONG.
I JUST CAME TO GIVE
YOU THIS.
IT'S A HOTEL ROOM KEY.
IT'S FOR LATER.
IF YOU NEED
A PLACE TO GO.
KATE:
ASHLEY, I MADE IT CLEAR.
THERE IS NO ROOM
FOR EXTRA GUESTS,
ESPECIALLY UNINVITED ONES.
ASHLEY:
JUST SHOWING HIM OUT, MOM.
OKAY.
NO PEEKING.
STAND RIGHT HERE.
NOW THIS WAS
SUPPOSED TO BE
FOR AFTER
THE REHEARSAL PARTY,
BUT...
OKAY, OPEN.
CRAIG,
THIS IS KINDA PERFECT.
NO MORE ANNOYING
FRIENDS,
BULLYING TEACHERS,
SHRIEKING PARENTS,
OR HORNY AUNTS.
YOU GOT A ROOM
WITH TWO BEDS.
THERE'S TWO OF US.
WELL...
WHAT IF WE ONLY NEEDED ONE BED?
ONE BED?
YEAH WELL,
YOU KNOW,
IF YOU BROUGHT SOMETHING.
NEVER AGAIN
WILL I BE WITHOUT.
THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR DOING THIS.
I LOVE YOU.
AND THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR SAYING THAT.
PERFECT.
I LOVE YOU TOO.
CRAIG:
SALVADOR KOVACK?
KILLER RAGE TWO?
OH, HOW ABOUT ELIMINATION
ROUND THREE?
(SOBBING)
I'M SORRY.
FOR WHATEVER I DID,
I INSTANTLY APOLOGIZE.
HEY, HEY, LOOK!
THERE IS A...
WE GOT JUJUBES -
I THINK THEY'RE BRITISH.
BELGIAN CHOCOLATES?
MAYBE CHIPS?
(SOBBING)
MAYBE NOT.
HEY, HEY, ASH.
ASHLEY:
I'M SORRY.
I'M HAPPY, REALLY.
JUST... I DON'T KNOW,
I'M OVERWHELMED.
KEEP TALKING.
PLEASE.
OKAY.
SO LET'S JUST...
LET'S JUST TAKE OFF.
GET AN APARTMENT -
ANYWHERE.
VANCOUVER.
I HATE TO LEAVE YOU.
SO DON'T LEAVE ME.
ASHLEY:
I HAVE TO GO TO MY DAD'S.
WHY?
I HAVE FOOD HERE.
HE'S MY DAD.
BUT I'M YOUR CRAIG.
YEAH.
YOU ARE.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE JUST AS IMPORTANT
TO ME AS HE IS.
SO GET DRESSED.
YOU'RE COMING WITH ME.
THERE SHE IS.
MANNY:
SO, HOW LONG HAVE YOU GUYS
BEEN WORKING TOGETHER?
LIBERTY:
"DRACULA" IS DEAD.
BUT "DEGRASSI: THE MUSICAL"
IS BORN.
SAY YOU'RE KIDDING.
PLEASE.
ANY TIME.
WE THOUGHT WE'D NEED TO SET
THE THING AROUND A CHARACTER;
SOMEBODY WHO'S BEEN
AT THE SCHOOL
SINCE IT OPENED -
A TEACHER,
A JANITOR,
A CAFETERIA WORKER
NAMED...
JT AND LIBERTY:
SHELLEY.
JT:
AND WHILE SHE WORKS,
SHE SINGS.
♪ OH THESE HALLOWED
HALLS OF STONE ♪
♪ MAKE ME WANT
TO DIAL HOME. ♪
♪ LOOK WAY UP
INTO THE SKY, ♪
♪ DEGRASSI'S NAME,
WRIT REAL HIGH. ♪
SAY YOU'RE KIDDING.
PLEASE.
ANY TIME.
SHE'S RIGHT.
THIS IS STUPID.
I QUIT.
GO AFTER HIM,
INVITE HIM BACK
TO YOUR PLACE.
BRAINSTORM IDEAS
IN THE HOT TUB -
SOMETHING THAT DOESN'T
INVOLVE ME WEARING A HAIR NET.
DO IT NOW.
PLEASE, LIBERTY.
♪♪♪
FIRST REAL BAR
WE GO TO.
AND IT'S
A GAY BAR?
I NEED A MOMENT
WITH THE MAID OF HONOUR?
MOM, WHATEVER YOU
HAVE TO SAY TO ME
YOU CAN SAY
TO CRAIG TOO.
NO, NO, NO.
IT'S OKAY.
YOU TWO TALK.
DAD IS MARRYING
A GUY TOMORROW
AND I'M DEALING
WITH THAT.
IT'S NOT THE SAME THING,
ASHLEY.
HE LEFT YOU, MOM,
FOR A MAN
AND YOU FORGAVE HIM.
I MEAN, YOU'RE THROWING HIM
A WEDDING.
BUT CRAIG...
CRAIG BROKE
MY DAUGHTER'S HEART.
AND I FORGAVE HIM.
ASHLEY, I FEEL LIKE WE JUST
PUT YOU BACK TOGETHER AGAIN.
LOOK, MOM,
I'M REALLY HAPPY
SO YOU'RE JUST GOING TO
HAVE TO BE HAPPY FOR ME.
SALLY:
HI MRS. KERWIN.
KATE:
HI SALLY.
TOBY:
CRAIG:
THIS IS AMAZING.
ASHLEY:
I KNOW.
I WANT TO BOTTLE THIS.
GET DRUNK ON IT
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
I SO, SO LOVE YOU.
(SLOW SONG CHANGES
TO SOMETHING FASTER)
AND I SO, SO WISH
THAT DIDN'T JUST HAPPEN.
I HAVE TO LEAVE
FOR A FEW MINUTES.
WHAT? WHY?
A HALF-HOUR.
JUST STAY HERE.
♪ WHAT I KNOW
IS THAT I HURT YOU, OH... ♪
CAITLIN:
YOU GOING OFF TO DO
A LOUNGE GIG?
SUIT'S FOR THE WEDDING.
ASHLEY'S AT THE PARTY
WAITING.
SO BYE.
JOEY:
WHOA, WHOA, CRAIG.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
YEAH.
WE'RE BACK TOGETHER.
ASH AND ME.
ME AND ASH.
WHAT WAS I THINKING BEFORE?
CHEATING ON HER WITH MANNY?
WHY DID I DO THAT?
PEOPLE MAKE MISTAKES.
NEVER EVER, EVER,
EVER, EVER AGAIN.
I'LL HELP YOU GUYS OUT LATER.
TONIGHT, I'M AT MARCO'S.
CRAIG, YOU'RE BACK.
IN A SUIT.
CAN I TALK YOU
FOR A SECOND?
ASHLEY:
IT'S A RING.
CRAIG:
YEAH.
IT WAS MY MOTHER'S.
SO IT'S YOUR
MOTHER'S RING?
WHY ARE YOU DOWN
ON ONE KNEE?
WILL YOU MARRY ME?
I-I'M SORRY,
I CAN'T.
NO. I ACTUALLY WANT YOU
TO MARRY ME?
CRAIG, I'M...
I'M SORRY, NO.
JUST... JUST...
CRAIG!
I WANT YOU TO MARRY ME!
DANNY:
HOW ABOUT PUTTING "DRACULA"
IN DEGRASSI?
HE TURNS THE TEACHERS
INTO VAMPIRES,
SAVING RADITCH FOR LAST.
HUH? HUH?
GOOD IDEA, HUH?
LIBERTY:
THE ELDERS ARE SLEEPING,
DANNY.
DANNY:
YOU GUYS AREN'T EVEN LISTENING
AND I'M GETTING PRUNED.
JT:
I'M EXPERIENCING MAJOR
PRUNAGE AS WELL,
AND I'M WAY TOO TIRED
FOR THIS.
LIBERTY:
WHAT ABOUT TOMORROW,
THOUGH?
WE NEVER CANCELLED
AND THE WHOLE DRAMA CLUB'S
GOING TO SHOW UP.
JT:
YES.
BUT WE CAN'T REHEARSE
A MUSICAL WITHOUT ANY SONGS.
LIBERTY:
RADISHES, RADISHES,
NOT SO SWEET;
RED AND ROUND
AND GROSS TO EAT.
WHAT IS THAT?
LIBERTY:
A SONG.
STICK A TUNE ON IT
♪ RADISHES, RADISHES,
NOT SO SWEET; ♪
♪ RED AND ROUND
GROSS TO EAT. ♪
♪ THEY HAVE POWER
AND CRUEL LITTLE VOICES. ♪
♪ I RUN DEGRASSI, ♪
♪ YOU HAVE NO CHOICES. ♪
NO, IT'S PERFECT.
I'LL FINISH IT TONIGHT,
WE'LL SING IT TOMORROW,
AND WE'LL SHOW RADITCH
WHAT AN IDIOT HE'S BEING.
WE'LL BE REBELS.
REBELS WHO SING.
THERE YOU GO.
SALLY:
TELL AUNTIE SALLY.
DID HE LET YOU DOWN EASY?
IT'S KIND OF THE OPPOSITE
OF THE CONVERSATION WE HAD.
SO YOU'RE
STILL TOGETHER?
I DON'T KNOW.
CRAIG ASKED ME
TO MARRY HIM.
OKAY...
DID YOU SAY YES?
I SAID MORE LIKE NO.
BUT I THOUGHT THAT
YOU LOVED HIM.
I DO.
I DO LOVE HIM.
WHERE IS MY PHONE?
I NEED MY PHONE.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO TELL HIM?
(PHONE RINGS)
(LIGHT SHATTERS)
(PICTURE SHATTERS)
(PHONE RINGS)
(CRASHING AND BANGING)