PAIGE:
SOMEONE TELL ME
I'M HALLUCINATING.
EMMA:
WHO IS HE?
SPINNER:
REMEMBER OUR FRIEND
TERRI MACGREGOR?
THE GIRL WHO WAS
IN A COMA LAST YEAR?
PAIGE:
HE'S THE PSYCHO
WHO PUT HER THERE.
HIS NAME'S RICK.
HER EX.
HE USED TO BEAT HER.
YEAH, AND HE'S YOUR
NEW CLASSMATE, EMMA.
HE STARTS TENTH GRADE
TOMORROW.
WE HAVE TO DO
SOMETHING.
I KNOW,
LET'S ADOPT A DOLPHIN.
TRAIN HIM TO DEFEND US
FROM RICK.
EMMA:
OR WE COULD TALK
TO MR. RADITCH.
SURE.
ME AND MARCO CAN HANDLE THAT
WITHOUT YOU.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be The best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
MALE FIGURE:
TAKE MY HAND, MANNY.
NOW PULL.
(FART)
OH! (LAUGH)
I COULD NOT RESIST.
AGH! THAT WAS A CLASSIC!
THANKS.
SO YOU'RE SURE
YOUR DAD WON'T MIND US
USING HIS HOT TUB
LIKE THIS?
SOMETIMES MANNY,
YOU JUST HAVE TO SAY
WHAT THE HECK.
YOU KNOW WHO
LOVES HOT TUBS?
EMMA NELSON.
NO.
EMMA LIVES FOR STABBING YOU
IN THE BACK,
RIPPING OUT YOUR HEART,
AND STOMPING IT
BLOODLESS
WITH HER POINTY
BALLERINA FEET.
TO TENTH GRADE.
(GOOFING AROUND)
WE'RE GONNA BE SIXTEEN
THIS YEAR.
TO THE FUTURE.
TO GROWING UP,
AND TO LEAVING CHILDISH
THINGS BEHIND.
TO LEAVING CHILDISH
DANIEL VAN ZANDT!
THAT'S MOM'S
IRONING BOARD!
DANNY:
IT WAS.
NOW IT'S A DIVING BOARD.
YOU GOTTA THINK
OUTSIDE THE BOX.
JT:
NOW, DIVING FOR CANADA,
IN THE SEXY RED TRUNKS
JAMES TIBERIUS YORKE!
(GASP)
(LAUGHS)
LOOK! IT'S A STACK
OF DIMES!
"I ALWAYS KNEW YOU WERE
A SMART BOY, MARCO."
CAN YOU EVEN BELIEVE
HE SAID THAT?
EMMA:
WOW, YOU GUYS REALLY
HANDLED RADITCH.
RICK:
MARCO. PAIGE.
SPINNER. JIMMY.
EXCUSE ME,
I'VE GOT TO GET BY.
EMMA, STEP ASIDE.
EMMA:
WE DON'T WANT HIM HERE,
MR. RADITCH.
THIS ISN'T ONE OF YOUR
LITTLE CRUSADES, EMMA.
THIS IS SERIOUS.
I'M WARNING YOU.
STAY OUT OF IT.
SO WHAT'RE WE DOING
FRIDAY NIGHT?
YOU, ME, A COUCH?
A ROMANTIC DVD?
UH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK I MIGHT BE BUSY.
OH.
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
IT'S JUST YOU'VE
BEEN KIND OF DISTANT
SINCE THE HOT TUB PARTY
AND UH...
IT'S NOT MY...
YOU KNOW?
NO, NO.
THAT WAS STUPID
AND EMBARRASSING.
YOU MUST FEEL AWFUL.
NOTHING A KISS
CAN'T CURE.
CRAIG, HI.
HI.
SORRY TO INTERRUPT.
NO. IT'S OKAY.
YOU WEREN'T INTERRUPTING
ANYTHING.
SO HOW WAS YOUR SUMMER?
NOTHING SPECIAL.
YOU?
SAME.
WELL,
I BETTER GET GOING.
BYE.
OKAY.
BYE CRAIG.
NICE TO SEE YOU TOO.
HEY MANNY,
I'M STALKER CRAIG.
CAN I LURK AROUND
WHILE YOU KISS JT?
DANNY:
I'D LURK TOO.
MANNY'S SMOKIN'.
MAYBE MANNY'S STILL
HOT FOR HIM.
PLEASE.
TOBY:
LOOK, JT, IN FOUR MONTHS,
YOU AND MANNY HAVE BARELY
EVEN KISSED.
DON'T YOU THINK
SOMETHING'S WRONG?
CRAIG, MANO A MANO?
MANNY IS MY GIRLFRIEND.
OKAY.
AND I NEED YOU
TO RESPECT THAT.
I DO. WHATEVER.
JT:
IT'S JUST THAT, YOU KNOW,
SOMETIMES YOU HANG...
DOWN AND IT'S-
I MEAN AROUND.
SOMETIMES YOU
HANG AROUND.
WHAT'RE YOU
LOOKING AT?
TALKING ABOUT?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT?
YOU WERE-
YOU WERE
CHECKING OUT MY-
NO, NO, NO,
I WASN'T!
WHAT?!
NO, NO, SPINNER,
I WASN'T!
THAT'S A LIE!
THAT'S A HORRIBLE...
LIE!
PAIGE?
A MOMENT?
I WAS THINKING MAYBE
WE COULD TALK.
MAYBE BURY THE HATCHET?
YOU PUT MY FRIEND
IN A COMA.
RICK:
ONE,
I KNOW I LET MY ANGER GET
THE BETTER OF ME LAST YEAR,
AND TWO,
I'M IN COUNSELING.
I'M EVEN SEEING
MS. SAUVE.
HOW IS TERRI,
ANYWAY?
(EXHALE)
PAIGE?
PAIGE.
IF YOU TELL ANYONE
ABOUT THIS...
I WON'T.
HONEST.
THERE'S A PSYCHO
IN OUR SCHOOL, EMMA,
AND NO ONE IS DOING
A DAMN THING ABOUT IT.
BUT WE WILL.
TOGETHER.
OKAY.
BUT I'M NOT SO GOOD
AT THIS WHOLE PROTEST THING.
THAT'S OKAY,
CAUSE I AM.
JUST DON'T CALL ME
"CAUSE GIRL", OKAY?
SO, EMMA,
WHAT'RE YOU DOING NOW?
EMMA:
I WAS GOING TO GO HOME.
PAIGE:
AFTER YOU HAVE
A GREEN TEA FRAPPE
WITH ME AT THE DOT.
EMMA:
GOTTA GO SIP A FRAP
WITH PAIGE.
HAVE FUN IN YOUR HOTTUB.
MAC LIPGLASS?
IT SMELLS LIKE VANILLA.
I CAN'T.
IT'S EXPENSIVE.
NO, GO AHEAD.
HAZEL AND I ALWAYS SHARE.
WE'RE COSMETIC
COMMUNISTS.
SPINNER:
PSYCHO AT 6:00.
OH MY GOD.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
LET'S GO.
NO.
WE DON'T WANT YOU
AT DEGRASSI.
I HAVE A RIGHT
TO AN EDUCATION.
LOOK...
WHAT I DID TO TERRI
LAST YEAR WAS HORRIBLE.
BUT... I'M GETTING
THERAPY.
I'VE CHANGED.
I DON'T CARE.
FIND ANOTHER SCHOOL,
RICK,
OR YOU'LL BE SORRY.
IS THAT A THREAT?
BECAUSE MR. RADITCH
WARNED YOU.
YOU CAN'T TOUCH ME.
YEAH. MAYBE NOT
AT DEGRASSI.
PAIGE:
OKAY, SUDDENLY,
EMMA IS COOLER THAN ME.
EMMA:
SUPPORT STUDENTS
AGAINST VIOLENCE.
SHOW THE SCHOOL
WHERE YOU STAND.
PAIGE:
ALL PROCEEDS GO TO THE
DIRECTIONS WOMEN'S SHELTER.
THANKS GUYS.
EMMA:
SUPPORT STUDENTS
AGAINST VIOLENCE.
PAIGE:
THANK YOU.
SEAN:
THIS IS ABOUT RICK,
ISN'T IT?
IT'S A SILENT PROTEST.
WE WANT TO PRESSURE RICK.
MAKE HIS LIFE HELL.
WITHOUT BREAKING
ANY RULES WHATSOEVER.
EMMA'S A GENIUS.
THERE'S NOTHING RADITCH CAN DO.
ELLIE:
WOW. SUCH HEROES.
PAIGE:
WANT TO BUY A RIBBON?
EMMA:
SUPPORT STUDENTS
AGAINST VIOLENCE.
DANNY:
GUYS, CHECK IT OUT.
I HAVE THE SOLUTION
TO JT'S LITTLE PROBLEM.
A PENIS PUMP?
HOW DID YOU BUY THIS?
WELL, I DIDN'T.
GUNTHER VON EISENSTADT DID.
TAKE IT OUT.
LOOK, NOT OUT HERE.
DANNY:
THE GUY SAID IT'LL TURN
YOUR GARTER SNAKE
INTO AN ANACONDA.
JT:
I'M NOT PUTTING MY THING
IN THERE.
IT'S A SNAKE.
SNAKES BITE.
DON'T BE STUPID.
IT'S DECORATION.
LET'S SEE
HOW THIS THING WORKS.
STEP ONE.
INSERT MEMBER INTO TUB?
TUB?
WE DON'T HAVE A TUB.
THEY MEAN TUBE.
ALL:
OH. (REALIZING)
(SQUEAKY NOISE)
ALL:
(CHUCKLE)
TOBY:
STEP TWO.
USE HAND-PUP
TO MAKE FINE SUCTION.
WHO WROTE THIS?
FORGET THE INSTRUCTIONS.
YOUR WANG GOES IN THE TUBE,
THEN YOU PUMP.
JT:
OKAY, OKAY.
I GOT IT. I GOT IT.
UH... CRAIG,
CRAIG:
YOU DON'T HAVE TO EXPLAIN.
REALLY.
♪♪♪
SIT SOMEWHERE ELSE,
PUNK.
(APPLAUSE)
SPINNER:
OKAY, SO UH...
MS. KWAN HAS ASKED US
TO READ A VERSE
THAT SPEAKS TO OUR HEARTS
AND THIS VERSE
BY KID ELRICK SPEAKS TO MINE.
"I WANTS ME TO FIND
A GIRL TO LOVE
A GIRL WIT WEALTH AND CLASS
BUT MOST OF ALL,
I WANTS ME A GIRL
WITH A BOOTYLICIOUS-"
ENOUGH, GAVIN.
TAKE YOUR SEAT.
OKAY, WHO'S NEXT?
RICK:
MAY I?
I'D LIKE TO READ YOU SOME
THOUGHTS FROM MAHATMA GANDHI.
"THE WEAK CAN NEVER FORGIVE.
FORGIVENESS IS THE ATTRIBUTE
OF THE STRONG."
IT IS THE QUALITY OF THE BRAVE,
NOT THE COWARDLY..."
KWAN:
GAVIN. PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE NOW!
NOW!
(BELL RINGS)
JT:
DANNY, THE COBRA HAS LANDED.
I JUST WENT FOR A WALK
WITH THE KING.
THE JAM,
DID IT WORK?
I THINK SO.
WELL, LET HER
BE THE JUDGE.
JT'S GONNA COME
OVER HERE.
I KNOW IT.
WHY WON'T HE LEAVE
ME ALONE?
BECAUSE HE'S YOUR
BOYFRIEND?
LOOK, MANNY, IF THAT'S
HOW YOU FEEL ABOUT HIM
THEN YOU NEED
TO BREAK UP.
NO, I CAN'T.
IT'LL KILL HIM.
BUT YOU CAN'T GO ON
LIKE THIS.
JUST SIT HIM DOWN
TONIGHT AND DO IT.
JT:
HEY.
HI.
I WAS WONDERING IF MAYBE
YOU WANTED TO COME OVER
TO MY PLACE.
AFTER SCHOOL?
MANNY:
UM...
YEAH.
OKAY.
ONE, IT'LL ONLY TAKE
A MINUTE.
TWO,
IT'S TO GIVE YOU THIS.
IT'S A CHEQUE.
I CAN'T TAKE YOUR MONEY,
RICK.
THE WHOLE RIBBON CAMPAIGN
IS ABOUT YOU.
$500.00?
$554 DOLLARS
AND 16 CENTS
TO BE EXACT.
I'D DONATE MORE
BUT IT'S ALL I HAVE.
YOU CAN'T BUY FORGIVENESS,
RICK.
IT'S AN ANONYMOUS DONATION.
NO ONE NEEDS TO KNOW
BUT YOU.
ALEX:
TOO LATE.
NOBODY WANTS
YOUR GUILT-MONEY.
ALEX, LISTEN TO ME-
OR WHAT, FREAK?
ARE YOU GONNA PUT ME
IN A COMA, TOO?
EMMA:
ALEX, CAN I HAVE THE CHEQUE,
PLEASE?
NICE.
REAL NICE, ALEX.
MAYBE IF YOU CARED
ABOUT THE CAUSE...
WHAT DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT IT?
YOU EVER ICE
YOUR MOM'S LIP?
BANDAGE HER UP?
LAY AWAKE AT NIGHT
LISTENING TO HER CRY?
DIDN'T THINK SO.
OH! MY GOD.
(KNOCKING)
ENTRE.
WHAT HAPPENED IN HERE?
OH, NOTHING.
I JUST MADE IT
A LITTLE COZIER.
ARE, ARE YOU NERVOUS?
NO. NOT AT ALL.
UM...
YOUR LIPS
ARE KINDA SWEATY.
OH, SORRY.
I GUESS I AM
KIND OF NERVOUS.
I HAVE TO GO
TO THE BATHROOM.
OH, ALL RIGHT.
WELL, NO RUSH.
I GUESS, I COULD USE
A MINUTE TO FRESHEN UP.
SUCK IT UP.
YOU CAN DO THIS.
AGH! I CAN EXPLAIN.
PAIGE:
DID YOU SEE HEATHER SINCLAIR'S
EYEBROWS?
TRAGICALLY OVER-PLUCKED.
EMMA:
THEY SHOULD CONFISCATE HER
TWEEZERS OR SOMETHING.
PAIGE:
HEY! WHAT IS HE DOING HERE
AGAIN.
HE PROBABLY CAME TO SEE
HIS NEW CRUSH -
EMMA.
PAIGE:
WHAT'S SHE TALKING ABOUT?
NOTHING.
RICK TALKED TO ME.
IT WAS NO BIG DEAL.
DIDN'T SEEM THAT WAY
TO ME.
IF YOU'RE STARTING
TO WIMP OUT
AND FEEL SORRY
FOR THAT PSYCHO...
I'M NOT.
HONEST.
AFTERNOON, EMMA.
(LAUGHING)
THAT'S IT.
IT'S ON!
EMMA:
LET HIM GO!
ALEX:
YOU STARTED THIS, CAUSE GIRL.
LET'S GO.
WHAT'RE YOU GOING
TO DO?
HURT ME?
ONE, VIOLENCE
IS NEVER THE ANSWER.
TWO,
WE DON'T CARE.
(PAINED GRUNT)
OOPS.
WHO WANTS THE NEXT SHOT?
SPINNER?
ALEX:
ME.
RIBBON CAMPAIGN'S OVER,
EMMA.
YEAH?
SO IS THIS.
JT:
MANNY!
MANNY:
GO AWAY, JT.
JT:
WILL YOU LET ME EXPLAIN?
I WAS JUST TRYING
TO LIVE UP TO CRAIG.
WHAT?
I SAW HIM
IN THE LOCKER ROOM...
NAKED.
AND IT BECAME
OBVIOUS TO ME THAT...
HE HAS SOMETHING
THAT I DON'T.
YOU KNOW WHAT, JT?
CRAIG DOES HAVE
SOMETHING YOU DON'T.
MATURITY.
AND I DON'T MEAN
HIS SIZE.
I MEAN THE WAY HE ACTS.
YOU'RE ALWAYS FARTING
AND JOKING AROUND.
WELL, I'M SORRY.
JUST GIVE ME ANOTHER
CHANCE, OKAY?
I CAN CHANGE.
NO.
JT, I'M SORRY.
IT'S OVER.
NICE GLASSES.
THEY'RE FROM
SIXTH GRADE.
I WANTED TO
THANK YOU.
WELL DON'T.
THINGS GOT OUT OF HAND
AND I STOPPED IT.
IT DOESN'T MEAN
I LIKE YOU
AND IT DOESN'T MEAN
WE'RE FRIENDS.
BUT...
RICK, WHY DID YOU
COME BACK HERE?
I LIKE IT AT DEGRASSI.
WELL, I USED TO.
I WAS HORRIBLE...
BUT I'VE CHANGED.
ALL THOSE PEOPLE
WHO HATE ME,
I WANT TO LET THEM SEE
WHO I REALLY AM,
SHOW THEM HOW WRONG
THEY ARE.
WELL...
THEY'RE NOT INTERESTED,
RICK.
THEY WILL BE.
SOMEDAY.