(LIFT WHIRS AS IT'S LOWERED)
(CHEERING)
HEYLA.
MY BOYFRIEND'S BACK.
PAIGE:
I KNOW.
THIS IS
SO SONG WORTHY.
OH.
HI.
WOW.
THANKS, YOU GUYS.
AND THANKS FOR NOT MAKING
A BIG DEAL OUT OF IT.
HAZEL TRIED
TO STOP US.
MARCO:
EMPHASIS ON TRIED.
EVERYONE WAS REALLY EXCITED
TO HAVE YOU BACK.
EVERYONE?
OKAY.
WHO'S RAMPING IT WITH ME?
MARCO:
LET'S GO.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
HEY.
UM, LISTEN ABOUT THE...
HOSPITAL.
WHEELS. CHAIR.
IT'S A WHEEL CHAIR.
GAWK ALL YOU WANT,
IT'S NOT GOING AWAY.
UM, DUDE...
I, I WOULD HAVE COME,
BUT THINGS GOT CRAZY BUSY
AROUND HERE.
YOU KNOW HOW IT IS.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I UNDERSTAND.
I PROBABLY SHOULD HAVE
BEEN THERE FOR YOU
INSTEAD OF AT THE HOSPITAL
GETTING A BULLET REMOVED
FROM MY SPINE.
MY BAD.
I'M SORRY, OKAY?
I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY
OR HOW TO ACT.
I SUCK.
SIT DOWN.
AT THIS ANGLE
I CAN SEE UP YOUR NOSE.
NOT GOOD.
YOU SHOULD HATE ME.
THAT TAKES TOO MUCH
ENERGY.
I GOT OTHER THINGS
TO DEAL WITH,
LIKE HOOKING UP SOME
PHAT RIMS FOR THE RIDE.
SIMPSON:
JIMMY BROOKS IS IN THE HOUSE!
HEY, WHAT'S UP,
MAN?
HEY.
YOU GONNA HELP ME
KEEP THAT GUY IN LINE?
JIMMY:
YEAH.
OKAY.
♪ I'M A CHEATER ♪
♪ I'M A LOSER ♪
♪ I FEEL LIKE A FALLEN USER ♪
♪ IN A WORLD
SO FULL OF PAIN... ♪
YOUR BINDERS,
SIR.
(UNINTELLIGABLE CHATTER)
♪ I'M ASHAMED
TO HEAR MY NAME ♪
♪ NEXT TO YOURS, ♪
♪ I'M ASHAMED
TO HEAR MY NAME. ♪
♪ YOU'VE GOT THE BIG HOUSE, ♪
♪ DRIVING YOUR FANCY CAR, ♪
♪ LIVING ON A QUIET STREET, ♪
♪ WHO DO YOU THINK YOU ARE? ♪
♪ YOU SEE YOURSELF
AS A SOCIAL DISEASE ♪
♪ WAY OUT IN THE SUBURBS,
THE SUBURBS. ♪
♪ YOU SHOULD TRADE IN
THAT SMILE ♪
♪ WITH A HEART THAT HASN'T BEEN
AROUND HERE IN A WHILE... ♪
OH COACH, SIR!
UM, AFTER,
AFTER THE GAME TODAY
I HAVE AN IDEA.
YOUR LIPS TASTE
LIKE SWEET JELLY.
HEY LIBERTY,
HOW'S YOUR MONO?
LIBERTY:
BRAVO, DANIEL.
YOU'VE DISCOVERED
HUMOUR.
SO JT,
THE BOARDING PARK
AWAITS.
AS DOES
THE HOT TUB.
A PERFECT
105 FAHRENHEIT,
40.56 DEGREES CELSIUS.
JUST CHECKED.
DID YOU CHECK
THE CHLORINE LEVEL?
IT'S BROMINE,
MY LITTLE ROTWEILER.
STILL NOT STRONG
ENOUGH TO KILL
WHATEVER FUNGUS
IS GROWING ON YOU.
KNOW WHAT?
MY SHORTS DOUBLE
AS A BATHING SUIT.
DANNY:
JT!
ROLLING ON CEMENT
WITH YOU;
ROLLING IN THE WATER
WITH YOUR SISTER.
IF DAD CATCHES YOU
IN THERE TOGETHER-
LIBERTY:
OH, BUT HE WON'T.
BECAUSE
IF HE COMES HOME,
YOU'LL GIVE US
A SIGNAL.
SOMETHING OBNOXIOUS,
YOU KNOW,
LIKE A BARK.
(BUZZER)
(CHEERING)
ARMSTRONG:
ALL RIGHT, BEFORE WE HEAD
TO THE PLAYOFFS,
THE TEAM WOULD LIKE
TO THANK SOMEONE
WHO HELPED GET THEM THERE.
LET'S HAVE A BIG
ROUND OF APPLAUSE
FOR JIMMY BROOKS!
(APPLAUSE)
SPINNER:
ALL RIGHT.
YOUR NAME'S ALREADY
ON HERE TWICE,
BUT FROM NOW ON,
DEGRASSI'S MVP BASKETBALL
AWARD WILL BE KNOWN AS...
THE JIMMY BROOKS TROPHY.
(CHEERING AND CLAPPING)
WOOOOW!
JIMMY:
WOW!
THIS IS DEFINITELY
A SURPRISE.
I GUESS,
ALL I CAN SAY IS
WE GO FOR MVP NUMBER 3
NEXT YEAR, RIGHT?
(CHEERING)
GO PANTHERS!
GOOD AFTERNOON,
DANIEL.
YOUR SISTER AROUND?
SHE'S OUT BACK,
SOAKING ALL HER
PROBLEMS AWAY.
MM-HMM.
WOOF.
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME
MY BUTT WAS SO BIG?
BECAUSE I LIKE
YOUR BUTT.
MR. VAN ZANDT:
OUT! NOW!
WE WERE JUST...
JT, GO HOME.
JT'S ONE OF MY OLDEST
FRIENDS!
MR. VAN ZANDT:
HE'S ALSO A TEENAGE BOY.
YOU WANT TO SEE JT AGAIN?
WAIT UNTIL YOU'RE TWENTY.
I WAS TRYING
TO DO A LAY-UP.
BETTER WATCH
THE TRAVELING
IF YOU WANNA BE BACK
NEXT YEAR, RIGHT?
THERE WON'T BE
A NEXT YEAR, SPIN.
MY BASKETBALL CAREER,
MY WHOLE FUTURE...
IT'S GONE.
JUST LIKE THESE
TWO PIECES OF MEAT.
DUDE, DON'T.
LOOK, STUCK IN A BED
FOR THREE MONTHS,
YOU CAN'T STOP THINKING...
ABOUT GETTING BETTER,
MAN,
AND YOU WILL.
ABOUT RICK,
AND HOW I RODE HIM
JUST AS HARD AS YOU GUYS.
EVEN HARDER.
YEAH, BUT YOU DIDN'T
SET UP THE PAINT.
I KNOW.
BUT THAT DOESN'T CHANGE
ANYTHING, DOES IT?
RICK PUT ME
IN THIS CHAIR FOR LIFE.
FOR LIFE!
SOMETIMES I JUST WISH
HE'D HAD BETTER AIM.
FINISH THE JOB.
YOU DON'T MEAN THAT.
HOW DO YOU KNOW
WHAT I MEAN?
ARE YOU IN THE CHAIR?
HUH?
DO YOU WAKE UP EVERY MORNING
THINKING YOU CAN WALK,
AND THEN REMEMBERING
THAT YOU WILL NEVER EVER
WALK AGAIN?!
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
IT'S MINE.
IN THE BATHROOM...
AFTER, AFTER WE DUMPED
THAT STUFF ON RICK,
ME AND JAY...
TOLD HIM
YOU WERE BEHIND IT.
AND THEN HE SHOT ME.
GIRL:
THERE HE IS.
BOY:
SUCH A JERK.
YOU ACTUALLY
SHOWED UP TODAY.
NOBODY WANTS
TO SEE YOU, SPIN.
YOU'VE DONE
ENOUGH DAMAGE.
EXACTLY.
AND NOW I HAVE
TO FIX IT.
GO FIX IT
SOME PLACE ELSE.
FAR AWAY FROM JIMMY.
MARCO:
AND THAT INCLUDES THE PARTY
TONIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
MAKE OTHER PLANS.
MANNY...
GIRL:
WHO IS HE GOING
TO TALK TO NOW.
GIRL 2:
NOBODY.
YOU KNOW IT'S AGAINST
THE CODE
FOR A GUY TO HOOK UP
WITH HIS BEST FRIEND'S
SISTER.
THE CODE?
SOMEBODY CUE
THE LAUGH TRACK.
FINE.
SHE'S MY SISTER,
AND YOU DON'T HAVE
MY PERMISSION
TO GO OUT WITH HER.
EXCUSE ME?
SHE'S THE SMARTEST
PERSON IN THE SCHOOL,
AND YOU DON'T EVEN
HAVE AN I.Q.
YOU DON'T DESERVE HER.
THAT'S TOO BAD
BECAUSE THE SMARTEST
GIRL IN THE SCHOOL
THINKS I DO.
I GUESS YOU'LL NEED
HER HELP
TO READ THE INSTRUCTIONS
TO YOUR PENIS PUMP!
BOY:
WHAT?!
ALL:
(GIGGLING)
DANNY, I SWEAR...
(STUDENTS CALL OUT
ENCOURAGEMENT)
(STUDENTS LAUGHING
AND YELLING)
JT:
AAHHHHH!
LIBERTY:
DANNY!
DANNY...
LIBERTY, HE-
LIBERTY:
HE'S BLEEDING.
MY BROTHER'S BLEEDING
BECAUSE OF YOU.
I THOUGHT THIS PLACE WAS
A MADHOUSE AFTER SCHOOL.
WHERE'S THE GANG?
WHO'S A GUY GOTTA
BRIBE AROUND HERE
TO GET SOME SERVICE.
YOU KNOW,
CALL ME PSYCHIC,
BUT I CALLED IT.
YOU HAD TO OPEN
YOUR TRAP, DIDN'T YOU?
JIMMY DESERVED
TO KNOW THE TRUTH.
OH, COOL.
SO TELL ME,
BEING AN OUTCAST?
EVERYONE HATING YOU?
DOES THAT MAKE YOU
FEEL ANY BETTER?
'CAUSE IF YOU
WANT TO BE PUNISHED,
I CAN SLAP YOU
AROUND MYSELF.
NEW MANAGER:
HEY! HEY! HEY!
IF YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO ORDER?
TIME TO LEAVE.
OKAY?
LET'S GO.
RIGHT NOW.
EASY.
I DIDN'T COME HERE
TO FIGHT.
I JUST WANTED TO
INTRODUCE YOU TO MY FRIENDS.
BECAUSE BUDDY,
YOU NEED FRIENDS.
THIS GUY?
HE'S NASTY.
TASTES LIKE FIRE.
RUBS PEOPLE THE WRONG WAY.
THIS GUY HERE?
WELL, SWEET, REFRESHING...
BUT WHEN THESE
TWO GET TOGETHER?
BAD NEWS.
KIND OF LIKE
YOU AND ME.
FIGURE WE OUTLAWS
MIGHT AS WELL TRY
TO HAVE A GOOD TIME.
DANNY:
LIBERTY?
NO TRESPASSING!
BECAUSE OF YOUR STUPID
LITTLE BOY-CRUSH,
YOU RUINED EVERYTHING.
LIBERTY, HE'S NOT
WHAT YOU THINK.
HE'S JUST JT!
A NON-STOP
FARTING HORN-DOG.
HE WAS MY BOYFRIEND.
SO, JIMMY'S PARTY?
DID YOU LOSE YOUR
INVITATION?
NO, MAN.
THEY ALL HATE ME.
HEY,
MY PHILOSOPHY?
THEY CAN ALL
GO TO HELL.
SPINNER:
YEAH.
BUT THEY WEREN'T
YOUR FRIENDS TO BEGIN WITH.
IT'S THIS WHOLE
BLAME THING, THOUGH.
RICK IS THE BAD GUY.
BUT NOW THAT HE'S GONE,
EVERYONE'S LOOKING
TO BLAME SOMEONE ELSE.
YEAH, MAN.
IT'S LIKE,
IT'S LIKE I'M THE GUY
WHO BROUGHT
THE GUN TO SCHOOL.
I'M, I'M THE GUY
WHO SHOT JIMMY, RIGHT?
I'M THE CRIMINAL.
IT'S NOT FAIR.
YOU WANT SOME CHEESE
WITH THAT WHINE?
OR YOU GONNA DO
SOMETHING ABOUT IT?
THINK I JUST FOUND
MY INVITATION.
(LAUGHS)
(LAUGHTER)
(CRAIG SINGS KARAOKE)
♪ 'CAUSE I'M SKIPPING
THE WORDS ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I DON'T KNOW THEM ♪
♪ TAKING CARE OF BUSINESS ♪
♪ EVERY DAY! ♪
(LIGHT BULB SHATTERS)
YOU LOST?
SPINNER:
OH, JIMMY.
LISTEN,
I WISH, I WISH NONE OF THAT
EVER HAPPENED, JIMMY.
YOU'RE DRUNK?
JUST HOW CAN I GET YOU
TO STOP HATING ME?
SPINNER?
YOU SHOULD REALLY GO.
CAN'T YOU
TAKE A HINT?
JUST CHEW ME OUT!
BITE MY HEAD OFF!
I DON'T CARE!
JUST, TELL ME.
PLEASE!
CRAIG,
IT'S YOUR SONG STILL.
OKAY.
(MUSIC BEGINS TO PLAY)
MARCO:
SPINNER!
SPINNER,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU GUYS DON'T
WANT ME HERE?
I'M GOING HOME.
COME ON, SPIN.
YOU'RE DRUNK, ALL RIGHT?
THE NEXT THING YOU KNOW
YOU'RE IN JAIL.
OR THE HOSPITAL
OR THE MORGUE.
I DON'T CARE.
CRAIG!
CRAIG:
SPINNER!
GET OUT OF THE CAR!
SPINNER,
GET OUT OF THE CAR.
MARCO:
SPIN, COME ON.
SPIN, DON'T.
COME ON, SPINNER,
DON'T BE STUPID!
(TIRES SQUEAL)
(REVS THE ENGINE)
MOVE JIMMY!
I MEAN IT.
LOOK, I DON'T FEEL
SORRY FOR YOU,
IF THAT'S WHAT
YOU WANT, OKAY?
I WANT MY FRIEND BACK.
WHEN HAVE YOU EVER
TREATED ME LIKE A FRIEND?
WHEN YOU LIED TO RICK?
WHEN YOU TOLD ME
ABOUT IT?
YOU NEEDED TO KNOW.
NO. YOU NEEDED TO MAKE
YOURSELF FEEL BETTER.
WHY DON'T YOU FOR ONCE
JUST THINK ABOUT SOMEBODY
OTHER THAN SPINNER.
OR YOU KNOW WHAT?
JUST GO DRIVE OFF
A BRIDGE.
I DON'T CARE.
I DON'T.
YOU'RE DEAD TO ME
ALREADY.
KEYS.
(CRYING)
LIBERTY:
I'M NOT IN THE MOOD
FOR YOUR HULLABALOO, DANNY.
THIS BETTER BE GOOD.
(GROAN)
WAIT.
JT DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
IT'S MY FAULT.
I STARTED THE FIGHT.
HE DIDN'T HAVE
TO FINISH IT.
MR. VAN ZANDT:
LIBERTY?
HEY, DANNY.
WHERE'S YOUR SISTER?
STUDENT COUNCIL MEETING.
SHE ALREADY LEFT.
MR. VAN ZANDT:
OH?
I COULD HAVE SWORN
I HEARD YOU TWO JUST TALKING.
WHO WERE YOU TALKING TO?
JUST PRACTICING.
ORAL PRESENTATION TODAY.
OH. WELL, KEEP IT UP.
AND DON'T BE LATE
FOR SCHOOL.
'KAY.
COAST IS CLEAR,
GUYS.
OH, GROSS!
I GIVE UP.
GAVIN?
IF YOU'D LIKE TO TALK
SOME OTHER TIME, I-
NO. NO.
I'M READY NOW.
(HEAVY SIGH)
I BULLIED RICK.
A LOT.
AND THE "WHACK
YOUR BRAIN" CONTEST -
THE PAINT
AND FEATHERS THING?
YEAH.
IT WAS MY IDEA.
IS THERE ANYONE ELSE
I NEED TO TALK TO ABOUT THAT?
WELL?
(CLEARS HIS THROAT)
JAY.
JAY HOGART.
HE WAS IN ON IT TOO.
SARAH,
CAN YOU PLEASE PULL
JAY HOGART
OUT OF CLASS?
PLEASE HAVE HIM
WAIT FOR ME.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHERE TO BEGIN.
THIS IS BEYOND ANYTHING
YOU'VE EVER DONE
AT THIS SCHOOL.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
AND IF YOU HAVE
TO SUSPEND ME-
SUSPEND?!
A BOY DIED.
ANOTHER ONE IS CONFINED
TO A WHEELCHAIR
FOR WHAT MIGHT BE
THE REST OF HIS LIFE.
I'M SORRY.
I KNOW YOU'RE SORRY.
BUT IT DOES NOT CHANGE
WHAT YOU DID.
LOOK, PLEASE GO
TO YOUR LOCKER,
PACK YOUR THINGS,
AND I'LL NOTIFY
YOUR PARENTS.
UM, WHEN DO I
GET TO COME BACK?
GAVIN, WE HAVE ZERO
TOLERANCE FOR BULLYING.
AND I HAVE NO CHOICE.
I'M EXPELLING YOU.
(CRYING)