SEAN:
WE'RE ON THE FRONT PAGE
OF SOME.
ISN'T THAT COOL?
ELLIE:
YEAH, IT'S MONDAY
AND THEY ARE STILL WRITING
ABOUT THE SHOOTING.
RADITCH:
TODAY IS A DAY OF REFLECTION.
COUNSELORS WILL BE AVAILABLE.
STUDENTS CAN TALK,
EXPRESS THEIR FEELINGS.
AFTER WHICH,
IT'S IMPORTANT THAT WE GET
THINGS BACK TO NORMAL.
SEAN CAMERON!
IF I COULD
JUST TALK TO YOU
FOR TWO MINUTES
ON CAMERA?
ELLIE:
C'MON, SEAN.
YOUR BOYFRIEND'S
A HERO.
ALL I WANT TO KNOW
IS WHAT IT FEELS LIKE?
UH...
GUESS I'M ABOUT
TO FIND OUT.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best that I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
PAIGE:
I FEEL TOTALLY HELPLESS.
WHAT IF JIMMY
NEVER RECOVERS?
WHAT IF HE NEVER
WALKS AGAIN?
SAUVE:
JIMMY NEEDS HOPE.
YOU CAN GIVE HIM THAT.
SIMPSON:
THERE IS NO EXCUSE, NONE,
FOR WHAT RICK DID.
BUT LABELING HIM A MONSTER
IS NOT GOING TO HELP US
UNDERSTAND
WHY IT HAPPENED.
TOBY:
RICK WAS BULLIED.
REALLY BAD.
COME ON, TOBY.
DON'T MAKE RICK THE VICTIM.
I'M NOT.
JUST...
THINK HOW HE MUST'VE FELT.
SIMPSON:
DO YOU EVER FEEL THAT DESPERATE
OR THAT ANGRY?
YOU NEED TO TALK TO AN ADULT
BEFORE IT REACHES
A CRISIS POINT.
WHAT IF NOBODY
LISTENS?
THEN KEEP TRYING.
SOMEBODY WILL.
CRAIG:
SO WHAT?
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO RAT?
SIMPSON:
IT'S NOT ABOUT GETTING PEOPLE
IN TROUBLE, CRAIG.
IT'S ABOUT GETTING THEM
AND YOU OUT OF TROUBLE.
MARCO:
I AM... SHAKEN.
I WANT TO TURN BACK TIME.
I NEED...
I NEED TO BELIEVE
THAT LIFE'S BETTER THAN THIS.
SAUVE:
THANK YOU, MARCO.
OKAY, WHO'S NEXT?
SEAN.
LET'S HEAR FROM YOU.
JUST REPEAT THE THREE PHRASES...
I AM, I WANT, I NEED.
GO AHEAD.
(MUMBLES) STUPID.
I AM SEAN CAMERON.
I WANT SOME
CHOCOLATE MILK
AND I NEED THIS STUPIDITY
TO BE OVER.
SAUVE:
FINE, NO MASK.
BUT I'D STILL LIKE
TO HEAR FROM YOU.
I WAS FACED
WITH A SITUATION,
I DEALT WITH IT.
END OF STORY.
IT'S PERFECTLY NORMAL
FOR THOSE WHO WITNESS VIOLENCE
TO HAVE FEELINGS OF GUILT,
SEAN.
GUILT?
I STOPPED RICK
FROM KILLING PEOPLE.
I SLEEP LIKE A BABY.
BUT SOMEONE DID DIE,
SEAN.
RICK.
LUCK OF THE DRAW.
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
SIMPSON:
SEAN. COME ON IN.
GLAD YOU'RE HERE TODAY,
AND THAT YOU'RE NOT GOING
THROUGH THIS ALONE.
SEAN:
THROUGH WHAT?
BULLET MISSED ME.
EVERYONE'S TALKING
ABOUT WHAT A HERO YOU ARE
AND HEY, I'M IN THE "SEAN'S
A HERO" CAMP MYSELF.
BUT YOU WERE INVOLVED
IN SOMETHING... HORRIBLE.
I HOPE YOUR FRIENDS
UNDERSTAND THAT.
EVERYONE'S BEEN GREAT,
MR. S.
AND ARE YOU LETTING
YOURSELF DEAL?
EMMA: (CRYING)
DAD, I CAN'T TAKE IT!
EVERYBODY'S STARING AT ME
EVERYWHERE I GO.
SEAN...
SEAN.
SEAN, I NEVER GOT TO SAY,
YOU SAVED MY LIFE.
WE ALL NEED SOME CLOSURE,
SEAN.
THAT'S WHAT TODAY
IS ALL ABOUT.
IT'S ONLY AN HOUR,
JAY.
60 MINUTES OF SAUVE
GOING BLAH BLAH BLAH,
IT'S OKAY TO CRY.
RIGHT.
YOU MAY NOT NEED TO TALK
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED,
BUT I DO.
YEAH? WELL, JUST WATCH
WHAT YOU DO TALK ABOUT.
ELLIE:
YOU DIDN'T TRY.
MASKS?
ELLIE, C'MON.
SO DO AN INTERVIEW.
YOU KNOW I'M PUTTING TOGETHER
A PIECE ON YOU, SEAN?
DO WHAT YOU WANT.
WE DON'T GET CABLE.
RACHEL:
SEAN'S MOM DOES.
I INTERVIEWED
HER YESTERDAY.
SHE HAD A LOT TO SAY.
MRS. CAMERON:
WELL, SEAN'S HAD
HIS SHARE OF PROBLEMS,
BUT NOTHING COMPARED
WITH THIS KID.
RACHEL ON TV:
SO DID IT COME
AS A SURPRISE TO YOU
WHEN YOU HEARD SEAN
WAS A HERO?
WELL, HE ALWAYS WAS
A STRONG BOY, NO FEAR.
AND THAT USED TO GET HIM
INTO TROUBLE
ALL THE TIME.
BUT IT SOUNDS LIKE IT
SAVED HIM HIS LIFE THIS TIME.
RACHEL ON TV:
IT SAVED A LOT OF LIVES.
MRS. CAMERON:
YEAH.
I'M SORRY, I JUST
CAN'T STOP THINKING
WHAT IF THAT KID
HAD SHOT MY SEAN?
WHAT IF I'D NEVER GOT
TO SEE MY BABY AGAIN?
(CRYING)
OH GOD.
I MISS HIM.
I LOVE HIM SO MUCH.
JUST RUNNING THE BATTERY,
GREENPEACE.
POLLUTION FREE.
IT'S NOISE POLLUTION.
BUT THAT'S NOT
WHY I'M HERE.
HAVE YOU SEEN SEAN?
HE'S TALKING TO HER?
RACHEL:
SEAN. THEY CLEARLY LOVE YOU.
SEAN:
I'M FULL OF LOVE TODAY.
JAY:
WHOA, BUDDY!
SEAN:
SHUT UP.
MOVE, I'M DRIVING.
GET IN.
ELLIE:
JUST CALM DOWN.
SEAN:
NO.
YOU WANTED ME
TO EXPRESS MYSELF?
THIS IS ME
EXPRESSING MYSELF.
EMMA,
YOU COMING OR WHAT?
SO WHERE TO,
BAM BAM?
WASAGA BEACH.
HOME.
TOBY:
JT? DANNY?
JT:
HI.
DANNY:
BYE.
TOBY:
UM, I JUST GOT
DRACO'S QUEST II
IF YOU GUYS EVER
WANNA PLAY.
JT:
I'M TRYING TO CUT DOWN.
I WAS THERE, JT.
SO WHAT DO YOU
WANT ME TO SAY?
OKAY, I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY THAT YOU BECAME
FRIENDS WITH A PSYCHO.
YOU KNEW
WHAT RICK WAS LIKE.
I DIDN'T KNOW HE WAS GONNA
BRING A GUN TO SCHOOL.
JT:
REALLY?
♪♪♪
JAY:
IS IT A HOUSE?
IS IT A LUNCH BOX?
SEAN:
IT'S WHERE I WAS BORN.
ELLIE:
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
COOL OFF A BIT.
WE'VE BEEN DRIVING
FOR TWO HOURS.
I'M COOL.
YOU'RE NOT.
LET HIM GO,
ELLIE.
HE SHOULD HAVE DONE
THIS YEARS AGO.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
MRS. CAMERON:
HOLD YOUR HORSES.
I'M COMING.
ALL RIGHT!
SEAN?
I HEARD WHAT HAPPENED.
YEAH, I KNOW.
THAT WAS QUITE
THE PERFORMANCE.
"OH, I MISS MY BABY.
WHAT IF I NEVER
GET TO SEE HIM AGAIN?
OH, I LOVE HIM,
BOO-HOO."
OH SEAN...
NEXT INTERVIEW?
TRY TELLING THEM
THE TRUTH.
LIKE HOW YOU GAVE UP
ON ME,
HOW YOU BOOTED ME
OUT OF YOUR LIFE.
JUST STOP PLAYING THE POOR
ABANDONED MOTHER ROLE
BECAUSE NOBODY'S
BUYING IT!
ESPECIALLY NOT ME.
OKAY.
ELLIE:
IT'S LIKE A MUD BATH.
BUT IT'S COLD AND SANDY,
AND IT KINDA SMELLS LIKE FISH.
EW.
JAY:
YO, CAMERON.
SPROUT'S GETTING LOOSE.
JAY:
WHO ARE YOU CHECKING OUT?
ALL I SEE IS SOME GUY.
THAT'S TYLER BISHOP.
EMMA:
HE'S THE KID YOU DEAFENED.
SEAN:
IN ONE EAR.
IDIOT JUMPED ME.
THOUGHT HE WAS TOUGH.
I WAS TOUGHER.
JAY:
SO HE GOT HALF DEAF,
WHILE YOU GOT SENT TO TORONTO,
TO TRACKER,
TO STUDENT WELFARE?
YOU ASK ME,
I'D SAY THIS GUY OWES YOU.
I DIDN'T KNOW JIMMY
HAD SO MANY FRIENDS.
JODIE MATENKO?
HEATHER SINCLAIR?
A LOT OF THESE
ARE FROM STRANGERS.
REALLY?
PEOPLE WHO DON'T
EVEN KNOW JIMMY
CARE ABOUT HIM.
MY OWN FRIENDS
WON'T TALK TO ME.
I-I HAVE TO GO
TO RICK'S VISITATION TONIGHT,
BUT I CAN'T FACE HIS MOM.
WHAT ABOUT JT?
WHAT ABOUT HIM?
SO UH, WHAT'S IT GONNA COST
TO RENT ONE OF THESE THINGS?
YOU KNOW,
ONE OF THESE THINGS?
TYLER:
I NEVER THOUGHT
YOU'D BE STUPID ENOUGH
TO COME BACK HERE,
CAMERON!
ELLIE:
STOP IT! STOP IT, OKAY?
PAPERS THINK YOU'RE
SOME KIND OF HERO...
WRESTLING GUN-SLINGERS.
DIDN'T KNOW
YOU COULD READ.
SAW YOUR PICTURE.
RECOGNIZED THE EYEBROWS.
PISSED?
GO ON.
SUCKER PUNCH ME
IN THE OTHER EAR
AND FLEE TOWN.
THAT'S YOUR MOVE,
ISN'T IT?
LET'S GO.
OR DO YOU KILL AND RUN
THESE DAYS?
CAUSE THE KID DIED
THIS TIME.
DIDN'T HE, HERO?
THINK YOU'RE A HERO?
HUH? YEAH?
SIXTY BUCKS,
SIXTY MINUTES.
FREE FOR YOU,
TRAILER PARK BOY.
WOULDN'T WANT TO TAKE
YOUR LUNCH MONEY...
AGAIN.
SO, THAT WAS FUN...
MEETING TYLER.
GOOD TIMES.
HE GOT A LOT
OFF HIS CHEST.
SEAN...
WHAT?
YOUR STORIES
DON'T REALLY MESH.
SO YOU BELIEVE HIM.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
TO BELIEVE, OKAY?
I AM TRYING TO UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU'RE GOING THROUGH,
BUT YOU WON'T
EVEN TALK TO ME.
YOU WANT ME TO TALK?
FINE.
WHEN THE GUN WENT OFF
MY HAND WAS COVERED
IN WARM LIQUID.
I THOUGHT
I'D PISSED MYSELF,
BUT THEN I REALIZED
THAT I WAS DRENCHED
IN RICK'S BLOOD.
AND THEN,
AND THEN WHEN HE FELL-
SEAN...
NO.
SEAN!
YOU'RE NOT DOING
THIS TO ME.
SEAN!
EMMA:
SEAN! SEAN! SEAN!
SEAN, WAKE UP. SEAN!
(COUGHING, SPUTTERING)
ELLIE:
COME ON.
WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU NEARLY DROWNED.
TYLER SAVED YOUR LIFE.
MANNY:
JT.
JT:
MANNY, HOW ARE YOU?
MANNY:
I'M ALL RIGHT.
BETTER THAN A CERTAIN
BEST FRIEND OF YOURS.
JT:
EX-BEST FRIEND.
THAT WAS BEFORE HE JOINED FORCES
WITH HELL BOY.
WHO I KNOW IS A SUPER-HERO,
BUT WHATEVER.
TOBY'S A GEEK.
HE ALWAYS HAS BEEN.
MANNY:
OKAY, YOU OUT-GEEK THEM
ALL JAMES TIBERIUS YORKE.
BUT TOBY WAS ALWAYS
THERE FOR YOU.
TIBERIUS IS A FAMILY NAME,
ALL RIGHT?
IF YOU HADN'T DITCHED HIM
FOR WEBSTER HERE,
HE WOULD HAVE NEVER
HOOKED UP WITH RICK.
AND YOU'RE LECTURING ME
ON DITCHING PEOPLE? HM.
NOW I REMEMBER
WHY WE BROKE UP.
YOU JUST CAN'T BE
THE BIGGER MAN.
DON'T SAY IT.
SEAN?
MAYBE YOU NEED
TO SEE A DOCTOR?
I'M FINE.
JUST THINKING.
ABOUT WHAT?
EM, I'M SORRY.
FOR WHAT?
FOR LAST YEAR,
YOU KNOW?
FOR EVERYTHING
I PUT YOU THROUGH.
EVERYTHING.
I'M SORRY.
ANCIENT HISTORY.
SO MAYBE WE SHOULD
GET GOING, HUH?
WE GOT A PIT STOP
TO MAKE FIRST.
MR. CAMERON:
DOOR!
MRS. CAMERON:
YOU HAVE LEGS,
DON'T YOU?
GEEZ.
SO UH... HOW LONG TILL
THE COPS GET HERE?
MRS. CAMERON:
NO, NO, NO.
SEAN, WAIT.
DON'T PLEASE.
JUST IGNORE HIM.
HE DIDN'T MEAN IT.
I'M HERE WITH FRIENDS,
DAD.
THAT'S ALL.
IT'S BEEN OVER FOUR YEARS.
NO CALLS, NO NOTHING.
NOW HERE YOU ARE,
YOU EXPECT US TO BELIEVE
IT'S JUST FOR KICKS?
WHAT I SAID
TO THAT REPORTER LADY?
IT WASN'T LIES.
I CAN'T CRY ON CUE,
SEAN.
I MEAN, WE'VE MADE
A LOT MISTAKES, BUT...
BUT SENDING YOU
TO TORONTO?
THAT WAS THE BEST THING
WE EVER DID.
HOW ELSE WAS I GONNA
KEEP YOU OUT OF JAIL?
I KNOW.
SO WHY ARE YOU BACK?
THAT KID AT SCHOOL,
HE WAS GONNA
SHOOT MY FRIEND.
SO, SO I GRABBED THE GUN...
AND IT WENT OFF.
I-I THINK-
I THINK I MIGHT'VE-
OH GOD!
I MIGHT'VE KILLED HIM.
(CRYING)
HE DIED.
IT'S OKAY, KID.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE HOME.
WE GOTCHA.
SEAN:
(SOBS) HE DIED.
(MUFFLED COMMENT)
MRS. CAMERON:
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
MR. CAMERON:
YOU'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
I-I CAN'T DO THIS.
IT'S, IT'S OKAY.
YOU CAN JUST LEAVE.
RICK'S MOM:
TOBY.
TOBE!
YOU CAME.
TOBY.
YOU WERE ALWAYS
SUCH A GOOD FRIEND.
JT:
MRS. MURRAY?
I JUST WANTED TO SAY
I'M VERY SORRY
FOR WHAT HAPPENED.
RICK'S MOM:
YOU WERE A FRIEND OF RICK'S?
IT WAS A TRAGEDY.
I'M VERY SORRY.
RICK'S MOM:
THANK YOU.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT I THOUGHT OF RICK.
IT STILL SHOULDN'T
HAVE HAPPENED.
I TOLD THEM
EVERYTHING.
LET'S GET YOU
OUT OF HERE.
ELLIE...
LOOK,
I DON'T HOW...
YOU'RE, YOU'RE STAYING,
AREN'T YOU?
SEAN, PLEASE.
I, I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU,
TOO.
BUT, ELLIE...
WELL, WHEN ARE YOU
COMING BACK?
YO CAMERON,
GET IN THE CAR.
STAYING.
I'M STAYING.
LOOK, FOR THE FIRST TIME
IN MY LIFE
I NEED TO BE HERE
WITH MY PARENTS...
TO DEAL.
YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
OKAY, MAN.
SEE YA.