SO YOUR BIG SCREEN
DEBUT, HUH?
ARE YOU NERVOUS?
YOU SEEM A LITTLE
NERVOUS.
IT'S NORMAL
WHEN YOU'RE PLANNING
A WEDDING, RIGHT?
WHAT?!
I ASKED JOEY
TO MARRY ME
AND HE SAID YES.
CONGRATULATIONS!
THAT IS
SO AMAZING!
KEVIN:
ALL RIGHT, FOLKS,
TIME TO SHOOT.
SHOOT- WHOA!
THIS IS WHY I CAME UP HERE
TO SHOOT,
SPEAKING OF WHICH,
A CHANCE TO CATCH
CANADIAN CHICKS
EMBRACING LIKE THAT.
EVEN IF THE "CHICKS"
ARE ALREADY SPOKEN FOR?
CHRISTINE,
YOU MAY BE SPOKEN FOR,
THIS ONE THOUGH...
ASKED JOEY
TO MARRY HER.
I'VE GOTTA CALL EMMA!
EXCUSE ME.
SERIOUSLY?
YEAH.
UM... WOW.
I MUST BE THE WORST KISSER
IN THE WORLD
'CAUSE...
NO. KEVIN, NO.
I JUST-
UH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M SORRY.
I'VE- I'VE GOT TO SET
THE FIRST SHOT FOR THE DAY.
SO I'LL JUST-
I'LL PEEP YOU OUT THERE.
HEY, UH... MEWES?
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
SPINNER:
JAY?
OKAY UM, I'M NOT
GETTING FREAKED OUT
BY THIS LAME
HIDE-AND-SEEK GAME.
I'M GONNA EAT
YOUR BREAKFAST, MAN.
HEY!
OOF! MY ARM.
OW!
CRAIG?
SPINNER!
GET OFF OF ME.
DUDE, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
GOING TO ENGLAND?
AFTER THE SONG'S DONE
FOR KEVIN SMITH'S MOVIE.
HE'S KINDA BENDING
THE RULES A LITTLE BIT.
HE'S LETTING ME
HANG HERE.
OH, MY EGGS
ARE DONE.
OH, NOBODY KNOWS,
OKAY?
LIPS ARE STEELED.
UM... DUDE, I JUST WANT
TO SAY ABOUT ASH
AND THE WHOLE
BAND THING...
OH, SPIN,
IT'S IN THE PAST.
IT'S LIKE...
IT'S WATER UNDER
THE BRIDGE.
OKAY.
UM... SHE WAS A GOOD
CONTRIBUTION, THOUGH.
I MEAN,
SHE KNEW HER STUFF.
NO.
SHE WAS A VIRUS.
SHE GETS HER
WAY INSIDE.
EVERYTHING'S OKAY
FOR A BIT,
THEN - BAM! -
SHE RIPS IT
ALL APART.
WELL, I'M GONNA BE
IN THE BOILER ROOM.
I GOT WORK TO DO.
BUT UH... LIPS SEALED,
MY FRIEND.
RIGHT?
YOU ARE THE ONES
WHO ARE THE FILTHY
POTTY MOUTHS!
THESE GUYS KEEP TALKING
ABOUT THE PERIODIC TABLE!
MRS. HOFFMAN,
HE WENT INTO MY PURSE,
STOLE MY TAMPONS.
AND DID...
DID THIS!
KEVIN:
UH... MRS. JOEY?
THAT'D BE YOUR LINE,
HON.
SORRY.
BRAIN-DEAD OVER HERE.
I WOULD NOT DISAGREE
WITH YOU.
CUT.
WE'LL BE GOING AGAIN,
KIDS.
UM, CAN YOU TAKE
YOUR HAND OFF MY KNEE?
WHAT? UH...
WHAT?
OH, WHAT WAS THAT
DOING THERE?
NAUGHTY!
NAUGHTY YOU!
CRAIG: (SINGING)
♪ NEVER BE A SINGLE PLACE... ♪
(TRYING TO FIND A CHORD)
♪ THERE'LL NEVER BE
A SINGLE PLACE ♪
♪ I COULDN'T SEE
YOUR FACE ♪
♪ BUT I KNOW FROM- ♪
♪ I KNOW FROM FAITH ♪
SLATE GIRL:
TAKE 35.
HAVE YOU HEARD ABOUT
THE OLD FASHIONED CAJUN-
CANA-JUN...
KEVIN:
WRONG! CUT!
SLATE GIRL:
TAKE 36!
HAVE YOU HEARD ABOUT
THE GOOD OLD FASHIONED
CANAJUN STRAP,
JASON?
KEVIN:
OKAY, CUT!
IT'S NOT JASON.
THAT'S HIS NAME
IN REAL LIFE.
IT'S JAY IN THE MOVIE.
(FRUSTRATED) GOOD-
IT'S THREE LINES!
CAN'T YOU GET THROUGH
THREE LINES?
I KNOW MY LINES, KEVIN,
I'M JUST-
AFTER 36 TAKES,
I'M LITTLE FLUSTERED.
KEVIN:
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M A LITTLE BIT
FLUSTERED.
AND I WOULD ALMOST RATHER
HAVE ANYONE ELSE IN THIS ROOM
DO THE PART EXCEPT YOU.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
HEY, UH, SLATE GIRL.
WHY DON'T YOU JUMP IN THERE
AND DO THE PART?
DO I GET PAID?
EVEN BETTER THAN THAT,
YOU SWING BY MY TRAILER,
WE'LL DO A LITTLE
OPEN MOUTH KISSING.
UH... NO.
KEVIN:
DON'T LISTEN TO THIS FOOL.
IT'S REAL EASY.
JUST JUMP BEHIND THERE,
AND START ACTING LIKE
YOU'RE NOT UP IN YOUR HEAD,
THINKING ABOUT
WEDDING GOWNS.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
CAITLIN:
MAYBE YOU SHOULD START
ACTING LIKE A DIRECTOR
AND NOT SOME JEALOUS
BOYFRIEND.
KEVIN:
YEAH? WELL, MAYBE YOU SHOULD
TRY ACTING LIKE AN ACTRESS
INSTEAD OF-
WHATEVER IT IS THE TV-
SHE'S GONE.
WELL, JAY,
THAT DOESN'T CUT IT FOR ME
OR FOR ANY OTHER WOMAN
AT THIS SCHOOL.
SO FROM THIS POINT ON-
CRAIG:
KEVIN?
IS KEVIN HERE?
KEVIN:
OH, MY GOD. CUT!
OKAY,
PROBLEM I WAS HAVING
WAS I WAS WRITING
A LOVE SONG.
IT SHOULD BE LIKE A,
LIKE A BREAK-UP.
LIKE LEAVING
HIGH SCHOOL
IS BREAKING UP
WITH YOUR TEEN YEARS.
WHAT DO YOU
THINK?
I THINK YOU GOTTA DO
WHAT YOU GOTTA DO.
CRAIG, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
SPINNER:
UH, MISTER SMITH?
YEAH? OH MY GOD.
WHO ARE YOU NOW?
I'M, I'M SPINNER.
I'M A FRIEND
OF CRAIG'S.
WELL, SPINNER,
FRIEND OF CRAIG'S,
WHAT IS CRAIG
DOING HERE
INSTEAD OF BEING
IN ENGLAND
WHERE HE'S SUPPOSED
TO BE?
HE'S STAYING HERE
ON SET.
HE'S SLEEPING HERE.
HE TOLD ME
YOU KNEW THAT.
I KNEW THAT.
SPINNER,
THE ONLY THING I KNOW,
IS THAT MAKING
A MOVIE
WITH A BUNCH
OF HIGH SCHOOL KIDS -
WAY WORSE THAN MAKING
A MOVIE WITH BEN AFFLECK.
WAY WORSE.
I'LL HAVE
ONE OF THESE.
(DIALS PHONE)
(DOOR CLICKS OPEN)
OH, KEVIN.
GREAT, GREAT, GREAT!
COME IN.
I'M STILL WORKING
ON THE LYRICS,
BUT LET ME
JUST PLAY WHAT I-
I THINK YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU CAN DO
WITH TESSA CAMPANELLI'S
ADDRESS, SNAKE.
OH, UH... THAT'S JOEY
COMING IN THE DOOR.
YEP. OKAY. BYE.
UH... INVITE LIST
IS SHAPING UP...
JOEY:
REMIND ME...
DID I OR DID I NOT
TELL YOU
THAT SENDING CRAIG
OFF TO ENGLAND
WAS A BAD IDEA,
CAITLIN?
WHOA.
DON'T MAKE IT MY FAULT.
OH NO?
IT WAS YOUR IDEA.
YOU SUPPORTED IT.
NOW HE AND ASHLEY
BROKE UP
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
HE'S BEEN LIVING
IN THE DEGRASSI BOILER ROOM.
ANGELA:
OKAY.
WE'RE GOING UPSTAIRS.
CAITLIN:
AREN'T YOU AT ALL CURIOUS
AS TO WHY HE LIED;
FELT LIKE HE COULDN'T
TRUST YOU?
JOEY:
TRUST ME?
I'M THE ONLY ONE
HE CAN TRUST.
JOEY, YOU FLY OFF
THE HANDLE!
AND YOU DON'T THINK!
YOU NEVER HAVE!
LIKE UP AND QUITTING
YOUR JOB -
WHY?
OH, OKAY,
THANKS FOR MIXING UP
THE FIGHT, JOEY.
AND AS FOR CRAIG,
KEVIN AND I SAW
WHAT YOU COULDN'T.
HIS HEART
WAS BREAKING.
JOEY:
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I AM MORE CONCERNED
ABOUT HIS MIND, RIGHT NOW.
BECAUSE IT IS A HELL
OF A LOT MORE FRAGILE.
AND LOOK, IF YOU WANT
TO CONSIDER YOURSELF
A PART OF THIS FAMILY-
DO NOT PULL
THE FAMILY CARD.
BECAUSE IF IT
WASN'T FOR ME,
YOU WOULDN'T EVEN HAVE A ROOF
OVER YOUR HEAD, REMEMBER?
YOU WERE RIGHT.
YOU'RE THE ONLY PERSON
I WANT TO TALK TO.
COME ON.
(DRUMMING)
HEY.
NOT A FREE SHOW.
UH...
I MEANT THAT
AS A DONATION,
NOT A DUET.
ALL RIGHT.
(PLAYING TOGETHER)
HUH.
BEGGARS CAN'T BE
CHOOSERS, HUH?
SKINNY.
CRAIG.
CRAIG,
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
YOU PLAY ANOTHER HOUR
AND I'LL SPLIT
WHAT WE RAKE IN 50-50.
THROW IN A PLACE
TO CRASH
AND IT'S A DEAL.
DONE.
(PLAYING TOGETHER)
IS IT KEVIN NOW
OR SILENT BOB?
WHAT BRINGS YOU BACK
TO MY SET, MISS RYAN?
UH, I JUST WANTED
TO THANK YOU
FOR THE PEP TALK
LAST NIGHT AND UM...
BEING A FRIEND.
I AM A FRIEND...
FOR NOW.
NEXT TIME YOU SHOW UP
IN MY ROOM
AT 2:00 IN THE MORNING,
I'M GETTING TO SECOND BASE,
AT LEAST.
MAYBE THIRD.
DEAL?
DEAL.
SET GUY:
(SHUSHES THEM)
APPOLONIA:
JAY, IF YOU REALLY LOVE ME,
THEN YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO WAIT
TILL I'M EIGHTEEN.
I'D WAIT FOREVER,
MY LOVE.
WHAT GRADE
ARE YOU IN?
I'M A FRESHMAN.
FRESHMAN?
YO, IS THERE ANY SENIORS
UP IN THIS PIECE?
COME ON.
SHOULDN'T YOU BE
DIRECTING?
LIKE I EVER DIRECT.
WHAT KINDA MOVIE
IS THIS, ANYWAY?
IT'S MY MOVIE,
ALL RIGHT?
AND IN MY MOVIE,
KEVIN SMITH GETS TO DANCE
WITH CAITLIN RYAN.
(EXPLOSION)
(CROWD SCREAMS)
OH, SNAP!
CANADIAN NINJAS,
LUNCHBOX!
HIP-HIP...
SNOOGAN!
(FIGHTING GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
OOOH-YAH!
AH-HAH!
OH SIR, LOOK!
DIE NINJA, DIE!
JOEY:
OH, HEY, HEY!
SORRY.
I'M LOOKING
FOR CAITLIN.
KEVIN:
CUT!
LISTEN, I KNOW
I SHOULD HAVE CALLED,
BUT BY THE TIME
I WOKE UP SPIKE
TO LET ME COME IN
AND CRASH-
LOOK, JUST FORGET
ABOUT THAT OKAY?
I CAN'T FIND
CRAIG ANYWHERE.
I THINK HE'S RUN
AWAY AGAIN.
WHAT?
LOOK, I CALLED
HIS FRIENDS,
I'VE CALLED
THE POLICE,
I EVEN CALLED ASHLEY
IN LONDON.
OKAY, THEY HAVEN'T
SEEN HIM,
HE'S JUST
DISAPPEARED.
HE EVEN STOPPED TAKING
HIS MEDICATION.
OKAY, WELL,
WE'LL FIND HIM, ALL RIGHT?
YOU AND ME.
$3.82.
YOU KNOW WHAT
THAT GETS US?
THESE ARE HARD TIMES
AND I THINK
WITH THE WEATHER
AND, I DON'T KNOW,
MAYBE THE ECONOMY AND ALL-
HEY, HEY.
CRAIG:
YOU WANNA ASK HIM FOR MONEY?
SKINNY:
WHY ASK WHEN I CAN
TAKE HIS WALLET.
WELL, WE CAN'T
JUST ROB SOMEBODY.
YOU KNOW HOW MUCH
HIS CAR IS WORTH?
AND WE CAN'T EVEN
AFFORD DINNER.
WAIT, SKINNY, STOP.
AGH!
WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
(YELLS)
(GRUNTS WITH EFFORT)
(COUGHING)
CRAIG:
NO, NO, NOT MY GUITAR.
NO, NO, NOT MY GUITAR,
PLEASE.
LOOKS MORE LIKE
BREAKFAST, LUNCH, DINNER
AND A LOT OF MEALS
AFTER THAT.
CRAIG:
NO, NO, NOT MY GUITAR.
NO, NO!
NO, PLEASE.
NOT MY GUITAR.
THAT'S PERFECT,
ANGIE.
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
HEY.
KEVIN:
I HOPE THIS ISN'T
BEING TOO INTRUSIVE.
I JUST...
I GOT A FEW HOURS
'TIL CALL TONIGHT
AND I FELT LIKE MAYBE
I SHOULD STOP BY
AND SEE IF YOU GUYS
HEARD ANYTHING?
CRAIG STILL
ISN'T HOME.
CAITLIN:
WE'RE DYING OVER HERE.
I JUST WISH WE COULD
TALK TO HIM, YOU KNOW?
TWO MINUTES.
ANYTHING.
WELL, DO YOU THINK MAYBE
A PUBLIC APPEAL
MADE BY A Z-GRADE
CELEBRITY
MIGHT HELP
IN ANY WAY?
I MEAN, IT'S WORTH
A SHOT, RIGHT?
CRAIG:
THIS IS FINE.
IT'S JUST LIKE HOME.
IT'S JUST LIKE MOM MADE.
THIS IS FINE.
KEVIN ON TV:
WE NEED YOUR HELP FINDING
THIS TEENAGER
HIS NAME IS CRAIG MANNING...
HEY, I KNOW THAT GUY, EH?
IT'S KEVIN.
HEY!
AND HE'S BEEN MISSING
SINCE YESTERDAY.
THIS IS HIS DAD,
JOEY.
CRAIG.
CRAIG:
IT'S KEVIN SMITH.
I'M WRITING A SONG
FOR HIS MOVIE.
IT'S KEVIN SMITH.
JOEY ON TV:
WE JUST WANT YOU BACK, OKAY?
CRAIG:
I'M WRITING A SONG
FOR HIS MOVIE,
HERE, LISTEN.
♪ THERE'LL NEVER BE
A SINGLE PLACE ♪
♪ WHERE I FEEL SAFE ♪
♪ WHERE I CAN ESCAPE
FROM YOU ♪
JOEY:
IF ANYONE KNOWS HIM,
PLEASE CALL
1-555-MISSING.
KEVIN:
SO, THANKS FOR
DROPPING ME OFF.
THAT WAS REALLY COOL
OF YOU.
SURE YOU DON'T WANT
TO HANG OUT TONIGHT?
WE'RE SHOOTING
THE BIG FOOTBALL GAME SCENE
WHERE JAY SAVES
APOLLONIA
FROM THE SOUL-SUCKING
CHEERLEADERS OF KINGSBERG.
I SHOULD REALLY
BE THERE
FOR WHEN JOEY
BRINGS CRAIG BACK.
YEAH.
JOEY.
THANK YOU.
FOR WHAT?
EVERYTHING.
I'M SORRY,
I HAVE TO TRY
THIS AGAIN.
JT:
MR. SMITH?
JAMES TIBERIUS.
THE TESTY FIRST A.D.
WANTS YOU ON SET.
AS IN IMMEDIATELY.
TELL HIM I'LL BE THERE
IN A COUPLE.
GO.
THE ADULTS
ARE TALKING NOW.
THAT A.D.'S KIND
OF A MANEATER
SO I'M GONNA HEAD OFF.
HEY, JUST DON'T SETTLE,
ALL RIGHT?
YOU KNOW,
FOR SOMEBODY ELSE'S IDEA
OF WHAT THE "REAL WORLD" IS.
YOU'RE JUST FAR TOO COOL
A CHICK FOR THAT.
PICK YOUR OWN
REAL WORLD.
YOU DESERVE THAT MUCH.
THANK YOU.
GUITAR.
MY GUITAR.
HE TOOK MY GUITAR.
WHEN I SAID-
WHEN HE KNEW
THAT IT WAS MINE.
JOEY. JOEY.
JOEY CAN HELP ME
GET MY GUITAR BACK.
CAN'T YOU, JOEY?
LISTEN,
HE STOLE IT.
MY FRIEND.
NOT MY FRIEND!
DOES CAITLIN
HATE ME?
WHY WOULD CAITLIN
HATE YOU?
BECAUSE I MAKE YOU FIGHT,
AND I RUN AWAY.
AND I,
I ALWAYS HURT YOU
LIKE MY DAD HURT ME.
YOU KNOW MY DAD
USED TO HIT ME?
OH, BUT YOU JUST THINK
I'M CRAZY.
EVERYONE JUST THINKS
I DON'T THINK
YOU'RE CRAZY,
YOU'RE ILL.
OKAY, CRAIG?
IT'S THE BI-POLAR
ACTING UP.
YOU BLAME EVERYTHING
ON ME BEING CRAZY.
I WON'T.
I PROMISE YOU
NEVER AGAIN, OKAY?
I JUST-
CAN WE GET YOU HOME?
CRAIG, PLEASE.
JOEY, MY GUITAR.
WHAT DID I DO
WITH MY GUITAR?
JUST HELP ME FIND IT,
PLEASE?
JOEY:
HE'S ASLEEP.
I GOT HIM TO AGREE TO GO
TO THE POLICE FIRST THING,
AND GIVE A DESCRIPTION
OF THIS "SKINNY".
WHO CALLS THEMSELVES
THAT ANYWAYS?
SNAKE OR WHEELS?
I JUST HOPE
THIS GUY'S NECK
IS SKINNY ENOUGH
FOR ME TO BREAK.
HE MIGHT BE MENTALLY ILL TOO,
JOEY.
REMEMBER THAT.
MAYBE HE'S ANOTHER
LOST CRAIG.
OH, COME ON.
YOU DON'T SEE CRAIG
BEATING UP STRANGERS
IN THE STREET,
DO YOU?
NO, HE JUST BEATS YOU UP
AT HOME.
JUST... FORGET IT.
WHAT ARE WE DOING,
JOEY?
FIGHTING.
LIKE USUAL.
ALL WE EVER DO
IS FIGHT.
I MEAN, CRAIG'S UPSTAIRS
SAFE AND SOUND.
HOW CAN WE GET
MARRIED?
REALLY.
I MEAN,
I LOVE YOU...
AND CRAIG,
AND ANGELA, SO MUCH.
BUT THIS,
IT'S JUST...
IT'S NOT
WHAT IT SHOULD BE.
SO ARE YOU GONNA TAKE
THAT JOB OFFER...
IN L.A.?
I'M THINKING ABOUT IT.
YEAH.
JAY:
YO, EDMUND FITZGERALD
SECONDARY,
ME AND LUNCHBOX WOULD LIKE
TO THANK YOUS CANADIANS
FOR TREATING US
LIKE ONE OF YOUS GUYS.
YOU ALL TALK STUPID,
BUT YOU HAVE GREAT BEER.
LET ME JUST ADD,
BECAUSE HEAVENS...
BUT BE IT YOUR
BLIZZARDS,
OR YOUR BONHOMMES
DE NEIGE
OR YOUR
COURRIERS DU BOIS, EH?
WHAT KINDA BABY
TALK IS THAT?
THAT IS JUST-
OOF!
KEVIN:
YOU MADE ME AND MY FALLEN
HETERO LIFEMATE
FEEL LIKE A BIG PART
OF YOUR HOME
AND NATIVE LAND.
AND, SERIOUSLY,
MADE THIS THE BEST BLEEPING
YEAR OF OUR LIVES!
WOO!
("POMP AND CIRCUMSTANCE" PLAYS)
CUT!
DEGRASSI,
THAT'S A WRAP!
(CHEERING)
KEVIN:
THANK YOU FOR ALL YOUR HELP.
YOU?
YOU WERE HEAVEN
ON EARTH, LOVE.
NOW GET OUT OF MY WAY.
SIR, WHY DO YOU ALWAYS HAVE
TO GET THE LAST LINE IN?
WHY DOES IT BOTHER
YOU SO MUCH
IS MY QUESTION?
'CAUSE YOU'RE ALWAYS
TRYING TO UPSTAGE ME.
"OH, LOOK AT ME,
I'M SILENT BOB!"
OH, LOOK AT THIS.
DUDE!
I TOOK THE CUP OFF.
AND I KNEW THAT.
MR. MANNING!
KEVIN.
(WHISTLING)
KEVIN:
WELL REMEMBERED, SIR.
OH, HELLO.
CONGRATULATIONS.
THANK YOU,
MS. RYAN.
AND NOW
CONGRATULATE ME.
WHY WOULD I BE
DOING THAT EXACTLY?
CAUSE I SAID YES
TO THE L.A. OFFER.
NO.
RYAN'S PLANET
WILL SPIN ONCE AGAIN
BECAUSE OF YOU.
COME HERE.
JOEY.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
THE PARTY'S JUST
GETTING STARTED.
HOME.
SORRY,
CAITLIN'S HOME.
CRAIG:
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO TALK,
REMEMBER?
IT GOES BOTH WAYS.
(SOBS)
I DON'T WANT HER
TO GO.
I KNOW.
BUT I'M HERE
AND ANGIE'S HERE.
AND WE'RE NOT
GOING ANYWHERE.
I'M NOT GOING
ANYWHERE.
OKAY.
KEVIN:
FOLKS, I WOULD LIKE TO RAISE
A VERY SIMPLE TOAST...
TO DEGRASSI!
(CHEERING)