(RING CLATTERS ON TABLE)
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
HELLO?
ASHLEY:
HEY YOU'RE THERE. FINALLY.
I CALLED YOU LAST NIGHT.
A COUPLE TIMES THIS MORNING.
I MUST'VE HAD THE RINGER OFF.
I COULDN'T REALLY SLEEP.
ASHLEY:
YOU... YOU NEED ME THERE
WITH YOU.
KATE:
ASH? WE'RE DUE AT
THE HAIRDRESSER'S.
NOW I REALLY WISH I WERE THERE.
ASH, LAST NIGHT I ASKED YOU
TO MARRY ME
AND YOU SAID NO.
ASHLEY:
I DID.
IS THERE A REASON YOU'RE
CALLING ME FIRST THING?
BEING ALL NICE?
I CAN'T MARRY YOU... YET.
BUT I WANT TO.
I DO.
SO...
THAT'S A "SOMEDAY"?
THAT'S A "YES".
(EXCITED SHOUT)
WOO!
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
CRAIG:
I AM AN IDIOT.
WORSE.
A PHENOMENAL IDIOT.
NO WORSE THAN THAT.
AN UNBELIEVABLE-
LOOK YOU SOUNDED DESPERATE
ON THE PHONE, OKAY?
WHICH IS THE ONLY REASON
WHY I'M HERE.
ASHLEY'S DAD.
HIS WEDDING'S THIS AFTERNOON.
I NEED A SUIT.
SO BUY A SUIT.
A NICE SUIT.
SOMETHING EXPENSIVE.
SO AVOID CHEAP AND UGLY.
CRAIG, I DON'T SEE
THE DRAMA HERE.
LOOK I HAVE TO MAKE
AN IMPRESSION HERE.
A GOOD ONE
WITH ASHLEY'S FAMILY,
AND A GREAT ONE WITH ASHLEY.
SO WHAT ARE WE SHOPPING WITH
EXACTLY?
SOLID GOLD, MY FRIEND.
♪♪♪
HEY, MARCO! CRAIG!
SORRY I'M LATE.
NO PROBLEM.
MY WORK HERE
IS DONE.
AND I HAVE A GAY WEDDING
TO GO TO.
I'M SO GLAD THAT GAYS
CAN GET MARRIED.
THAT YOU TWO CAN GET MARRIED.
YOU GAYS.
I MEAN IF YOU EVER WANTED TO.
IT'S GREAT, GREAT.
THANKS... FOR THE SUPPORT?
SO WE'RE A HUNDRED PERCENT
DOING THIS?
CLICK-CLOCK?
WORKING TOGETHER?
RADITCH ISN'T GOING TO KNOW
WHAT HIT HIM.
NATE:
(RECITING) "LATER ON...
HE WILL UNDERSTAND
HOW SOME MEN SO LOVED HER,
THAT THEY DID SACRIFICE
SO, SO..."
SO CLOSE.
ALEX:
YOU GOT RADITCH TO CHANGE
HIS MIND ABOUT THE PLAY?
NOT YET.
DRACULA IS STAKED FOR NOW.
YOU COULDN'T TELL ME
THIS YESTERDAY?
I'M WASTING MY SATURDAY
REHEARSING...
WHAT EXACTLY?
"THE RADISH SONG".
JT:
YES, "THE RADISH SONG".
SUNG TO THE TUNE:
(SINGING)
♪ TWINKLE, TWINKLE,
LITTLE STAR. ♪
(SINGING)
♪ RADISHES, RADISHES
NOT SO SWEET, ♪
♪ RED AND ROUND,
GROSS TO EAT. ♪
MMM, GETS EVEN MORE WICKED
IN AN "EVIL" SENSE.
BUT THERE'S NO WAY
I'M DOING THIS.
BUT IT'S A SONG
OF REBELLION -
OUR NOT-SO-SILENT
PROTEST
AGAINST TYRANNY
AND OPPRESSION.
ALEX:
I'M ALL ABOUT REBELLION.
NOT SO MUCH INTO GETTING
EXPELLED OVER A PLAY.
SORRY GUYS.
"A" FOR EFFORT THOUGH.
JT:
YOU CAN'T-
YOU CAN'T JUST LEAVE.
UNITED WE STAND!
DIVIDED WE SUCK.
UM...
IF I LEAVE NOW
I CAN STILL CATCH MY DAD.
CLICK-CLOCK, EH?
NICE DAY.
IT'S NOT TOO WARM.
I BOUGHT THIS SUIT.
(CHUCKLES)
IT'S FOR MY GIRLFRIEND'S
WEDDING...
OF HER FATHER
TO ANOTHER GUY.
LET ME START THAT AGAIN.
HER FATHER'S UH,
HER FATHER'S GETTING MARRIED,
WHICH IS WHY LOOKING
GOOD'S IMPORTANT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
DOES THAT LOOK GOOD?
YEAH? MAYBE GREAT?
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
OH MY FLOOR.
(CHUCKLES)
MY GOSH.
BYE.
WRONG FLOOR.
CRAZY, CRAZY ME.
WHERE'S YOUR BATHROOM?
UH IT'S A BATHROOM
IN A BAG.
I'D GO INTO DETAILS,
BUT I'M EATING.
I GOT NEWS.
BIG NEWS!
YOU READY?
WHAT?! NO.
NO, NO, NO. HOLD ON.
FIRST WEDDING I EVER WENT TO
WAS MY MOM'S TO JOEY.
SPIKE AND SIMPSON'S
WAS NUMBER TWO.
ASH'S DAD MAKES THREE.
SEE I WANT TO GET MY PRACTICE
DOWN, YOU KNOW?
GET THINGS RIGHT...
BEFORE MY OWN WEDDING.
OKAY. YOU GOT TIME FOR THAT.
I ASKED ASHLEY
AND SHE SAID YES.
(LAUGHS)
YOU AND ASH
ARE GETTING MARRIED?
CONGRATULATIONS!
ANY TIME.
YOU'RE SIXTEEN.
DON'T YOU WANT TO WAIT FOR,
I DON'T KNOW,
GRADUATION?
MAYBE AN OCCUPATION?
CAN YOU DO THIS UP?
PLEASE.
ARE YOU DRUNK?
ARE YOU HIGH
OR ARE YOU JUST
OUT OF YOUR MIND?
I LOVE HER!
OKAY, THAT STILL DOESN'T
EXPLAIN WHAT'S UP WITH YOU
OR THIS INSANE IDEA.
WELL MAYBE YOU SHOULD JUST
THINK ABOUT IT
AND TRY TO UNDERSTAND.
I DON'T KNOW?!
BE HAPPY FOR ME!
JUSTICE OF THE PEACE:
WE'RE BROUGHT HERE BY
ONE THING - LOVE.
IT'S A STRANGE THING, LOVE.
THERE'S A MILLION POEMS
ABOUT IT;
SONGS;
HOLLYWOOD MOVIES, TOO.
IT'S LIKE WE'RE TRYING
TO TACK IT DOWN,
TRYING TO FIGURE LOVE OUT.
BUT NO WORDS CAN DEFINE LOVE,
JUST LIKE NO LAWS CAN PROPERLY
RESTRICT IT.
ONLY THING CERTAIN IS THAT LOVE
IS NECESSARY TO ALL OF US.
THAT'S WHY IT IS MY PLEASURE
IN FRONT OF ALL THESE PEOPLE
TO DECLARE THIS UNION OFFICIAL;
THIS UNION OF LOVE.
GUESTS:
AW.
(CHAMBER MUSIC PLAYS)
(CLAPPING AND CHEERS)
IT'S HERE.
AT LEAST IT SHOULD BE.
CAITLIN,
DO YOU HAVE ENOUGH CASH
TO PAY FOR
THE CHINESE FOOD?
CAN'T YOU PUT IT ON YOUR CARD?
WELL EITHER IT'S MISSING
OR CRAIG STOLE IT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT KID!
SPIKE:
UH, HAPPY HOUSE PAINTING.
MY TREAT.
THANKS SPIKE.
JOEY, UM...
HOW'S CRAIG BEEN LATELY?
HE'S GONNA BE A LOT WORSE
WHEN I'M DONE WITH HIM.
ACTUALLY, I'M A BIT CONCERNED.
I'M CONCERNED TOO.
CAITLIN'S GOT FIRST DIBS
ON THE CHOW MEIN.
JOEY...
CRAIG'S DAD,
HE WASN'T THE MOST STABLE GUY,
WAS HE?
CRAIG IS NOTHING
LIKE HIS DAD.
ALL RIGHT? HE'S JUST-
HE'S JUST BEING A TEENAGER.
I SEE A LOT OF TEENAGERS
EVERY DAY
AND I'M AFRAID CRAIG'S GOING
THROUGH SOMETHING MORE.
LOOK SNAKE...
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
I APPRECIATE YOUR WORRY, OKAY?
BBUT THERE'S NOTHING WRONG
WITH CRAIG
THAT A GOOD GROUNDING
WON'T TAKE CARE OF.
ALL RIGHT?
IT'S FOR YOU.
HELLO?
THIS IS MR. JEREMIAH.
DAMAGES?
MY HOTEL ROOM?
HOW MUCH?!
(RAUCOUS LAUGHTER)
KATE:
(LAUGHING)
NO SERIOUSLY.
AS ROBERT'S EX-WIFE,
IT'S NOT USUAL I'D BE HERE.
ESPECIALLY SINCE HE'S MARRYING
SOMEONE YOUNGER
AND PRETTIER THAN ME.
(LAUGHTER)
OUR FAMILY MAY BE UNUSUAL,
BUT IT'S ONE I'M THANKFUL FOR.
AS, I'M SURE,
IS OUR LOVELY DAUGHTER.
COULD YOU STAND UP, ASHLEY.
(APPLAUSE)
NO IT'S OKAY.
HI. I'M CRAIG MANNING.
I'M ONLY ASHLEY'S BOYFRIEND.
I'M NOT PART
OF THE "UNUSUAL" FAMILY
MS. KERWIN'S TALKED ABOUT,
WELL NOT YET.
KATE:
IS THERE A TOAST IN THIS,
CRAIG?
THERE'S AN ANNOUNCEMENT.
CRAIG, DON'T.
ASH AND I ARE GETTING MARRIED.
ASHLEY:
CRAIG!
(SMATTERING OF APPLAUSE)
TO US!
HEY, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
ASHLEY:
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?!
CRAIG:
I SAW YOUR DAD GET MARRIED.
ASHLEY:
OH, OH, OH.
AND YOU THOUGHT
PERFECT TIME
TO ANNOUNCE
OUR FUTURE LIFE.
THIS MORNING YOU SAID
THAT YOU WANTED TO BE TOGETHER.
AND RIGHT NOW
I'M CHANGING MY MIND.
ASHLEY,
ARE YOU OKAY?
I WILL BE.
AS SOON AS CRAIG LEAVES.
YOU ARE EVERYTHING, ASH.
CRAIG, I WANT YOU
TO GO HOME NOW.
OKAY.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
BUT I HAVE TO DO
SOMETHING FIRST.
THAT'S NOT HOME, CRAIG!
CRAIG:
I HAVE TO TALK TO YOU.
BOTH OF YOU AND KATE.
CRAIG, PLEASE,
NOT IN FRONT OF THE GUESTS
IT'S URGENT, SIR.
KATE:
ASHLEY, COULD YOU PLEASE
ASK CRAIG TO WAIT OUTSIDE.
I'M TRYING, MOM.
I LOVE ASHLEY.
AND TO HAVE TO KEEP-
TO KEEP PROVING THAT
IS DISRESPECTFUL
AND IT'S OBNOXIOUS!
WE'LL TALK ABOUT
THIS LATER.
CRAIG:
WE CAN BUT WE WON'T.
YOU'RE GOING TO TELL ASH
TO STOP SEEING ME AGAIN.
ONLY THIS TIME...
THIS TIME SHE'S GONNA LISTEN.
CHRISTOPHER:
WE CAN DISCUSS THIS
ON THE DRIVEWAY.
CRAIG:
NO. LET ME GO!
(CRASH)
DON'T.
LIBERTY:
THE ENEMY APPROACHES FINALLY.
WHERE'S THE DRAMA CLUB?
OH WELL,
YOU KNOW ACTORS,
NOTORIOUSLY LATE.
YOU'VE MADE SOME PROGRESS
I ASSUME.
LIBERTY:
WE'VE PROGRESSED, SIR,
AND WE'D LIKE TO SING
OUR PROGRESS FOR YOU.
READY WHEN YOU ARE, JT.
READY FOR SOME
LIGHTHEARTED FUN.
PICTURE IT -
THE MID 1980'S.
WHAT?
OUR HEROINE,
DEGRASSI'S CAFETERIA WORKER,
HAS JUST SEEN "E.T."!
THAT'S NOT THE SET-UP.
JUST PLAY THE SONG,
PLEASE LIBERTY.
(PIANO PLAYING)
(SINGING)
♪ OH THESE HALLOWED HALLS
OF STONE ♪
♪ MAKE ME WANT TO DIAL HOME. ♪
♪ LOOK WAY UP INTO THE SKY ♪
♪ DEGRASSI'S NAME IS WRIT
REAL HIGH... ♪
AND THOSE AREN'T
THE WORDS.
THOSE WERE FINE WORDS, LIBERTY.
A STUDENT DIED IN THIS SCHOOL,
MR. RADITCH.
AND FUZZY SONGS
WITH AWKWARD CHOREOGRAPHY
ISN'T GONNA HELP US
DEAL WITH IT.
UH... (NERVOUS LAUGH)
LIBERTY.
LIBERTY: (SINGING)
♪ RADISHES, RADISHES
NOT SO SWEET, ♪
♪ RED AND ROUND
AND GROSS TO EAT. ♪
(SPEAKING) THEY HAVE POWER
AND CRUEL LITTLE VOICES SAYING,
"I RUN DEGRASSI.
YOU HAVE NO CHOICES."
UGLY AND MEAN
AND SLIGHTLY OBSCENE,
STUBBORNNESS RADISHES
I'VE EVER SEEN.
INTERESTING SONG.
I'D APPRECIATE A REPRISAL
MONDAY IN DETENTION.
BOTH OF YOU.
(SOBBING)
(PHONE RINGS)
(CRIES)
ASH, I NEED YOU.
I NEED YOU.
(CRIES)
(ANGRILY SMASHES PHONE)
I NEED YOU!
ASH, I NEED YOU!
(ANGRY GRUNTS)
(CRIES)
JOEY'S NOT HERE IS HE?
NO, HE'S OUT LOOKING
FOR YOU.
WHAT HAPPENED?
YOUR HAND!
I'LL GET YOU A TOWEL.
I SHOULD CLEAN UP.
ANGELA:
DADDY'S MAD, YOU KNOW.
CRAIG:
ANGIE.
LISTEN TO ME.
I NEED YOU TO GIVE THIS
TO ASHLEY.
CAN I OPEN IT?
IT'S JUST A RING.
(KISS)
I LOVE YOU MOST.
ASHLEY, MR. JEREMIAH WOULD LIKE
TO TALK TO YOU.
WHERE'S CRAIG?
I DON'T KNOW.
HE'S NOT HERE ANYMORE.
JOEY:
BUT YOU KNOW WHERE
HE IS THOUGH, RIGHT?
LOOK, I KNOW ABOUT
THE HOTEL ROOM.
HOTEL ROOM?!
GREAT.
WHAT I CAN'T UNDERSTAND
IS WHY DID YOU TRASH IT?
$4,000 IN DAMAGES!
I DIDN'T...
CRAIG, HE MUST'VE DONE IT
LAST NIGHT
AFTER HE PROPOSED.
PROPOSED?
KATE:
CRAIG HAS PROBLEMS.
HE'S GOT A LOT OF PROBLEMS.
ASHLEY:
NO, NO, MOM.
HE'S NOT LIKE THIS!
NOT EVER.
JOEY, TELL HER.
WHAT DO I DO?
WHAT IS HAPPENING TO MY SON?
CAITLIN:
(READING) HE DASHED DOWN
THE STEPS AND CROSSED MY YARD
BEING CAREFUL TO STAY AWAY
FROM THE LIGHT
IN FRONT OF THE CANNONS.
CAN YOU GIVE SOMETHING
TO JOEY?
CRAIG, WE KNOW YOU STOLE
THE CREDIT CARD.
IT'S A CHEQUE FOR $3,000.
IT'S ALL I HAVE.
JOEY'S CREDIT CARD'S
IN THERE TOO.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
BACK TO THE WEDDING.
TO MARCOS.
NOWHERE.
THE PLACE LOOKS GREAT.
I BARELY RECOGNIZED IT.
SIT DOWN.
CAITLIN'S GOT YOUR CARD.
YOU'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
THERE'S SOMETHING'S
NOT RIGHT WITH YOU.
I'M FINE. I'M FINE.
LOOK SIT DOWN!
DON'T... (CRASH)
DO THAT!
JOEY:
I'M TRYING TO HELP YOU HERE!
ANGELA:
NO!
(PUNCHES)
CAITLIN:
CRAIG, STOP IT!
STOP IT!
CRAIG! CRAIG!
CRAIG, CALM DOWN!
CRAIG.
YOU CAME BACK.
ANGELA:
DADDY! DADDY!
YOU-
YEAH, YEAH I DID.
AFTER EVERYTHING
THAT HAPPENED,
AFTER ALL THAT I DID,
YOU CAME BACK.
CRAIG.
CRAIG, YOU NEED HELP.
ANGELA:
DADDY, ARE YOU OKAY?
WE'RE GONNA GET YOU HELP.
JT:
DON'T THINK OF IT AS DETENTION.
THINK OF US
AS EXIT DELAYED.
THANKS,
I'M HERE ALL WEEK.
I DON'T KNOW WHY
YOU'RE HERE.
I MEAN, I'M THE ONE
WHO SANG THE STUPID SONG.
YEAH, BUT IT WAS
TOTALLY WORTH IT.
THE LOOK ON RADITCH'S FACE
WHEN HE FIRED US.
NOT HELPING, JT.
I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY THAT
I CHICKENED OUT.
BUT WHAT YOU DID,
THE WAY THAT YOU
STOOD UP TO RADITCH,
TOOK GUTS.
BRILLIANT.
YOU KNOW WHAT
I WISH I'D DONE?
I'VE CRUSHED ON YOU
FOR FOUR YEARS.
MY STOMACH HURTS
A LITTLE.
CRAIG:
I STILL CAN'T SLEEP.
I'VE GOT 17 NEW SONGS.
MORE IN A WEEK THAN
I'VE WRITTEN MY WHOLE LIFE.
BUT YOU'RE OKAY?
I'M CRAZY, ASH.
YOU'RE NOT CRAZY.
WELL THEN EXPLAIN
THE MEDICATION
AND THIS TRENDY BRACELET
ON MY WRIST.
AND EXPLAIN WHY,
DESPITE EVERYTHING
THEY TELL ME,
I FEEL FINE.
YOU'RE BI-POLAR.
YOU'VE GOT A CHEMICAL IMBALANCE
IN YOUR BRAIN
BUT YOU'RE GETTING HELP.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD GO.
I DON'T WANT TO.
LOOK, I WON'T BLAME YOU
IF YOU WANT TO LEAVE.
JUST GO.
IF I'M SICK LIKE THEY SAY
I AM,
I'M GOING TO BE MANAGING THIS
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
MEDICATIONS, SHRINKS...
I'M NOT LEAVING, CRAIG.
THE FIRST TIME WE DATED
IT WAS A DISASTER.
THIS TIME WAS NUCLEAR.
WE'RE NOT OVER.
SO...
YOU'RE HERE WITH ME?
ABSOLUTELY.