FIRST,
THERE WAS THE EPISODE
WITH MR. WALFISH'S
TOQUE IN THE EAVESTROUGH.
AND WE MUSTN'T FORGET
THE VISITING
LEF-TENANT
YOU DEKED OUT
AND ACCOSTED
ON THE TARMAC.
YOU UNDERSTAND
A WORD
THIS HOSER'S SAYING,
SILENT BOB?
HOW THE HELL'D
SHE GET TO BE PRINCIPAL
WHEN SHE DON'T
EVEN SPEAK
GOODER ENGLISH
LIKE US AMERICANS?
YOU BOYS ARE TOO
BLOODY STUPID
TO MAKE THE GRADE
DOWN IN THE STATES,
AND YOUR LAST HOPE
IS THE SCHOOL SYSTEM
OF THE GREAT WHITE
NORTH, EH!
YOU WANNA GET
OOT OF GRADE TWELVE?
YOU'D BETTER
START LEARNING
WHAT THE METRIC
SYSTEM'S ALL ABOOT!
I GOT THREE WORDS
FOR YOU: GO TO-
SIR!
THERE'LL BE
NO MORE CUSS WORDS,
OUTTA YOU YA
POTTY-MOUTHED MALL-RAT!
YOU'RE GONNA LEARN
THE DUAL LANGUAGES
OF MY HOME
AND NATIVE LAND,
AND YOU'RE GONNA
SAVOUR MY POUTINE!
YOU'RE IN
CANADA NOW, EH?
AND THAT'D BE A CUT!
VERY NICE.
OOH, VERY NICE.
REALLY?
IT WASN'T TOO SUBTLE
FOR YOU?
SUBTLE?
NO.
BUT I DO
THINK THE PM
IS GOING TO REVOKE
YOUR CITIZENSHIP.
WELL, WHERE AM
I GONNA HIDE OUT
FROM FOUR MORE YEARS
OF BUSH IN THE STATES?
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
IS THAT WHY
YOU'RE HERE, MEWESY?
OH, NO, SIR...
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
HEY, HOW YOU DOIN'?
KEVIN:
CRAIG, DO NOT LET THIS FOOL
MACK ON YOUR BROAD
JUST 'CAUSE HE'S BEEN
IN A FEW MOVIES, KID.
A FEW BAD MOVIES.
EXAC-
AH, I'M SO
SORRY KEVIN.
THAT WAS OUT LOUD,
WASN'T IT?
I'M SO SORRY.
COME ON MEWESY,
LET'S GO MAKE OUT
IN THE TRAILER.
JASON:
FOR REAL?
ALANIS:
FOR REAL.
AND I CAST HER
IN TWO MOVIES AS GOD.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE, SIR?
SHOULDN'T YOU BE
HOME WRITING ME A TUNE?
ASHLEY:
MY FAULT.
I DRAGGED HIM AWAY.
SHE'S, UH... ABANDONING
ME TOMORROW.
KEVIN:
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
LONDON CALLING.
WHAT'RE YOU GONNA DO
BEFORE YOU LEAVE THE UK?
SEE A MOVIE
IN LEICESTER SQUARE.
KEVIN:
VERY, VERY GOOD.
AND MAKE SURE
YOU WRITE THIS DUDE
TONS OF LOVEY
DOVEY POSTCARDS.
I NEED HIM IN THAT
FRAME OF MIND
SO HE CAN WRITE
ME A POWER BALLAD.
I GOTTA GO BACK
TO WORK.
YOU - I SUGGEST
YOU DO THE SAME.
BEAT IT!
CRAIG:
ALL RIGHT.
NOT LIKE I'LL HAVE ANYTHING
BETTER TO DO ALL SUMMER.
RIGHT?
CRAIG, PLEASE.
YOU SAID.
IT'S A JOKE.
IT'S ME, IT'S JOKING.
IT'S GREAT.
IT'S A GREAT
OPPORTUNITY.
AND I'LL BE FINE.
HONEST.
LESS THAN 24 HOURS
FROM NOW,
AND I'M ON A PLANE
TO ENGLAND!
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
SO, I'VE ALWAYS BEEN
A HUGE FAN OF CANADA.
OBVIOUSLY.
AH, I LOVE YOUR COUNTRY.
I LIKE IT A LOT.
YOU DON'T INVADE
OTHER COUNTRIES.
YOU KINDA HANG BACK,
TRY TO GO UNNOTICED.
SO YOU DON'T
GET INVADED.
WHICH IS VERY SWEET.
RIGHT. SO, UM...
JUST FOR A SEC,
COULD WE TALK
ABOUT THE MOVIE?
"MOVIE"?
C'MON MAN,
WHO'RE YOU,
REGIS AND KELLY?
I MEAN,
SINCE WHEN DOES
"SIGNING-OFF-FROM-PLANET-
EARTH-I'M-CAITLIN-RYAN"
WANT TO TALK
ABOUT THE MOVIE?
HOW DO YOU KNOW
THE SIGN-OFF
FROM MY OLD SHOW?
NO ACTUALLY...
WHY?
WELL, IF YOU'D LISTEN
TO ME THE OTHER DAY,
YOU'D KNOW.
'CAUSE I'M CREEPY.
I TOLD YOU.
I WAS A BIG FAN.
SEE, GOT A
REAL THING
FOR PRETTY GIRLS
WHO CHAIN THEMSELVES
TO BIG TREES
AND SAY "ABOOT".
UH... YOU ARE USING
REAL DEGRASSI KIDS
AS ACTORS, YES?
I DO.
WE USE REAL STUDENTS
FROM THE SCHOOL.
WE'RE SHOOTING
IN THE SCHOOL, OBVIOUSLY.
AND I'M VERY INTERESTED
IN KEEPING IT REAL.
OKAY, AND SO WHY
SET THE FILM-
YOU, YOU DON'T WANT
TO SAY THE TITLE
DO YOU?
JAY AND SILENT BOB
GO CANADIAN, EH?
RIGHT. WHY MAKE THEM
"GO CANADIAN"?
UM... WELL I DON'T KNOW.
IF THEY EVER NEEDED
A REASON
I WOULD SAY
THAT THE UM...
VERY ALLURING WOMEN
OF THE TRUE NORTH
WOULD MAKE ANY
RIGHT THINKING MAN
WANNA "GO CANADIAN",
MS. RYAN.
YEAH, I'M TALKING
ABOUT YOU.
AND CUT!
DIRECTOR:
THAT'S LUNCH EVERYBODY!
LIBERTY, YOU CAN BUY BOTTLES
OF THOSE AT THE GROCERY STORE.
WHY BUY WHEN THEY'RE
HERE, GRATIS?
SPINNER:
YOU SHOULDA SEEN HER
YESTERDAY
WITH THE MINI-CORN.
THAT WAS REALLY GROSS.
THE DOT'S CATERING
THE SHOOT, OKAY?
SO, UNTIL SUMMER
SCHOOL STARTS, I'M HERE.
AND, GOT JAY
A JOB, TOO.
SO, UH, WHAT
ARE YOU HAVING?
WE HAVE PRIME RIB,
CHICKEN CORDON BLUE?
I'D RATHER EAT
MY OWN LIVER
THAN ACCEPT FOOD
FROM YOU TWO SCUMBAGS.
MANNING, DO I NEED
TO REMIND YOU
THAT I'M HOLDING A BIG,
SCARY KNIFE IN MY HAND?
YEAH?
WATCH YOUR FINGERS.
DID YOU TAKE YOUR
PILLS LAST NIGHT?
BUT DON'T ASK THAT.
IT'S EMBARRASSING.
NO,
THAT WAS EMBARRASSING.
SORRY. I'M SORRY.
JAY, C'MON.
WHEN I WAS BORN,
STAR WARS HAD ALREADY
BEEN OUT ON VIDEO
FOR TEN WHOLE YEARS.
YOU'RE TOO OLD.
EVEN THOUGH THERE'S
LAWS TO PREVENT IT,
I'M GONNA MARRY APOLLONIA.
SHE'S THE SUGAR
IN MY MAPLE,
SHE'S MY POUTINE,
THE BACK IN MY BACON!
THE "ICK"
IN PATHETIC.
(LAUGHS)
CUT!
VERY NICE ELLIE.
"ICK" IN PATHETIC.
MANNY?
NICE JOB.
YOU, EH.
HAIR DIRECTOR WANTED
"A REAL GOTH GIRL".
FROM 1988,
I GUESS.
HE HEARD THAT,
MARILYN MANSON.
I DID.
AND IT REALLY HURT.
I FOUGHT TO CAST YOU.
ONLY TRYING TO GET
MORRISSEY HERE
TO CRACK A SMILE.
CRAIG:
WHY?
ASH'S LEAVING
TO ENGLAND.
WHERE SHE'S GONNA FIND
SOME WAY COOLER GUY
WITH AN ACCENT.
FALL MADLY IN LOVE.
AND NEVER,
EVER COME BACK.
UGH! THE ANGST.
THANK GOD I'M NOT
A TEENAGER ANYMORE.
IT'S NOT FUNNY.
JASON:
IT'S RIGHT.
IT'S "PATHETIC."
SIR...
WHAT, AH, FLIRTING
WITH DISASTER OVER HERE
IS TRYING TO SAY
IS JUST GO
ALREADY, MAN.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING
HANGIN' AROUND
THE HALLWAYS OF DEGRASSI
ALL SUMMER ANYWAY.
JUST-
FIND SOME SUMMER MUSIC
PROGRAM WITH COLDPLAY
OR SOME EXCUSE,
DUDE.
BUT JUST GO
HANG OUT
WITH YOUR OLD LADY
IN LONDON.
YOU KNOW? WHAT COULD
BE BETTER THAN THAT?
BEATS THIS.
CAN I SPEAK WITH
YOU FOR A SECOND?
THE TEENAGE GIRL
THING HAS TO STOP.
IT WAS FUNNY
THE FIRST TIME,
NOW IT'S JUST
SICK. SICK.
YOU HAVE A PROBLEM.
JAY:
I KNOW.
♪♪♪
CAITLIN:
STEPMOM ALERT!
MINIMIZE!
YOU CAN'T EVEN GET
TO PORN IN HERE.
SIMPSON HAS
ONLINE OFFICER.
WHAT ABOUT
TRAVEL PORN?
MONEY SHOTS OF PIGEONS
FOULING TRAFALGAR SQUARE?
BIG BEN IN THE RAIN?
SO YOU DON'T THINK
ME GOING TO ENGLAND'S
THE WORST IDEA SINCE...
WHATEVER MY LAST
IDEA WAS?
I THINK A SUMMER AWAY
WOULD BE GREAT
FOR YOU, ACTUALLY.
KEVIN:
I'M TRYING TO GET
A CANADIAN FLAG
INTO EVERY SHOT
OF THE MOVIE.
'CAUSE I'M A REALLY BIG FAN
OF THE CANADIAN FLAG.
SO WAS MEWES,
'TIL HE FIGURED OUT
IT WAS A MAPLE LEAF.
INSTEAD OF...
THE WACKY
YOU'VE GOT SOMETHING
MORE HOLLYWOOD, RIGHT?
MORE, MORE DISHY?
KEVIN IS NOT
EXACTLY "DISHY."
I MEAN, HE'S MORE
"SELF-DEPRECATING,"
"FUNNY".
FUNNY'S GOOD.
ESPECIALLY WHEN
IT'S COMING
FROM A BONA FIDE
CELEBRITY.
LET'S USE THIS
OPPORTUNITY, OKAY?
TAKE "LOCAL HEROES"
TO A NEW LEVEL.
A LOWER LEVEL...
THAT'S RIGHT.
WE'RE TALKING
THE SAME LANGUAGE.
WOULD YOU AH, CALL
SOMETHING UP FOR ME?
IT'S AROUND THE
THREE MINUTE MARK.
IF YOU LOOK AT IT,
MORE DEMOCRATS WENT
TO SEE SHREK 2 LAST YEAR,
THAN VOTED
IN THE ELECTION
SO, WHAT'S THERE
TO GET EXCITED ABOUT?
OR BOO?
THAT'S GOING IN.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT TOMAS.
I'LL TAKE THE BULLET.
(PHONE RINGS)
HELLO, CAITLIN RYAN.
YES, THIS IS SHE.
WHAT?!
THIS GUY BUYS
AN SUV YESTERDAY.
TOP OF THE LINE,
80-PLUS.
HE COMES BACK TODAY,
BUYS ONE FOR THE WIFE.
WOW. AMAZING
FOR YOU.
NOT FOR
GLOBAL WARMING...
I KNOW,
AS USUAL,
YOU'RE MY CONSCIENCE.
BUT HONEY,
TWO SUV'S!
UM...I HAD A WINDFALL
TODAY, TOO, ACTUALLY.
UH, A REP FOR A BIG...
WELL, BIG-ISH -
BROADCASTER
IN LA CALLED.
THEY WANT TO REVIVE
"RYAN'S PLANET".
REALLY?
FROM UP HERE?
DOWN THERE.
BUT, UM...
WELL, OF COURSE
I CAN'T ACCEPT IT.
LEAVE MY FAMILY?
"FAMILY"
WHICH INCLUDES A SEXY
LITTLE CAR MAGNATE
WHO LOVES YOU,
VERY MUCH.
BUT WHAT AN HONOR
BEING ASKED, HUH?
YEAH.
AH SO, CRAIG'S
IN THE GARAGE.
AND HE HAS SOMETHING
HE WANTS TO TALK
TO YOU ABOUT.
AS A FAVOUR,
TRY TO LISTEN?
(PAYING GUITAR)
APPARENTLY I'M SUPPOSED
TO BE OPEN.
AS IN, "MY MIND".
OKAY, THERE'S THIS
A GREAT MUSIC SCHOOL...
IN CAMDEN.
IT'S PART OF LONDON.
I'D BE EARNING
A CREDIT FOR NEXT YEAR.
YOU WANT TO GO
TO ENGLAND?
IT'S JUST FOR
THE SUMMER.
AND HE'S GOT
EDUCATION MONEY
IN HIS TRUST FUND.
YUP. ASHLEY'S DAD
IS THERE.
AND THERE ARE LIKE
TEACHER-TYPES
IN MY DORM.
JUST SAY YES?
JUST GIVE IN
ALREADY.
CAITLIN AND I'VE
THOUGHT OF EVERYTHING.
NOT SIX MONTHS AGO
YOU WERE HOSPITALIZED.
DIAGNOSED BI-POLAR.
I'M OKAY NOW.
I'M ON MY MEDS.
I'VE BEEN ON THEM
FOR MONTHS.
CRAIG, NO.
I, I DON'T FEEL
COMFORTABLE WITH YOU
BEING THOUSANDS
OF MILES AWAY FROM YOU.
WHAT, WHAT IF
SOMETHING WENT WRONG?
RIGHT.
I MEAN,
ENGLAND PROBABLY
WOULDN'T EVEN LET
A PSYCHOPATH LIKE ME IN.
RIGHT?
THEY ALREADY HAD
ONE JACK THE RIPPER,
AND MAD COW DISEASE.
I'M NOT SAYING
THAT, CRAIG-
(DOOR SLAMS)
LISTEN, GIRL-FIEND,
YOU AND YOUR
SO POST-PUBESCENT
HE MAKES THE BACKSTREET BOYS
LOOK RELEVANT BOYFRIEND
CAN KISS
MY YOGA-TONED ASS.
LISTEN LADY,
THERE ARE SOME PLACES
EVEN I WON'T
PUT MY MOUTH.
AND THAT'D BE A CUT.
THANK GOD.
THAT WILL UH, BRING US
OUT OF THE SCENE PEOPLE.
AND...PAIGE?
YES, MR. SMITH?
DID YOU LOVE ME,
DID YOU REALLY,
REALLY LOVE ME?
OH, LOVE'S NOT
THE WORD, HON.
THAT'S A WRAP
FOR YOU TODAY.
THANK YOU.
YOU WERE VERY,
AH...YOU WERE VERY.
KEVIN:
YOU GUYS WERE GOOD.
REALLY GOOD.
LET'S DO THE NEXT ONE.
OH, MY GOD.
LADY YOU ARE JUST
FLAT OUT HAUNTING ME.
YOU HANG OUT ON MY SET
ANY LONGER
I'M GONNA HAVE
TO GIVE YOU SOME LINES.
PUT YOU IN THE MOVIE.
JASON:
YEAH. SHE BETTER NOT
GET MORE LINES
THAN ME, SIR.
DON'T WORRY, DUDE.
THE MOVIE'S
NOT CALLED
"CAITLIN
AND SILENT BOB"?
OH, BUT THAT'S
THE MOVIE YOU WANNA MAKE.
OH, I BET.
X-RATED VERSION.
WELL,
THAT WAS AWKWARD.
HOW ARE YOU?
GREAT.
I GOT A CALL
LAST NIGHT, FROM LA.
A CALL FROM LA?
NO.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
SO I JUST WANTED TO THANK YOU,
FOR SETTING IT UP.
NO NEED TO THANK ME.
WELL, I DO.
BECAUSE UM...
I SAID NO.
UM, NO? WAIT. NO.
YOU DIDN'T.
YOU CAN'T SAY NO.
I HAVE MY FAMILY,
I HAVE MY OWN SHOW.
I MEAN I CAN'T
JUST TAKE OFF TO LA?
NOT FOR NOTHING,
BUT YOU GOT TO GO BACK
TO ACTING GLOBALLY,
NEVER MIND ALL THIS
LOCAL STUFF.
AND IT'S JUST
HEARTBREAKING
TO SEE YOU
SITTING AROUND
COBBLING TOGETHER
PUFF PIECES
ABOUT VISITING
D-GRADE CELEBRITIES.
IT'S BENEATH YOU.
D-GRADE CELEBRITIES?
YEAH.
LIKE YOU?
WAIT...
I'M AT LEAST A C-GRADE
CELEBRITY, THOUGH.
I, I HAVE
NO PROCESS.
I DON'T CONSIDER
MYSELF A,
A FILM MAKER,
REALLY.
I'M JUST A GUY WHO GETS
TO DIRECT THE STUFF
THAT HE WRITES. AND -
SORRY, CAITLIN,
BUT I'M LOCKING
YOU OUT
OF THE EDIT SUITE
ON THIS ONE.
WHAT?!
WHAT, YOU'RE TAKING
THE KEVIN SMITH SPOT
AWAY FROM ME?
YEAH. I WANT CELEBRITY
GOSSIP, ALL RIGHT?
EVEN NON-CELEBRITY
GOSSIP.
HELL, IF THIS GUY
SPENT THE WHOLE SEGMENT
TALKING ABOUT
HIS GAY DOG,
IT'D BE MORE
ENJOYABLE THAN THIS.
I, I TRY NOT
TO OVER THINK IT.
IT'S JUST A
COMMUNICATION-
WELL, IT'S HIS PROCESS
AS A FILM-MAKER.
YEAH, AND I'M NOT
LAUGHING, ALL RIGHT?
I'M NOT HEARING
ANYTHING ABOUT BENNIFER.
EVERY TIME I HAND
SOMETHING IN TO YOU,
YOU RIP IT APART
OR YOU CHANGE IT.
WHY?
WHY? YOU TELL
ME, CAITLIN.
THIS ISN'T
"RYAN'S WORLD".
"RYAN'S PLANET."
OR THAT.
IT'S "LOCAL HEROES".
I QUIT.
(PLAYING GUITAR)
YEAH, SO,
IT STILL NEEDS LYRICS.
BUT WHAT
DO YOU THINK?
IT'S GOOD.
I GOT SOMETHING FOR YOU:
ASHLEY PLEASE DON'T GO,
PLEASE DON'T LEAVE ME,
DON'T FALL IN LOVE
WITH AN UGLY LIMEY...
SHUT UP.
OKAY, YOU CAN'T -
YOU CAN'T
THROW FRIES
AT A KID IN
A WHEEL CHAIR.
CRAIG.
LET'S GO GET
OUR SEATS.
JOEY:
CRAIG, LISTEN.
I KNOW YOU THOUGHT
I WAS BEING OFFENSIVE,
BUT HONESTLY,
I WASN'T TRYING
TO HURT YOU.
YEAH, WELL?
YOU DID.
I MEAN, WHY DO I TAKE
THE STUPID PILLS?
YOU DON'T BELIEVE
I'M BETTER.
THERE ARE
CONDITIONS, THOUGH.
I'M GOING TO BE CALLING
THE SCHOOL
TO DISCLOSE YOUR ILLNESS.
I WANT YOU TO CALL ME,
EVERY DAY -
ESPECIALLY IF SOMETHING
DOESN'T FEEL RIGHT.
AND I WANT MR. KERWIN
TO KEEP AN EYE ON YOU TOO.
YEAH. EVERYTHING.
ANYTHING.
I CAN HANDLE IT.
I CAN. REALLY.
CRAIG:
HEY!
(GRUNTS)
WHAT D'YOU
GOT IN HERE?
EVERY SHOE I OWN.
HEY.
YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT
THIS WHOLE GOODBYE THING
WAS GOING TO BE
SO HARD.
BUT I'M, I'M
SO GLAD YOU'RE HERE,
THAT YOU SURPRISED ME.
PARTING IS SO NOT
SWEET SORROW.
I'M AH, I'M COMING.
TOMORROW.
BUT SINCE IT'S
A RED-EYE,
I'LL BE IN LONDON
THE DAY AFTER THAT.
YOU'RE JUST
FLYING TO LONDON?
THAT'S WHAT
PLANES ARE FOR.
YOU - YOU CAN'T FOLLOW
ME TO ENGLAND.
ASH, C'MON.
LOOK...WHY,
WHY ARE YOU HERE?
DOING THIS?
ARE YOU OFF
YOUR MEDS?
NO! I'M NOT
OFF MY MEDS.
I'M HERE 'CAUSE
I LOVE YOU
AND I HAVE PLANS.
YEAH.
SO DO I, CRAIG.
AND YOU SAID YOU WERE
OKAY WITH THEM.
YOU SAID IT REPEATEDLY -
SO WHAT IS THIS?
THIS IS ME TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT
HOW WE'RE GONNA SPEND
THE SUMMER TOGETHER.
YOU THINK I'M HAVING
AN EPISODE!
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO THINK.
LOOK, I NEED SPACE.
I NEED TO GET AWAY.
OH, OKAY.
FROM YOU.
LOOK, CRAIG.
I LOVE YOU.
BUT EVER SINCE
MY DAD'S WEDDING
IT'S JUST BEEN ME,
WORRYING.
I MEAN, WATCHING
FOR SIGNS,
WATCHING WHAT I SAY.
WHY WON'T YOU
JUST BELIEVE ME?
I'M BETTER NOW.
I'M OKAY. I AM.
EMAIL ME, OKAY?
I'LL SEE YOU
IN SEPTEMBER.
(CRYING)
CAITLIN:
HE SAYS,
"IT'S "LOCAL HEROES."
LIKE, LIKE IT'S
ACTUALLY A GOOD TITLE.
IT IS THE SINGLE
WORST TITLE
SINCE "HOPE FLOATS".
THANK YOU.
YES.
YEAH. 'CAUSE YOU
THINK HE'D WANT ME
TO ADD SOME SUBSTANCE
TO HIS CRAPPY,
UNORIGINAL IDEA
OF A SHOW.
IF HE WAS HERE,
RIGHT NOW?
I WOULD THROW
THIS DRINK -
WITH THE ICE CUBES
IN HIS FACE.
LISTEN TO YOU, BABE.
RIGHT ON.
THIS IS THE CAITLIN RYAN
I REMEMBER.
THE CAITLIN RYAN
FROM THE DVDS,
"RYAN'S PLANET".
ADVOCATE
CAITLIN RYAN.
NO, THIS IS
THE CAITLIN
THAT PRODUCES FLUFF
LIKE CAMPING TRIPS
AND HIGH SCHOOL BLOOD
DRIVES AND -
AND I NEED
ANOTHER DRINK.
NO, HON. YOU DON'T
NEED ANOTHER DRINK.
YOU KNOW, I NEED
ABOUT TEN DRINKS
TO GET TO
WHATEVER PLANE
YOU'RE ON, RIGHT NOW.
UH-HUH.
SO, WHO'S ON KEVIN'S
"PLANE" ANYWAY?
IS THAT YOUR VERY
DRUNK CHARMING WAY
OF ASKING ME IF I'M INVOLVED
WITH ANYONE, MS. RYAN?
'CAUSE -
(GIGGLES) NO.
NO?
I'M JUST, ACTUALLY,
ASKING IF YOU'RE GAY.
GAY?! WHAT?
NO, I'M NOT GAY.
IS THAT WHAT
YOU THINK?
HEAVENS, NO.
WHY? DO I COME
OFF AS GAY?
'CAUSE I THOUGHT -
A LITTLE.
DO I REALLY?
RIGHT ON.
GOOD TO KNOW.
NO, NO. I'M VERY
INTO CHICKS, ACTUALLY.
I LIKE CHICKS
QUITE A BIT.
SO WHY AREN'T
YOU MARRIED?
AH, WELL...UM...
I THINK I'VE JUST
ALWAYS BEEN
KINDA WAITING FOR
THAT ONE WOMAN
WHO I LIKE TO REFER
TO AS "THE IRIS."
OH MY GOD, YOU'RE ENGAGED
TO A WOMAN NAMED IRIS,
AND I'M SITTING HERE,
HITTING ON YOU -
NO, HON. NO,
CALM DOWN. IT'S-
BOY, YOU'RE DRUNK.
DO YOU, DO YOU KNOW WHAT
IT MEANS TO IRIS-IN?
NO, YOU WOULDN'T
REMEMBER IF YOU DID.
UM, IT'S A FILM TERM.
AND IT'S LIKE
AT THE END OF
A CHAPLIN SHORT -
YOU EVER SEE
ONE OF THOSE?
WHEN CHAPLIN'S
WALKIN' AWAY
AND THE CAMERA
AND IMAGE
IS GOING INTO SHRINKING
INTO A LITTLE CIRCLE.
"IRISING IN."
AND I THINK THAT I'VE
ALWAYS KINDA BEEN WAITING
FOR THAT ONE WOMAN
THAT JUST,
YOU KNOW,
MAKES ME IRIS IN.
I'M SORRY,
DO YOU SAY YOU WERE
LIKE, HITTING ON ME?
UM... I SHOULD...
EXCUSE ME.
OH MY GOD,
THAT WAS SO AWESOME.
WHAT?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T -
I, ARE YOU OKAY?
THAT WAS -
'CAUSE I - THAT WAS
AWESOME FOR ME.
CAITLIN:
I'M SO STUPID
ARE YOU?
CAITLIN, WAIT!
JOEY:
SO?
SO.
SO, YOU'VE BEEN
HOME HALF AN HOUR
AND YOU HAVEN'T
SAID A WORD.
I GET IT.
YOU DON'T WANT
TO TELL THE "DAD"
ALL THE PRIVATE
DETAILS.
EVEN IF THAT DAD DID PAY
FOR THE PLANE TICKET?
ASHLEY WAS HAPPY,
RIGHT?
THRILLED.
BLISSED OUT.
NEITHER OF US CAN WAIT
'TIL I GET THERE.
GOOD.
YEAH.
ALL THIS EXCITEMENT.
GOTTA SLEEP.
ALL RIGHT, BUDDY.
GET SOME REST.
WE GOT A BIG
DAY TOMORROW.
WE GOTTA GET YOU
LUGGAGE, MONEY BELT
SOME BRITISH POUNDS.
TALLY HO!
YOUNG LOVE.
AND NOT QUITE
SO YOUNG LOVE.
MMM.
MMM?
(LAUGHS)
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
KIND OF LOVE THAT WAS,
BUT THAT WAS GOOD.
MARRY ME?
HAVE YOU BEEN
DRINKING?
YES. NO. YES.
JUST MARRY ME.
I WANT TO COME
HOME TO YOU.
I WANNA WAKE
UP WITH YOU.
I WANT TO FOCUS ALL
MY ATTENTION ON YOU.
I THOUGHT YOU'D
NEVER ASK.
YES.
♪♪♪
HEY, YOU READY?
YOU GOT EVERYTHING?
YOUR CAMERA, PASSPORT?
ALL MY PHONE NUMBERS,
ASHLEY'S DAD'S NUMBER?
YES!
FOR THE 400TH TIME.
STOP WORRYING!
YOU'RE ALL GROWN UP.
HEY, I'M PROUD OF YOU,
YOU KNOW THAT?
YEAH.
HAVE A GREAT TRIP.
SEE YOU
IN SEPTEMBER.
YEAH.
WE'RE NOT GOING
TO THE AIRPORT.
THERE'S BEEN
A CHANGE OF PLANS.
CABBIE:
OKAY.