ALEX:
OW! STOP! OW!
AMY:
I LOVE HOW MATURE
YOUR BOYFRIEND IS.
ALEX:
PUT ME DOWN.
GREAT.
FIRST DOCTOR'S NOTE
I HAVE
THAT ISN'T A FORGERY
AND MR. "I-CAN-PICK-
UP-A-GIRL"
HAS TO MAKE IT
LOOK ALL SUSPICIOUS.
NATE:
HEY, EMMA.
DID JT SAY WHERE WE'RE SUPPOSED
TO LEAVE OUR COSTUMES?
NATE:
I'VE HAD MORE CONVERSATIONS
WITH THE JANITOR
THAN I'VE HAD WITH YOU.
I WAS ACTING.
JUST KISSING ALL MY NERVES OUT
PRE-DRESS REHEARSAL.
BUT DON'T WORRY, NATE.
I'LL WAIT FOR MY CUE
NEXT TIME.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
ARE YOU HOT
FOR DRACULA
OR ARE YOU TRYING
TO MESS WITH ME?
ARE YOU GOING TO BE
IN THE RAVINE AGAIN TONIGHT?
ARE WE GOING TO PARTY?
I THINK I NEED
ANOTHER BRACELET.
I DON'T LIKE BEING
MESSED WITH, OKAY?
I KNOW.
SIMPSON:
I NEED A MINUTE
WITH MY DAUGHTER.
OH, THAT'S ADORABLE, SIR.
CUT THE COMMENTARY,
JASON. GO.
AND STAND BY FOR CONCERNED
FATHER FIGURE LECTURE.
YOU COME IN AT 3:00
IN THE MORNING
HYSTERICAL, CRYING,
WANTING TO TALK
ABOUT THE SHOOTING
AND NOW YOU'RE KISSING
RANDOM GUYS?
IT WASN'T RANDOM.
PLEASE, EM.
LET ME BE HERE FOR YOU.
LET ME TALK TO YOU.
THE BELL'S GOING
TO GO.
NURSE PAULA:
THANKS, MARCO.
I'M TAPING THIS ONE
RIGHT TO MY COMPUTER MONITOR.
TAKE CARE, JIMMY.
JIMMY:
POOR NURSE PAULA,
SHE'S GONNA MISS ME.
BUT HOME...
HAS A FULL FRIDGE
AND A WIDE-SCREEN.
MARCO:
CRAIG AND I CAN COME
HANG OUT
WITHOUT VISITING HOURS.
WE CAN PLAY KID ELRICK
AS LOUD AS WE WANT.
YEAH, YOUR DAD
CAN TUCK YOU IN
INSTEAD OF
NURSE PAULA.
SHE'S THE ONLY THING
I'M GOING TO MISS
ABOUT THIS PLACE.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
DON'T BLOCK THE DOORWAY,
POPS.
NO TIME FOR SPEEDBUMPS.
YOU READY?
YOU LOOK GOOD, JIM.
I DON'T LIKE
"YOU LOOK GOOD, JIM".
THE RAILS THEY'RE
PUTTING IN AT THE CONDO,
THEY'RE NOT DONE.
NOT YET.
JIMMY:
SO?
SO I'M ALL OVER
THE CONTRACTORS.
SO?
ONE MORE WEEK - TOPS.
MAYBE SOONER
IF I CAN STRING IT.
MR. BROOKS,
JIMMY GETS AROUND
WELL.
I KNOW, JIMMY HAS MADE
GREAT PROGRESS,
BUT I CAN'T BE WITH HIM
24-7 RIGHT NOW.
AND I DON'T WANT SOMETHING
HAPPENING,
SOMETHING THAT'S
GOING TO TRASH
ALL THE PROGRESS
THAT HE'S MADE.
HE REALLY WANTS
TO GO.
WHAT ABOUT
MRS. BROOKS?
OR A NURSE?
I MEAN, WE COULD
EVEN HELP OUT.
FORGET IT, GUYS.
WHATEVER.
DANNY:
16TH MAY.
CASTLE DRACULA
IS A VIRTUAL PRISON
AND I'M ITS PRISONER.
IF NATE WAS
FIFTY AND FAT,
YOU COULD'VE CAUSED
CARDIAC ARREST.
ANYTHING FOR
THE THEATRE.
SHHHHH!
I NEED COMPLETE
TEEN-GIRL DETAILS.
WHY? GOOD? TONGUE?
LIKE IT OR NOT,
YOU BRING ANSWERS
OVER TONIGHT.
I HAVE TO GO TO
THE RAVINE TONIGHT.
I'M MEETING
SOME PEOPLE.
IS IT TOO MUCH
TO ASK FOR SILENCE
IN THE PEANUT GALLERY?
DANNY:
THERE IN THE MOONLIGHT
WERE THREE YOUNG WOMEN.
THREE?
AM I EVER GONNA
GET THREE OF THEM?
ALEX IS AT THE DOCTORS.
SHE SHOULD BE BACK.
JAY:
LEXI, IT WAS NOTHING.
C'MON.
JT:
"LEXI" IS LATE FOR HER SCENE.
ALEX:
YOU WANT A SCENE, JT?
HEY "BEST FRIEND AMY",
LET'S GIVE JT A SCENE.
TELL ME ABOUT
THE RAVINE, AMY!
ABOUT HOW YOU WENT DOWN
ON MY BOYFRIEND, AMY!
AND THE BRACELETS
YOU GOT FOR IT.
AMY:
I DIDN'T SLEEP WITH HIM!
ALEX:
BY WHOSE DEFINITION?
JAY:
COME OUTSIDE, ALEX.
DON'T TOUCH ME.
DON'T TALK TO ME.
I'LL DECK YOUR
SMUG FACE, TOO.
NURSE PAULA:
SHAKE IT OFF, MOPEY BROOKS.
I'M NOT MOPEY.
YOU KNOW,
A CHAIR'S ONLY A PRISON
IF YOU LET IT BE.
OKAY. STOP THE
INSPIRATIONAL QUOTES.
I'M NOT BUYING IT.
WHAT YOU SHOULDN'T BUY
IS YOUR DAD'S ATTITUDE.
YOU AND I BOTH KNOW
JIMMY BROOKS CAN DO WHATEVER
HE SETS HIS MIND TO.
AT LEAST, I KNOW IT.
MANNY:
IT DOESN'T TAKE SHERLOCK HOLMES
TO FIGURE IT OUT.
WHY WOULD YOU HOOK UP
WITH JAY?
ARE YOU IN LOVE
WITH HIM?
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
SO WHAT DO YOU
GET OUT OF IT?
THAT'S A REALLY
STUPID QUESTION.
NO, WHAT YOU'RE
DOING IS STUPID.
YOU'RE LETTING A DISGUSTING
BOTTOM-FEEDER USE YOU
TO SERIAL-CHEAT
ON HIS GIRLFRIEND.
SHOULD YOU REALLY BE PREACHING
TO ANYONE ABOUT THAT?
WE'RE NOT HAVING
REAL SEX.
IT'S PRETTY CLOSE!
BUT I'M NOT
GETTING PREGNANT.
WHY ARE YOU TRYING
TO HURT ME?
BECAUSE YOU WON'T
LEAVE ME ALONE.
YOU'RE BETTER THAN THIS.
YOU'RE BETTER THAN
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT WHO I AM
OR WHAT I'M WORTH
OR ANYTHING?
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
MARCO:
SPECIAL DELIVERY
FROM THE SORRY-YOUR-DAD-
A-SUCKS-A PIZZERIA.
JIMMY:
I'LL HOLD OUT 'TIL TOMORROW.
CRAIG:
WHAT'S TOMORROW?
JIMMY:
STUDENT COUNCIL PREZ-MAN
GETS YOU BOTH OUT
OF SCHOOL.
AND THEN YOU COME OVER HERE
AND BUST ME OUT.
CRAIG:
SOUNDS LIKE TROUBLE.
I'M NOT GOOD
WITH TROUBLE.
I NEED TO SEE
SOMETHING
BEYOND YOU TWO
AND THESE
UGLY-ASS WALLS.
TOMORROW.
YOU'RE HOUDINI
ON WHEELS.
OKAY.
AND HOUDINI WANTS
TO SEE KID ELRICK.
LIVE.
TOMORROW NIGHT.
YEAH.
EMMA:
HEY, HAVE YOU SEEN JAY?
GUY:
HANG WITH ME INSTEAD.
YOU CAN USE ANOTHER FRIEND,
RIGHT?
EMMA:
FRIENDS WITH BENEFITS.
GUY:
HEY, WE COULD ALL USE
A GOOD BENEFIT TOO.
EMMA:
MAYBE NEXT TIME.
JAY? CAN I CLIMB IN?
I WENT TO THE RAVINE,
BUT YOU WEREN'T THERE.
JAY:
MY DAY KINDA SUCKED
IN CASE YOU DIDN'T NOTICE.
EMMA:
SO LET'S MAKE YOU
FEEL BETTER.
JAY:
ALEX IS SICK
WITH SOME THING.
SHE THINKS
I GAVE IT TO HER
AND SHE WON'T TALK TO ME
SO I DON'T FEEL LIKE IT
TONIGHT.
AW, ARE YOU GOING
TO CRY NOW?
YOU ARE ONE
COLD GIRL.
THERE'S A TON OF GUYS
WHO WOULD LOVE A CHANCE
TO BE WITH ME.
RIGHT NOW,
I'M NOT ONE OF THEM.
JIMMY:
IT'S SWEET OF YOU TO BRING THIS
INCREDIBLE DISGUISE.
I HATE TO TELL YOU,
BUT IT DOES ABSOLUTELY
NOTHING
TO HIDE THE ENORMOUS
SHINY MASS OF SCRAP METAL
THAT I'M SITTING IN.
I THOUGHT
IT'D BE COOL
TO LOOK LIKE NINJAS.
HUSH. HE'S COMING.
HERE HE COMES.
IT'S COOL.
I'M HERE FOR DOCTOR
SCHINKELHATEN?
RECEPTIONIST:
I'M SORRY?
I MEAN
DR. SCHPITZELHAVEN!?
SIR, I'M AFRAID WE DON'T
HAVE ANYONE HERE BY THAT NAME.
(PHONE RINGS)
H.S. RYAN RECOVERY CENTRE,
GOOD AFTERNOON.
DR. SCHPILKISCHUN!
MARCO ON THE PHONE:
DR. SCHPIKENZITSKI HERE.
IT'S AN EMERGENCY
OF THE HIGHEST DEGREE.
(HYPERVENTILATING)
ARE YOU OKAY, SIR?
GO GET DR. SCHONKENHAUZER!
MARCO:
THE MAN IN FRONT OF YOU
IS EXTREMELY DANGEROUS.
I ASK YOU
TO LEAVE THE AREA.
ABANDON IT NOW!
RECEPTIONIST:
COULD YOU, UM,
WAIT HERE A SEC?
GO GET
DR. SCHONKENHAUZER!
GO, GO!
CRAIG:
COME ON, COME ON!
MARCO:
OPERATION JIMMY FREEDOM IS GO!
JIMMY:
OPEN THE DOOR.
RUSHING! RUSHING!
ALWAYS WITH YOU.
EMMA:
JAY.
JAY!
UM, ABOUT LAST NIGHT...
YOU ALL RIGHT?
IT'S JUST A SORE THROAT
THAT'S ALL.
I DON'T CARE ABOUT
ALEX OR ANYTHING, YOU KNOW.
REALLY I DON'T.
JT:
RAW EGG, HONEY AND LEMON.
DRINK.
JT MY VOICE IS JUST TIRED,
THAT'S ALL.
JT:
JUST DRINK, OKAY?
YOU TOLD ME YOU'D BE
ABLE TO DO THE SHOW,
SO YOU'RE GOING TO DO
THE SHOW. PERIOD.
THIS STUFF IS SO RUDE.
PERINO:
COME ON, TAKE YOUR SEAT,
THE BOTH OF YOU.
JT:
"PUBLIC HEALTH NURSE"?
OH GOODY. ANOTHER EVIL OMEN
TO PUT ME AT CALM.
MRS. BANERJEE:
SHOW OF HANDS.
ORAL SEX IS SAFER THAN
REGULAR INTERCOURSE?
WE THINK THERE'S BEEN
A MINI OUTBREAK
HERE AT DEGRASSI,
OF THIS.
GONORRHEA?
SORRY.
DID I SAY THAT OUT LOUD?
MRS. BANERJEE:
IT'S NOT A VERY NICE WORD,
IS IT?
GONORRHEA.
AND HOW DO YOU KNOW
IF YOU HAVE GONORRHEA?
WELL...
SOME SYMPTOMS
ARE GENITAL DISCHARGE,
BLEEDING, BURNING.
ORALLY, YOU MIGHT GET A FEVER
OR SORE THROAT.
HEY, EM, YOU GOT
SOMETHING TO TELL US?
SHUT UP.
MRS. BANERJEE:
AND SOMETIMES
THOSE WITH THE DISEASE
SHOW NO SYMPTOMS AT ALL.
LUCKY, YOU MIGHT THINK.
THINK AGAIN.
UNTREATED, GONORRHEA
CAN CAUSE ARTHRITIS,
HEART DISEASE,
INFERTILITY.
OKAY.
RECOGNIZE THIS?
(GIGGLES) GOOD.
IF YOU'VE HAD ANY SEX
WITHOUT USING ONE OF THESE,
YOU'RE AT RISK.
THIS APPLIES TO ORAL SEX
AS WELL,
ESPECIALLY IF YOU'VE HAD IT
WITH A BUNCH OF PEOPLE.
OR IF YOUR PARTNER HAS.
JIMMY:
THAT WAS SO INCREDIBLY
SCHTUPID.
CRAIG:
YOU'RE HERE, AREN'T YOU?
BREATHING FRESH BAR AIR?
MR. MOBILITY
JUST GOT CHECKED OUT.
THAT WAS MORE LIKE
A WHAT'S WITH THE GIMP
DRIVE-BY.
OH...
OH, MAN,
I'M SO SORRY.
LEAVE IT.
JIMMY:
YOU SURE?
I'M REALLY SORRY.
OKAY, GUYS,
LET'S GO BACK NOW.
NOT UNLESS THE KID
IS PERFORMING LIVE
IN YOUR HOSPITAL WING.
COME ON.
LIBERTY:
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I HAVE TO BE ALEX.
TELL ME YOU'RE AS NERVOUS
AS I AM?
MANNY:
IS THE POPE CATHOLIC?
DOES JAY HAVE
GONORRHEA?
MANNY.
ALEX AND AMY
HAPPEN TO BE SICK?
WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO DO OUT THERE?
I'M EMMA.
I PLAY THE PART OF MINA.
AND IF YOU HAVE
ANY CONSCIENCE AT ALL
YOU WILL NOT KISS
DRACULA!
EMMA!
THE KID'S GOING TO BE
ON ANY SECOND.
I CAN'T SEE A THING.
THERE AREN'T REALLY
ANY WHEELCHAIR SEATS.
THERE AREN'T ANY SEATS.
MAYBE THERE'S SOME
DOWN IN FRONT?
MAYBE THERE'S
A MANAGER.
YOU GUYS CAN'T
LEAVE ME HERE.
JUST TWO SECONDS,
OKAY BUDDY?
KID ELRICK:
GOOD EVENING, TORONTO!
OH, COME ON.
KID ELRICK:
YO, WHEN MY MANAGER SAID
WE SHOULD DO A SMALL
SHOW LIKE THIS,
I THOUGHT HE WAS BACK
ON THE SAUCE.
BUT IT'S WICKED-GOOD
TO SEE Y'ALL!
EXCUSE ME.
EXCUSE ME, EXCUSE ME...
I CAN'T REALLY SEE.
NO PROBLEM, MAN.
♪♪♪
JIMMY:
EXCUSE ME.
VIP, COMING THROUGH.
♪♪♪
NATE:
WHEN MY BRAIN SAYS COME TO YOU,
YOU SHALL CROSS LAND
OR SEA TO DO MY BIDDING.
AND TO THAT END - THIS!
EMMA:
BUT NO, I CANNOT!
DRACULA!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
KEEP GOING!
WHAT HAVE I DONE?
WHAT HAVE I DONE
TO DESERVE SUCH A FATE?
I, WHO HAVE WALKED
IN MEEKNESS
AND RIGHTEOUSNESS
ALL MY DAYS.
GOD, PITY ME!
(APPLAUSE)
EMMA:
YOU THREW THE SCENE!
THAT WAS COMPLETELY
UNPROFESSIONAL!
I'D RATHER BE THAT
THAN DISEASED.
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
THERE ISN'T ENOUGH
ANTIBIOTIC IN THE WORLD
THAT WOULD MAKE ME
KISS YOU.
AND THAT LITTLE SMOOCH
IN THE HALL THE OTHER DAY?
WHO KNOWS WHAT I CAUGHT
FROM THAT.
THANKS SO MUCH.
SCREW HIM.
WHY DID YOU
DO THIS TO ME?
JAY:
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
YOU GAVE ME
A SOCIAL DISEASE.
YOU SAID
YOU DIDN'T CARE.
EVEN THIS MORNING
YOU SAID IT.
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE,
OKAY?
LOOK, I NEVER TOLD ALEX
ABOUT YOU, EMMA.
I LIKED HOW YOU HAD
VIRTUE OR WHATEVER.
I DON'T.
NOT ANY OF THAT.
COME ON, WHO ARE YOU
TRYING TO FOOL?
EVERYBODY KNOWS.
EVERYBODY KNOWS
ABOUT THE REAL YOU.
JUST...
DANNY:
DEAREST LUCY...
FORGIVE ME.
FORGIVE US ALL!
(SCREAMING)
HOLD FAST, DEAR BOY.
HOLD FAST!
CRAIG:
MAN, WE WERE SO CLOSE
THE KID WAS BASICALLY
SWEATING ON US.
MARCO:
MAN, I'M NEVER GONNA SHOWER.
CRAIG:
WHAT?
JIMMY:
THE KID SMELLS
LIKE JACK DANIELS.
MR. BROOKS:
YOUR NURSE CALLED.
I'M FURIOUS.
SO WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO,
GROUND ME?
LOOK, TODAY WAS
AN OBSTACLE COURSE, OKAY?
AND I BROUGHT MY "A" GAME.
I HAD AN "A" GAME.
JAMES, LISTEN.
NO, I'M READY
TO COME HOME.
NOW YOU HAVE
TO BE READY FOR IT.
WILL YOU BE HERE
TOMORROW MORNING?
DEPENDS.
WHAT ARE YOU OFFERING?
WE'LL FIND YOU
A HOME-CARE PERSON
TO FILL IN THE GAP,
BE WITH YOU
ALL THE TIME.
OKAY?
OKAY.
THANK YOU.
SPIKE:
SHE WAS SO AMAZING.
I COULDN'T BELIEVE
IT WAS THE SAME GIRL.
SIMPSON:
KATE HEPBURN WAS REBORN.
SPIKE:
DID WE WAKE YOU,
MISS HEPBURN?
EMMA:
I WASN'T ASLEEP.
SIMPSON:
POST-SHOW ADRENALINE.
YOU PROBABLY FEEL FANTASTIC
RIGHT NOW, HUH?
AND FOR THE RECORD?
SNAKE AND ME WALKING
ON EGGSHELLS AROUND YOU
IS OFFICIALLY OVER.
OUR GIRL'S BACK.
I JUST WANTED YOU
TO BE PROUD BEFORE
OF HOW BRAVE
AND PERFECT I WAS.
AFTER EVERYTHING HAPPENED
AND RICK DIED...
I COULDN'T HOLD ON
TO IT ANYMORE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE
BRAVE OR PERFECT EVER.
JUST BE YOU.
BUT WHAT IF I DON'T LIKE ME
VERY MUCH RIGHT NOW?
I NEED SOMEBODY
TO TAKE ME TO THE CLINIC.
ARE YOU SICK?
DO YOU HAVE A FEVER?
I JUST NEED TO GO
TO THE HEALTH UNIT.
TOMORROW.
SIMPSON:
THERE'S SOMETHING GOING
AROUND THE SCHOOL RIGHT NOW,
BUT IT WAS A VERY
SPECIFIC GROUP,
AND EM,
IF YOU'RE WORRIED
THERE'S A GOOD CHANCE
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE.
I HAVE TO BE.
SPIKE:
EMMA?
JUST SAY
YOU'LL TAKE ME.
JUST SAY.