I WAS FIXATED
ON YOUR EARLOBES
FOR MOST OF THE CLASS.
SO MY NANOCOMPUTER
LESSON WAS DULL.
THAT MY EYES WERE EVEN OPEN
IN MEDIA IMMERSION
IS A TESTAMENT TO YOU.
SO STOP WORRYING,
OKAY?
I'M BEING GRADED
ON HOW WELL I HOLD
A CLASS TOMORROW.
THAT'S SCARY.
YOU GUYS ARE SCARY.
MARCO'S NOT SCARY.
MARCO'S AFRAID
OF BEES.
HEATHER SINCLAIR -
NOT SCARY.
UNLESS MAYBE YOU SEE HER
IN HER GRANNY PANTIES
AFTER GYM.
THERE'S ALSO
THE TINY FACT
THAT YOU'RE A PHENOMENAL
TEACHER.
SO PLEASE,
FEAR NOT.
YOU'RE SWEET.
AND NOT JUST BECAUSE
YOU MADE LEMON SQUARES.
(BABY CRYING)
THE PARK.
GREAT ROMANCE IDEA,
HON.
POOR KID'S BLINDED BY THE GLARE
OFF HIS DAD'S LEGS.
CAN YOU SAY
WHITER-THAN-WHITE?
YEAH, SIMPSON.
OH MY GOD.
HE DIDN'T SEE US.
NO WAY.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
I TOTALLY MISSED
WASHING MY HAIR
TO MAKE IT IN TIME
FOR THIS?
DARCY:
PAIGE SKIPS
PRACTICE AGAIN.
GUYS, LET'S GO
WITH A 3-4-3 START.
READY FOR A RIGHT
HERKIE JUMP.
OKAY. LET'S GO.
JUST SO YOU KNOW,
I AM NOT COOL
WITH YOU TAKING OVER.
PAIGE WON'T CARE.
SHE'S TOO WRAPPED UP IN MATT
TO EVEN NOTICE.
IT'S A CRUSH.
NO BIG THING.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO LIE.
PAIGE TOLD ME ABOUT HER HOT
AFTER-SCHOOL AFFAIR.
OOPS.
I DID IT AGAIN.
MANNY:
ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
LETS GET IT TOGETHER.
MATT:
LET'S DISCUSS HOW
THIS CIGARETTE AD
TRIES TO MANIPULATE US.
ANYONE?
EMMA. LET'S HEAR IT.
OKAY. WELL, I THINK IT'S AIMED
AT A FEMALE DEMOGRAPHIC?
AND I THINK THE TOBACCO
COMPANIES
ARE TRYING TO TELL US
THAT HEALTHY WOMEN CAN SMOKE
BECAUSE SHE'S HIKING
OR WHATEVER.
MATT:
GOOD.
NOW AND IN TERMS OF SUBTLER
MESSAGING,
LIKE WHERE IS SHE?
OR WHERE IS SHE GOING?
I'M LESS SURE.
PROBABLY TO THE RAVINE.
THAT'S ENOUGH,
MR. SHARPE.
WHAT ISN'T THE AD
SHOWING US, EMMA?
ANYTHING NEGATIVE.
UM... LUNG CANCER,
EMPHYSEMA, STROKE.
GONORRHEA.
MATT:
OKAY. SEE ME AFTER CLASS.
WE'LL HAVE A LESSON
ON RESPECT.
THANK YOU,
MR. OLEANDER.
MATT:
OKAY, MOVING ON.
NANOTECH IS FINALLY WINNING
THE RESPECT IT DESERVES
AS A SCIENCE.
PAIGE.
SHH! MR. OLEANDER
IS TEACHING.
IS MANNY YOUR
NEW BEST FRIEND?
OKAY, CAN WE PLEASE DEAL WITH
WHATEVER YOUR PROBLEM IS LATER,
GREEN-EYED HAZELMONSTER?
MATT:
HAZEL.
CAN I HAVE
YOUR ATTENTION PLEASE?
SHE SPILLED.
ABOUT YOU AND MR. O.
YOU DO KNOW
THAT YOU CAN BE SECRECY
CHALLENGED SOMETIMES, RIGHT?
HOW COULD YOU
NOT TELL ME?
HAZEL. HI.
DIDN'T YOU HEAR ME?
GEE, MR. OLEANDER,
I THOUGHT YOU ONLY HAD
EYES FOR PAIGE.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
UH, YEAH.
I'VE JUST UM...
I'VE JUST LOST MY,
LOST MY PLACE.
UM... HOLLYWOOD HAS SEIZED
ON NANOTECH LATELY.
CAN ANYONE NAME A MOVIE
ABOUT SELF-REPLICATING
MACHINES?
ANYONE?
DARCY:
SHEILA TOLD ME
THAT IF YOU PUT KETCHUP
ON YOUR FRIES,
THE TOMATO ACID BURNS
THE CARBS RIGHT AWAY.
CHANTAY:
SHE'S A CAFETERIA LADY.
EVER THINK SHE'S TRYING
TO GET YOU TO BUY MORE FRIES?
EM, WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOUR EYES?
I'M TRYING TO KILL CHRIS
WITH MY MIND.
OH, GOODY.
THEN YOU CAN GET SPINNER,
JAY, CRAIG,
JT, NATE AND SEAN.
HERE'S ME WISHING
I LET MY DAD TALK ME
INTO AN ALL GIRLS SCHOOL.
NO JOKE,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
HONEY, YOU CAN'T LET HIM
UPSET YOU LIKE THAT.
HE'S JUST ONE DOOF.
NO, IT'S ALL THE GUYS.
JUDGING CONSTANTLY.
CHESTER:
MMM, DEEP-FRIED STARCH.
IS HE NOT THE YUMMIEST
THING YOU EVER SAW?
MANNY:
EM, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
THIS WEEKEND?
EMMA:
NOTHING.
HOW ABOUT THE GIRLS
AND I COME OVER
AND WE'LL HAVE THE GIRLIEST SPA
WEEKEND EVER.
ZERO TESTOSTERONE.
HELLO?
IS ANYONE FREE TO CONSOLE
A SISTER THIS WEEKEND?
ABSOLUTELY.
WE'RE THERE FOR YOU.
I AM SO, SO,
SO SORRY.
MATT:
TEENAGERS ARE EVIL.
I CAN'T GO BACK IN THERE
AND TEACH TWO MORE PERIODS.
WHAT HAZEL DID?
IT WAS JUVENILE
AND HATEFUL
AND HUMILIATING.
I PROMISE YOU,
NOTHING LIKE IT
WILL EVER HAPPEN AGAIN.
EVER.
I DON'T WANT TO GET BOOTED OUT
OF TEACHER'S COLLEGE.
I CAN'T.
YOU WON'T.
I WON'T LET YOU.
SORRY, MADAME PAGE.
EXCUSEZ-MOI.
HAPPY WEEKEND, PAIGE!
WHY THANKS, MANNY.
AND THANKS FOR TAKING
MY PRACTICE THIS MORNING.
YOU WANT ME
TO THANK YOU?
FOR WHAT?
DROPPING A DIRTY BOMB
ON MY LIFE?
PRACTICE WENT AWESOME
WITHOUT YOU.
AND IF YOU ASK
SOME OF US,
THAT WASN'T
A COINCIDENCE.
YOU TOLD HAZEL.
WHEN YOU SWORE THAT
YOU WOULDN'T.
I THOUGHT SHE KNEW,
OKAY? CHILL.
DON'T USE YOUR OUTDATED
SLANG ON ME.
I DOUBT THAT YOUR MOUTH
IS EVEN CONNECTED
TO YOUR TINY, SHRIVELED,
BOY-OBSESSED BRAIN!
I'M THE DUMB ONE?
WHO STILL HASN'T FIGURED OUT
NOT TO CHASE OLDER GUYS.
GUYS SO OUT OF HER LEAGUE
IT'S NOT FUNNY?
BIG WORDS FROM A GIRL
WHO PICKS UP MY LEFTOVERS.
COULD YOU BE
MORE SELF-OBSESSED?
ALL YOU THINK ABOUT
IS YOUR OWN BUTT,
WHICH PROBABLY DOES REQUIRE
A LOT OF THOUGHT
GIVEN THAT IT'S HUGE.
♪ DO YOU WANT
TO TOUCH ME TONIGHT? ♪
TO GET ME TONIGHT? ♪
♪ GOOD LUCK CATCHING ME
TONIGHT ♪
♪ I'M A BAD... ♪
♪ BABY, BABY PLEASE, ♪
♪ WHY DON'T YOU COME TO ME ♪
♪ AND I'LL MOVE THAT BODY,
YEAH ♪
♪ IS IT DIGGING ME? ♪
♪ OH, COME ON! ♪
HATZILAKOS:
STOP!
MATT:
MANNY. CALM DOWN.
HEY, MR. PEDOPHILE.
I MEAN OLEANDER.
DON'T MAKE YOUR
GIRLFRIEND PAIGE
EVEN MORE JEALOUS OF ME.
HATZILAKOS:
MANNY. MY OFFICE, MONDAY.
PAIGE.
MR. OLEANDER. NOW.
ALL RIGHT EVERYONE
SCHOOL IS OUT.
GO HOME!
SHOW IS OVER.
NOW!
I SAID NOW.
THE WHOLE WORLD'S GOING
TO HATE ME
IF I GET HIM FIRED.
YOU'RE IN LOVE.
WHAT WERE YOU
SUPPOSED TO DO?
ABSTAIN FROM CONTACT
WITH MALE HUMANS.
SEEING AS HOW I'M PAIGE,
THE BERMUDA TRIANGLE
OF LOVE.
HAZEL:
HI, I'M HAZEL.
JUST WHO YOU WANT TO SEE.
WOW, SHE'S NOT JUST
AN EVIL BACK-STABBER,
SHE'S KINDA WITTY,
TOO.
HAZEL:
PAIGE.
I'M SO SORRY.
YOU WERE RIGHT.
I AM SECRECY CHALLENGED.
AT LEAST YOU DIDN'T CALL HIM
A PEDOPHILE.
HATZILAKOS:
PAIGE?
WELL, THIS WAS
A RATHER UPSETTING DAY.
MANNY SANTOS IS A LIAR,
OKAY?
SHE LIES.
NOTHING EVER HAPPENED
BETWEEN YOU AND MR. OLEANDER?
THAT WOULD BE WRONG.
HE WAS TUTORING ME
AND THAT'S ALL.
MR. SIMPSON HAS ALREADY
LEFT FOR THE DAY,
AND FRANKLY, I'M LESS THAN
COMFORTABLE DISCUSSING THIS
WITHOUT ONE OF YOUR
PARENTS BEING HERE.
IS THAT TOTALLY NEEDED?
HATZILAKOS:
WE'LL ALL GONNA MEET MONDAY
AT 8:00 A.M.
BUT I THINK
I SHOULD WARN YOU.
THERE'S A PRETTY BIG
DISCREPANCY
IN YOUR REPORTS.
REPORTS?
TAKES ON THE SITUATION.
MR. OLEANDER HAS A VERY
DIFFERENT ONE.
HE TOLD ME THAT YOU WERE
OBSESSED WITH HIM.
THAT YOU FOLLOWED HIM,
WOULDN'T LEAVE HIM ALONE.
YOU STALKED HIM.
SPIKE:
HOLD THIS RIGHT
ON THE SCRATCHES.
MORE MOCKTAILS,
COMING RIGHT UP.
CHANTAY:
SO PAIGE BASICALLY FIGHTS YOU
BECAUSE OF A GUY?
MANNY:
PAIGE BASICALLY FIGHTS ME
BECAUSE SHE'S A PSYCHO WENCH.
SHE FOUGHT YOU
BECAUSE GUYS ARE ALWAYS TURNING
WOMEN AGAINST EACH OTHER.
WELL, THAT'S TRUE.
EMMA:
I'D RATHER BE THE WAY
WE ARE NOW.
NO GUYS, NO JUDGING,
NO UPSET.
I LIKE THAT WE DON'T HAVE
TO WORRY ABOUT BEING PRETTY.
JUST US.
LET'S DECLARE
THE REVOLUTION BEGUN.
TO HECK WITH GUYS!
CHESTER:
'SUP, GIRLS?
ALL:
CHESTER'S YOUR NEIGHBOUR?
HE JUST MOVED IN.
SO?
CHESTER:
YOU'RE LOOKING
A LITTLE GREEN.
WHERE ARE YOU
GOING?!
I AM DISFIGURED!
HAVING A SLUMBER PARTY,
EMMALINE?
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
HI.
PAIGE:
(ANGRILY) HI?
YOU'RE JUST GONNA
SAY HI?
LOOK,
I TRIED CALLING.
YOU WEREN'T PICKING UP
YOUR PHONE.
I'M GLAD YOU CAME OVER.
GEE, WHY DIDN'T I PUT
A MICROPHONE IN MY BRA?
THAT'S SUCH A NOVICE
PSYCHO STALKER MISTAKE.
I KNOW YOU'RE UPSET.
ME, TOO.
NO, I'M NOT.
I'M LIVID. BOILING.
PISSED BEYOND
ALL RECOGNITION.
CAN WE TALK
ABOUT THIS?
YOU HAVE THREE MINUTES.
PAIGE, YOU KNOW WHAT
THIS JOB MEANS TO ME.
YOU KNOW WHAT SCHOOL
MEANS TO ME.
I'M WAITING
FOR THE US PART.
US...
I FIGURED WE LEAVE TIME
FOR IT TO BLOW OVER AND...
WHEN IT'S SUMMER,
WE'RE HOME FREE.
AND IN THE MEANTIME
I GET - WHAT - EXPELLED?
REFERRED TO AS THAT SAD,
DESPERATE LOONY
WHO STALKS T.A.S?
I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT ELSE TO SAY.
PLEASE. YOU WANTED
TO LOOK LIKE THE GOOD GUY.
DON'T KID YOURSELF!
OKAY, PAIGE,
YOU HAD A PUBLIC FIGHT
WITH MANNY SANTOS
AFTER PROMISING ME
NOTHING ELSE WOULD BE SAID!
SHE WAS REALLY MEAN!
WHY AM I DOING THIS?
MY ENTIRE FUTURE
IS ON THE LINE.
MANNY:
EMMA'S TAKING DIBS
ON ALL THE GOOD T-SHIRTS.
SHE MUST BE STOPPED.
EMMA:
THEY DON'T SEEM TOO CONCERNED
WITH THEIR TIE-DYE PROSPECTS
AT THE MOMENT.
CHESTER HAD BETTER
COME OUT SOON.
THESE ARE FIFTEEN
MINUTE SHOES, MAX.
THIS IS SUPPOSED
TO BE ABOUT US.
BOY-LESS FUN,
REMEMBER?
A MOVEMENT?
DARCY:
OH MY GOD,
THERE'S THREE OF HIM.
MULTIPLE ADORABLE
CHESTERS?
EM, I'M SORRY,
BUT IT'S THE CALL
OF THE WILD.
HEY CHESTER
AND COPIES,
HIT ME!
BOY:
OH, NICE ONE.
WHY DID YOU DO THAT?
(SCREAMING)
DARCY:
CHESTER! THIS ISN'T FUNNY!
CHESTER:
YOU GIRLS HAVE NO SENSE
OF HUMOUR.
THAT WAS HILARIOUS.
HE'S SO GONNA REGRET THAT.
ALEX:
DID YOU KNOW FAKE CHEESE
IS ONE INGREDIENT AWAY
FROM BEING PLASTIC?
JUST LIKE
MANNY SANTOS.
MR. O'S THE ONE
YOU SHOULD BE MAD AT.
THAT WASN'T EXACTLY
A PRINCE CHARMING MOVE.
YEAH.
EXCEPT WHAT IF I KIND OF
MISS HIM ALREADY?
IS THAT BAD?
SHOOT ME.
DROWN ME IN FAKE CHEESE.
ALEX:
IT'S NOT THAT BAD.
AND HEY, NOW YOU KNOW
HE'S HUMAN.
NOT SOME YOGA-BODIED
TEACHER GOD.
MEERI:
IS THIS A COFFEE KLATSCH
OR A WORKPLACE?
BECAUSE IT SURE AIN'T
A SELF-SERVE.
THOSE THINGS ARE CUSTOMERS.
WELCOME TO MY NIGHTMARE.
COMBO?
DYLAN:
WHERE IS HE?
MARCO:
DYLAN'S FEELING ALL MACHO
ABOUT THE WHOLE MATT THING.
SORRY.
DYLAN:
NO ONE TAKES ADVANTAGE
OF YOU LIKE THAT, OKAY?
YOU'RE MY SISTER.
I'M WORKING, OKAY, HULK?
SHHH!
THE GUY'S A PREDATOR.
PAIGE:
HE'S, LIKE,
THE SAME AGE AS YOU.
ARE YOU PREYING ON MARCO?
PAIGE:
MATT'S NOT PERFECT.
HE'S JUST...
JUST DISGUSTING.
JUST WONDERFUL.
AND SWEET AND FUN
AND HE PUT EVERYTHING
ON THE LINE FOR ME.
I'M SUCH A JERK.
♪♪♪
MANNY:
HE'S GOING TO BE
SO GROSSED OUT.
EMMA:
HOLD THE LADDER STEADY.
DARCY:
THERE'S NO TIME!
PLEASE. MANNY?
WE ARE WOMEN,
HEAR AS ROAR, CHESTER.
EMMA, PLEASE BE CAREFUL.
HURRY UP.
(SIRENS)
CHESTER:
HEY, EMMALINE.
MONDAY...
I'LL GO ALONG WITH IT.
WITH YOUR STORY.
I LOST MY TEMPER WITH MANNY.
MICHALCHUKS,
WE HAVE TEMPERS.
(SIGHS) PAIGE.
YOU CAN'T LOSE
YOUR ENTIRE LIFE.
NOT JUST FOR KISSING SOME
SELFISH HIGH SCHOOL CHICK.
CAN'T HAPPEN.
I UH...
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY.
PLEASE DON'T SAY ANYTHING.
JUST TRY AND LOOK
CUTE ON MONDAY
SO IT ALL FEELS LIKE
IT WAS WORTH IT?
PAIGE.
THERE IS NO
STRINGS ATTACHED.
DON'T WORRY.
THERE'S NO STRINGS
WITH US.
I DON'T NEED MY PARENTS
TO PROTECT ME.
I'M ONLY TELLING THE TRUTH.
I WAS INAPPROPRIATE
WITH MR. OLEANDER
AND I'D LIKE TO TRANSFER OUT
OF HIS CLASS IMMEDIATELY.
SIMPSON:
IT'S THE ONLY MEDIA IMMERSION
CLASS OFFERED IN GRADE 11.
YOU WILL FAIL THE COURSE.
PAIGE:
SO I'LL REPEAT IT NEXT YEAR.
SIMPSON:
EVERY GRADE TWELVE CREDIT
IS TAKEN, PAIGE,
FOR UNIVERSITY
APPLICATIONS.
WELL, THEN MAYBE I SHOULD
JUST TRANSFER SCHOOLS ENTIRELY.
NOW.
HATZILAKOS:
IT'S MAY.
TRANSFERRING SO LATE,
CHANCES ARE YOU CAN'T COMPLETE
THE ACADEMIC YEAR.
YOU WILL FAIL ENTIRELY.
HAVE YOU REALLY THOUGHT
THIS THROUGH?
YOU SHOULD BE GETTING
SET UP FOR UNIVERSITY,
NOT ACTING LIKE
YOU'RE IN KINDERGARTEN.
MR. SIMPSON.
I'M SORRY, BUT I'M NOT BUYING
WHAT SHE'S SELLING.
ANYTHING I SAW
DIDN'T LOOK TOO ONE-SIDED.
YOU SAW SOMETHING?
PAIGE:
LEAVE IT, SIR.
PLEASE LEAVE IT.
SIMPSON:
NO, I CAN'T.
I TRUSTED YOU WITH MY KIDS.
AND MY KIDS TRUSTED YOU,
INCLUDING HER.
PLEASE STOP IT?
CAN WE JUST STOP?
MATT'S PROFESSOR:
STUDENTS OFTEN HAVE FEELINGS
FOR THEIR TEACHERS.
YOU JUST TOOK YOUR FEELINGS
TOO FAR.
WE CAN HELP.
SIMPSON:
OKAY, I'M NOT GONNA SIT HERE
AND WATCH THIS.
PAIGE:
I DON'T CARE IF I FAIL,
JUST CAN WE FINISH THIS NOW?
PLEASE?
DAPHNE,
WHOSE SIDE ARE WE ON, HUH?
THE STUDENTS
OR THE TEACHERS?
I NEED TO KNOW
WHAT YOU SAW ARCHIE.
HOW CAN I MAKE A DECISION
IF I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU SAW?
MATT'S PROFESSOR:
THERE IS A LOT AT STAKE HERE.
WE HAD A RELATIONSHIP.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WE'VE SEEN EACH OTHER
OUTSIDE OF SCHOOL.
IT SHOULDN'T HAVE HAPPENED.
I TAKE FULL RESPONSIBILITY.
CHESTER:
HO HO HO.
EMMA:
YOU CAN'T LABEL PEOPLE.
CHESTER:
WHOA.
I THOUGHT
IT WAS CHRISTMAS.
HOW WAS JAIL?
I ONLY GOT A WARNING.
SADLY,
I GOT ANOTHER WARNING
ABOUT CHUCK AND CHAD.
ABOUT WHO?
MY BROTHERS.
THEY'RE PLOTTING
THEIR REVENGE.
SO YOUR NAMES ARE CHESTER,
CHUCK AND CHAD?
CONSIDER ME YOUR MOLE
BEHIND ENEMY LINES,
TWO DOORS DOWN.
I'LL KEEP YOU POSTED.
OKAY, THANKS.
I APPRECIATE IT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU DID THAT.
THAT MAKES TWO OF US.
YOU DOING OKAY?
WELL, I CAN STAY
IN THE B.A. PROGRAM
BUT TEACHER'S COLLEGE
IS DONE.
WELL, MAYBE I COULD
CALL YOUR SCHOOL,
TELL THEM IT WAS
MY FAULT OR SOMETHING?
I THINK WE'VE LEARNED
THAT REALLY DOESN'T WORK.
I WANT YOU TO KNOW,
YOU WOULD'VE BEEN WORTH
LOSING MY YEAR OVER.
EXCEPT I WOULDN'T
HAVE BEEN WORTH VERY MUCH
IF I LET YOU DO THAT.
AND I WOULDN'T
HAVE LET YOU DO IT.
YOU KNOW THAT,
RIGHT?
AND NOT BECAUSE
OF GUILT,
OR ME BEING
A GENTLEMAN OR-
MATT. I KNOW.
I GUESS
THE GOOD NEWS IS
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHO SEES US IN THE PARK?
YEAH.
THAT IS THE GOOD NEWS.