I CHRISTEN THEE...
UH, WHAT'S YOUR
NEW BABY'S NAME, SPIN?
SPARKY?
LOOKS LIKE A SPARKY.
HERBIE? THOMAS?
THE LOVE-MOBILE.
THAT'S WHAT THIS IS.
IT'S OUR LOVE-MOBILE.
AND YOU'RE CALLING
ME A DORK?
HEY! YOU DON'T OWN
THAT QUITE YET.
TWENTY SEVEN HUNDRED DOLLARS.
386 MISERABLE HOURS
OF WAITING TABLES.
JOEY:
CONGRATULATIONS.
♪♪♪
WICKED, WICKED,
WICKED DAY!
OKAY.
TONIGHT I'M TAKING YOU
TO THE DRIVE-IN!
WE LOAD UP THE CAR
WITH SOME BLANKETS,
SOME SLOW JAMS
OF LOVE.
UHM.
BREATH SPRAY FOR YOU.
SPINNER:
HOLY CRAP ON A STICK.
OH MY GOD!
I TOLD YOU
WE WERE SPEEDING!
WHAT DO WE DO?
NICE DAY,
HUH OFFICER?
LOVELY.
I'M LOOKING FOR
A PAIGE MITCHELLCHOOK
AT THIS ADDRESS?
MICHALCHUK.
UM, I'M PAIGE.
NOTICE TO APPEAR?
YOU PRESSED CHARGES
IN A SEXUAL ASSAULT CASE
IN 2002?
WOW. UM...
REALLY?
NOW?
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(SCREAMING)
(SCREAM)
EW! CUDDLES PLEASE!
AHHHH!
ARR!
I HATE ZOMBIES MOVIES,
DIDN'T I TELL YOU?
OH, THEY'RE TOTALLY
DEVOURING THAT CHICK!
GROSS!
YET, I CAN'T EVEN SEE.
OKAY. WELL,
IT'S MORE THAN
WE SHORTIES COULD SEE
IF WE WERE STUCK
BEHIND YOU, BEE-BEE!
YEAH,
BUT IT'S MY CAR.
AAHHH!
OKAY, ENOUGH
WITH THE CREEPY
UNDEAD WRESTLERS.
WHO NEEDS MORE CORN?
THIS MOVIE SURE
DOESN'T.
(CHUCKLES)
UH, YEAH.
I'LL COME WITH YOU.
UH, YOU GUYS
NEED ANYTHING?
YOU KNOW,
KEEP UP YOUR ENERGY...
OR FLUIDS?
GUYS?
NO?
OH, I WANT MORE
OF THOSE SOUR
THINGIES TOO.
WHO CARES
ABOUT CARBS?
EWW! WOW.
UM, ROMANTIC.
AND SINCE
I'M AS HUNGRY
AS PARIS HILTON
LOOKS...
COME ON,
THERE'S NO WAY
YOU'RE SURVIVING
THIS FLESH-EATING-FEST
ON YOUR OWN, LOV.
DID YOU SEE HOW
THOSE VEINS
WERE DANGLING
FROM THEIR SEVERED HEADS?
I WAS DISTRACTED
BY HER HUGE SILICONE
INVESTMENTS.
IT'S THE HEAVIEST BOX
IN THE WORLD!
DON'T MAKE ME LAUGH.
I'LL DROP THIS
ON YOUR TOE.
UGH!
ARR!
COME HERE.
WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
FOR BEING
SO DARNED CUTE.
TURN IT OVER.
AWW. UGH.
FOR HELPING ME MOVE.
FOR BORROWING
YOUR DAD'S VAN.
FOR TELLING
YOUR DAD
A FANTASTIC LIE
ABOUT WHO NEEDED
TO BORROW IT.
UM, ALL I KNOW
IS THAT YOU OWE US, DYLAN,
FOR MAKING US DO THIS
ON LABOUR DAY -
THE OFFICIAL FUNERAL
OF SUMMER VACATION.
WELL, CONSIDER ME
YOUR LIVING, BREATHING
VIP PAS
TO EVERY DORM PARTY
THIS YEAR.
AND THE FIRST ONE IN,
OH, ONLY 54 HOURS.
GRADE ELEVEN
WITH DORM PARTIES...
HAVING CAKE,
EATING CAKE TOO.
AND, UH, WON'T YOU
BE THE LIFE
OF MY ALL-YEAR PARTY,
MR. POUTY?
YEAH, LIKE YOU WANT
TO PARTY WITH ME.
OKAY,
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
YOU'RE MY GIRLFRIEND.
THAT'S MY PROBLEM.
SPINNER.
WE'RE ALWAYS WITH
THREE THOUSAND PEOPLE.
AND IF WE'RE NOT,
YOU INVITE THEM.
UH, DYLAN'S MOVING
AND MARCO'S
HIS BOYFRIEND.
THEY HAVE TO BE HERE.
WE'RE NEVER ALONE,
OKAY?
YOU MAKE ME FEEL LIKE
SOME KIND OF LEOPARD.
LEPER.
THE WORD IS LEPER.
I'M SORRY.
OKAY?
IT WON'T ALWAYS
BE LIKE THIS.
REALLY?
IT'LL CHANGE.
ONCE THAT STUPID TRIAL
IS FINALLY OVER.
I PROMISE.
LOVEBIRDS...
I NEED SOMEONE
TO HELP ME
MOVE MY WARDROBE
AND I NEED SOMEONE
TO GO TO MRS. SPINNELI'S
TO GET OUR PIZZA.
I GOT THE PIZZA PART.
OKAY.
HOW MANY BOXES
ARE LEFT?
OH 25, MAYBE.
OH...
THAT ONE'S 60 POUNDS.
(DOG BARKING)
JR PISTONS,
NEW RAD.
PAIGE:
I DON'T THINK SO!
DEAN!
DEAN:
...FLY WHEEL,
FRICTION CLUTCH,
AND THESE UH,
HIGH CORE EXCEL WIRES.
SERIOUS STUFF.
HEY!
PAIGE:
DON'T!
WAIT. PAIGE.
I'M NOT STALKING YOU.
WE'RE IN A PUBLIC PARK,
THERE'S PEOPLE
EVERYWHERE.
COULD WE TALK?
JUST ONE MINUTE?
SO, COURT, HUH?
I'M NOT SUPPOSED
TO TALK TO YOU.
IT'S GOING
TO BE REALLY HORRIBLE,
GOING THROUGH
IT ALL.
OUR PARENTS HEARING
THE DETAILS,
MY GIRLFRIEND,
YOUR BOYFRIEND.
IT WAS A REALLY
LONG TIME AGO.
I'M SORRY,
I SHOULD'VE LISTENED TO YOU.
IT WAS A HUGE MISTAKE.
IF I COULD GO BACK...
DO YOU HAVE A POINT?
WHY GO THROUGH THIS?
YOU COULD TELL THEM
YOU DON'T WANT TO TESTIFY,
SKIP IT.
IT'D BE THAT EASY.
THEY'D HAVE TO DROP
THE CASE.
MY BROTHER'S PIZZA.
UM...
IT'S GETTING COLD.
OKAY. BUT...
YOU'LL THINK ABOUT IT,
RIGHT?
I MEAN, MAYBE
WE NEVER SEE
EACH OTHER AGAIN.
AND YOU COULD FORGET.
EMMA:
CHRIS AND I BROKE UP
IN JULY.
SORRY.
KENDRA AND I BROKE UP
IN AUGUST.
SORRY. I BELIEVE
I WAS ABDUCTED BY ALIENS
OVER LABOUR DAY
WEEKEND.
AND TOWERZ AND I
BROKE UP.
SORRY.
MORNING, ELLIE!
HEY, PAIGE.
GREAT OUTFIT.
NEW YEAR, NEW LOOK,
NEW PAIGE!
ELLIE.
JUST BECAUSE PRINCESS PISSY
TALKS TO YOU,
DOESN'T MEAN YOU
HAVE TO ANSWER.
I'M GOING,
I'M GOING.
AS USUAL,
GLAD WE'RE GUYS.
(CHUCKLES)
OH MY GOD,
THEY'RE SO CUTE!
REMEMBER WHEN WE WERE
THAT AFRAID
OF DEGRASSI?
REMEMBER WHEN WE WERE
THAT SHORT?
REMEMBER WHERE
THE PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE IS?
UH, YEAH.
IT'S DOWNSTAIRS,
THROUGH THE FOYER
AND TO THE LEFT.
GOOD.
GO ON DOWN.
I NEED SPEND
TIME ALONE
WITH YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
ASHLEY?
DID YOU?
NICE GOING, CRAIG.
REALLY, UH,
REALLY, REALLY SMOOTH.
OH, HEY!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, BUDDY!
WOW!
YOU HIT THE MALL LATELY?
YOU THINK IT WAS EASY
FINDING THOSE STREAMERS
AND MUSICAL NOTES?
NO,
I MEANT YOUR OUTFIT.
YOU LIKE IT?
YEAH, MAN, AND UH...
I LOVE THE LOCKER.
THANKS.
NO PROBLEM.
HEY MAN,
YOU DATING ANYBODY?
(GIGGLES)
I'M SERIOUS.
SPINNER:
THINK PAIGE WILL BE MAD
IF I PUT UP A PICTURE
OF MANDY MOORE?
I SAW HER IN L.A.
WHEN THAT SCOUT
WHO LIKED ME
TOOK THE WHOLE CAMP
TO SEE A LAKERS GAME.
ARE YOU LISTENING?
MAYBE HILLARY DUFF
WILL BE BETTER.
WHY?
WHY WOULD THAT BE BETTER?
SHE LOOKS MORE
LIKE PAIGE.
I'D RATHER LOOK LIKE
LINDSEY LOHAN.
AREN'T YOU
AT COURT TODAY?
I ALWAYS WANTED
AN ASSISTANT
TO HANDLE MY CALENDAR,
THANKS JIM.
IT WAS SUPPOSED
TO BE TOMORROW.
WAIT. SUPPOSED?
I'M NOT GOING.
DON'T REALLY SEE
THE POINT.
I DO.
OKAY.
THEN YOU CAN GO.
YOU - YOU'RE REALLY-
YOU'RE NOT GOING?
NOPE.
I CAN'T DO
THIS ANY MORE.
DO WHAT ANY MORE?
THIS.
US.
WHAT WAS THAT?
DID HE JUST DUMP ME?
SPINNER!
GAVIN!
HONEYBEE!
YOU SAID:
"EVERYTHING WOULD BE OKAY,"
PAIGE,
"AFTER THE TRIAL."
I DON'T NEED
THE TRIAL.
LOOK,
IT WAS ONE NIGHT,
ALMOST THREE YEARS AGO.
I'VE MOVED ON.
YOU KNOW I HAVE.
LOOK, LET'S GO PARK
SOMEPLACE.
TONIGHT, OKAY?
JUST US.
GUESS I'D SET
A PRETTY BAD EXAMPLE
IF I TURNED
THAT DOWN.
CAITLIN:
HEY CRAIG.
IT'S USUALLY
A BIG LOAD OF IT
WHEN SO-CALLED GROWN-UPS
GIVE YOU
THAT "THESE ARE THE BEST
YEARS OF YOUR LIFE" STUFF.
BUT, UM, MY WISH FOR YOU,
CRAIG,
IS THAT THESE
REALLY ARE.
SO, HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
SIGNING OFF
FROM THAILAND,
SAWASDEE KA!
NOW WE EAT CAKE.
HEY,
I AM THE BIRTHDAY
PERSON HERE,
AND I'M DYING TO OPEN
MY BIG PRESENT, JOEY.
AH, SORRY ANGIE,
CRAIG IS RIGHT.
CAKE WILL HAVE TO WAIT.
(CHUCKLES)
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
HOLY.
TEN GRAND?
JOEY!
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU
DID THIS!
NO, CRAIG, I DIDN'T.
CRAIG:
WAIT.
THIS IS FROM
MY DAD'S ESTATE?
HE SPECIFIED IT
AS A BIRTHDAY GIFT.
I GUESS TO TIDE
YOU OVER
TILL YOUR EIGHTEENTH,
WHEN YOU GET YOUR
FULL INHERITANCE.
WOW!
CAKE NOW?
JOEY:
YOU OKAY, CRAIG?
HM? YEAH.
NO, I'M FINE.
IS IT OKAY?
MM-HM.
GET BACK HERE.
HEY, UM,
WHERE'D YOU
GET THIS SONG?
HER, HER VOICE
SOUNDS LIKE-
SHHH!
SPINNER:
WHAT?
DID I DO IT WRONG?
SORRY.
NO!
STOP!
WHAT? HEY!
STOP! NO!
HEY, COME ON.
BREATHE.
I SAID NO!
YOU'RE OKAY.
I'M NOT!
I'M NOT OKAY!
PAIGE...
I HAVE TO DO IT.
I HAVE TO GO.
I'LL GO WITH YOU.
I UNDERSTAND....
YEAH, BUT LAST WEEK
DOESN'T HELP ME
WITH THIS WEEK.
RADITCH:
I DON'T KNOW WHAT ELSE
I CAN TELL YOU
THE BOARD DIDN'T
GIVE ME THE FUNDS
IN ORDER NEW BOOKS
UNTIL A WEEK AGO.
THOSE ARE BACKWARDS.
THANKS.
LISTEN,
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO BE ALL WEIRD YESTERDAY.
NO, YOU WEREN'T WEIRD.
YOU JUST IGNORED ME.
WHICH, I GUESS,
IS SORT OF BEING WEIRD.
BUT... BUT NOT.
SORRY.
NOW I'M BEING WEIRD.
LOOK...
I WAS HOPING
WE COULD BE FRIENDS,
BUT AS SOON
AS I SAW YOU-
YOU GOT SUCKED INTO
SOME BIZARRO
LAST-YEAR TIME WARP?
YEAH.
SO...
GOOD BIRTHDAY?
ALSO WEIRD.
WEIRD-GOOD?
WELL, MY FREAK
OF A DAD
LEFT ME THIS CHEQUE
FOR TEN GRAND
IN HIS WILL.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
CRAIG:
YEAH, THE GUY'S
HALF-EATEN BY WORMS
AND HE'S STILL TRYING
TO BUY ME.
IT'S PATHETIC.
HEY, YOUR DAD OWES YOU.
MAYBE HE WAS JUST TRYING
TO MAKE IT UP A LITTLE.
WELL, JOEY GAVE ME
THIS LECTURE
ABOUT INVESTING IT
FOR MY FUTURE,
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
BUT... I'M GONNA RIP
THE CHEQUE UP.
I DON'T WANT IT.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW MUCH FUN
YOU COULD HAVE
WITH THAT MUCH MONEY?
(DOOR BANGS SHUT)
ARMSTRONG:
ALL RIGHT...
GRADE ELEVEN.
TIME TO START
REALLY PREPARING YOU
FOR UNIVERSITY MATH.
THANKS FOR BEING HERE TODAY,
MOM.
OH, HONEY,
WHERE ELSE WOULD I BE?
YOU'RE GOING TO DO GREAT
IN THERE.
I JUST WANT THIS
ALL TO END.
I KNOW.
AND IT WILL.
WHEN HE GOES
TO JAIL.
MRS. MICHALCHUK:
REMEMBER WHAT
WE TALKED ABOUT
IN COUNSELING,
PAIGEY,
ABOUT WHY WE'RE
DOING THIS?
SO YOU COULD GET
SOME CLOSURE;
FEEL HEARD.
SPINNER:
PAIGE!
HEY, PAIGE!
HEY, MRS. MICHALCHUK!
HELLO, GAVIN.
IGNORE HIM.
HE CAN'T HURT YOU.
MORNING ALL.
ROSE, COULD I ACTUALLY
HAVE A MINUTE, PLEASE?
YOU'LL BE OKAY?
I HATE THAT GUY.
YOU SHOULD GO HOME,
SPIN.
I DON'T WANT YOU
HEARING ALL OF THIS.
I KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
NOT THE DETAILS.
WHEN YOU HEAR THEM?
PICTURE IT?
IT'LL KEEP PLAYING
ON THE VCR
IN YOUR HEAD.
REWIND-PAUSE-PLAY-
REWIND-PAUSE...
YOU CAN'T STOP IT.
YOU'LL DUMP ME
AND I'LL DIE ALONE,
WITH MY SIX CATS.
PAIGE,
I'LL NEVER DUMP YOU.
HELLO,
YOU DID IT YESTERDAY?
YEAH,
BUT THAT WAS A TEST.
CAN'T DUMP A GIRL
AS COOL AS YOU.
AND YOU JUST BEING HERE
DOING THIS...
IT'S AMAZINGLY COOL.
(SIGHS)
LET'S GET THIS OVER WITH.
DEFENSE ATTORNEY:
MISS MICHALCHUK,
DID YOU GO UPSTAIRS
WILLINGLY WITH MY CLIENT?
DID YOU NOT,
IN FACT, SUGGEST IT?
YEAH.
WHY'D YOU DO THAT?
I... JUST THOUGHT WE-
DEFENSE ATTORNEY:
WHAT? PLAY PINOCHLE?
CRAZY EIGHTS?
OBJECTION, YOUR HONOUR.
PLEASE REPHRASE
THE QUESTION.
WHAT WERE YOUR INTENTIONS,
MISS MICHALCHUK,
IN GOING UP
TO THAT ROOM?
I JUST THOUGHT
WE WOULD BE ALONE TOGETHER.
AND YOU FIND MY CLIENT
ATTRACTIVE?
YES.
I DID.
BEFORE.
WHEN MY CLIENT
PUT HIS HAND
INSIDE YOUR BLOUSE,
DID YOU IMMEDIATELY
REJECT HIM?
SLAP HIM?!
FOR THE RECORD,
PLEASE?
NO.
THIS IS VERY DIFFICULT
FOR YOU, I KNOW,
BUT WHEN MY CLIENT
TOUCHED YOUR BREAST,
HOW DID YOU RESPOND?
DID YOU ENJOY IT?
NO.
WELL, AT FIRST,
YEAH.
DEFENSE ATTORNEY:
YOU'RE TELLING US
THAT YOU DID.
MISS MICHALCHUK,
DID MY CLIENT EVER HOLD
A GUN TO YOUR HEAD,
A KNIFE TO YOUR THROAT,
A GRENADE?
NO.
DEFENSE ATTORNEY:
DID HE NOT,
IN FACT, WEAR A CONDOM?
YEAH,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MAKE HIM-
DEFENSE ATTORNEY:
YOU COULD SHOW ME
HOW HE MANAGED TO OPEN
ONE OF THESE
AND ROLLED IT
ONTO HIS PENIS
WITHOUT OFFERING YOU
A CHANCE TO GET AWAY
IF YOU WANTED TO?
I SAID NO!
BUT HE IS BIGGER
THAN ME,
STRONGER.
I WAS AFRAID.
I'M NOT SURE.
DEFENSE ATTORNEY:
OH! SO YOU DON'T KNOW.
HOW MANY MEN
HAVE YOU HAD SEX WITH,
MISS MICHALCHUK?
OBJECTION.
PAIGE:
ACTUALLY,
I'D LIKE TO ANSWER THAT.
THAT WAS MY ONLY
EXPERIENCE.
AND I CERTAINLY WOULD
NOT HAVE CHOSEN
TO LOSE MY VIRGINITY
UPSTAIRS AT A HOUSE PARTY
WITH A GUY
I'D KNOWN FOR AN HOUR.
20 SETS OF HANDMAIDS?
JACK WHITE DOESN'T GO THROUGH
THAT MANY STRINGS
IN A YEAR.
MAYBE HE SHOULD.
AWW!
HOW 'BOUT THIS?
LEGENDARY CRY BABY
WAA WAA.
I THOUGHT IT ALREADY
MADE YOU
CRY ENOUGH
LAST YEAR.
WAA, WAA, WAA.
CRAIG!
UGH!
SORRY, WOW,
THAT WAS REALLY STUPID.
ASHLEY:
HOW BEAUTIFUL IS THIS?
IS THAT A 62'
STRATOCASTER?
UH, 69'.
MASTER-BUILT AMERICAN.
SUNBURST FINISH.
CLASSIC.
ROSEWOOD FRETBOARD.
THREE-WAY SWITCH
WITH PHASING?
UH... IT'S GOT
ALL THE ORIGINAL HARDWARE.
I FEEL LIKE
I'M IN CHURCH.
YOU THINK YOU COULD
PUT THAT BACK NOW?
IT'S WORTH OVER
FOUR GRAND.
I'LL TAKE IT.
MY DAD WOULD HATE IT.
PERFECT.
YEP.
BAILIFF:
ALL RISE!
IT'S GOOD THAT
SHE'S READY
FOR THE VERDICT ALREADY,
RIGHT?
SURE. YEAH,
SURE, IT IS.
BAILIFF:
BE SEATED.
MISS MICHALCHUK'S TESTIMONY
WAS EXTREMELY COMPELLING
AND I WANT TO APPLAUD HER
FOR HAVING THE COURAGE
AND THE STRENGTH
FOR DOING WHAT SHE DID
HERE TODAY.
IT'S THE KIND OF CASE
THAT KEEPS ME AWAKE
AT NIGHT
BECAUSE IT'S NOT
THE KIND
A JUSTICE IN MY POSITION
WANTS TO HEAR.
GIVEN THAT THERE
ARE NO EYEWITNESSES
AND NO PHYSICAL EVIDENCE,
I HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO FIND THE DEFENDANT...
NOT GUILTY.
MR. WALTON,
YOU ARE FREE TO GO.
(MIXED REACTIONS
IN THE COURTROOM)