MARCO:
SO FOR TOMORROW,
ELLIE?
I NEED YOU TO HAND OUT
STICKERS, OKAY?
CRAIG, I NEED YOU
TO PACK BLOOD BAGS.
AND ALEX-
ALEX!
THIS I WILL NOT
BE WEARING.
IT'S FOR TV -
CAITLIN RYAN'S
COMMUNITY SHOW.
LOOK, WHEN PEOPLE SEE
"DEGRASSI",
I WANT THEM TO THINK,
CUTE AND CUDDLY.
I'M GOING TO
CLOBBER YOU.
THAT'S NOT CUDDLY.
AND AS A PRESIDENT
SPEAKING TO HIS VICE...
ALL RIGHT.
CALM DOWN.
EVERYTHING HAS TO BE PERFECT.
ELLIE:
SHE'S RIGHT.
WHAT YOU'VE DONE
FOR THE SCHOOL THIS YEAR...
EVER CONSIDER RUNNING
A SECOND TERM?
ALEX:
FOUR MORE YEARS!
I CAN'T.
I WAS THINKING
OF PICKING UP
A FEW EXTRA CREDITS
THIS SUMMER.
THIS WAY,
I CAN GRADUATE AFTER
FIRST SEMESTER'S DONE.
MAYBE EVEN MOVE IN
WITH DYLAN
BEFORE UNIVERSITY.
MY BOYFRIEND?
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS KNOW
I'M GAY, RIGHT?
I'M STUCK ON
"GRADUATING EARLY".
I'M ON
"MOVE IN WITH DYLAN".
GUYS, IT'S NOT
THAT BIG A DEAL.
OKAY, IT'S HUGE.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best that I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
DYLAN:
SO YOU'LL CALL BEFORE
YOU COME OVER FOR THE PARTY?
MARCO?
THE DAY'S GOING
TO GO FINE.
THERE'S BEEN A BEE
IN THIS CAR
FOR THE ENTIRE RIDE.
FEAR IS MY FRIEND.
YOU KNOW,
A YEAR AGO,
YOU WOULD HAVE JUMPED OUT
OF A MOVING VEHICLE.
YEAH, WELL,
A YEAR AGO,
I WASN'T WITH YOU.
GO...
BACK TO YOUR DORM.
I'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT.
AT THE PARTY.
SPIKE:
IT'S LIKE BREAST-FEEDING
ONLY OUT OF YOUR ARM.
EMMA:
I THINKS IT'S FASTER
IF YOU'RE QUIET.
CAITLIN:
SO YOU INHERITED A SCHOOL
WHERE A STUDENT DIED
AND ANOTHER, PARALYZED.
HATZILAKOS:
NOT THE BEST SITUATION
TO ASSUME PRINCIPAL, I AGREE.
CAITLIN:
AND YET YOU'VE MANAGED
TO TURN IT ALL AROUND?
HATZILAKOS:
OH, NO. NOT ME.
MARCO'S THE HERO HERE.
ORGANIZING THE DANCES,
THE ASSEMBLIES.
THAT'S WHERE
THE WORK HAS BEEN.
CAITLIN:
HAVE YOU DONATED YET, MARCO?
WELL, I'M PLANNING-
ALEX!
WILL YOU STOP
TACKLING ME?!
CUT.
SO WHEN'S THIS
GOING TO AIR?
8:00 P.M.
TONIGHT.
AND I WANNA ADD SOME
SHOTS OF MARCO DONATING.
WHEN YOU'RE RECOVERED.
(REPEATED CLINK OF SPOON
HITTING A GLASS)
IF I'M STILL SERVING YOU
TEN YEARS FROM NOW,
KILL ME, ALL RIGHT?
STUDY HARD
AND STAY IN SCHOOL.
OH, RIGHT.
YOU GOT US EXPELLED.
SPINNER:
HERE YOU GO, LADIES.
CLARE'LL BE WITH YOU
IN A MOMENT
TO TAKE YOUR ORDER.
MARY:
WE ASKED FOR LEMON
WITH OUR WATER.
(DOG BARKS)
YOU CAN'T BRING
A DOG IN HERE.
I DIDN'T HEAR COMPLAINTS.
LADIES?
WE'LL HAVE
THE LUNCH MENUS INSTEAD.
I'M JUST GOING OFF SHIFT,
SO CLARE-
MARY:
AND LEMON FOR THE WATER,
AND A BOWL FOR
BABY BEAR HERE,
SO SHE CAN HAVE SOME,
TOO.
(BABY TALKS TO HER DOG)
SO IF I PASS OUT
AND START DROOLING,
SWEAR YOU'LL STOP
FILMING?
DAVIS:
MR. DEL ROSSI?
COULD YOU PLEASE
ASK THEM TO STOP FILMING
FOR JUST A MINUTE?
CAITLIN:
WE'RE NOT SHOOTING
THE WHOLE "GIVING OF BLOOD".
WE'RE JUST GONNA SHOOT A FEW
FRAMES OF THE PRESIDENT.
DAVIS:
I'M SORRY, MS. RYAN.
IS THERE SOME
KIND OF PROBLEM?
THERE'S A QUESTION HERE
THAT YOU ANSWERED "YES" BESIDE.
IT ASKS IF I'M MALE,
IF I'VE HAD-
WITH ANOTHER MALE.
YES,
IF YOU'VE HAD SEX.
SO?
WELL, IT'S POLICY,
YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND,
BUT I CAN'T LET YOU
BE A DONOR.
(KNOCKS)
YOU SHOULDN'T BE HERE,
GAVIN.
I DIDN'T MAKE
AN APPOINTMENT.
I WAS AFRAID
YOU WOULDN'T SEE ME.
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW,
THIS "BEING EXPELLED"?
I'M NOT TAKING IT
LIKE IT'S A VACATION.
I'VE BEEN KEEPING UP
IN MY TEXTBOOKS.
YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO RETURN THOSE.
BUT I NEED THEM
TO WRITE EXAMS.
YOU DON'T GET
TO DO THAT.
SO THAT'S IT?
I JUST LOSE MY YEAR?
I'M WILLING TO OFFER
SUMMER SCHOOL.
BUT THAT ONLY GIVES ME
TWO CREDITS
THAT'S NOT EVEN
ENOUGH TO GRADUATE.
I MEAN, THAT'S A WHOLE YEAR
OF MY LIFE
I'LL HAVE TO DO OVER.
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
WHAT ISN'T FAIR IS
THAT RICK MURRAY IS DEAD
AS AN INDIRECT RESULT
OF YOUR BULLYING.
I NEED TO FINISH
MY YEAR, MS. H.
NO.
DYLAN?
HEY! IT'S ME.
LOOK, JUST PLEASE
CALL ME.
WHENEVER.
I'M HERE.
CRAIG:
WHY'S YOUR BLOOD
ANY MORE RISKY THAN OURS?
ELLIE:
DON'T THEY TEST
EVERYTHING ANYWAY?
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG
WITH ME.
I'VE ONLY BEEN WITH DYLAN,
HE'S ONLY BEEN WITH ME.
EVEN THEN,
WE WERE TOTALLY SAFE.
SO STOP WHINING;
START COMPLAINING.
THERE'S YOUR SOAPBOX.
USE IT.
CAITLIN?
HEY.
HOW'S THIS FOR A STORY?
PREJUDICE AND HOMOPHOBIA
AT LOCAL HIGH SCHOOL.
I'D SAY
WE'RE ON YOU.
MARCO:
NURSE DAVIS?
HEY.
YEAH.
MARCO:
HI.
LOOK,
I WANT TO ASK WHY
WHY BLOOD MANAGEMENT
REFUSES GAY PEOPLE
FROM GIVING BLOOD.
DAVIS:
UM...
WELL, IT'S POLICY.
I'M NOT A SPOKESPERSON
SO I CAN'T REALLY
COMMENT FURTHER.
FINE.
MY NAME'S MARCO DEL ROSSI,
STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT.
TODAY, A STUDENT WAS DENIED
AS A BLOOD DONOR
BECAUSE OF HIS SEXUALITY.
EXCUSE ME,
THAT'S NOT THE REASON.
MARCO:
THEN WHAT IS?
WELL...
THERE IS UM...
WITHIN THE GAY COMMUNITY,
THERE IS AN INCREASED RISK
OF HIV INFECTION.
SAYING THAT
IS LUMPING UP
ALL GAY PEOPLE AS DISEASED.
I LISTENED
IN HEALTH CLASS
AND ANYBODY WITH A PULSE
CAN GET HIV.
YES, BUT-
HATZILAKOS:
MARCO?
PLEASE.
THANK YOU.
LOOK, THIS BLOOD DRIVE,
YOU SHOULD BE
SO PROUD OF YOURSELF
FOR EVERYTHING
YOU'VE DONE.
LOOK AT THE THESE PEOPLE.
MY WHOLE POINT IS
THAT I'M SUPPOSED TO BE
ONE OF THEM.
HEY!
YOU WANT A KICK,
TOO?
IT'S MY BIKE,
GOOFBAG.
YEAH? WELL, IT'S YOUR FAULT
I'M SO BORED.
SO? I'M STUCK WITH YOU?
HAVEN'T I BEEN
PUNISHED ENOUGH?
NOT YET.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
BIKE STEALING?
IT'S KID'S STUFF.
BUT REAL STEALING,
FROM DEGRASSI...
(LOUD MUSIC PLAYS)
DYLAN:
MARCO. MARCO, WAIT!
MARCO:
NO!
DYLAN:
ABOUT ERIC...
I MEANT TO TELL YOU.
HE'S A FRIEND
FROM PSYCH CLASS.
THERE'S OTHER WAYS -
BETTER WAYS OF BREAKING UP,
DYLAN.
WHO'S BREAKING UP?
HONEY,
I'M IN UNIVERSITY NOW
AND THERE ARE
PEOPLE HERE,
REALLY INTERESTING
PEOPLE,
THAT I REALLY,
REALLY LIKE.
OH YEAH,
LIKE ERIC.
I LOVE YOU.
AND I DON'T WANT
TO STOP SEEING YOU.
WHAT I'D LIKE
TO DO IS...
OPEN THINGS UP A BIT.
YOU KNOW,
SEE OTHER PEOPLE.
HE WANTS TO
"OPEN THINGS UP."
HE'S A COLOSSAL
JERK.
IT'S SO HUMILIATING.
FIRST I GET REJECTED
AS A BLOOD DONOR,
NOW BY DYLAN.
MAYBE THE BLOOD
PEOPLE WERE RIGHT.
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOU?
MY "EX"
FORMERLY KNOWN
AS JAY HOGART
SCREWED AROUND WITH
EVERY GIRL AT THIS SCHOOL.
IT'S NOT
A "GAY" THING.
PROMISCUITY?
IT'S A GUY THING.
CRAIG:
HEY.
DIDN'T I HEAR
THAT YOU CLOCKED AMY
FOR BEING EQUALLY TRAMPY?
OH...AND HOW'S ASH,
CRAIG?
OR ARE YOU BACK
WITH MANNY?
IT'S HARD TO TELL,
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU
SECRETLY DATED THEM
AT THE SAME TIME.
LET'S JUST CALL IT
A PEOPLE THING.
LET'S CALL IT
A CHOICE.
MONOGAMY.
WOW.
WHAT A DIFFICULT
CONCEPT.
I JUST WANT
MY BOYFRIEND BACK.
HE'S GOT A PARTY
TONIGHT, RIGHT?
WELL, THEM BACK IS
WHAT WE'LL GET HIM.
CRAIG:
GIRLS AND BOYS?
I DIDN'T THINK DYLAN'S DORM
WOULD BE SO CO-ED.
MARCO:
YOU SEE HIM YET?
CRAIG:
WHO?
MARCO:
DYLAN.
HEY.
I'M REALLY HAPPY
YOU CAME.
YEAH?
THAT'S... GOOD.
CRAIG:
(CLEARS THROAT)
I'M GOING TO GO UH...
SEE WHAT THEY'RE STOCKING
FOR POP.
GENTLEMEN.
C'MON.
(MUSIC BLARES,
PEOPLE LAUGHING AND TALKING)
CRAIG,
UM, LOOK,
EVERYTHING IS UNFOLDING
PRETTY GOOD,
SO IF YOU DON'T
WANT TO,
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO STAY.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
IT'S 8:00 P.M.
DYLAN:
WHAT'S 8:00 P.M.?
MARCO:
OH, CAITLIN RYAN.
DEGRASSI.
ME, AT THE BLOOD DRIVE.
CAN I?
THANKS.
CAITLIN:
YOU INHERITED A SCHOOL
WHERE A STUDENT DIED,
ANOTHER PARALYZED?
HATZILAKOS:
NOT THE BEST SITUATION
TO ASSUME PRINCIPAL, I AGREE.
CAITLIN:
AND YET YOU'VE MANAGED
TO TURN IT AROUND?
HATZILAKOS:
OH NO, NOT ME.
MARCO IS THE HERO HERE.
ORGANIZING THE ASSEMBLIES,
THE DANCES...
(GROANS)
TELL ME THAT MY HEAD
DOESN'T LOOK THAT BIG.
YOUR HAIR -
THAT'S WHAT'S BIG.
IT LOOKS GREAT.
YOU LOOK GREAT.
CAITLIN:
AND SO DEGRASSI HAS RISEN
FROM THE ASHES
OF A TUMULTUOUS SCHOOL YEAR
THANKS TO THIS WEEK'S
"LOCAL HERO",
MARCO DEL ROSSI.
I'M CAITLIN RYAN.
THAT'S IT?
NO, THERE'S MORE.
THERE'S THEM NOT LETTING ME
GIVE BLOOD. AND THEN I-
ERIC:
DYLAN?
WE'RE TOASTING TO SUMMER
WITH KAMIKAZES.
DYLAN:
WAIT A SECOND.
YEAH.
IT'S NOTHING.
GO KAMIKAZEE.
WHATEVER.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
DYLAN GAVE ME THE KICK
OUT OF THE CLOSET LAST YEAR.
AND HERE IT WAS,
RIGHT?
MY TURN TO MAKE
HIM PROUD.
AND WHAT I SHOULD
BE DOING...
IS MAKING HIM
JEALOUS.
UM...
SPINNER:
WELL, WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE?
"DEGRASSI:
A YEAR OF MEMORIES."
JAY:
I SAID SOMETHING
WORTH SOMETHING.
I ALWAYS LIKE COUNTING
HOW MANY TIMES
I'M IN THIS THING.
THE WAY I SEE IT,
THE LESS, THE BETTER.
AW, CRAP.
ONE.
THE LAST THING
I WANT TO SEE
IS ME SMILING GOOFY
AND HANGING OFF
MY BESTEST FRIENDS.
NO! TWO.
I'M A FREAK,
A FAILURE.
NOTHING COMPARED TO YOU,
THOUGH.
I MEAN, YOU'RE-
YOU'RE ALL THROUGH
THIS THING.
YOU ALL RIGHT THERE,
SPINSTER?
SPINNER:
FOLLOW ME
AND GRAB SOME MORE.
HI.
I'M MARCO.
MIKE.
SO UH, MIKE...
I WAS THINKING
OF COMING HERE NEXT YEAR.
I WAS ACTUALLY THINKING
ABOUT RESIDENCE
BUT SO FAR THE ONLY ROOM
I'VE SEEN IS DYLAN'S.
DO YOU WANT,
LIKE, A TOUR?
YEAH.
NO.
A TOUR WOULD BE GREAT.
AND MAYBE I CAN SEE
YOUR ROOM.
YOU KNOW,
LIKE TO COMPARE.
OKAY.
UM, IT'S TWO FLOORS DOWN,
403.
BUT, JUST GIVE ME A SEC
TO CLEAN UP, OKAY?
YEAH.
OKAY.
I'LL SEE YOU
IN A BIT...
MIKE.
MARCO.
YO! WHERE'D YOU
DISAPPEAR?
SCIENCE LAB.
I GOT FLUID...
OF THE "LIGHTER" KIND.
SERIOUSLY?
IT'S BONFIRE NIGHT?
LOOK, I KNOW MATH WASN'T
YOUR STRONGEST SUBJECT,
BUT YEARBOOKS PLUS FIRE
EQUALS THE WHOLE SCHOOL
UP IN FLAMES.
OH YEAH,
AND US IN JAIL.
PUT THE TOY AWAY,
FLIP-HEAD.
YOU'RE STOPPING ME?
SHOCKING BUT TRUE.
YOU'RE A FREAK
THE SAME WAY THAT I AM.
YEAH? WELL, AT LEAST I'M NOT
TORCHING THE SCHOOL.
(STRUGGLING AND GRUNTING)
DO YOU WANT YOUR
FORMER FRIENDS TO SUFFER?
HUH, DO YOU?
I WANT THEM BACK!
JAY:
LISTEN,
AS YOUR FRIEND SUBSTITUTE,
I'M TELLING YOU,
THIS ISN'T THE WAY.
IT'S NOT.
I JUST WANT THEM BACK.
COME ON, MAN,
WE GOT TO CLEAN THIS UP.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU ARE A GREAT GUY.
THE MOST HONEST,
DOWN-TO-EARTH,
NICEST PERSON
THAT I KNOW.
YOU'RE A LITTLE SHORT,
BUT THAT JUST ADDS
TO THE CUTENESS...
THAT I WOULD FIND YOU
TO BE...
IF YOU WERE A GIRL
OR I WAS NOT A GUY...
WHO IS NOT GAY.
JUST TELL ME
THIS IS HELPING.
YOU'RE TELLING ME
WHAT I REALLY WANT TO HEAR.
I APPRECIATE IT.
THANKS .
IF YOU WANT TO HELP?
TELL ME I'M AN IDIOT.
YOU'RE AN IDIOT?
I CAN'T GO DOWNSTAIRS.
I CAN'T STAY HERE.
I CAN'T TALK TO DYLAN.
WHAT DO I DO?
DYLAN:
MARCO?
I UM... WOW.
SO WHEN IN DOUBT,
YOU KISS CRAIG?
I GOTTA SETTLE
THIS WITH DYLAN.
YEAH. YOU DO.
YOU REALLY,
REALLY DO.
I LOVE YOU.
LIKEWISE.
BUT WHAT WAS THAT?
DYLAN?
A LOT OF THINGS AREN'T
MAKING SENSE RIGHT NOW.
SO WHAT DO YOU
WANT ME TO SAY?
THAT IT MADE
YOU JEALOUS?
IT WAS CRAIG.
I DON'T WANT YOU
TO SEE OTHER PEOPLE.
I DON'T LIKE IT.
AND I'M NOT GONNA LIKE IT
AND I'M NOT GONNA FEEL BAD
THAT IT BUGS ME.
IT BUGS YOU?
IT BUGS ME!
IT DOESN'T
HAVE TO, OKAY?
HOW I FEEL ABOUT YOU
THIS CHANGES
NONE OF THAT.
THAT'S FINE
AND OKAY,
BUT YOU SEE,
IT CHANGES
HOW I FEEL ABOUT ME.
MY FREEDOM,
THAT'S IMPORTANT
TO ME RIGHT NOW.
I CAN'T GIVE THAT UP.
THEN YOU AND ME?
I CAN'T.
AND IT'S OVER.
♪ GOODBYE ♪
♪ MADE UP MY MIND ♪
♪ OH, OH, GOODBYE ♪
MS. H?
GAVIN, I DON'T HAVE
TIME TO ARGUE.
YOU MENTIONED
SUMMER SCHOOL.
I OFFERED,
YOU DECLINED.
THEN WHAT IF I TAKE IT
AT ANOTHER SCHOOL
OR BY CORRESPONDENCE,
AND MAKE THE CREDITS UP
THAT WAY?
COULD I COME BACK
NEXT FALL?
THERE ARE TWO THINGS
THAT I WANT:
TO FINISH SCHOOL
AND TO GET MY FRIENDS BACK.
BUT SOMEONE'S GOT
TO GIVE ME A CHANCE.
PLEASE?
HATZILAKOS:
HERE ARE THE FORMS
AND THE SUMMER SCHEDULE -
A.K.A YOUR CHANCE.
GAVIN?
DON'T SCREW IT UP.
UM, OKAY.
HEY, MARCO.
HEY.
SO THE BLOOD DRIVE,
IT WAS A HUGE SUCCESS.
THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR COVERING IT.
OH,
MY PLEASURE.
I JUST HAD A QUESTION,
ABOUT THE SCENE
I STARTED IN THE GYM?
ARE YOU GONNA AIR THAT
AT A DIFFERENT TIME OR...?
ACTUALLY,
SOME PEOPLE HERE
WOULD RATHER BURY
THAT PART OF IT.
OH. OKAY.
UH NO, IT'S NOT OKAY,
ACTUALLY.
I'M SICK OF SEEING
AIDS VIEWED
SOLELY AS A HOMOSEXUAL
DISEASE.
I'VE TRIED DOING SOMETHING
ABOUT IT BEFORE.
LAST YEAR
I EVEN WENT TO AFRICA.
ONE WORD:
EDUCATING.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU'RE INTERESTED
IN VOLUNTEERING,
I'VE GOT SOME FRIENDS
WE COULD TALK TO.
YEAH,
SURE I'M INTERESTED.
INTERESTED ENOUGH
IN SPENDING SOME TIME
IN AFRICA
OR THE CARIBBEAN?
YEAH!
YEAH, OF COURSE.
IT WOULD MEAN
GIVING UP YOUR
ENTIRE SUMMER.
ANY BIG PLANS?
I DID...
HAVE SOME.
BUT YOU KNOW
HOW IT IS WITH PLANS.
THEY CHANGE.