SHELLY ON TV:
AND GOOD MORNING TO YOU,
BOBBY.
I'M HERE WITH PEARL PINKTON.
PEARL, YOU'RE AN ERASER
CONNOISSEUR.
SEAN.
OH, WOW.
DOUBLE WOW.
I'M LATE.
"HOME BY ELEVEN"
DOES NOT MEAN A.M.
DID YOU TURN THE RINGER OFF?
I NEED A CAB.
I NEED TEN DOLLARS
TO PAY FOR A CAB.
RINGER'S ON.
NOBODY'S CALLED.
ELLIE:
MY MOM PROBABLY LOST
YOUR NUMBER.
OR FELL ASLEEP WATCHING
THE SAME LAME MOVIE WE DID.
SNUGGLING UP
WITH A FEW EMPTY BOTTLES.
I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT THIS.
YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE WELCOME HERE.
LET'S SEE
IF I'M EVEN ALLOWED BACK.
I MEANT TO STAY.
YEAH.
AS IN MOVE IN.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
WHAT, YOU JUST FORGOT
TO PUT ANY ON?
ASHLEY:
LEFT MINE AT MY MOM'S
DIDN'T WANT TO USE MY DAD'S
"SPORT SCENT"
OR HIS BOYFRIEND'S
"MOUNTAIN ICE."
ELLIE:
MEN'S DEODORANT
GIVES ME A RASH.
ASHLEY:
YEAH, WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE
GIVES ME A RASH
IS THAT MY DAD IS BRINGING
HIS BOYFRIEND
TO THE OPEN HOUSE TODAY.
IMAGINE THE RASH I GOT
WHEN SEAN ASKED ME
TO MOVE IN.
THIS MORNING.
WHAT?
MOVE IN, CO-HABITATE,
LIVE IN SIN.
YOU CAN'T!
MY MOM ISN'T DOING
SO WELL.
IT'S PRETTY BAD.
AND HOW IS SEAN?
WELL, IS IT GOOD ENOUGH
TO RISK GIVING YOUR MOM
A HEART ATTACK?
MANNY:
HEY, SPINNER.
WHY, IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU TOO,
MANNY.
HAVE A GOOD DAY.
HEY, YOU WANT TO EARN SOME
MAJOR POINTS
BY HELPING WITH PAIGE'S
SPIRIT SQUAD CAR WASH?
PAIGE SORT OF OWES ME
THE MAJOR POINTS THESE DAYS.
MANNY:
OKAY.
SO WHY NOT EARN MAJOR POINTS
WITH ME THEN?
PAIGE IS OFF SICK,
WITH THE FLU.
YEAH. I KNOW.
SO I'M IN CHARGE.
AND HONESTLY?
I NEED HELP.
WE NEED TO EARN
A LOT OF MONEY
TO GET THOSE
NEW UNIFORMS.
SO YOU THINK
IT WOULD HELP
IF I WASHED CARS
IN MY WET T-SHIRT?
NO, I WANT YOU TO PLAY
WITH YOUR BAND, YOU IDIOT.
NO. YOU GUYS WOULD ATTRACT
SO MUCH ATTENTION.
YEAH, BUT THE SQUATCH
ISN'T MY BAND.
YOU'D HAVE TO ASK-
CRAIG.
YEAH. THAT'D BE
JUST A BIT AWKWARD.
PLEASE, PLEASE,
PLEASE, PLEASE.
WITH KETCHUP AND GRAVY
AND BIG HUGE HUGS ON TOP?
GRAVY?
YEAH, I'LL SEE
WHAT I CAN DO.
OKAY, THANKS.
OH. AND GET CRAIG
TO BRING HIS CAMERA, 'KAY?
'KAY!
WHY NOT?
MY DAD'S GOT
SIX MONTHS OF SERVICE.
SO THAT'S SIX MONTHS
OF HOMEWORK .
THAT'S SIX MONTHS
OF DINNERS.
HE'S IN THE MIDDLE EAST,
SEAN.
IF THE CALL CAME IN
HE WAS HURT, OR WORSE,
MY MOM WOULD-
SHE WOULD WHAT?
SHE WOULD CRACK OPEN
HER THIRD BOTTLE
FOR THE EVENING?
WE CAN DO DINNERS, OKAY?
MAYBE WATCH SOME CRAPPY TV,
BUT AFTER THAT?
LET ME MAKE IT SIMPLE.
MOVE IN WITH SOMEONE
WHO LOVES YOU.
I'M SORRY.
SHE NEEDS ME.
IT'S FINISHED.
NO ONE CARES ABOUT
AUTO SHOP ANYWAYS.
NO, EMMA'S DOING PRETTY WELL.
POLYNOMIALS CAN BE
A BIT OF A STRUGGLE.
ME AND MATH?
MORTAL ENEMIES.
YOU BALANCE YOUR OWN BOOKS
AT THE SALON.
DON'T BELIEVE HER.
MRS. NASH:
ELLIE MUST LOVE YOUR CLASS.
ALL HER CLASSES.
SHE SPENDS ALMOST EVERY NIGHT
AT HER BOYFRIEND'S
DOING HOMEWORK.
WELL, MEDIA IMMERSION
IS VERY INTENSE.
THE COURSE IS CENTRED ON-
MEDIA. COMPUTERS.
YEAH, I GET IT.
TELL ME, DO YOU ASSIGN
EVERY PROJECT IN PAIRS?
WELL, NO.
IN FACT,
MOST OF THE WORK IS-
THOUGHT SO.
WELL, THANKS YOU VERY MUCH,
MR. STANTON.
IT'S SIMPSON.
(LAUGHS)
LIKE THE CARTOON.
THAT'S PRICELESS.
ASHLEY:
ELLIE.
ELLIE:
HEY MOM?
YOU REMEMBER ASHLEY?
MRS. NASH,
THIS IS MY FATHER, ROBERT,
AND HIS PARTNER.
CHRISTOPHER:
HI, I'M CHRISTOPHER.
PARTNERS, HUH?
DO YOU RUN
A BUSINESS TOGETHER?
OR IS IT PAIRS
FIGURE SKATING?
ROBERT:
WE'RE LIFE PARTNERS,
ACTUALLY.
OH, I KNOW.
MUST BE NICE,
HAVING A MAN AROUND.
MY HUSBAND IS OFF
FIGHTING FOR HIS COUNTRY.
ROBERT:
THAT MUST BE DIFFICULT
FOR YOU AND ELLIE.
MRS. NASH:
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
OR DO THEY LET YOU PEOPLE
IN THE MILITARY NOW?
YOU RE-DECORATE THE ENEMY
INTO SURRENDERING.
(FAKE LAUGHTER)
ELLIE:
MOM, YOU'RE TIRED.
WE SHOULD GO.
BYE.
MRS. NASH:
OH, WAIT. ISN'T THAT
YOUR BOYFRIEND?
ELLIE:
IT'S OKAY.
I'LL CALL HIM LATER.
SEAN, ISN'T?
I WAS HOPING TO SEE YOU.
AH, NICE TO SEE YOU TOO,
MRS. NASH.
MRS. NASH:
YOUR PARENTS?
THEY'RE NOT HERE TO SEE THIS
FINE AUTOMOTIVE DISPLAY?
I'M ALONE.
I LIVE ALONE.
NOT LATELY.
MOM...
MIDNIGHT STUDY SESSIONS,
DAWN TUTORIALS.
SOMETIMES I CAN'T REMEMBER
WHAT ELLIE LOOKS LIKE.
ELLIE:
MOM. LET'S GO.
SEAN:
LOOK, I-
I CARE ABOUT HER,
OKAY?
NOT OKAY.
CRAIG:
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR.
♪♪♪
CRAIG:
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
YOU'RE COMING IN
WAY TOO EARLY!
SPINNER:
DUDE, HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO GET BETTER
IF ALL WE DO IS REHEARSE?
I MEAN, WE SHOULD PLAY
ANOTHER GIG.
WELL, WE WILL
WHEN WE'RE SMOKIN' HOT.
IN THE 23RD CENTURY.
SPINNER:
EXACTLY.
WE NEED PLAY SMALLER GIGS
TO STOKE US UP TO SMOKIN' HOT.
SPINNER
HAS A POINT.
WHO ASKED YOU?
I MEAN, YEAH.
WHAT SHE SAID.
SORRY.
ALL RIGHT. WELL,
I GUESS WE COULD PUT
A LITTLE MORE PRESSURE
ON OURSELVES.
YES!
THAT'S WHY I BOOKED US
FOR THE SCHOOL SPIRIT SQUAD
CAR WASH THIS WEEKEND.
WHAT?
WHOA, SPIN!
WE'RE NOT READY.
DUDE, IT'S A CAR WASH.
WE'RE NOT OPENING FOR
KID ELRICK AT THE DOME.
ALL RIGHT,
WE'LL TAKE IT TO A VOTE.
ALL FOR THE GIG?
JIMMY:
ALL AGAINST?
SPINNER:
OKAY. WELL, THREE TO TWO,
MAJORITY RULES.
MANNY'LL BE STOKED!
ASHLEY AND CRAIG:
MANNY?
JIMMY:
SPEAKING OF SMOKIN' HOT.
(FIRE ALARM BEEPS)
(SNIFFS)
(SMOKE ALARM)
(COUGHING)
MOM!
MOM! GET UP!
GET UP!
(COUGHING)
MOM! GET UP!
MOM! MOM!
I MUST'VE TAKEN IN A LIFE'S
SUPPLY OF SMOKE TONIGHT.
I'M NOT PROUD RIGHT NOW,
ELLIE.
I ALMOST BURNT
THE PLACE DOWN.
DON'T MAKE THIS
ANY WORSE FOR ME.
I'M EXHAUSTED.
I HAVE TO SLEEP.
FINE. THERE'S A FOLD-OUT
AT ELAINE'S.
ELAINE'S?
SHE LIVES IN FERGUS.
WHY DO I HAVE TO GO THERE?
BECAUSE I'M STILL YOUR MOTHER,
AND I SAID SO.
OKAY.
BUT WHAT IF I STAY OVER
AT ASHLEY'S INSTEAD,
IN THE CITY?
WELL, I WOULDN'T HAVE TO DRIVE
YOU IN TO SCHOOL EVERY DAY.
EXACTLY WHAT I WAS THINKING.
BUT IT'S UP TO YOU.
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
WELL, IF IT'S ALL RIGHT
WITH ASHLEY'S MOTHER
IT'S ALL RIGHT WITH ME.
AT LEAST UNTIL OUR PLACE
IS READY.
I'LL GO CALL ASHLEY RIGHT NOW.
(GROAN)
YESTERDAY, YOU MIGHT HAVE
MENTIONED THE WORDS "MOVE IN".
ELLIE:
HOME SWEET HOME.
SEAN:
MY CLOTHES STINK
AFTER BEING AT YOUR PLACE.
LOOKS LIKE MY CD COLLECTION
JUST DOUBLED.
ELLIE:
I WAS THINKING,
WE NEED A PET.
A DOG,
OR A PARROT, OR A-
I THOUGHT
YOU STOPPED CUTTING.
I DID.
I JUST DIDN'T WANT
TO LEAVE IT THERE.
I WOULDN'T LIE TO YOU
ABOUT THIS.
I CLEARED A DRAWER.
YOU DID?
SEAN:
YEAH.
AND SOME SPACE IN THE CLOSET
AND IN THE MEDICINE CABINET
JUST ABOVE THE SINK.
LISTEN, THERE'S SOMETHING
WE SHOULD-
I KNOW.
AND IT'S FINE.
I'LL JUST SLEEP ON THE COUCH.
YOU HAVE A BED.
YOU JUST HAD A FIRE.
SO FOR NOW, I'LL JUST SLEEP
ON THE COUCH, OKAY?
SPINNER,
I SAID STOP IT!
WHAT? IT WASN'T ME.
NEW GIRL.
NEW GIRL?
I PREFER DARCY,
THANKS.
OH. OKAY, DARCY.
HEY CRAIG.
THANKS FOR DOING THIS.
IT'S REALLY GREAT.
ANY TIME, MANNY.
ASHLEY:
CHECK, ONE, TWO.
DO WE HAVE CRAIG MANNING
IN THE HOUSE?
ANY MORE BITTER
AND SHE'D BE A LEMON.
HEY, YOU THINK
THAT'S FUNNY, RIGHT?
OH NO! NO!
I HATE YOU!
BUT YOU'RE ALL RIGHT,
RIGHT?
I MEAN, AFTER BREATHING IN
ALL THAT SMOKE?
I DON'T HAVE BLACK LUNG,
MARCO.
AND YOUR MOM?
HOW IS SHE DOING?
I ONLY HAVE A FEW
MOM-FREE DAYS LEFT.
IF IT'S OKAY,
I'D RATHER KEEP IT THAT WAY.
WELL, I'M MORE INTERESTED
IN YOU, ANYWAY.
SO, OKAY.
FIRST SHOWER
AT YOUR BOYFRIEND'S.
WERE YOU NAKED?
UH, YEAH?
AND ALONE.
WHAT?
DISAPPOINTING,
BUT STILL PARTY WORTHY.
ME SHOWERING
IS PARTY WORTHY?
NO, BUT YOU
BEING HAPPY IS.
PLUS YOU'RE YOUNG, CUTE,
CLEAN AND BLACK LUNG FREE.
AND YOU SURE MAMA DEL ROSSI
WILL LET US HAVE A PARTY?
NO, BUT I KNOW
PAPA SEAN WILL.
♪♪♪
♪ THE NIGHT IS NEVER ENDLESS ♪
♪ THE DAWN IS NEVER SOON ♪
♪ ALL AROUND WE ACHE
AND WHISPER ♪
♪ THE DEVIL IN THE MOON ♪
♪ OLD ENOUGH TO KNOW BETTER ♪
♪ STILL TOO YOUNG TO CARE ♪
♪ NOBODIES BUSINESS WHAT WE DO ♪
♪ WHATEVER YOU GETS YOU THERE ♪
♪ NIGHT IS NEVER ENDLESS ♪
♪ THE DAWN IS NEVER SOON ♪
♪ ALL AROUND WE ACHE
AND WHISPER ♪
♪ THE DEVIL IN THE MOON ♪
(APPLAUSE AND CHEERING)
THAT SUCKED.
KEEP SMILING.
NO ONE NOTICED.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
HELPING OUT
MY FELLOW STUDENTS.
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM, PSYCHO?
RICK:
MY MOTHER WANTS THE CAR WASHED.
JIMMY:
OKAY. UNLESS YOU
WANT A WASH,
I'D BOUNCE.
MANNY:
HEY...
I NEVER KNEW WHAT A GREAT
DRUMMER YOU WERE BEFORE.
SPINNER:
YEAH, I GUESS IT'S KINDA
HARD TO SEE ME
BEHIND THE LEAD SINGER
SOMETIMES.
WELL, NOT TODAY.
CONGRATULATIONS.
THANK FOR COMING OUT.
SPINNER:
THAT'S HOW YOU REPAY ME?!
MANNY:
I OWED YOU!
SPINNER:
YOU'RE SO COLD, WOMAN!
SO COLD!
I'M SORRY!
YOU TOTALLY SAVED MY BUTT!
(CHUCKLING)
ELLIE:
ALWAYS WITH THE BANNERS, MARCO?
MARCO:
CURSE OF A PRINTER'S SON.
UGH.
WHAT IS THIS?
IT'S GUACAMOLE.
SEAN MADE FOR ME.
IT'S MY FAVORITE.
HE'S SWEET.
BABE?
THIS GUAC'S RANCID.
JAY:
NICE LITTLE HOUSEWARMING.
WHATEVER.
SHE'LL GO BACK
IN A FEW DAYS.
MAYBE THIS TIME HER MOM'LL
BURN DOWN THE WHOLE PLACE.
NOW, THAT WOULD BE
A HOUSEWARMING.
JAY:
SO IT'S ACTUALLY A "BON VOYAGE,
SEE YOU LATER,
THANKS FOR ALL THE SEX" PARTY.
WHAT?
ELLIE.
LOOK, HE SHOULDN'T
HAVE SAID THAT.
I DON'T CARE
THAT HE DID.
I JUST...I DON'T WANT
TO GO BACK TO HER.
THEN YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
OKAY?
YOU CAN STAY HERE.
MRS. NASH:
WHAT IS THIS?
MOM?
MRS. NASH:
HOUSEWARMING.
I WENT TO ASHLEY'S
AND HER MOM TOLD ME
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN STAYING THERE.
YOU'VE BEEN HERE
THE WHOLE TIME, HAVEN'T YOU?
HAVEN'T YOU?!
CAB'S WAITING.
LET'S GO.
LET'S GO. NOW!
MRS. NASH, IT'S BETTER
IF ELLIE STAYS HERE.
YOU DON'T COME NEAR ME.
AND DON'T COME
NEAR MY DAUGHTER.
MRS. NASH:
THIS WAS A BLESSING.
YOU KNOW, ELLIE, A BLESSING.
ALL THAT OLD FURNITURE,
GRIMY PAINT.
WE CAN START FROM SCRATCH.
YEAH.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
HOW ABOUT A PERIWINKLE BLUE
IN HERE?
MOM, YOU SLAPPED
MY BOYFRIEND.
ELLIE, THAT BOY'S
NO GOOD FOR YOU.
I KNOW, YOU THINK
IT'LL BE HARD,
THAT YOU LOVE HIM.
I KNOW WHAT'S BEST.
ELEANOR, STOP DOING THAT.
PICK ONE, MOM.
KNIFE? RAZOR?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT'S BEST FOR ME,
MOM?
BECAUSE IF I STAY HERE,
I'M GOING TO DO IT AGAIN.
YOU'RE MAKING ME DO IT AGAIN!
ELLIE?
THIS IS WHAT IT COSTS.
YOUR DRINKING MADE ME
CUT MYSELF.
NO, BABY.
NO, I CAN'T.
YOU NEED TO UNDERSTAND.
NO. YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND...
WHY I CAN'T KEEP LIVING
WITH YOU.
NO.
(SOBBING) OH MY GOD.
(CRYING)
HEY.
ARE YOU READY
TO ORDER?
NO, ACTUALLY,
I'M NOT EATING.
I'M JUST WAITING
FOR SOMEONE.
OKAY. WHO?
PAIGE.
RIGHT.
LOOK, I HAVE
LOT'S OF TABLES...
YEAH.
THE EXCITEMENT
FROM YESTERDAY
MUST'VE GOT TO MY HEAD
OR SOMETHING.
YEAH.
I KNOW THE FEELING.
I WOULDN'T WANT YOU
OR PAIGE TO THINK-
PAIGE!
PAIGE:
JUST THE TWO PEOPLE I'VE BEEN
LITERALLY DYING TO SEE.
BUT NOW I HAVE RISEN
TO THANK MANUELLA SANTOS,
MY GUARDIAN ANGEL!
EIGHT HUNDRED BUCKS
AND OUR NEW UNIFORM DREAM
IS A REALITY!
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
OH, AND I HEARD
YOU GUYS ROCKED, BEE-BEE.
I DID IT
ALL FOR YOU.
ELLIE:
SHE DROPPED ME OFF.
SEAN:
SHE DROVE?
SOBER, HONEST.
HOPEFULLY WILL BE
FOR THE NEXT TWO MONTHS.
SHE'S GOING TO REHAB.
AND I'M HERE TO STAY,
IF I WANT TO.
DO YOU STILL WANT ME TO?
YEAH.
WHAT IS THAT?
HOLD ON, HOLD ON.
IT'S A WEASEL.
IT'S A FERRET.
I SAW HIM
AT THE PET STORE AND...
SHOULDN'T WE HAVE TALKED
ABOUT THIS FIRST?
A HOME ISN'T A HOME
WITHOUT A PET.
(GIGGLE)