THANKS.
SPINNER:
I WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
RIGHT AFTER I GET THIS.
THE NEW MANAGER
IS A BATTLE AXE.
I NEED TO BOOST
TURNOVER OR ELSE...
SWEAT ON YOU,
KIND OF CUTE.
YOU SWEATING
ON FOOD SERVICE ITEMS?
A LITTLE LESS CUTE.
ALL BETTER.
OH MY GOD,
THIS IS MY FAVOURITE
SONG EVER.
OH MY GOD,
MY EARS ARE BLEEDING.
WHY AM I YOUR FRIEND?
FRIEND?
UH...
YOU GIRLFRIEND,
ME BOYFRIEND.
YOU MAKE ME BATHE DAILY,
ME MAKE YOU GO CAMPING.
NOW I KNOW WE'RE NOT
"OFFICIAL"
BUT WE SHOULD BE.
SO WHAT DO YOU SAY?
SAY YES.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
MANNY:
FOR SCIENCE YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE MS. HATZILAKOS.
AND FOR MATH,
MR. ARMSTRONG.
MATH IS CHAFE.
I HATE IT.
SO IS THE ROYAL TOUR
STANDARD DEGRASSI
PROCEDURE?
OR IS IT JUST 'CAUSE
OF THE SHOOTING?
THE SHOOTING IS NOT WHAT
OUR SCHOOL'S ABOUT.
SO I GUESS THE WELCOMING
COMMITTEE
IS JUST ME TRYING
TO SHOW PEOPLE
THAT THERE'S OTHER
STUFF.
THE CAFETERIA'S NEXT.
TASTY BURRITOS.
SIMPSON:
PLEASE EXCUSE THE INTERRUPTION.
WOULD PAIGE MICHALCHUK
AND MARCO DEL ROSSI
PLEASE REPORT
TO THE PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE?
THIS IS CRAIG MANNING,
FROM GRADE ELEVEN.
THIS IS CHESTER'S FIRST DAY.
OH. COOL.
WELCOME.
CAN I TALK TO YOU
FOR A SECOND?
UM ACTUALLY,
I'M JUST-
THIS WAY
TO LOS BURRITOS?
YEAH.
CRAIG:
SO A LOT HAS BEEN GOING ON
IN MY HEAD LATELY.
INCLUDING THINKING
ABOUT LAST YEAR.
CRAIG, IT'S OKAY.
NO, IT'S NOT OKAY.
I'VE MADE A LOT OF MISTAKES
SINCE COMING HERE,
BUT YOU WERE PROBABLY
THE BIGGEST.
I MEAN...
IF I COULD GO
BACK IN TIME,
I WOULD HAVE STOPPED
THAT NIGHT,
SAVED US BOTH
A LOT OF PAIN.
THAT'S ALL YOU
THINK IT WAS?
A LOT OF PAIN?
GEE, THANKS FOR YOUR
APOLOGY,
BUT I'M FINE.
PAIGE:
MADEMOISELLE SPIRIT SQUAD,
MR. PREZ.
THAT'S WHY WE WERE
CALLED DOWN.
MARCO:
YEAH, BUT WHAT IF IT'S NOT?
WHAT IF WE'VE DONE
SOMETHING BAD?
WILL IT GO ON MY RECORD?
PAIGE, WILL IT COST ME GETTING
INTO THE MY SCHOOL OF CHOICE?
IT'S GONNA COST YOU
A HANDSHAPED WELT
IF YOU DON'T CALM DOWN.
MANNY, HON,
WHAT'RE YOU UP TO?
I'M JUST GOING TO MATH
UNFORTUNATELY.
WELL,
BECAUSE I AM SO NICE?
YOU CAN TAKE MY RADITCH
MEETING INSTEAD, OKAY?
MANNY:
RADITCH?
BUT I'M ACTUALLY REALLY-
SOMETIMES
I SO HATE THAT GIRL.
UH... LEFT SIDE,
SMIDGE LOW.
DON'T THEY TEACH
"DISPLAYS"
IN TEACHER SCHOOL?
YEAH.
IT'S MY MINOR.
SOCIAL FAUX PAS?
IT'S NOT REALLY ME.
WHICH IS WHY SHOWING UP
AT THE BAR THAT NIGHT?
IT MAKES ME
A COMPLETE DORK.
YEAH WELL,
YOU KNOW,
A DORK
WITH A LOT OF GUTS.
AND SOME PRETTY GOOD
FAKE I.D.
YEAH, I KNOW
THE RIGHT PEOPLE.
SO, CHARLIE...
SHE'S PRETTY.
GREAT SENSE
OF HUMOUR.
TOTAL PACKAGE.
YEAH...
AND NOW SHE'S TOTALLY
IN MY PAST.
WE BROKE UP.
NOT BECAUSE OF US.
NOT THAT THERE
IS AN US,
BUT CHARLIE AND I,
WE JUST WEREN'T
WORKING OUT.
YOU'RE, WHAT,
MY BROTHER'S AGE?
A YEAR OLDER THAN THAT?
HE'S DATING MARCO.
YEAH, BUT HE'S NOT
MARCO'S TEACHER.
WELL,
YOU'RE NOT MINE.
NOT REALLY.
SIMPSON:
PAIGE.
CLASS ISN'T QUITE THE SAME
WITHOUT YOU TALKING
TO HAZEL SO...
(BELL RINGS)
RADITCH:
IF YOU'RE WAITING
FOR THE PRINCIPAL,
AND I ASSUME YOU ARE,
I'M NOT THE PRINCIPAL
YOU'RE WAITING FOR.
SHE'S INSIDE.
IS THAT, LIKE,
A RIDDLE, SIR?
NO.
IT'S LIKE, THE BOARD HAS
ASSIGNED ME TO ANOTHER SCHOOL.
SURPRISE, SURPRISE.
WHOA.
YOU'RE OUR NEW PRINCIPAL?
YES, I AM.
FOR THE TIME BEING.
SO WHERE'S PAIGE?
I'M PAIGE.
FOR THE TIME BEING.
ALL RIGHT.
SO THE BOARD HAS DONE
THEIR PART
IN HELPING EVERYONE DEAL
WITH THE SHOOTING.
AND NOW IT'S OUR TURN.
WE NEED TO BRING
SCHOOL SPIRIT BACK.
WELL, WHAT ABOUT
THE SCHOOL PLAY?
AH, THAT'S MY
NEXT MEETING
WITH JT AND LIBERTY.
I'M GONNA GREEN-LIGHT
THEIR PROJECT.
THIS IS GREAT
FOR SO MANY REASONS.
MARCO THOUGHT WE WERE
IN TROUBLE.
SHUT UP, MANNY.
NO.
YOU'RE NOT IN TROUBLE,
AT ALL.
IN FACT...
WE NEED SOME
MORE GREAT IDEAS.
AND WHEN I SAY WE,
I MEAN YOU TWO.
SO SHE WANTS US
TO ORGANIZE
THIS HUGE EVENT
TO RAISE SCHOOL SPIRIT.
ISN'T THAT AMAZING?
YEAH. THAT'S COOL.
I NEED IDEAS.
EMMA, PLEASE HELP ME?
NOW, PLEASE?
I'M SURE YOU'LL
THINK OF SOMETHING.
BAAA, BAAAA...
WELL, HI.
I'M LA-LA-LLAMA,
FROM FLUFFY-FLUFF
COLLECTIONS.
OH, IT'S SO CUTE!
COOL.
SO, ABOUT WHAT
I ASKED YOU YESTERDAY...
WE'RE HAVING FUN,
RIGHT?
SO WHY DO WE HAVE TO GO
AND MAKE IT ALL OFFICIAL?
'CAUSE THAT'S WHAT
COUPLES DO.
OOH YIKES,
I'VE SO GOTTA RUN.
BUT THANKS FOR THE LLAMA!
MARCO:
ALL RIGHT, SO WHAT'VE YOU GOT?
HIT ME.
UH, I'M THINKING...
FUN FAIR AND FIELD TRIP.
WHAT?
NAH. COME ON.
THAT'S TOO JUNIOR HIGH.
MANNY:
YOU JUST WANT TO DANCE.
ADMIT IT.
EVERYBODY LIKES
TO DANCE.
THE YOUNG, THE OLD...
MY EX-SCHOOL HAD THIS GREAT
DANCE THIS ONE TIME.
IT WAS A CUPID THEME.
EVERYBODY PAIRED OFF
BY COMPUTER.
ELECTRONIC ICE-BREAKING.
NICE.
THE IDEA'S YOURS
IF YOU WANT IT.
OF COURSE, IT'LL COST YOU
A FREE TICKET
AND A DANCE.
AND YOU KNOW, I THINK
HE WAS TALKING TO YOU.
(BELL RINGS)
AND THIS FRIDAY
WE'RE HAVING A MAJOR DANCE.
HOLD ON TO YOUR HEARTS
AS CUPID HAS HIS WAY.
COMPUTERS WILL BE SET UP
AROUND THE SCHOOL.
ANSWER A FEW QUESTIONS
AND WHEN YOU ARRIVE
AT THE DANCE,
YOUR LOVE MATCH
WILL BE WAITING.
MR. OLEANDER
IS A TEACHER, PAIGE.
THANKS MARCO,
I DIDN'T REALIZE THAT.
WELL, YOU KEEP
TALKING ABOUT HIM
LIKE HE'S SOME HOT
12TH GRADER OR SOMETHING.
NO, HE'S A BIG BABY
WHO WON'T TAKE
THE NEXT STEP.
HE WON'T EVEN CRAWL
TOWARDS IT.
OW, LEG CRAMP.
OW, UNWISE DECISION.
IT'S NOT A DECISION.
I CAN'T TURN OFF HOW I FEEL.
FINE,
IT'S NOT CONVENTIONAL,
BUT I THOUGHT YOU
OF ALL PEOPLE WOULD UNDERSTAND.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
BE ON MY SIDE,
FOR STARTERS.
KWAN:
NAMASTE,
YOGIS AND YOGINIS.
UM, MS KWAN?
THIS IS MR. OLEANDER'S
ASHTANGA CLASS.
KWAN:
NOT ANY MORE.
WITH HIS WORKLOAD,
YOGA WAS TOO MUCH
OF A COMMITMENT.
SO, YOU AND MARCO
HAVE PASSWORDS.
YOU CAN ACCESS THE PROGRAM
BEFORE THE DANCE
AND GENERATE YOUR RESULTS.
WOW.
YOU MAKE IT SOUND COOL.
WELL, BASICALLY
YOU PLUG IN A NAME...
THEN YOU ANSWER FIELDS LIKE
FAVORITE SUPERHERO?
DOES BUBBLES FROM
THE POWER PUFF GIRLS COUNT?
NO.
HOW ABOUT FAVOURITE MOVIE?
OOOH.
DEFINITELY "HONEY!"
BOYFRIEND'S NAME?
I DON'T HAVE ONE.
NOTHING SERIOUS ANYWAY.
SO WHY DON'T YOU
PUT IN YOUR NAME?
JUST FOR FUN.
OKAY.
COMPATIBLE.
EVEN IF WE ARE THE ONLY
TWO PEOPLE IN THE PROGRAM.
(KNOCKING)
THANKS, CHESTER.
IT'S GOING TO BE
AMAZING.
I'LL MAKE SURE THAT MARCO
GETS HIS PASSWORD.
BANANA SANDWICH
FOR YOUR THOUGHTS?
NOT ABOUT THAT KID,
ARE THEY?
WHO, CHESTER?
NO. NO.
I'M JUST DISTRACTED
LATELY
'CAUSE I'M ORGANIZING
THIS ENTIRE DANCE.
WITH MARCO.
WHO I'VE SPOKEN TO,
OH I DON'T KNOW,
8 TIMES TODAY.
LOOK, I'M SORRY.
TOMORROW, EVERY SINGLE
DANCE IS YOURS.
YOU'LL GET SICK
OF ALL THE ATTENTION.
I WORK TOMORROW NIGHT.
SO?
ASK FOR IT OFF.
SAY YOUR SICK
OR SOMETHING.
I CAN'T.
GRIM REAPER
WILL FIRE ME.
MY OWN BOYFRIEND
CAN'T MAKE IT TO MY DANCE?
BOYFRIEND?
FUNNY, I THOUGHT
WE WERE JUST DATING.
YOU DON'T WANT ME
TO BE YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
YOU JUST THINK
IT'S WHAT COUPLES DO.
AND YOU'RE NOT GONNA
CONVINCE ME
WITH A STUPID STUFFED LLAMA
FOR 10-YEAR-OLDS.
CRAIG GAVE ME ONE
TWO YEARS AGO.
WHAT? WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
IF YOU CAN'T COMMIT
TO A SIMPLE DANCE,
HOW CAN YOU COMMIT TO ME?
SPINNER:
MANNY? WHAT-
RADITCH:
I LOVE DEGRASSI.
IT'S BEEN SUCH AN IMPORTANT
PART OF MY LIFE.
BUT ALL GOOD THINGS
MUST COME TO AN END.
I LOOK FORWARD TO THE
CHALLENGES AND OPPORTUNITIES
THAT ARE SET OUT BEFORE ME.
AS DOES YOUR NEW ACTING
PRINCIPAL, MS. HATZILAKOS.
(APPLAUSE)
HATZILAKOS:
THANK YOU, MR. RADITCH.
AND THANK YOU FOR YOUR MANY
YEARS OF DEDICATED SERVICE
TO THIS SCHOOL AND STUDENTS.
YOU DUMPED SPIN
BECAUSE OF A DANCE?
I DIDN'T DUMP SPIN
BECAUSE WE WERE
NEVER GOING OUT.
HE'S HEARTBROKEN.
YOU KNOW THAT, RIGHT?
SO AM I,
BUT...
IT WASN'T WORKING OUT.
AND WE NEED TO MOVE ON.
WHY?
(AHEM) MARCO?
THE UH, PRESENT?
MARCO:
YEAH...
THANK YOU. THANKS.
THIS IS ON BEHALF
OF ALL THE STUDENTS
HERE AT DEGRASSI,
MR. RADITCH.
WE'RE GONNA MISS YOU.
THANK YOU. THANKS.
(APPLAUSE)
THANKS.
PLEASE. THANK YOU.
SIMPSON:
STUDENTS ARE REMINDED
THAT TONIGHT'S CUPID DANCE
STARTS AT 7:00 P.M.
BE THERE.
I HAD TO GO HOME
AND CHANGE.
SO WHERE'S MY
TRUE LOVE-O-GRAM?
DANNY?
OH, MANUELLA?
I USED TO
BABYSIT YOU.
SO LET'S TAKE IT
TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
I WAS SUPPOSED
TO GET CHESTER.
MARCO:
FIRST OF ALL - OW!
AND SECOND?
THE COMPUTER DECIDES,
MANNY, NOT YOU.
MANNY:
WHY WOULD YOU DO THIS TO ME?
WHY WOULD YOU
DO THIS TO SPIN?
EXCUSE ME?
MARCO:
HE LOVES YOU, OKAY?
AND I KNOW YOU CARE ABOUT HIM.
SO STOP BEING AFRAID OF WHAT
HAPPENED LAST YEAR WITH CRAIG
AND JUST TAKE A CHANCE.
YOU NEEDED TO HEAR IT
FROM SOMEONE.
AND YOU NEED TO GET
OVER YOURSELF.
HEY,
CONGRATS ON THE KISMET.
UM, HEY, MANNY.
HEY.
SO, CHESTER
I OWE YOU.
YOUR THEME.
YOUR ONE DANCE.
CHESTER:
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M JUST GOING TO GO
GET A BAG OF CHIPS.
DO WANT ANYTHING,
CHESTER?
NAH.
I'M FINE AS IS.
PARTNER ME, DEL ROSSI.
SO WHO'S
THE LUCKY GUY?
HUH, ISN'T THAT ODD?
IT'S YOU.
AND UH,
WHO DID YOU GET, MR. O?
I'M NOT A STUDENT.
I DIDN'T PARTICIPATE,
PAIGE.
WHAT DO I DO?
DON'T ASK ME.
AS OF NOW, PAIGE,
YOU'RE FRESH OUT
OF MARCO'S FAVOURS, OKAY?
I WAS AT THE DOT
AND I THOUGHT,
I CAN CLEAR PLATES ANYWHERE,
BUT WHERE DO I ORDER ME
ANOTHER MANNY?
I TOLD YOU-
I KNOW, I KNOW.
I SHOULD'VE TAKEN
THE NIGHT OFF.
PLUS GIVEN YOU
A REAL REASON
WHY I WANT US
TO BE OFFICIAL.
I WANT YOU TO BE MY GIRLFRIEND
BECAUSE WE HAVE FUN.
BECAUSE YOU MAKE ME HAPPY.
AND I WANT YOU TO BE
MY GIRLFRIEND BECAUSE...
I CAN'T IMAGINE IT
ANY OTHER WAY.
YOU'RE ON
THE REBOUND.
THAT DOESN'T
MEAN ANYTHING.
IT MEANS EVERYTHING.
REBOUNDS NEVER
WORK OUT.
SO WE END IT NOW
BEFORE EITHER OF US
GETS HURT.
CHESTER:
I THOUGHT YOU'D WANT
THE PINK POP.
SHE DOESN'T KNOW
WHAT SHE WANTS.
(FAST DANCE TUNE PLAYS)
DO YOU LOVE THIS SONG?
I LOVE IT.
IT'S A BIT BRITNEY,
BUT UH, SURE.
COME ON!
GUY:
(LAUGHING) NICE.
LET'S GO GET SOME AIR
OR SOMETHING.
OKAY. AS SOON
AS THIS SONG ENDS.
GUY 2:
SO EMBARRASSING!
I'M GONNA GO NOW.
MEET ME IN THE HALL
WITH THE STRIPES?
HATZILAKOS:
THERE YOU ARE.
THANKS FOR ALL
YOUR WORK TONIGHT.
SUCH A SUCCESS.
WE NEED MORE OF THESE.
MATT:
WHY ARE YOU ACTING LIKE THIS?
PAIGE:
WHY DO YOU CARE?
YOU'RE ONLY MY TEACHER,
REMEMBER?
MATT:
IF YOU'RE GOING
TO BEHAVE LIKE THIS-
PAIGE:
WHAT, YOU'LL GIVE ME
A DETENTION?
MATT:
STOP TRYING TO PROVOKE ME,
PAIGE.
STOP ACTING LIKE
A JEALOUS BOYFRIEND.
YOU EITHER LIKE ME
OR YOU DON'T.
I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY... SORRY.
MATT...
CHESTER:
MANNY...
THERE YOU ARE.
LOOK, I'M SORRY
ABOUT THE DANCE FLOOR.
EVERYONE WAS
WATCHING AND-
SO?
I DON'T KNOW.
I GET EMBARRASSED.
I'M SORRY FOR BEING
EMBARRASSING.
NO.
I DIDN'T MEAN THAT-
CAN WE JUST START AGAIN?
WHAT AM I DOING?
IT'S OKAY.
IT'S JUST, LET'S JUST
GO BACK TO THE DANCE.
I'M SORRY, CHESTER.
IS IT 'CAUSE I'M THE NEW KID
ON THE BLOCK?
NO. NO.
YOU'RE A NICE GUY,
IT'S JUST
I HAVE A BOYFRIEND.
WELCOME TO DEGRASSI.
MATT!
GO HOME, PAIGE.
WE'VE ALREADY CAUSED
ENOUGH DAMAGE TONIGHT.
PAIGE:
I'M SORRY.
NO, YOU KNOW,
I SHOULDN'T HAVE BEEN-
WE WERE BOTH THERE.
AND I UNDERSTAND
IF YOU CAN'T DO THIS.
MATT...
OKAY...
BUT WE CAN'T GET CAUGHT...
NOT AGAIN.
BUT WE HAVE TO MEET
OFF SCHOOL GROUNDS.
LIKE THIS BUS STOP.
IT'S TECHNICALLY,
CITY PROPERTY.
AND AT DEGRASSI,
WE'RE TOTALLY NORMAL.
TOTALLY.
'TILL END OF TERM.
IT'S NOT SO LONG
AT ALL.
(CAR HONKS)
YOU WERE WRONG EARLIER
WHEN YOU SAID I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT I WANTED.
OKAY.
MANNY:
LAST YEAR,
WITH CRAIG -
WHAT HE DID TO ME,
AND HOW HE TREATED ME -
IT HURT...
SO MUCH.
SO WHAT I WANT IS
TO NEVER, EVER FEEL
THAT WAY AGAIN.
OKAY.
YOU HAVE TO PROMISE ME...
PROMISE ME...
THAT YOU'LL NEVER EVER
BREAK MY HEART.
OKAY.
NO, NOT OKAY, SPIN.
PROMISE ME.
I PROMISE.
I WILL NEVER HURT YOU.
YES.