MARCO:
YOU KNOW MY MOTHER WORKS HERE,
RIGHT?
DYLAN:
IT'S NOT LIKE SHE SAW US.
HEY MA.
SO YOU TOOK
THE PICTURES?
YEAH AND THEY ALL
TURNED OUT HORRIBLE.
MRS. DEL ROSSI:
IF PAPA GETS TO MAKE YOUR
ELECTION SIGNS,
I GET TO CHOOSE THE SHOT.
SHOULDN'T THERE BE
FOUR?
NO. NO.
THERE'S JUST THREE.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT,
HORRIBLE?
EVERY ONE OF THESE SAYS
PRESIDENT TO ME.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL SEE YOU AT HOME, MA.
BYE.
DYLAN.
DYLAN, WAIT UP.
DYLAN,
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
DYLAN:
BACK TO MY DORM.
OH.
OKAY THEN, HERE,
TAKE THIS WITH YOU.
MAKE YOUR DORM MATES
JEALOUS.
THEY'RE STRAIGHT.
OKAY.
SO MAKE THEM
UNCOMFORTABLE.
ACTUALLY, THEY DON'T HAVE
A PROBLEM WITH ME BEING GAY.
I'M YOUR BOYFRIEND, MARCO.
I KNOW-
DYLAN:
YEAH, WELL...
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
IN YOUR FAMILY THAT DOES.
BABE-
DYLAN:
I'LL CALL YOU LATER.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ Be the best I can ♪
♪ And I say to you ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
PAIGE.
HEY! I TRIED CALLING YOU
LAST NIGHT.
HMM, SO SAID
THE CALL DISPLAY.
NOT AS MANY TIMES
AS MY BROTHER, THOUGH.
DO YOU THINK I'D MAKE
A GOOD TRAVEL AGENT?
I SO NEED A JOB.
WAIT.
YOU TALKED TO DYLAN?
IN BETWEEN REPEATED
CALLS TO SPINNER.
WEIRD.
HE SAID HE WAS GOING
TO PHONE ME LAST NIGHT.
HE WAS PROBABLY
BUSY STUDYING,
OR JOINING SECRET
SOCIETIES.
WHATEVER THEY DO
AT UNIVERSITY.
SHOULD I BE WORRIED?
PAIGE.
DYLAN'S HARD TO READ,
OKAY?
HE HAS HIS LITTLE TANTRUM,
AND THEN-
OW.
PROSTRATE MUCH?
ALEX:
TRY LOOKING
WHERE YOU'RE WALKING.
ICE PATCHES,
BOTTOMLESS PITS, DOG CRAP
AND ALEX.
PEDESTRIAN HAZARDS
TO AVOID.
NICE SHIRT.
HATE TO BLOODY IT.
NICE ATTITUDE.
HATE TO DEFLATE IT
BY REMINDING YOU
THAT YOU'RE A LOSER.
REALLY.
WHO DECIDED THAT?
EVERYBODY.
MAJORITY RULES ON THESE
MATTERS, SWEETIE.
(BELL RINGS)
SO, WHY DO YOU GIRLS ALWAYS
MAKE YOUR HAIR BIGGER?
WHY ARE YOU GUYS
ALWAYS CATCHING US
DOING EMBARRASSING
STUFF?
HOW YOU BEEN?
LIBERTY:
GOOD MORNING.
WHO ELSE IS READY TO SAY GOUDA
OR PERHAPS GRUYERE?
EMMA AND CHRIS:
HEY, LIBERTY.
HEY CHRIS,
I'M SORRY FOR WHAT
HAPPENED WITH US
IN THE SUMMER.
MAYBE WE COULD GO
FOR A SHAKE SOMETIME?
YEAH.
MAYBE.
ALEX:
GAY KID, HEY.
I SAID HEY.
YOU ALSO SAID,
"GAY KID."
SOMETHING I TEND NOT
TO ANSWER TO.
THANKS.
OKAY. SCHOOL PRESIDENT,
MR. PREZ, BIG GUY.
THAT MORE YOU?
THIS ELECTION THING,
WHAT ARE THE ISSUES?
LOOK, I'M SORRY PAIGE
WAS RUDE TO YOU, OKAY?
DOESN'T MATTER.
C'MON, ANSWER MY QUESTION
LIKE YOU CARE.
SAVE IT FOR THE ASSEMBLY,
ALEX.
GIRL:
ALEX, COME HERE.
HEY MARCO.
I HOPE YOU'RE READY
FOR A HORSE RACE.
ALEX IS RUNNING?
UM-HMM.
TELLS ME SHE'S HUNGRY
FOR BLOOD.
AT ANY RATE,
SHE'S GOT A LOT OF KIDS
TALKING ALREADY
AND NOT ABOUT YOU.
♪♪♪
IS THIS SEAT TAKEN?
I'M SORRY,
KISS SWEET BACON?
IS THIS SEAT TAKEN?
NO, NO, NO.
GO AHEAD,
SEAT DOWN.
UH... BUCK 65.
FOR THE HEADPHONES?
THAT'S WHO'S
ON THE SYSTEM.
(CHUCKLE)
I LIKE THIS PART.
HMM. YEAH.
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED
TO BROADEN MY KNOWLEDGE
OF POPULAR MUSIC.
PROFESSOR CHRIS,
AT YOUR SERVICE.
REALLY?
YEAH.
WELL, MAYBE WE COULD GO
TO THE RECORD STORE
SOMETIME TOGETHER,
OR THE CD SHOP.
WHATEVER.
I'LL BUY YOU
A FALAFEL?
IT'S A DATE.
ALEX?!
CRAIG:
AS IN MOST-LIKELY-TO-SUCCEED-
IN-KILLING-SOMEONE ALEX?
HAND ME YOUR
NOMINATION FORM.
YOU NEED CASH
OR WHATEVER,
I'M HERE.
SPINNER:
WE'LL HANG POSTERS.
HAZEL:
HAND OUT FLYERS.
PAIGE:
WHATEVER IT TAKES TO HELP.
MARCO:
ALEX'S CAMPAIGN IS AN
ILLITERATE CATCH PHRASE.
I'M NOT SO WORRIED.
I'LL SEE YOU
GUYS LATER.
LATER.
SPINNER:
NO, MARCO'S NOT
WORRIED AT ALL.
NOT ABOUT ALEX.
LET'S JUST SAY
SIEGFRIED MIGHT BE
LOOKING FOR A NEW ROY.
DYLAN. HEY.
UH, CAN WE TALK?
NOW'S NOT A GOOD TIME,
MARCO.
MARCO:
LOOK, I JUST HAD
THIS REALLY HUGE DAY.
THERE'S SOMEONE RUNNING
AGAINST ME NOW.
WELL, THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS
IN ELECTIONS, RIGHT?
RIGHT.
YOU FORGOT TO CALL ME
LAST NIGHT.
AFTER THAT THING
WITH THE PICTURES,
I CAME BACK TO MY DORM.
AND UH...
I DID A LOT OF THINKING.
DYLAN, COME ON,
IT WAS JUST A STUPID PICTURE.
DYLAN:
IT'S NOT JUST A PICTURE, MARCO.
AND I CAN'T DO THIS ANYMORE.
I'M SORRY.
NOT LIKE THIS.
I GOT TO GO.
ARMSTRONG:
SO IF A IS EQUAL TO 26
IN THIS TRAPEZOID,
WHO CAN TELL ME
WHAT THE VALUE OF B IS?
ANYONE?
LIBERTY,
YOU WANNA GIVE IT A TRY?
LIBERTY!
UH, BUCK 65?
ARMSTRONG:
NICE TRY.
J.T.?
OKAY, LET'S TRY THIS
ONE MORE TIME.
LIBERTY'S LOSING
HER MATH?
IT MUST BE LOVE.
YOU ALWAYS THINK THAT.
AND LIBERTY HAS DYSCALCULIA,
REMEMBER?
MANNY:
UH, NO.
ARMSTRONG:
GIRLS!
THE CLASS IS UP HERE?
AND MANNY, SO ARE YOU.
MR. DEL ROSSI:
HEY MARCO, WHERE DO YOU GO?
YOU DON'T WANT TO SEE
YOUR POSTERS?
UH, YEAH! SURE.
MY POSTERS.
JUST A MINUTE.
HEY, YOUR MOM AND I
ARE VERY PROUD OF YOU, HUH?
WE'RE GOING TO COME
TO THE ASSEMBLY...
FOR YOUR VICTORY SPEECH.
ACTUALLY, PAPA,
THERE'S COMPETITION NOW.
THAT'S OKAY.
THEN THIS SHOULD
HELP YOU WIN.
SEE?
YOUR MAMA, SHE PICKED
THE PERFECT PICTURE.
PRESIDENT.
THAT'S YOU.
YEAH, YEAH.
IT'S ME.
I HAVE TO WRITE
A SPEECH.
MARCO, WHAT'S WRONG?
THE FACT THAT I'M GOING
TO HAVE TO EVENTUALLY
DELIVER SAID SPEECH.
MARCO?
RELATIONSHIP STUFF, MA.
I MET THIS PERSON
LAST YEAR AND...
WELL, WE...
LOOK, PEOPLE BREAK UP.
I'LL BE FINE.
IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU HAD A GIRLFRIEND.
I DON'T.
SO IT WAS DYLAN.
WHAT?
DYLAN'S A FRIEND, MA.
I'M NOT GAY.
(CRYING)
I AM.
MA, I'M GAY.
(CRYING)
SO...
LIBERTY AND CHRIS.
IT'S A CRUSH.
BIG DEAL.
MANNY:
FUNNY, I HEARD IT WAS A DATE...
TOMORROW,
AFTER SCHOOL.
LIBERTY SEES AN OPPORTUNITY,
SHE GOES FOR IT.
SHE'S LIKE A RABID
WOLVERINE.
SO I'VE GOT EAR CANCER,
THANKS.
LAST NIGHT,
DYLAN HAD ME ON
THE PHONE FOR 3 HOURS,
ALL WORRIED.
AND SINCE SANITY'S
FLED YOU,
I'M WORRIED TOO.
I CAME OUT TO MY MOM
LAST NIGHT.
(HAPPY SQUEAL)
I LOVE YOU,
YOU KNOW THAT, RIGHT?
YEAH.
JUST...
I HOPE SHE STILL DOES,
YOU KNOW?
I MEAN,
SHE SEEMED A LITTLE...
ALL RIGHT,
SHE SEEMED A LOT-
YOU'VE HAD A YEAR OF BEING GAY,
MARCO.
SHE'S HAD A NIGHT
OF YOU BEING GAY.
OKAY, I'M SO CALLING
DYLAN RIGHT NOW.
MARCO:
WHA-? HEY! HEY!
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
ALEX:
MOST YOU CAN SPEND
ON YOUR CAMPAIGN IS $40.00.
PAIGE:
UM, THEY WERE FOR FREE.
HIS DAD IS-
DOESN'T MATTER.
UNFAIR ADVANTAGE.
MARCO:
LOOK, WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
BECAUSE YOU'RE RUNNING.
AND BECAUSE I CAN.
NOBODY IS GONNA VOTE
FOR YOU, OKAY?
NOBODY.
NOT YET.
NOT EVER.
UNLESS THEY OPEN UP VOTES
TO HIGH SCHOOL DROP-OUTS
OR YOUR PAROLE OFFICER.
WE'LL SEE.
WE'LL ASK THE CROWD
TOMORROW AT THE ASSEMBLY,
SEE WHAT THEY SAY.
"WHO WOULD YOU
RATHER VOTE FOR?
THE FREAK?
OR THE QUEER?"
BY THE WAY,
I'M THE FREAK.
EMMA:
NICE FORM.
HMPH.
DON'T TEASE ME.
EMMA:
YOU KNOW,
WHAT YOU SAID YESTERDAY
ABOUT GETTING BACK TOGETHER?
I'D REALLY, REALLY,
REALLY LIKE THAT.
I SAID
DON'T TEASE ME.
I'M NOT.
WHAT ABOUT TOMORROW
AFTER SCHOOL?
TOMORROW?
I GOT-
EMMA:
OKAY...
I JUST THOUGHT WE COULD
START THIS YEAR OFF RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL SEE WHAT I CAN DO.
OKAY.
AND I WAS TEASING
ABOUT YOUR FORM, YOU KNOW.
IT'S AWFUL.
♪♪♪
MANNY:
OKAY, TOMORROW AFTER SCHOOL
I'M GONNA COME OVER,
AND I'M GONNA LOAN YOU
THE COOLEST NEW SKIRT.
OKAY,
AND I NEED THIS WHY?
FOR THE WHOLE
GET CHRIS BACK THING.
I MEAN,
THOSE LEGS OF YOURS
THEY'RE A KILLER ASSET.
I'M NOT TRYING
TO GET HIM BACK.
BUT YOU LOVE HIM.
I CAN SEE IT
IN YOUR EYES.
I NEVER SAID THAT.
OKAY, I'M TOTALLY CONFUSED.
I DIDN'T WANT HIM
TO GO ON A DATE.
BECAUSE YOU'RE JEALOUS?
OF LIBERTY VAN ZANDT?
YEAH.
YOU'RE EMBARRASSED?
EMMA:
YOU WOULDN'T BE?
WHAT ARE PEOPLE
GONNA THINK OF ME
IF CHRIS GOES OUT
WITH LIBERTY NEXT?
THAT'S THE MEANEST THING
I'VE EVER HEARD YOU SAY.
AND THAT'S REALLY SAYING
SOMETHING.
MARCO:
MAYBE WE CAN TELL PAPA
THAT THE ASSEMBLY'S
STUDENTS ONLY.
THAT PARENTS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
MRS. DEL ROSSI:
YOU WOULD LIE TO HIM LIKE THAT?
WELL, MAYBE...
MAYBE WE DON'T HAVE TO.
MAYBE ALEX IS JUST BLUFFING;
TRYING TO FREAK ME OUT
BEFORE MY SPEECH.
AND IF SHE'S NOT?
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO, MA.
IT BREAKS MY HEART
THAT BECAUSE YOU ARE GAY,
THESE PEOPLE WILL HATE YOU.
MA, NOBODY HATES ME.
THIS GIRL?
YEAH,
BUT THAT'S NOT BECAUSE I'M-
MR. DEL ROSSI:
I'M HOME!
HEY!
THE POSTERS,
THEY WORKED GOOD, MARCO?
PA, I'M DROPPING OUT
OF THE ELECTION.
LOOK, I TALKED TO THE PRESIDENT
FROM LAST YEAR,
AND HE SAID
IT'S A LOT OF WORK.
MR. DEL ROSSI:
NO, NO, MARCO.
YOU WILL DO IT.
BUT MY STUDIES
ARE GONNA-
NO, MARCO!
FOR RUNNING,
I AM PROUD OF YOU.
BUT NOW QUITTING?
NO. DON'T MAKE ME
LESS PROUD.
HEY LIBERTY!
I THINK I'M ACTUALLY
VOTING FOR ALEX TODAY.
ARE YOU?
YOU'RE DEAD TO ME.
WHAT?
MANNY TOLD ME.
JEALOUSY'S REALLY UGLY,
EMMA.
NO. NO. NO.
LIBERTY...
IT'S HARD FOR ME
LETTING CHRIS GO,
THAT'S ALL.
GUESS WHAT?
IT'S EASY FOR ME
LETTING YOU GO...
STRAIGHT TO HELL.
RADITCH:
ALL STUDENTS ARE REMINDED
TO REPORT TO THE GYM
FOR STUDENT COUNCIL ELECTIONS,
NOT HOME ROOM.
ALEX:
I FEEL LIKE I'M GONNA BARF.
JAY:
DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE SERIOUS
ABOUT THESE STUPID ELECTIONS.
ALEX.
JUST WHO I WANTED
TO SEE.
WHAT?
YESTERDAY, WHEN YOU SAID
YOU'D CALL ME GAY
IN FRONT
OF THE WHOLE SCHOOL-
I WAS GONNA
CALL YOU "QUEER,"
BUT IF YOU
PREFER "GAY"...
MARCO:
I DON'T, THANKS.
LOOK, YOU HAVE AN ACTUAL CHANCE
AT WINNING THIS.
YOU THINK?
SO CALL ME "GAY," "QUEER"
WHATEVER.
BUT IS THAT
HOW YOU WANT TO FIGHT?
OR DO YOU WANNA TRY
AND WIN THIS ELECTION
FOR REAL.
JAY:
SAVE IT FOR MS. SAUVE.
ALEX:
IT'S ALWAYS THE SAME.
SOME PRETTY BOY OR GIRL
WANTS TO BE PRESIDENT,
AND ME... WE...
SIT OUT WHILE THEY HAVE THEIR
"SPECIAL DANCES"
OR TRIPS NOBODY CAN AFFORD.
SO I SAY SCREW 'EM.
SCREW STUDENT COUNCIL.
I SAY NO DANCES,
NO TRIPS, NOTHING.
NOT IF IT'S GOING TO BE
JUST LIKE LAST YEAR.
BUT TAKE A CHANCE,
AND VOTE FOR ME?
IT WON'T BE LIKE LAST YEAR.
I WILL MAKE CHANGES
WHERE THEY COUNT.
SO IT'S UP TO YOU,
DEGRASSI.
WHAT'RE YOU GONNA DO?
ARE YOU GONNA VOTE
FOR THE FREAK?
OR THE PRETTY BOY?
'CAUSE YOU'LL HAVE MORE FUN
WITH THE FREAK.
(APPLAUSE)
THANK YOU, ALEX.
UP NEXT IS MARCO DEL ROSSI.
PAIGE:
MARCO!
(CHEERING)
LOOK, SHE'S RIGHT.
NO, ALEX IS RIGHT.
THE SCHOOL'S SPLIT.
BUT... WHERE SHE'S WRONG?
LOOK, COME ON,
IT'S NOT THE PRESIDENT'S JOB
TO REMIND US
THAT WE'RE FREAKS.
I MEAN, I DO THAT FINE
ALL BY MYSELF.
QUEER! (COUGH)
RADITCH:
MISTER HOGHART,
I'LL SEE YOU AFTER
IN MY OFFICE.
PAIGE:
MARCO!
HEY! QUEER?
SURE.
ODD? WHY NOT?
STRANGE? YOU BET.
I LOVE THIS SCHOOL.
AND I PROMISE
IF YOU VOTE FOR ME,
I WILL BRING DEGRASSI
TOGETHER IN...
FREAKISH HARMONY
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
FOR REAL.
THANK YOU.
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
THE FIRST COUNCIL MEETING
WILL BE THURSDAY AT LUNCH.
AND LAST BUT NOT LEAST,
YOUR STUDENT COUNCIL
PRESIDENT IS...
MARCO DEL ROSSI!
(APPLAUSE)
OUT OF MY WAY.
I GET TO PICK
MY VICE PRESIDENT.
I GET TO PICK MY NOSE.
ALEX.
I DON'T PLAY WELL
WITH OTHERS.
GOOD.
I'M NOT ASKING YOU TO PLAY.
I REALLY LIKED YOUR SPEECH.
BUT, MOST IMPORTANT,
I THINK YOU CAN BRING
A LOT TO THE POSITION.
THURSDAY, RIGHT?
BRING YOUR LUNCH.
DYLAN:
CONGRATULATIONS,
MR. PRESIDENT.
SO, WHAT DOES IT FEEL LIKE
TO BE THE MOST POWERFUL MAN
AT DEGRASSI?
MIXING ME UP
WITH MR. RADITCH, EH?
NOT COOL
NOR FLATTERING.
I LIKED YOU BEING HERE
TODAY, DYLAN.
PROBABLY BECAUSE I JUST
PLAIN OLD LIKE YOU.
I TOLD MY MOM.
DYLAN:
PAIGE TOLD ME.
BUT I'M NOT READY
TO TELL MY DAD,
NOT YET.
YOU'RE EVENTUALLY GONNA
HAVE TO TELL HIM,
BUT WHEN YOU'RE READY.
AND I'M OKAY
WITH THAT PART.
MR. DEL ROSSI:
HEY MR. PRESIDENTE!
THAT'S OUR NEW PRESIDENT, HUH?
I'M SO HAPPY FOR HIM.
SO HOW MUCH DID YOU WIN BY?
MARCO:
I WON.
LET'S LEAVE IT AT THAT.
I STILL THINK YOU COULD HAVE
USED MORE POSTERS.
MARCO, THAT BOY.
WHAT HE CALLED OUT?
AND WHAT YOU ANSWERED BACK?
WHAT IS THAT?
DIRTY POLITICS.
I MEAN, I GUESS "QUEER"
WAS THE WORST THING
HE THOUGHT HE COULD CALL ME,
YOU KNOW?
STILL,
YOU MAKE ME AND YOUR MAMA
VERY PROUD OF YOU TODAY.
VERY PROUD.
DIDN'T HE, DYLAN?
HE WON, MRS. DEL ROSSI
AND...
I THINK THAT'S GREAT.
MRS. DEL ROSSI:
ANDIAMO.