(TAPPING MIC)
(FEEDBACK SQUEALS)
SAV:
THIS IS DEGRASSI RADIO,
COMING AT YOU
FROM THE CAF.
NOW I KNOW I DON'T NEED
TO REMIND YOU
THAT WE ARE IN THE FINAL STAGES
OF CHOOSING A FLY NEW DJ
TO DISH OUT SOME EAR CANDY.
SO LISTEN UP,
TO SEE WHO WILL BE...
THE NEW VOICE
OF DEGRASSI!
BUT... ENOUGH FROM ME.
LET'S GET BACK
TO THE TUNES.
(SMATTERING OF APPLAUSE)
HAS SAV HEARD YOUR DEMO?
OH, IT'S ONLY A MATTER
OF TIME
UNTIL I HAVE MY OWN SHOW.
BUT DON'T WORRY,
I WON'T LET THE FAME
GET TO ME.
MUCH.
I CAN'T WAIT.
GO ASK!
ASK?
OKAY,
HERE GOES NOTHING!
HEY, DJ DAVE,
REPORTING FOR DUTY!
ADAM:
DAVE, YOU HERE
FOR THE RADIO TOO?
DAVE:
YEAH. WHAT DO YOU DO?
YOU, UH, YOU WORK
THE TECH STUFF, RIGHT?
YOU WORK THE KNOBS?
UH, ACTUALLY,
I'M HERE FOR THE ON-AIR GIG.
"THE MAN SHOW"
WITH ADAM TORRES.
YOU'RE DOING A "MAN" SHOW?
YEAH. YOU?
UH, "DAVE TURNER'S
MAN HOUR."
KINDA THE SAME, HUH?
SAV:
YEAH, YOU GUYS ARE MAKING
MY LIFE REALLY DIFFICULT.
YOU EACH SUBMITTED
A GREAT DEMO.
YEAH, FOR PRACTICALLY
THE SAME SHOW.
SO WHO, UH,
WHO GETS THE JOB?
WELL, ACTUALLY,
I'M GONNA LET
THE SCHOOL DECIDE.
YOU TWO WILL DUKE IT OUT
ON-AIR.
WHAT,
LIKE A COMPETITION?
SAV:
EXACTLY!
YOU TWO WILL TEST FOR
THE NEW DEGRASSI RADIO SHOW,
"MANO A MANO."
DAVE:
ALL RIGHT, WELL...
MAY THE BEST MAN WIN.
OKAY.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh... ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
MS. DAWES:
WELL, CLASS,
WE HAVE A LATE ADDITION.
WELCOME TO GRADE 11 DRAMA,
MISS COYNE.
IMOGEN:
AREN'T YOU IN GRADE 12?
I'M SHORT AN ARTS CREDIT.
OKAY, SO WE'VE GOT
SOME EXCITING NEWS!
BECAUSE SO MANY STRONG
DRAMA STUDENTS
HAVE CHOSEN TO GRACE
THIS CLASS,
WE ARE RESPONSIBLE
FOR MOUNTING THE SCHOOL PLAY!
WHAT KIND OF PLAY
EXACTLY?
MS. DAWES:
THAT'S THE CLASS'S
FIRST ASSIGNMENT,
MR. GOLDSWORTHY;
TO FIGURE OUT WHAT PLAY
WE WANNA DO.
SO, I WANT YOU TO BREAK
INTO GROUPS OF...FOUR
AND LET THE BRAINSTORMING BEGIN!
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
(SIGHS)
HEY, DO YOU HAVE ROOM
FOR ONE MORE?
WE ALREADY HAVE FOUR.
I RHYMED,
SO IT MUST BE TRUE!
(LAUGHS)
MS. DAWES:
FIONA, I KNOW THIS MUST BE HARD.
I'LL JUST BRAINSTORM
ON MY OWN.
THEY'RE PROBABLY
JUST INTIMIDATED,
YOUR BROTHER WON
THE GRUNDY.
DON'T WORRY, YOU'LL FIND
YOUR PLACE SOON ENOUGH.
(SIGHS)
MAY I GO TO THE GIRLS ROOM?
YEP.
SAV: (OVER PA)
THERE ARE DOZENS OF CLUBS
STILL LOOKING FOR MEMBERS.
STOP BY THE DISPLAY
TO JOIN ONE TODAY.
CLUBS ARE BACK!
FINALLY,
THIS IS A HIGH SCHOOL AGAIN,
AND NOT A PRISON CAMP.
QUESTION IS,
WHICH CLUB TO JOIN?
NOT THE USUAL?
DRAMA, FICTION...
THOSE ARE ELI ZONES.
HE'S ON SOME KIND OF
ANTI-ANXIETY MEDS,
AND I DON'T WANT
TO PUSH HIS BUTTONS.
WELL, HOW ABOUT...
ORIENTEERING?
ALLI,
FOR THE MILLIONTH TIME,
I'M NOT INTERESTED
IN JAKE MARTIN.
WELL, YOU DID KISS HIM.
ONCE, BY ACCIDENT.
BESIDES, THIS SEMESTER
IS NOT ABOUT BOYS.
IT'S ABOUT ME,
AND MY HEART IS SET ON...
NEWSPAPER.
IT'LL BE A GREAT WAY
TO DIVERSIFY
MY WRITING PORTFOLIO.
THERE'S KATIE MATLIN,
THE EDITOR.
KATIE:
I'M HOME FROM PRACTICE
SEVEN-ISH.
CAN WE TALK CHEMISTRY
HOMEWORK THEN?
EVER HEARD
OF TAKING A BREAK?
EVER HEARD OF NOT BEING
A SLACKER?
(LAUGHS)
LOVE 'YA, BABE!
KATIE?
HI, I'M CLARE.
I'D LIKE TO JOIN
YOUR WRITING STAFF.
UH, YOU CAN'T JUST
JOIN THE NEWSPAPER,
YOU NEED TO BE SELECTED.
OKAY, WHAT DO I DO?
WRITE A SAMPLE ARTICLE.
A CONCISE HUNDRED WORDS
BY THE END OF DAY.
NO ADJECTIVES,
NO ADVERBS.
GREAT. WHAT SHOULD
THE ARTICLE BE ABOUT?
HOW ABOUT...
TEN WAYS TO GET OVER
A BREAK-UP.
CAN YOU HANDLE THAT?
I'M LIVING IT.
YES, YES.
ABSOLUTELY.
HOLLY J:
WHO LOOKS GOOD
IN THESE THINGS?
UH, YOU?
HOLLY J:
I KNOW. (LAUGHS)
I CAN'T BELIEVE GRAD PHOTO DAY
IS HERE!
ONE OF THE LAST STOPS
ON THE WAY
TO THE REST OF MY LIFE!
WELL, DON'T BE IN TOO MUCH
OF A HURRY TO DITCH ME, OKAY?
I'M GONNA BE ALL BY MYSELF
NEXT YEAR!
WHO WILL PROOFREAD
MY ESSAYS?
WHO WILL I GOSSIP WITH ME
IN BETWEEN CLASSES?
SPEAKING OF CLASS,
SHOULDN'T YOU BE IN DRAMA?
YEAH,
BUT WE GOT OUT EARLY.
OKAY, I GOT OUT EARLY.
BUT IT WAS FILLED
WITH GRADE ELEVENS -
UNFRIENDLY, RHYMING ONES.
ONCE THEY SEE WHAT
A DRAMA QUEEN YOU ARE,
THEY'LL LOVE YOU!
FIONA:
HOLLY J, YOU KNOW I HAVE TROUBLE
MAKING FRIENDS.
EVEN YOU I INHERITED
FROM DECLAN.
WHAT ABOUT CHARLIE?
WEREN'T YOU GUYS
ON THE FRIEND PATH?
YEAH, BUT WE HAVEN'T SPENT
MUCH TIME TOGETHER
SINCE SPRING BREAK.
YOU CAN'T MAKE FRIENDS
WITH SOMEONE
UNLESS YOU SPEND TIME
WITH THEM!
YEAH...
YOU KNOW, HOLLY J,
YOU MIGHT BE RIGHT.
(HOLLY J CHUCKLES)
SO WE'RE SUPPOSED TO LIKE,
JOUST ON AIR,
TO SEE WHO WINS.
YOU'RE FUNNY AND ADORABLE;
YOU'VE SO GOT THIS!
DAVE:
I NEED THIS.
PLUS, I MEAN,
I CAN'T LOSE TO ADAM,
OF ALL PEOPLE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"OF ALL PEOPLE"?
WELL, HOW'S HE SUPPOSED
TO HOST A MAN SHOW?
BECAUSE HE'S TRANSGENDERED?
YEAH, IT'S WEIRD.
ADAM'S NICE.
YOU THINK EVERYONE'S NICE.
WHAT?
SADIE:
MY LOCKER'S NEAR ADAM'S,
AND I HEAR HIM TALKING
TO HIS FRIENDS SOMETIMES.
HE'S PRETTY FUNNY.
OKAY, SO I'LL PULL OUT
THE "A" GAME,
AND I'LL PROVE
THAT I'M BETTER,
FUNNIER, AND MANLIER.
HOW HARD CAN IT BE?
(TAXI RUMBLES)
(HORNS HONK)
FIONA:
SURPRISE!
CHARLIE:
FIONA? WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
WE JUST HAVEN'T HUNG OUT
IN SO LONG,
I THOUGHT WE COULD HAVE
SOME LUNCH.
I BROUGHT A PICNIC,
INCLUDING HOMEMADE APPLIE PIE.
YOU BAKED A PIE?
WELL, SOMEONE DID.
SO...
DO YOU WANNA SPEND
SOME TIME WITH ME?
I'D LOVE TO,
BUT I CAN'T LEAVE THE STORE.
OH, OF COURSE, WORK.
GOD, I'M SO STUPID.
BUT WE CAN HAVE IT HERE.
ELISE:
SEE YA, CHARLIE.
SEE ANYTHING YOU LIKE?
ELISE:
OH! I'M STILL DESPERATE TO MAKE
THAT SHINY BLACK STELLA MINE.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU CAN'T GET ME A DISCOUNT?
YOU DO KINDA OWE ME.
CHARLIE:
UH, ELISE,
THIS IS MY FRIEND, FIONA.
FROM SPRING BREAK.
OH, RIGHT.
I HEARD CHARLIE GOT YOU
HOOKED ON SCOOTERS TOO.
OH YEAH, I'M STILL TRYING
TO GET THE HANG OF IT.
FIONA BROUGHT A PICNIC LUNCH.
UM...
THERE'S ENOUGH
FOR THREE.
YOU'RE WELCOME TO JOIN US.
ARE YOU SURE?
I-I WAS JUST LEAVING.
OF COURSE!
THE MORE, THE MERRIER.
(SIGHS)
WELL?
UH...
WELL, IT'S THE MOST
WELL WRITTEN,
AND DETAILED ARTICLE
ON SURVIVING A BREAK-UP
THAT I'VE EVER READ.
BUT?
DON'T YOU THINK
IT'S A LITTLE LONG?
I WANNA STAND OUT!
ALLI:
KATIE ONLY ASKED
FOR A HUNDRED WORDS.
ANYONE CAN DO THAT.
KATIE WILL BE IMPRESSED
THAT I WENT ABOVE AND BEYOND.
IF YOU SAY SO...
I KNOW SO!
ALLI:
WELL, YOU GET AN "A"
FOR EFFORT.
(CLARE LAUGHS)
(SIGHS HAPPILY)
OKAY,
BEFORE WE GET STARTED,
DO I NEED TO REMIND YOU TWO
HOW NERVOUS SIMPSON IS
ABOUT HANDING THE AIRWAVES
OVER TO STUDENTS?
ADAM: NOPE.
DAVE: GOT IT.
GOOD. KEEP IT CLEAN,
KEEP IT FUN,
LET ME KNOW
WHEN YOU'RE READY.
OH, I WAS BORN READY.
OH, IS THAT HOW
YOU WERE BORN?
HOW WERE YOU BORN?
SHORT?
MMM, IT'S LIKE THAT.
YOU WANT ME TO TAKE
THE GLOVES OFF?
GO AHEAD, DAVE!
SHOW ME WHAT YOU'RE PACKING.
(DAVE BARKS)
DAVE:
THAT'S MY ATTACK DOG.
I TRAINED HIM
TO CRAVE WEAKLING.
ADAM:
YO, I WILL DOG WHISPER
YOUR BUTT.
I WILL OWN YOU!
DAVE:
YOU CAN'T OWN ME, HOLMES,
I GOT THE MIND OF A NINJA,
THE EYE OF THE TIGER,
THE COURAGE OF A LION!
ADAM:
THE BRAIN OF A SCARECROW,
AND THE HEART OF A TIN MAN.
BOOM!
DAVE:
OH, YOU DID NOT
JUST "BOOM" ME!
ADAM:
OH, I BOOMED YOU, DOROTHY.
I BOOMED YOU BIG TIME,
AND I'LL DO IT AGAIN!
DAVE: OH NO, YOU-
ADAM: BOOM!
(LAUGHS) ALL RIGHT,
WELL, LOOK,
WE'LL SEE HOW FUNNY YOU ARE
WHEN WE'RE ON THE AIR.
ARE WE READY?
LET'S DO THIS.
(MUFFLED LAUGHTER
FROM OUTSIDE BOOTH)
IT'S BEING DONE,
MY FRIEND.
(STUDENTS LAUGH AND CLAP)
WE'RE ON AIR?
AND THE PEOPLE HAVE SPOKEN.
(CHEERING AND CLAPPING)
BOOM!
(SIGHS)
ADAM:
"MANO A MANO"
WITH DAVE AND ADAM!
THIS IS GONNA BE AWESOME!
DAVE:
LOOK, I GOTTA SAY
I WANTED TO BEAT YOU,
BUT IT'LL BE WAY MORE FUN
TO JOIN YOU.
WE RULE!
I'LL BE OUT IN A SEC.
(DOOR CLICKS)
AH, YOU...CAME IN.
YOU GOTTA WHIZ TOO?
NO, JUST, UH...
WANNA WASH MY HANDS.
SO, WHAT ARE WE GOING
TO TALK ABOUT TOMORROW?
DAVE:
UH...GIRLS? MUSIC?
WHATEVER WE WANT.
DAVE:
OR WE COULD, UH,
PUSH THE ENVELOPE,
TAKE ON SOME ISSUES,
SEE HOW FAR WE CAN GO
UNTIL SIMPSON REAMS OUT SAV.
ADAM?
WHAT? OH! UM...
YEAH, SIMPSON.
DUDE,
YOU'VE GOT ISSUES!
NO, DAVE,
I WASN'T STARING!
LOOK, WHATEVER.
I'VE GOT CLASS.
DAVE:
EL PRESIDENTE,
YOU GOT A MINUTE?
DAVE! YEAH.
ANYTHING FOR MY NEW SHOCK JOCK!
WHERE'S YOUR OTHER HALF?
DAVE:
YOU MEAN ADAM?
SAV:
YEAH. YOU TWO ARE ALL THE BUZZ.
DUDE,
CHECK THIS OUT.
NEW T-SHIRT PROTOTYPE.
MADE IT MYSELF.
YEAH, LOOK,
IT-IT'S GREAT AND...
I HAD FUN AND EVERYTHING,
BUT...
I GOTTA QUIT THE SHOW.
UM, YOU HAVEN'T EVEN
STARTED YET.
AND WHY?
I CAN'T REALLY TALK
ABOUT IT.
LOOK, ME AND ADAM,
WE'RE JUST,
WE'RE NOT A GOOD FIT.
IT'S JUST A RADIO SHOW,
DUDE!
YOU'RE NOT MARRYING ANYONE.
BESIDES, PEOPLE LOVE
YOU TWO TOGETHER!
YOUR FIRST BROADCAST
GOT A HUNDRED EMAILS.
A HUNDRED?!
I'M SAYING,
GIVE IT A WEEK,
YOU TWO ARE GONNA BE
THE MOST POPULAR GUYS
AT THIS SCHOOL.
YOU WANNA GIVE THAT UP?
OFFICER TURNER:
SON! YOUR SHOW WAS HILARIOUS!
YEAH? YOU HEARD?
YOU DA MAN!
YOU'RE GONNA BE BACK ON
AGAIN TOMORROW, RIGHT?
YEAH, YEAH.
CAN'T WAIT TO HEAR IT.
PROUD OF YOU.
TWELVE NOON.
♪ "MANO A MANO"
WITH DAVE AND ADAM! ♪
(SIGHS)
CHARLIE:
HOME SAFE AND SOUND.
SO YOUR FRIEND ELISE
WAS SO NICE TO ME!
DOESN'T EVERYONE LOVE YOU
AT FIRST SIGHT?
I WISH!
I'M NOT EXACTLY FITTING IN
AT SCHOOL.
IT'S HIGH SCHOOL;
WHO DOES?
PLUS, YOU ONLY HAVE
A FEW MONTHS LEFT.
NEGATIVE.
IT'S A LONG,
BORING STORY,
BUT I'M SHORT
A FEW CREDITS,
SO I'LL BE BACK
NEXT YEAR,
AND THE FEW FRIENDS
THAT I DO HAVE
WILL BE HEADING
TO THEIR IVORY TOWERS.
I'LL BE ALL ALONE.
HEY, YOU'LL HAVE ME.
(LAUGHS)
I SHOULD REALLY GO,
BEFORE MY BOSS NOTICES
I'VE BEEN GONE
FOR AN HOUR AND A HALF!
ARE YOU SURE
YOU DON'T WANT ME
TO DROP YOU OFF AT SCHOOL?
VERY SURE.
WHAT ABOUT TONIGHT?
ANY PLANS?
YEAH.
BOWLING NIGHT.
OH.
THERE'S ALWAYS ROOM
FOR ONE MORE.
REALLY?
I LOVE BOWLING.
I MEAN,
I ASSUME I WILL.
YOU'VE NEVER BEEN?
WELL THEN,
TONIGHT'S YOUR LUCKY NIGHT!
(GIGGLES)
FIONA, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
MOM, I THOUGHT YOU HAD
A SPA THING.
LARA:
I CANCELLED.
WHY AREN'T YOU AT SCHOOL?
I SHOULD GO.
LARA:
THAT'S AN EXCELLENT IDEA.
MY DAUGHTER AND I NEED TO TALK.
♪♪♪
HI, KATIE.
CLARE, WHAT DO YOU
HAVE FOR ME?
ONE SAMPLE ARTICLE,
SIGNED, SEALED,
AND DELIVERED.
W-WELL, NOT SEALED,
BUT THE OTHER TWO.
GREAT.
UH, LEAVE IT ON MY DESK.
(SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
SO WHEN DO YOU THINK
YOU'LL GET A CHANCE
TO READ MY ARTICLE?
KATIE:
I HAVE SOME TIME NEXT FRIDAY.
NEXT FRIDAY?!
I'M JOKING, CLARE.
UNCLENCH!
PEOPLE SAY I'M INTENSE.
HOW ABOUT I READ IT NOW?
GREAT!
I SAID A HUNDRED WORDS.
I WANTED TO DO MORE
THAN A FLUFF PIECE.
THIS IS FIVE PAGES!
YOU PUT IN FOOTNOTES,
AND THERE'S AN APPENDIX!
KIDS AREN'T GOING
TO READ THIS.
WELL,
YOU DON'T KNOW THAT.
YOU'RE TELLING ME
WHAT I DON'T KNOW?
MAYBE IT JUST NEEDS
A CATCHY HEADLINE.
I'M SORRY, CLARE,
THE NEWSPAPER STAFF IS FULL.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
I GUESS DAVE
ISN'T COMING.
I ONLY WENT INTO
THE GUY'S BATHROOM
BECAUSE I WANTED HIM
TO SEE ME AS A GUY.
BACKFIRE MUCH?
BECAUSE YOU GOT CAUGHT
SNEAKING A PEEK.
NO! I-I TOLD YOU,
I WASN'T SNEAKING A PEEK!
I JUST WANTED TO CHECK OUT
HIS STANCE AT THE URINAL.
WHY THE SUDDEN INTEREST
IN URINALS?
BECAUSE OF THIS.
WHAT THE HECK IS THAT?!
ADAM:
A STAND-TO-PEE DEVICE.
I GOT IT ONLINE.
IT'S SO I CAN-
STAND TO PEE?
HOW DOES IT WORK?
HOW DO YOU THINK
IT WORKS?
ELI:
MAYDAY, TEN O'CLOCK.
WHAT DO I SAY?
JUST BE COOL.
ACT LIKE IT NEVER HAPPEND.
NO, BUT IF-IF DAVE
CAN'T HANDLE THIS,
THEN WHO CAN?
GIVE HIM SOME CREDIT.
HEY.
HEY, I THOUGHT
YOU WEREN'T COMING.
WELL, UH, WE HAVE A SHOW
TO PLAN FOR, DON'T WE?
WELL, GOOD LUCK.
WELL, WE SHOULD GET STARTED.
UH...
MOM, WILL YOU LET ME
EXPLAIN?
WHY YOU SKIPPED SCHOOL?
IT WAS A REALLY HARD DAY
FOR ME.
SO YOU DECIDED TO LEAVE.
AND YOU DECIDED
TO EMBARRASS ME
IN FRONT OF CHARLIE!
THAT IS NOT WHAT
WE'RE DISCUSSING RIGHT NOW!
FINE, I GET IT.
YOU'RE MAD.
THIS IS WHAT MAD
LOOKS LIKE!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
BUT UNDERNEATH THE MAD
IS A LOT OF WORRY, FIONA!
YOU'VE ALREADY LOST
ONE SEMESTER!
YOU CAN'T AFFORD
TO LOSE ANOTHER.
BUT I DON'T NEED SCHOOL.
I COULD GET A JOB!
YOU'RE SEVENTEEN.
YOUR JOB IS TO GO
TO SCHOOL.
BUT WHAT IF I HATE IT -
A LOT?!
IF THAT'S TRULY
HOW YOU FEEL,
WE'LL GO BACK TO NEW YORK.
WHAT? NO!
THE ONLY REASON
WHY WE'RE HERE
IS BECAUSE YOU PROMISED
DEGRASSI WOULD BE
GOOD FOR YOU.
(SIGHS)
OKAY, FINE,
I'LL GO TO SCHOOL.
I PROMISE,
NO MORE SKIPPING.
GOOD!
OTHERWISE, YOU'RE ON
THE NEXT PLANE TO LA GUARDIA.
ALLI:
SO, BASICALLY, YOU BLEW IT.
CLARE:
KATIE DIDN'T EVEN READ
MY ARTICLE.
ALLI:
WELL, MAYBE SHE'LL GIVE YOU
A SECOND CHANCE?
(CLARE SIGHS)
THERE SHE IS,
I SHOULD GO TALK TO HER.
NOW LET'S SEE YOUR BEST
"I'M SORRY" FACE.
THAT'LL DO.
NOW, I'LL BE OVER THERE
GETTING MY LATTE ON.
KATIE, CAN WE TALK
FOR A SECOND?
I HAVE SOCCER PRACTICE.
SEE YOU LATER, MARE.
MARISOL, CAN YOU PLEASE
TELL YOUR FRIEND I'M SORRY?
IT'S, UH, GONNA TAKE
MORE THAN THAT.
SEE, KATIE GOES OUT OF HER WAY
TO AVOID DRAMA,
AND YOU...ARE DRAMA.
I AM NOT DRAMA!
♪ These friends of mine ♪
♪ They try, they try ♪
♪ We all struggle,
we all strive ♪
SO WE SHOULD COME UP
WITH SOME BITS
WE CAN USE
OVER AND OVER.
YEAH, LIKE UH...
JOKE OF THE DAY.
YEAH,
OR STUMP THE DORK.
PEOPLE CAN SEND YOU
THEIR TRIVIA QUESTIONS.
EXCUSE ME?
I'M THE DORK?
WE DON'T HAVE
TO CALL IT THAT.
OKAY. UM, ANYWAY,
HOW ABOUT WE DO THIS?
WE CAN DO A QUIZ,
LIKE...
HERE, HAND ME YOUR PEN.
WHAT IS YOUR PROBLEM?
NO PROBLEM.
WAS IT SOMETHING I DID?
I MEAN, EVER SINCE YOU RAN
OUT OF THE BATHROOM...
LOOK, ADAM, IT'S NOT YOU,
IT'S NOT THE BATHROOM.
WE'RE GOOD.
OKAY.
I, UH, JUST HAD
TOO MUCH CAFFEINE.
COOL.
WELL, WE SHOULD PROBABLY
GET BACK TO WORK.
I, UH, HAVE TO...
JUST GIVE ME A MINUTE.
BATHROOM BRAINSTORM,
I HAVE ANOTHER IDEA.
AND IT COULDN'T WAIT?
WELL, I GOTTA GO TOO.
SO ON "JESSE AND GENE,"
THEY USED TO WRITE
NEW LYRICS TO OLD SONGS.
I MEAN,
THEY WERE NO WEIRD AL,
BUT IT WAS PRETTY GOOD.
WHAT-WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
JUST GOING TO THE BATHROOM.
ADAM:
SO THIS ONE TIME,
GENE SANG LIKE
THIS DYING OLD GUY,
AND INSTEAD
OF "CRY ME A RIVER,"
IT WAS "BUY ME A LIVER."
WHAT-WHAT IS THAT?
NOBODY SAID
YOU HAVE TO STARE!
OH! AH!
DUDE! MY SHOES!
I'M SORRY, I'M STILL TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO WORK THIS THING.
OH, GROSS!
OH! THIS- LOOK,
THIS IS TOO MUCH!
ADAM:
DAVE, COME ON.
I'M SORRY!
LOOK, JUST STAY AWAY
FROM ME, OKAY?
(BATHROOM DOOR SLAMS)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
HEY CHARLIE, IT'S ME.
AGAIN.
I HOPE YOU GOT MY MESSAGES
FROM LAST NIGHT.
(SIGHS)
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT MAD.
THE CAR'S DOWNSTAIRS!
GOTTA GO TO SCHOOL.
BUT PLEASE...
CALL ME BACK.
(PHONE BEEPS)
LARA:
DON'T OBSESS, SHE'LL CALL.
♪ Everything is gonna change ♪
(SIGHS)
♪ Everything is wrong ♪
♪ Wrong people are being loved ♪
♪ wrong ones dying ♪
HEY, IS DAVE ALMOST HERE?
UM... YEAH,
ANY-ANY MINUTE NOW.
I CAN'T WAIT TO HEAR YOU GUYS
TOP YESTERDAY'S SHOW.
FOR SURE,
IT'LL BE SICK.
HEY.
HEY, I'M-I'M STILL REALLY SORRY
ABOUT YESTERDAY.
YEAH,
LET'S JUST DO THE SHOW.
YEAH, WE'RE BOTH MEN.
WHO NEEDS TO TALK,
RIGHT?
MAYBE THAT CAN BE THE TOPIC.
HEY DEGRASSI,
WELCOME TO "MANO A MANO"
WITH DAVE AND ADAM!
LET ME TELL YOU,
IT DOES NOT SMELL GOOD
IN THE BOOTH TODAY,
SO LAY OFF THE BURRITOS
OUT THERE!
(FORCED LAUGH)
WHAT I WANT TO TALK ABOUT TODAY
IS BATHROOM RULES.
NOW, NOT TO GET
ALL POLITICALLY INCORRECT,
BUT SHOULD GIRLS
BE ALLOWED
TO USE THE GUYS' BATHROOM
AT SCHOOL?
SAV:
DAVE, SERIOUSLY, WATCH IT!
DAVE:
BECAUSE HOW I SEE IT IS,
I MEAN...
YOU'RE IN THERE
DOING YOUR THING,
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN
THERE'S A TRANNY
STARING AT YOUR JUNK!
SAV:
DAVE!
WHY IS THIS COOL?
(CUTS TO A SONG)
THAT'S IT, I'M CUTTING YOU OFF.
DAVE:
TEXT ME.
LET ME KNOW
WHAT YOU THINK.
NOT COOL, DAVE.