(HIP HOP MUSIC PLAYS)
OWEN:
GREAT.
IT'S OUR BIG DATE
AND YOU'RE NOT EVEN HAVING FUN.
ANYA:
NO, I AM. SERIOUSLY.
YOU KNOW, I CAN TAKE YOU HOME
IF YOU WANT.
UH, NO, NOT YET.
THE MINUTE I GO HOME,
I HAVE TO BREAK THE BAD NEWS.
WHAT, ABOUT UNIVERSITY?
WHY TELL THEM YOU DIDN'T
GET ACCEPTED TONIGHT?
WELL, THE MANDATORY
GRADUATE EXIT MEETING
WITH SIMPSON IS TOMORROW,
SO THEY'RE GOING
TO FIND OUT.
MAYBE IT WON'T BE
SO BAD.
NO, YOU DON'T GET IT.
MY MOM'S MY BEST FRIEND
AND I LIED TO HER.
SHE THINKS I'M GOING
TO TORONTO UNIVERSITY,
PURSUING MY DREAMS...
BIANCA:
(LAUGHING)
WHY AREN'T YOU GUYS
DANCING?!
OWEN:
ANYA, YOU KNOW BIANCA?
HEY.
NO, DON'T MIND US.
WE'RE JUST ENJOYING
FROM THE SIDELINES.
BIANCA:
COOL.
THIS IS PAULY AND CHLOE.
I LIKE YOUR NECKLACE.
WHERE DID YOU GET IT?
ANYA:
I GOT IT
WHEN I WAS LIKE TEN.
MY MOM PUT SAND IN IT.
OH MY GOD,
THAT IS SO SWEET.
DID YOU GUYS WANT A BUMP?
OWEN:
UH, I DON'T THINK
SHE'S IN THE MOOD.
HAVE YOU EVER
DONE IT?
COKE? NO.
YOU?
NEVER.
WOULD YOU?
I GOT PRACTICE EARLY
IN THE MORNING, SO...
YOU CAN DO IT
IF YOU WANT.
I'M NOT YOUR MOM.
WELL, THINGS CAN'T POSSIBLY
GET ANY WORSE, SO...
(LAUGHS)
OH MY GOODNESS.
UM...
WOO! LET'S GO DANCE.
(LAUGHS)
YES!!
(LOUD CLUB MUSIC PLAYS)
♪ Cannot take no more
of that lions ♪
of that science ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh... ♪
♪ I can make it! ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
CHARLIE?
WHO NEEDS A WAKE-UP?
FIONA:
(GASPS) YOUR FIRST MORNING,
AND YOU GOT UP TO GET COFFEE?
I'M IN ROOMMATE HEAVEN.
YEAH, WELL,
I SLEPT LIKE A LOG.
MY LAST PLACE WAS ABOVE
A SUBWAY LINE
AND IT RATTLED
EVERY THREE MINUTES.
(SIGHS)
NO MORE LASCIVIOUS CHATS
WITH THE CONCIERGE REQUIRED.
YOUR VERY OWN FOB.
MY VERY OWN WHAT?
OH, THE BEEPY KEY THING!
YES, THE BEEPY KEY THING.
(LAUGHS)
YOU'LL BE USED TO LOFT LIVING
IN NO TIME.
SO, WHAT'S ON
THE SKEDGE TODAY?
MORNING CLASS
AND THEN I HAVE A SIX HOUR SHIFT
AT MOTORETTA,
AND THEN I VOLUNTEER
AT A HOMELESS SHELTER.
LIKE WITH HOMELESS PEOPLE?
THAT'S HANDS-ON OF YOU.
(BIANCA SIGHS,
HEARS A MEOW)
WHAT'S THAT?
MR. TUXEDO PANTS.
YOU HAVE A CAT?
WE HAVE A CAT?
I HAD TO PICK HIM UP
THIS MORNING.
EX-ROOMMATE'S ORDERS.
(MR. TUXEDO PANTS MEOWS)
YOU'RE JUST FULL OF SURPRISES!
YOU'RE SURE YOUR MOM
WON'T FREAK OUT
WHEN SHE COMES BACK
FROM HER TRIP?
NO, IT'S FINE.
RIGHT, LITTLE GUY?
(MEOW)
BOTH:
(LAUGH)
HOLLY J:
IT'S NOT TOO LATE TO SIGN UP
FOR THE "VOLLEY FOR KIDNEYS"
BEACH VOLLEYBALL TOURNAMENT.
YOUR SUPPORT GOES
TO KIDNEY RESEARCH.
WHOA!
YOU LOOK LIKE CRAP.
THANKS.
HOW WAS HOCKEY PRACTICE?
GREAT.
TOP LINE
FOR THE TOURNAMENT.
HOW ARE YOU,
PARTY GIRL?
TERRIBLE.
NOT ONLY DID I FEEL CRAPPY
FROM THIS COMEDOWN,
BUT... (LAUGHS)
I JUST HAD THE WORST
FAMILY BREAKFAST EVER.
OH, YOU BROKE
THE NEWS, HUH?
YUP. THEY CRIED.
WELL, MAYBE THE WORST
OF IT'S OVER.
UM, I DOUBT IT.
MY MOM'S IN THE CAR RIGHT NOW
RE-APPLYING HER MASCARA
BEFORE SHE GETS TO COME IN
AND HEAR SIMPSON TELL HER
HOW I DIDN'T LIVE UP
TO MY FULL POTENTIAL.
THIS IS FUN.
BACK TO REALITY.
SUCKS.
FOR A WHILE LAST NIGHT,
I FELT LIKE I COULD
DO ANYTHING,
AND NOW I FEEL WORSE
THAN I'VE FELT IN WEEKS.
MAYBE COKE WAS A BAD IDEA.
YA THINK?
OOOH...
YOUR MOM LOOKS BUMMED.
I HATE MY LIFE.
HI, MOM.
I KNOW YOU'RE UPSET
AND I'M SORRY I LET YOU
AND DAD DOWN.
IF WE'RE UPSET,
WE'RE ONLY UPSET
BECAUSE YOU LET YOURSELF DOWN.
WE JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU ONLY APPLIED TO T.U.?
HONEY, I LIKE THE IDEA
OF YOU BEING NEARBY,
BUT WHY LIMIT YOUR OPTIONS?
WE RAISED YOU
TO BE INDEPENDENT.
I DID IT...
FOR A GUY.
WAS THIS GUY
ALSO A DOCTOR?
I KNOW,
AND I'M SO STUPID.
I WASTED SO MUCH TIME
OBSESSING OVER GUYS
AND HAD I JUST FOCUSED
ON SCHOOL
AND I MIGHT BE GOING TO YALE
WITH HOLLY J.
OH, IT MUST HAVE BEEN HARD
TO FOCUS ON UNIVERSITY
WHEN I WAS GOING
THROUGH CHEMO.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT,
MOM.
SIMPSON:
WELL, I TALKED
TO THE GUIDANCE COUNSELOR
AND THERE'S A SLIM CHANCE
THAT HASLETT UNIVERSITY
WILL ACCEPT LATE ADMISSIONS.
SO, THIS SHOULD BE SENT
WITHIN THE NEXT COUPLE
OF DAYS.
OKAY,
I'LL FIX THIS,
GET MY LIFE ON
THE RIGHT TRACK,
AND MAKE YOU PROUD.
MAKE YOURSELF PROUD.
RIGHT.
LAST CHANCE U,
HERE I COME!
OKAY, HAVE YOU THROWN OUT
ALL THE GIRLS UNDERPANTS?
I TOLD YOU,
IT WAS A PHASE.
I WAS CURIOUS,
BUT I'M NOT ANYMORE.
I FOUND SOMETHING ELSE
TO FOCUS ON.
THE APP CONTEST?
WILL YOU AND HANNAH
BE MY PARTNERS?
OKAY, PROMISE YOU WON'T
STARE AT HER...
CHESTAL AREAS.
I SWEAR ON MY IPAD,
OKAY?
HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO FINISH THIS
AND WRITE
AN ADMISSIONS ESSAY?
I GUESS THIS MEANS
YOU'RE BAILING ON PLAYING
FOR MY VOLLEYBALL TEAM LATER?
SORRY, I'M EXHAUSTED.
BUT YOU LOOK SO GOOD
IN A BIKINI!
WHY SO TIRED, ANYWAY?
OKAY, PROMISE YOU WON'T
JUDGE ME, HOLLY J?
ME? NEVER!
IS THAT NOT WHAT
THE J STANDS FOR?
IT STANDS FOR JEANNETTE.
I PROMISE.
WHAT'S UP?
OKAY, YOU MIGHT
WANT TO SIT DOWN.
UM...
LAST NIGHT
I TRIED COCAINE.
ANYA!
I MEAN, ANYA.
WHY?
(SIGHS)
UM...
SOME OF OWEN'S FRIENDS
WERE DOING IT
AND I WAS HAVING
A REALLY BAD NIGHT.
CLEARLY.
I PROMISE
I WON'T DO IT AGAIN.
GOOD.
'CAUSE IN A FEW MONTHS
WE'RE GOING TO BE ON
TO BIGGER AND BETTER THINGS.
DON'T LET SOME GRADE ELEVEN
WITH BLUE EYES
AND TOO MUCH GEL
DRAG YOU DOWN.
STOP BLAMING OWEN
FOR EVERYTHING.
HE DIDN'T MAKE ME DO IT.
FINE.
JUST FOCUS ON YOUR ESSAY.
CONSIDERING YOU MISSED
THE DEADLINES,
YOUR CHANCES HERE
ARE KINDA SLIM TO NONE.
WELL, THANK YOU FOR THE VOTE
OF CONFIDENCE.
I WOULD BE AN IDEAL CANDIDATE
FOR YOUR UNIVERSITY BECAUSE...
BIANCA:
ATTENTION!
ASK ME WHAT IT'S LIKE-
NO, NO, NO,
NOT LISTENING.
OKAY, I'VE GOT APPLICATIONS
AND I'VE GOT TO FOCUS, OKAY?
PLEASE TELL ME YOU'RE HERE
TO HELP ME MAKE POSTERS?
ASK ME WHAT IT'S LIKE
LIVING WITH THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL GIRL ON EARTH.
WHAT IS IT LIKE LIVING
WITH THE MOST-
WONDERFUL!
SHE BROUGHT ME COFFEE.
OOH LA-LA!
I'M SO GLAD MAMA COYNE
LET CHARLIE MOVE IN.
MAMA COYNE HAS NO CLUE.
ONCE SHE GETS BACK
FROM HER BUSINESS TRIP
IN NEW YORK
AND SEES HOW HAPPY I AM,
SHE'LL NEVER KICK
CHARLIE OUT.
DOES CHARLIE KNOW
SHE'S A DIRTY LITTLE SECRET?
AS THEY SAY, NO NEED
TO AIR OUT DIRTY LAUNDRY
WHEN THERE'S PLENTY
OF FRESH!
I DON'T KNOW ANYBODY
WHO SAYS THAT.
(LAUGHS)
HOLLY J, WE HAVE SO MANY
GOOD THINGS TO DISCOVER
ABOUT EACH OTHER
AS WE FALL DEEPLY IN LOVE.
WHY GET HUNG UP
ON THE BAD?
AND SHE HAS A CUTE KITTY.
HIS NAME IS
MR. TUXEDO PANTS.
AND YOU'RE ALLERGIC
TO HIM?
DON'T SAY THAT!
I LOVE KITTIES.
BOTH:
(LAUGH)
SO, I LEAVE FOR MY HOCKEY
TOURNAMENT TOMORROW.
DO I GET SOME ANYA TIME
BEFORE I GO?
I'M ONLY THREE LINES
INTO MY ADMISSION ESSAY.
SO, I GUESS WE'RE NOT
HANGING OUT.
OKAY, WHAT IF I DON'T
GET IN, OWEN?
THIS IS ALL I HAVE
GOING FOR ME RIGHT NOW.
YOU KNOW, SCHOOLS AREN'T GOING
TO CARE IF YOU SUBMIT
SOME STUPID APPLICATION.
SO YOU'RE SAYING
I SHOULD JUST GIVE UP?
YOU'RE SUCH
A CRAB BUCKET-ER!
NO. I'M SAYING,
IF YOU WANT SOMETHING,
TAKE IT.
LIKE I DID WITH YOU.
AND WHAT IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
CALL 'EM.
TELL THEM YOUR STORY.
YOU CAN'T JUST CALL.
THAT'S NOT HOW IT WORKS.
SAYS WHO?
EXPLAIN YOU HELPED YOUR MOM
THROUGH CANCER.
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE LATE.
YOU THINK THEY'LL CARE?
LOOK, A FEW PIECES OF PAPER
WITH SOME CHECKED BOXES ON IT
AREN'T GONNA SHOW THEM
HOW AMAZING YOU ARE.
AND AT OWEN UNIVERSITY,
YOU'D BE ON THE DEAN'S LIST.
SHUT UP.
(DIALLING BEEPS)
NO, NO, NO.
YOU KNOW HOW NERVOUS I GET
ON THE PHONE!
I'LL BE RIGHT HERE.
(BELL RINGS)
HI, ADMISSIONS?
ELI:
GET THIS,
WE OPEN THE PLAY WITH A SONG,
THAT ESTABLISHES THE THEME!
SO, LIKE A THEME SONG?
EXACTLY!
ELI:
ANTIHISTAMINE?
YEAH, I'M ALLERGIC
TO MR. TUXEDO PANTS.
I'M NOT FOLLOWING.
MY ROOMMATE'S CAT.
AND LOOK - HIVES!
ELI:
THOSE LOOK LIKE BITES.
MAY I?
GROSS.
WHAT KIND OF BITES?
ELI:
WEIRD. YOU'VE GOT BED BUGS.
THEY HAVE EYES?
UGH! OKAY,
I DO NOT HAVE BED BUGS!
EWW!
(BELL RINGS)
ANYA:
A FACE-TO-FACE INTERVIEW
WITH THE HEAD OF ADMISSIONS!
I TOLD YOU.
YOU'RE AMAZING.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE LIKE
MY CONFIDENCE.
YOU MAKE ME FEEL
LIKE I CAN DO ANYTHING.
OH STOP,
I'M BLUSHING.
YOU KNOW, MY MOM ACTUALLY
DROPPED THE PHONE
WHEN I TOLD HER.
I'M GONNA GET
INTO UNIVERSITY!
YOU KNOW, YOU ARE LIKE
THE ONLY PERSON
WHO'S MADE ME FEEL GOOD
ABOUT MYSELF IN WEEKS.
ARE YOU REWARDING ME
BY BEING IN A BIKINI?
AND BY GOING OUT TONIGHT.
HOLLY J:
ANYA!
OH, ONE SEC.
OKAY, IT'S OUR LAST CHANCE
TO BE TOGETHER
BEFORE THE TOURNAMENT,
SO...
HOLLY J:
YOU MADE IT!
GUESS WHO SCORED AN INTERVIEW
WITH HASLETT U?
ANYA,
THAT IS AWESOME.
YOU BROUGHT COMPANY?
TWO TEAMS,
TWENTY BUCKS A PIECE.
WHAT'S THAT,
LIKE FORTY BUCKS?
THERE ARE MORE TEAMS
REGISTERED.
THEY'RE ON THEIR WAY.
WHAT HE MEANT TO SAY
IS THAT HE CALLED SOME OF HIS
HOCKEY FRIENDS TO COME PLAY
AND THAT THEY WILL
BE HERE SOON.
THANK YOU, OWEN.
LET'S TALK ABOUT MY FUTURE
AS A UNIVERSITY GIRL.
DO YOU THINK I CAN
GET INTO A SORORITY?
I'M CREATING A DATABASE,
THEN I'LL CODE
THE ALGORITHM.
WAIT, FOR THE APP COMPETITION?
THIS SOUNDS ADVANCED.
NO, IT'S ACTUALLY
QUITE SIMPLE.
BEFORE THE DRESS CODE,
I STRUGGLED
WITH PICKING CLOTHES,
AND GIRLS HAVE SO MANY
VARIETIES OF MATERIALS
AND COLOURS.
YOU KNOW, YOU MIGHT BE ON
TO SOMETHING HERE.
YEAH, OUR APP CAN MAKE
GETTING DRESSED AN EQUATION.
TOP OPTION A,
PLUS BOTTOM OPTION B,
EQUALS OUTFIT X!
AND THEN THE USERS TELL THE APP
HOW THEY'RE FEELING,
AND THEN IT RECOMMENDS
AN OUTFIT
FROM ARTICLES
IN THEIR WARDROBE.
WOW, CONNOR.
LET ME KNOW IF YOU'RE
LOOKING FOR INVESTORS.
I'M PROUD OF YOU,
BUDDY.
(CAMERA CLICKING)
WHAT THE?
(GARBAGE CAN CLATTERS)
YUP.
IT'S DEFINITELY BED BUGS.
WHY DIDN'T I SEE THEM?
MY MOM IS GONNA BE
SO MAD AT ME.
WELL, THESE BLOOD SUCKERS
ONLY COME OUT AT NIGHT.
THEY HIDE IN SMALL PLACES -
SEAMS, TUFTS,
THE CREVICES IN YOUR MATTRESS.
UGH! DISGUSTING!
WHAT DO I NEED TO DO?
WELL, IT'S A PROCESS.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO GET
ALL YOUR CLOTHES, LINENS,
CARPETS CLEANED.
AND WE CAN HELP YOU WITH
THE CLEANING AND STEAMING,
BUT YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO KEEP UP THE WORK
TO MAKE SURE
THEY DON'T COME BACK.
I'M A CLEAN PERSON,
YOU KNOW!
HOW DID THEY EVEN
GET IN HERE?
WELL, THEY CAN COME
FROM APARTMENT COMPLEXES,
HOTEL BEDS, MOVIE THEATRES...
I HAVEN'T BEEN
TO ANY OF THE ABOVE.
WELL, MAYBE SOMEONE ELSE
BROUGHT THEM IN.
ANY NEW PEOPLE COME OVER?
(MR. TUXEDO PANTS MEOWS)
(SIGHS)
YES, ACTUALLY.
♪♪♪
♪ Yeah,
s-o u-n-d the a-l-arm ♪
♪ You led the red (unclear) ♪
♪ Yeah, come on, get ready ♪
♪ Bring it all around ♪
♪ I've got the girl down
and I'm real unsteady ♪
♪ Bring it all around, yeah ♪
ANYA:
WOOOO! KEEP IT UP!
SPREAD THE WORD, GUYS!
HOLLY J:
AND GET SOME SNACKS.
ALL PROCEEDS GO
TO KIDNEY RESEARCH.
SO, WHEN YOU GET INTO HU,
ARE YOU GONNA STAY IN RESIDENCE,
GET YOUR OWN PLACE?
I THINK RESIDENCE WILL
BE BETTER.
MEET NEW PEOPLE,
MAKE FRIENDS.
BY FRIENDS
YOU MEAN CUTE COLLEGE GUYS?
NO, I ACTUALLY
MEAN FRIENDS.
SERIOUSLY, YOU'RE NOT GONNA
STAY WITH OWEN, ARE YOU?
I DON'T KNOW...
I'LL BE THERE,
HE'LL BE HERE.
HOLLY J:
YOU'RE FINALLY GETTING
BACK ON TRACK.
OKAY, GIRLS LIKE US
DON'T NEED GUYS LIKE THAT
LINGERING AROUND.
BESIDES, YOU'RE BETTER
THAN HIM.
AHHHH! OHH!
OOPS.
I'M SOAKED!
OWEN!
SORRY, BABE.
DEFECTIVE SQUEEZE BOTTLE.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
I'M FINE.
IT'S JUST A LITTLE WATER.
♪ Hello, goodbye ♪
♪ Come to sing
this lullaby ♪
♪ Open up your eyes,
so you see what I'm sayin' ♪
♪ Stop pickin' up the telephone,
just wanna be on my own ♪
♪ Just get outta my way! ♪
♪ Your heart is pumpin' for me
I don't need a one and only ♪
♪ Don't believe
in fairytales...♪
(CLUB MUSIC PLAYS)
♪♪♪
YOU KNOW,
IT'S NOT CELEBRATING
IF I'M THE ONLY ONE
DANCING.
I'M DANCING.
WHAT MORE DO YOU WANT?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET'S JUST GO HOME.
OH, YEAH, RUN ALONG.
CALL HOLLY J.
WHAT IS THAT SUPPOSED
TO MEAN?
(MOCKINGLY) OH,
WE DON'T NEED BOYS
DRAGGING US DOWN.
SCREW THAT, MAN!
OWEN...
DID SHE NOT SAY THAT?
THAT YOU'RE TOO GOOD FOR ME?
SHE SAID THAT,
I DIDN'T.
SHE'S TRYING TO TURN YOU
AGAINST ME.
CAN'T YOU SEE THAT?
AND YOU LISTEN TO EVERYTHING
THIS GIRL SAYS.
I DON'T WANT YOU
HANGING AROUND HER.
YOU CAN'T TELL ME
WHAT TO DO.
TRUST ME,
IT'S FOR YOUR OWN GOOD.
SHE'S GIVING YOU FALSE HOPE
ABOUT THIS UNIVERSITY STUFF.
FALSE HOPE?
YOU THINK I'M GONNA
SCREW THIS UP?
YEAH, IF YOU KEEP LISTENING
TO HOLLY J
AND BEING HER LAP DOG,
ABSOLUTELY.
I'M NOT ANYBODY'S DOG.
YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
CHARLIE:
HEY, I'M HOME.
SORRY, I DIDN'T PICK UP...
DINNER.
DID YOU GET MY TEXT?
ARE WE MOVING?
IT CROSSED MY MIND.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WE HAVE BED BUGS!!
BED BUGS?!
WITH EYES.
I'M DOING DAMAGE CONTROL
BEFORE MY MOM GETS HOME.
I'VE NEVER FELT SO FILTHY
IN MY ENTIRE LIFE.
WHAT CAN I DO TO HELP?
NOTHING. PEST CONTROL'S
COMING BACK TOMORROW.
THIS SUCKS, FIONA.
FIONA:
DOESN'T IT?
THANKS TO YOU,
I HAVE TO SLEEP
ON THE FLOOR TONIGHT.
THANKS TO ME?
YOU THINK
I BROUGHT THEM IN?
WHO ELSE?
OH, I DON'T KNOW...
MAYBE ANYBODY?
DID YOU CONSIDER THAT
MAYBE IT WASN'T ME?
WELL, THEY WEREN'T HERE
BEFORE YOU MOVED IN.
AND I HAVEN'T BEEN
ANYWHERE SKETCHY, SO...
OH, I'M SKETCHY,
IS THAT IT?
YOU SAID YOU LIVED
ABOVE A SUBWAY LINE.
THAT DOESN'T MEAN
I HAD A BED BUG INFESTATION!
YOU VOLUNTEER AT
A HOMELESS SHELTER
AND YOU KEEP YOUR CLOTHES
IN THAT OLD DUFFEL BAG!
YOU ACTUALLY THINK
YOU'RE BETTER THAN ME
BECAUSE YOU HAVE MONEY.
CHARLIE...
NO, SORRY I'M NOT
A PORCELAIN DOLL LIKE YOU.
OKAY, THAT'S NOT
WHAT I MEANT.
I'M JUST SO GROSSED OUT.
AWESOME.
I'M GONNA GO
HAVE A SHOWER.
AND MAYBE I'LL SLEEP
IN THE TUB
SINCE YOU THINK
I'M SO DIRTY.
(SIGHS)
CHLOE:
PRETTY NECKLACE GIRL.
BIANCA:
YOU ALL RIGHT?
NOT REALLY.
(LAUGHS)
I'D LIKE TO GO HOME.
OWEN LOOKED PISSED.
YEAH. MY BOYFRIEND SUCKS.
MY FRIENDS SUCK.
SO, WHAT HAPPENED?
I'M REALLY SICK AND TIRED
OF HAVING EVERYBODY
TELL ME WHAT TO DO ALL THE TIME,
YOU KNOW?
BREAK UP WITH HIM,
DON'T BE FRIENDS WITH HER...
YOU CAN'T JUST LET PEOPLE WALK
ALL OVER YOU LIKE THAT.
I KNOW.
IT'S JUST...
IT SEEMS LIKE EVERYONE KNOWS
WHAT'S BEST FOR ME,
EXCEPT FOR ME.
CHLOE:
SO PROVE THEM WRONG.
DO YOUR OWN THING.
MAKE YOUR OWN CHOICES.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
LIKE TONIGHT,
I WANNA HAVE FUN.
CAN I BORROW
SOME OF THAT?
UH, REALLY?
YEAH, I NEED IT.
HERE.
TAKE THE REST
OH, I CAN'T, IT'S...
IT'S A GIFT.
♪ Now who else in here ♪
♪ Can make that thing move
from left left, right right ♪
♪ I'm caught in a trance ♪
♪ That's why we keep dancing
all night, night, night... ♪
HOW'RE YOU FEELING?
UH, LIKE THE NIGHT
IS YOUNG. (LAUGHS)
I CALLED MY OLD ROOMMATE.
NO SIGN OF BED BUGS,
SO... BEATS ME.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
STEAMING.
WHAT ARE YOU
STEAMING ABOUT?
US...
LIVING TOGETHER.
AND IF WE'RE GONNA
BE ROOMIES,
WE SHOULD GET TO KNOW
EACH OTHER,
SO YOU START.
SHORT VERSION.
(SIGHS)
I'M FROM THE 'BURBS.
MY PARENTS GOT DIVORCED
WHEN I WAS FOURTEEN.
MET SOME BAD PEOPLE,
LIVED ON THE STREETS FOR A BIT.
A COUPLE OF YEARS AGO,
I MEET UP WITH MY MOM.
SHE PAYS FOR MY ART SCHOOL
AND I WORK SO I CAN PAY
FOR MY LIVING EXPENSES.
CLASSIC RAGS TO SLIGHTLY
BETTER RAGS STORY.
(LAUGHS)
NOW YOU.
WELL, MY DAD'S A DIPLOMAT,
SO I SPENT MY ENTIRE LIFE
TRAVELLING FROM ONE CAPITAL
TO THE NEXT.
MY LAST STOP WAS AT
A PREP SCHOOL IN NEW YORK,
WHERE I DIDN'T FIT IN.
AND NOW I'M BACK HERE.
(LAUGHS)
I GUESS I LIKE MY LIFE
RIGHT NOW.
I LIKE MY LIFE RIGHT NOW
TOO...
WITH YOU.
(PHONE RINGS)
OH.
MOM? HOW ARE YOU?
AH, YOU'RE KIDDING!
OH MY GOD.
OKAY,
I HAVE TO CALL YOU BACK.
LOVE YOU. BYE.
WHAT?
OH!
I OWE YOU
A TITANIC APOLOGY.
THEY'RE FUMIGATING
THE PENTHOUSE IN NEW YORK.
(LAUGHS)
MY MOM BROUGHT
THE BED BUGS.
GUESS I'M THE ONE WITH
THE DIRTY LITTLE SECRET.
YOU DISGUST ME.
(GIGGLES)
♪ Desire ♪
♪ You all know I want it,
you'll never have to ask ♪
♪ Desire ♪
♪ I told you with my body
that the answer is yes ♪
LOOK, I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO...
WAIT.
WERE YOU JUST AT A BATHROOM
COKE PARTY?
WHAT DO YOU CARE?
SHE'S ALL YOURS.
HAVE FUN.
THAT'S RIGHT.
WALK AWAY. BYYYE!
♪ Desire... ♪
♪ Desire ♪
♪ You all know I want it,
you'll never have to ask ♪
♪ Desire ♪
♪ I told you with my body... ♪