ADAM AND DREW:
♪ SPEND MY EVENINGS
DOWN AT THE DRIVE-IN ♪
♪ AND THAT'S WHEN I MET YOU,
YEAH! ♪
♪ STANDIN' ON
YOUR MAMA'S PORCH ♪
♪ YOU TOLD ME
THAT YOU'D WAIT FOREVER ♪
ADAM:
♪ OH, AND WHEN YOU HELD
MY HAND ♪
DREW:
♪ I KNEW THAT IT WAS NOW
OR NEVER... ♪
DAVE, COME ON, MAN,
STOP TEXTING;
YOU'RE DRIVING!
DAVE:
I'M SORRY,
I'M JUST CHECKING
IF ALLI NEEDS HELP
ORGANIZING THE MODEL U.N.
WHAT?
LOOK, IT'S THE PERFECT
OPPORTUNITY FOR US
TO GET BACK TOGETHER.
WOULDN'T THAT REQUIRE ALLI
ACTUALLY TALKING TO YOU?
YOU CHEATED.
WE WERE ON A BREAK.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE BRINGING UP JACINTA.
SUMMER WAS SO LONG AGO.
♪ We were young
and restless... ♪
DAVE!
(TIRES SCREECH)
(BOX THUMPS HEAVILY)
WATCH WHERE YOU'RE GOING!
(ENGINE SHUTS OFF,
MUSIC CUTS OUT)
ALLI, I AM SO SORRY.
ARE YOU OKAY?
HEY,
DID YOU GET MY TEXT?
(EXHALES)
AT LEAST
SHE TALKED TO ME.
BECAUSE YOU ALMOST
HIT HER.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
MOVE ON.
AMEN, BROTHER.
LOOK, NOTHING WORTH HAVING
COMES EASY.
I'M NOT GIVING UP.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh... ♪
(Oh-oh-oh)
♪ I can make it through ♪
(I can make it!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
HEY, GIRL!
ALL READY FOR SURGERY?
AWWW!
WELL, IT'S BOOKED
FOR THIS MORNING,
SO FINGERS CROSSED.
WELL, WHO ARE ALL
YOUR ADMIRERS?
OH... MOSTLY DREW.
HE'S BEEN BY MY SIDE
THROUGH ALL OF THIS.
IT'S SWEET.
WOW.
IT MUST BE NICE
TO HAVE A BOYFRIEND
WHO LOVES YOU SO MUCH.
AH, MARE,
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH!
I'M JUST SAYING
DEGRASSI IS GOING TO BE
LONELY WITHOUT YOU.
(TOUCHED)
MM...
BUT WE GOT ASSIGNED
OUR COUNTRIES
FOR MODEL U.N.
USA, BABY!
SO WHEN DO YOU WANNA START
PREPPING FOR SATURDAY?
YEAH, UM...
THE DOCTOR WANTS ME
TO STAY HERE POST OP
TILL MONDAY.
I CAN'T COME.
NO! WHO'S GOING
TO BE THE BRAINS
BEHIND MY CHARISMA?
(LAUGHING)
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU TALK
TO MR. PERINO.
MAYBE HE'LL SET YOU UP
WITH A CUTE, SINGLE BOY.
MM! I'M NOT OPPOSED
TO THAT.
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
(GIGGLES)
WELL, MAYBE MY NEW PARTNER
WILL BRING ME FLOWERS
SOME DAY.
(LAUGHS)
(INHALES
AND SIGHS WISTFULLY)
PERINO:
THANKS TO ALLI'S HARD WORK,
DEGRASSI WILL BE HOSTING
THE PROVINCIAL MODEL U.N.
CONFERENCE.
AND THIS IS REALLY
BIG STUFF, GUYS.
SO LET'S LISTEN TO ALLI.
ALLI:
WELL, FIRST OFF,
THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR VOLUNTEERING TO SET UP.
WE'VE GOT A LOT OF WORK TO DO.
SO FAR TEN SCHOOLS
HAVE CONFIRMED...
FOR A TOTAL OF
22 COUNTRIES REPRESENTED.
HEY!
(WHITE BOARD CRASHES)
WHOA! WHOA!
(MAP SNAPS UP)
CAN WE HELP YOU,
MR. TURNER?
UM, I'M HERE TO SIGN UP.
I WANNA HELP.
UH, YEAH, I DON'T THINK
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA, SIR.
DAVE HAS ULTERIOR MOTIVES.
DAVE?
OH... WELL,
IF BY ULTERIOR MOTIVES,
SHE MEANS I WANNA
SPEND TIME WITH HER?
I'M NOT GONNA LIE;
SHE'S RIGHT.
BUT THIS IS A BIG EVENT
AND YOU NEED MAN POWER.
WELL, I'M RELIABLE MAN POWER,
SO...
ALLI, CAN YOU PUT YOUR ISSUES
WITH DAVE ASIDE
FOR THIS EVENT?
UM...
YES, SIR.
PERINO:
ALL RIGHT, DAVE,
DON'T FORGET TO CLEAN UP
YOUR MESS.
SO, ALLI, I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU WANT TO HAVE LUNCH
WITH ME?
UM, NO.
DAVE:
OH, OKAY.
HOW ABOUT WE JUST TALK?
ALLI:
NO.
DAVE:
ALLI, PLEASE.
GIVE ME FIVE MINUTES.
ALLI: NO.
DAVE: ONE MINUTE?
DAVE: A WORD -
A SINGLE, MEASLY WORD?
ALLI:
NO.
DAVE:
ALLI...
ALLI, ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YES.
ADAM:
"IT WAS THE LOUDEST SOUND
I EVER HEARD.
I FELL.
MY BROTHER STOOD OVER ME,
LIKE EVERYTHING WAS ENDING.
BUT IT WAS JUST BEGINNING.
SO GETTING SHOT SUCKS,
BUT IT MADE ME REALIZE
I HAVE TO START DOING THINGS
THAT SCARE ME,
LIKE SKATEBOARDING.
'CAUSE TODAY I'M HERE
AND I CAN DO ANYTHING."
HOW LAME?
NO! IT WAS REALLY GOOD,
ADAM.
IT MAKES MY GROW OP ENTRY
SOUND LIKE A SUNDAY PICNIC.
ADAM:
THAT'S WEIRD.
WHAT IS IT?
A NOTE...
FROM A SECRET ADMIRER.
CLARE:
OOOOOOOOOH.
SO DOES "I CAN DO ANYTHING"
INCLUDE GOING ON A DATE?
(PAPER RIPS)
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?!
OBVIOUSLY,
IT'S A PRANK.
YOU DON'T KNOW THAT.
COME ON, CLARE.
WE BOTH KNOW THERE ARE
STILL TRANSPHOBES OUT THERE.
AND BESIDES, I'M...
CLOSED UNTIL
FURTHER RENOVATIONS.
DON'T DROOPY-EYE ME!
MY "ANYTHING" HAPPENS
TO BE SKATEBOARDING.
NOT DATING.
CAN YOU GET BEHIND THAT?
I'M BEHIND IT.
THANK YOU.
(SIGHS)
PERINO:
A ROMAN BATH WASN'T
JUST USED FOR BATHING,
IT WAS A MEETING PLACE
FOR PEOPLE
OF ALL SHAPES AND SIZES.
IT WAS WHERE CONNECTIONS
WERE MADE.
SO, LIKE FACERANGE?
PERINO:
HA, THANK YOU, MO.
YES, LIKE FACERANGE.
(BELL RINGS)
DON'T FORGET TO READ CHAPTER
TWELVE AND THIRTEEN!
MARISOL: MR. PERINO?
PERINO: YEAH?
KATIE HAS TO BACK OUT
OF MODEL U.N.
AND I WAS WONDERING
IF I COULD PICK
A REPLACEMENT PARTNER?
I HAVE STUDENTS
ON THE WAITING LIST.
YOU DO?
MM-HMM.
LET'S SEE WHO'S UP FIRST-
ACTUALLY,
I WAS THINKING BEN.
HE'D BE PERFECT.
UH, SORRY, I DON'T SEE HIM
ON MY LIST.
BUT MR. MASHKOUR'S UP FIRST.
MEET YOUR NEW U.N. PARTNER!
MARISOL?
PERINO:
YEP.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
REALLY.
AND MISS OUT
ON EXTRA CREDIT?
YOU'RE STUCK WITH ME.
SO WANNA THROW AROUND
SOME IDEAS?
WHY DON'T WE WORK
SEPARATELY?
I'LL MESSAGE YOU LATER.
TORI:
I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU SKATEBOARDED!
ADAM:
UH, I'M NEW.
I'M TORI.
I'M ADAM.
I KNOW.
UM...
NOT TO BE MEAN,
BUT CAN I HELP YOU?
I'M, UM, DOING
A STATISTICS PROJECT.
I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU COULD SPARE A MINUTE
FOR A SURVEY?
SURE.
ALL RIGHT.
ARE YOU IN A RELATIONSHIP?
NOPE.
NEWLY SINGLE?
MORE LIKE PERPETUALLY.
WAIT.
WHAT CLASS IS THIS FOR?
UM, MATH.
UH, IF SOMEONE LIKED YOU,
WOULD YOU GIVE THEM
A CHANCE?
I DON'T KNOW.
DEPENDS...
WHAT IF
IT WAS MEANT TO BE,
LIKE CHUCK AND BLAIR?
I GUESS, SURE.
WAIT, DO YOU KNOW SOMEONE?
I GOT THIS NOTE...
UM, LIKE I SAID,
MATH PROJECT.
(SHOCKED GASP)
SURPRISE.
YOU DID ALL THIS?
YEAH. I THOUGHT
IT MIGHT HELP OUT.
UH, WELL, IT DOES.
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
I STILL HAVE A COUPLE
MORE FLAGS TO PUT UP -
YEMEN,
AND A COUPLE OF OTHERS.
YOU WANNA GIVE ME
A HAND?
LOOK, I KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TRYING TO DO
AND IT'S NOT GONNA WORK,
SO...
OKAY, LOOK,
IF YOU TELL ME RIGHT NOW
THAT YOU'LL NEVER FORGIVE ME
UNTIL THE END OF TIME,
I'LL LEAVE YOU ALONE.
BUT HAVEN'T YOU EVER DONE
SOMETHING YOU REGRETTED?
YOU WANTED A SECOND CHANCE
SO BAD IT HURTS?
(SIGHS) YEAH, I HAVE.
I WANT US TO GO BACK,
OKAY,
BACK BEFORE THE MISTAKES,
THE LIES.
BACK WHEN WE WERE
UNSTOPPABLE.
WE WERE PRETTY TIGHT,
WEREN'T WE?
YEAH, WE WERE.
THE TIGHTEST.
(SIGHS) OKAY. FINE.
LET'S TALK.
♪ A-a thousand miles ♪
♪ To tell a-a-a thousand lies ♪
(HORN HONKS,
DAVE AND ALLI LAUGH)
SORRY.
I MISS YOUR CUTE LAUGH.
YOUR CUTE LIPS.
YOUR CUTE STRIP MALL
STYLES.
HEY, I DO NOT HAVE
STRIP MALL STYLES.
WHAT? I LIKE IT.
DO YOU KNOW
WHAT I LIKE?
JUST HANGING OUT,
FEELING GOOD.
YEAH?
YEAH.
♪ Baby, I know you feel
the same ♪
♪ I just want it right ♪
(PHONE BUZZES)
SORRY. ADAM, ALWAYS TEXTS
AT THE WRONG MOMENTS.
IT'S OKAY.
(PHONE BUZZES)
WELL, MAYBE IT'S IMPORTANT.
ANSWER IT.
NO, NO.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
LOOK, HE WON'T BE
INTERRUPTING US AGAIN.
YO! YO, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING SATURDAY?
UH, DEPENDS...
OKAY, GOOD.
YOU'RE MY MOCK U.N. PARTNER.
THE PERKS OF HAVING
A JOINER GIRLFRIEND.
GIRLFRIEND?
YEAH. ME AND ALLI
ARE BACK, BABY!
WHAT?
YOU'RE KIDDING, MAN.
THAT'S CRAZY.
(DAVE'S PHONE CHIRPS)
OH CRAP! AGAIN?
YO, YOU KNOW, THAT GIRL
I HOOKED UP WITH LAST SUMMER?
SHE STARTED TEXTING ME AGAIN
LAST NIGHT.
SAY WORD.
WORD.
(PHONE CHIRPS)
DREW:
HELLO, JACINTA.
I MEAN, SHE'S CUTE.
YEAH,
AND ALSO CRAZY.
I THOUGHT SHE GOT THE POINT
WHEN I IGNORED HER LAST TIME.
I'D GO THERE,
IF I WERE SINGLE.
YEAH, WELL, I DID,
AND THEN I REALIZED
SHE'S A STALKER
AND SHE'S OBSESSED
WITH ME.
SHE ALREADY GOT BETWEEN ME
AND ALLI ONCE,
AND I'M NOT GONNA LET THAT
HAPPEN AGAIN.
ARE YOU GOING
TO ASSASSINATE HER, DAVE?
NO.
BUT I AM GONNA BLOCK HER
ON FACERANGE,
UNFOLLOW HER TWITTER,
AND PRIVATISE ALL MY ACCOUNTS.
DREW:
UH, CHANGE YOUR NAME,
GET A FACE TRANSPLANT.
YEAH, BLOCK HER ON GCHAT,
WHATSAPP AND PING.
DREW:
YOU'RE REALLY SET ON
MAKING THIS JACINTA DISAPPEAR.
GOTTA CLEAR THE CLOUDS
FOR SOME BLUE SKIES, RIGHT?
I JUST HEARD A RUMOUR!
YOU AND DAVE?
NEWS TRAVELS FAST.
OKAY, WHY DIDN'T YOU
TELL ME?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
(SIGHS)
BECAUSE!
CAN I JUST FOCUS
ON MODEL U.N.?
IT'S WAY LESS COMPLICATED
THAN DAVE AND I KISSING.
JENNA: YOU KISSED?!
ALLI: SHHHHHHHH!
THAT'S SO EXCITING!
YEAH, I'M NOT SO SURE
THAT IT IS.
WHY AREN'T YOU HAPPIER
ABOUT THIS?
BECAUSE, JENNA,
I JUST DON'T WANT
TO GET HURT AGAIN, YOU KNOW?
WE DIDN'T EVEN TALK ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED LAST SUMMER.
WE JUST WENT STRAIGHT
TO KISSING.
AND IT MADE YOU FORGET
ALL THE BAD STUFF
FOR A SECOND,
DIDN'T IT?
EXACTLY!
BUT EVERYTHING'S STILL
UNRESOLVED, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN,
HE SLEPT WITH SOMEONE ELSE
WHILE STRINGING ME ALONG.
LOOK, WHATEVER HAPPENED
IS IN THE PAST.
WHAT'S IMPORTANT NOW
IS THAT YOU TRUST DAVE
100% GOING FORWARD.
YEAH... (SIGHS)
I'M JUST NOT SURE
THAT I DO.
ONE LAST EMAIL TO DELETE.
WAIT, WAIT...
CAN I... CAN I SEE IT
BEFORE YOU DELETE IT,
PLEASE?
(CLEAR HIS THROAT)
OH... MY... GOODNESS.
OH!
OKAY, ARE YOU SURE YOU
WANNA DELETE THOSE, MAN?!
NO-NO-NO-NO!
DUH-NAH...
NO!
HUH?
DON'T DO IT!
(CLICK)
NOOOOOOOOOOOO!
OKAY, SO WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU RUN INTO HER?
DUDE, SHE LIVES LIKE
TWO HOURS AWAY IN KITCHENER.
SHE WAS ONLY IN THE CITY
FOR THE SUMMER.
I'M SAFE.
DREW:
OKAY.
(DAVE'S PHONE CHIRPS)
OH, IT'S HER.
WHAT DO I DO?
DREW:
UH, ANSWER IT.
WHAT? NO! UH...
SHE COULD BE PREGNANT,
BRO!
HELLO.
HEY, JACINTA.
YEAH, I BLOCKED YOU
ON EVERYTHING.
UH, ARE YOU PREGNANT?
DO YOU HAVE AN STI?
OKAY, WELL, LOOK,
DO US BOTH A FAVOUR
AND NEVER CALL ME AGAIN.
OKAY. BYE.
OUCH.
WHAT? TOO HARSH?
JUST A LITTLE BIT.
WHATEVER.
I GOT A DATE TO PLAN.
PERINO:
DELEGATES!
I TRUST YOU'VE HAD A CHANCE
TO LOOK OVER THE ISSUE
POSTED FOR TOMORROW'S
MODEL U.N.?
WHERE FAMINE HAS BEEN DECLARED
IN TWO AREAS
IN SOUTHERN SOMALIA,
AS THIS COUNTRY SUFFERS
ITS WORST DROUGHT
IN OVER HALF A CENTURY.
SO I'D LOVE TO HEAR
SOME OF YOUR PROPOSAL IDEAS.
AND WHY DON'T WE BEGIN
WITH UH...
USA.
MO:
WELL, AFTER LOOKING
INTO SOMALI POLITICS,
DEMOCRACY MAY NOT NECESSARILY BE
WHAT'S BEST FOR THEM, YOU KNOW?
AUTOCRATIC GOVERNMENTS
CAN HAVE GOOD QUALITIES,
BUT CAN ALSO SUPPRESS
SOME BASIC LIBERTIES.
A STRONG-HANDED GOVERNMENT
IS SOMETIMES NEEDED,
BUT USUALLY CAUSES
MORE CORRUPTION
THAN IT DOES LEADERSHIP.
SO WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS?
MARISOL:
UH, I WAS THINKING A CONCERT,
YOU KNOW,
TO RAISE MONEY -
COLDPLAY, BEYONCE -
AIRS ON EVERY CHANNEL.
(CHUCKLES)
WHAT IS SO FUNNY?
I'M TALKING FAMINE.
OKAY,
YOU'RE TALKING BEYONCE.
YOU CAN'T JUST THROW MONEY
AT A PROBLEM!
WHY NOT?
THEY'RE POOR!
MO:
YOU KNOW WHAT? YOU'RE THE
PROBLEM WITH THE WORLD, 'KAY,
JUDGING FROM YOUR HIGH
WESTERN HORSE,
ALL LIKE, "OH HEY, PROBLEM,
WHAT'S UP?
I'LL JUST THROW
SOME MONEY AT YOU."
PERINO:
OKAY, ENOUGH, MO.
MARISOL,
COULD YOU ELABORATE, PLEASE?
I WAS THINKING IT COULD BE
AN INTERNATIONAL EVENT,
BROADCAST ON EVERY CHANNEL,
WITH STARS
AND A DONATIONS HOTLINE.
WE CAN ALSO RAISE MONEY
BY SELLING SONGS
FROM THE CONCERT
ON ITUNES.
MO, WHAT DO YOU GOT?
I WAS GONNA HAMMER OUT
SOME IDEAS...
TONIGHT,
WHEN I GET HOME.
OKAY, NEXT TIME,
PLEASE DO NOT DISRESPECT
YOUR PARTNER'S IDEAS
WHEN YOU HAVE NONE
OF YOUR OWN.
WHO'S LAUGHING NOW?
ADAM?
ARE YOU SURVEILLING
THE HALLWAY?
I FOUND ANOTHER NOTE,
THIS TIME IN MY LOCKER.
SOMEONE'S COMING.
NO WAY...
CLARE:
SHE'S REALLY PRETTY.
ADAM:
YEAH, BUT BASED ON
SOME FACERANGE RESEARCH-
STALKING.
WHATEVER.
I THINK SHE'S IN
A RELATIONSHIP
WITH A ZIG.
WELL, YOU SHOULD
FIND OUT FOR SURE.
THAT'S... OKAY.
ADAM!
HI, UM...
SO YOU'RE
THE NOTE-INSERTER?
YES... NOT REALLY.
I MEAN, I HAVE A BOYFRIEND,
OBVIOUSLY.
THIS IS ALL...
A LOT CONFUSING.
RIGHT. CLARITY.
UM...
MY FRIEND HAS A CRUSH
ON YOU,
AND I WAS KINDA WONDERING
IF WE COULD
ALL HANG OUT TOGETHER.
(CHUCKLES)
YOU WANT ME TO GO
ON A BLIND DATE
WITH A BUNCH
OF GRADE NINES?
WE'RE REALLY MATURE
FOR OUR AGE.
I'M SURE,
BUT DOES YOUR FRIEND
KNOW I'M-
YES! YES.
TOTALLY KNOWS,
HENCE THE DOUBLE
DATE OFFER.
YOU HAVE TO SAY YES.
SAY YES?
OKAY.
ONE DOUBLE DATE,
NO EXPECTATIONS.
PROMISE?
I SWEAR ON MY EAST REGIONAL
MISS PRETEEN PAGEANT
RUNNER-UP SASH.
SATURDAY?
WORKS FOR ME.
THIS IS GONNA BE
THE BEST EVER!
CLARE:
SO MUCH FOR NO EXPECTATIONS.
YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
I MADE A LIST.
OH, OKAY.
WHAT KIND OF LIST?
"TEXT OR CALL EVERY NIGHT."
"NO HANGING OUT ALONE
WITH OTHER GIRLS,
ESPECIALLY EX'S."
"A HUNDRED PERCENT HONESTY
FROM BOTH OF US."
UM...
THERE'S MORE
ON THE BACK THERE.
YEAH, I SEE THAT.
WHAT'S WITH
ALL THE RULES?
WE RUSHED BACK TOGETHER
WITHOUT TALKING ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED.
I JUST, I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT ELSE TO DO, SO...
YOU DON'T TRUST ME?
I LOST MY VIRGINITY
IN THE BACK OF A VAN
PARKED IN A RAVINE
AT FOURTEEN.
DREW CHEATED ON ME
IN THE BOILER ROOM,
AND THEN...
AND THEN THE GUY I LOVED
AND TRUSTED THE MOST
HAD SEX WITH A STRANGER
THIS SUMMER
AND THEN LIED TO ME
ABOUT IT.
SO YES,
I HAVE TRUST ISSUES.
I'M SORRY.
I JUST WANNA FEEL SAFE
IN WHATEVER RELATIONSHIP
I'M IN, YOU KNOW?
AND I KNOW THIS IS NOT
EXACTLY ROMANTIC,
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
MAYBE I'M JUST NOT MEANT
FOR ROMANCE.
ALLI! ALLI!
WAIT! WAIT! WAIT!
(SNAPS HIS FINGERS)
NOBODY DESERVES ROMANCE
MORE THAN YOU.
(MARIACHI BAND PLAYS
A SLOW SONG)
IF THAT'S WHAT IT TAKES
TO EARN YOUR TRUST,
THEN I'LL ACCEPT ANY RULE
YOU THROW AT ME, ANYTIME.
REALLY?
ALLI, THE GIRL
FROM LAST SUMMER?
SHE'S GONE,
SHE'S OUT OF MY LIFE.
YOU'RE THE ONLY GIRL
IN THE WORLD TO ME.
I'VE GOT ONE RULE
FOR YOU.
WHAT?
DANCE WITH ME.
IN LITTLE MISS STEAKS?
WHAT?
IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG?
NO.
NOTHING'S WRONG.
EVERYTHING'S PERFECT.
♪♪♪
MARISOL:
SINCE YOU CAN'T BE
AT MODEL U.N. TODAY,
I THOUGHT YOU COULD
REPRESENT FROM HERE.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
WELL, MCL'S REPAIRED.
JUST RECOVERY'S HARD
AND PAINFUL.
MM...
COME CLOSER.
UH, WHY DO YOU SMELL
LIKE PEANUT BUTTER?
UGH!
IT STILL SMELLS?
I SPENT THE ENTIRE NIGHT
TRYING TO GET GUM
OUT OF MY HAIR,
AND I'M PRETTY SURE
MO IS RESPONSIBLE.
(DREW AND KATIE LAUGH)
LAUGH AWAY.
I'M THE ONE WHO HAS TO SPEND
THE ENTIRE DAY WITH HIM.
CLASSIC MOVE.
IT MEANS HE LIKES YOU.
YOU'RE SO DUMB.
WE OBVIOUSLY HATE
EACH OTHER.
I DON'T KNOW, MARE.
DREW'S GOT A POINT.
IN GRADE 8, GIAN-FRANCO AMATO
PUT GUM IN MY HAIR,
AND THEN TRIED TO KISS ME
ON THE LIPS.
YOU AND MO...
ARE GONNA KISS
ON THE LIPS.
THE FACT THAT YOU WOULD
EVEN SAY THAT
IS SO CLUELESS!
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOUR PROBLEM IS.
HE'S FUNNY,
HE SMELLS GOOD,
AND HE'S A GREAT BLOCKER.
OH, I'M SURE
HE'S A GOOD BLOCKER.
AHHHHHH, I SEE.
YOU WON'T DATE MO
BECAUSE HE'S BIGGER.
DING-DING-DING!
VERY NICE, MARISOL.
AND HE'S A JERK.
CAN YOU STOP?
THIS IS JUST...
GROSSING ME OUT.
YOU NEED TO GET OVER
YOURSELF
AND GIVE IN
TO SOME MO-MANCE.
OOOOH...
I'M PUKING.
CAN WE GO NOW?
NURSE: THERE YOU GO.
KATIE: THANKS.
OKAY.
DAVE AND I ARE FRANCE.
OOH, BONNE CHANCE!
MARI-SEE!
HAVE FUN!
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
DAVE:
HELLO, EVERYBODY! WELCOME
TO THE 14TH ANNUAL MODEL U.N.
YOU'RE GONNA CHECK IN WITH ALLI,
AND ENTER THIS WAY!
DREW:
BONE-JURY.
AM I EN RETARD?
DAVE:
YOUR FRENCH IS TERRIBLE.
JE THINK THAT GIRL
IS STARING AT VOUS.
THAT'S JACINTA.
SNAP.
JACINTA:
HI.
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
YOU CAN BLOCK ME
ALL YOU WANT,
BUT YOU CAN'T MAKE ME
DISAPPEAR.
UH, HI.
DID YOU CHECK IN?
JACINTA.
FROM KITCHENER HIGH.
HI, I'M ALLI.
THAT'S A REALLY
PRETTY NAME.
WELL, WELCOME TO MODEL U.N.
SEE YOU INSIDE,
DAVE.
DO YOU KNOW HER?
NAME TAGS, RIGHT.
SORRY.
I AM NOT A PARANOID
GIRLFRIEND,
NOT AT ALL!
SORRY.
YOU HAVE NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT, OKAY?
OKAY.