ANYA:
SOMEBODY TOOK MY MAGAZINE.
FIONA:
THERE HAS TO BE SOMETHING HERE.
VAMPIRE THEME?
THAT WOULD ACTUALLY BE NOT BAD.
FIONA:
THAT'S SO CLICHE THOUGH!
YOU WOULD THINK
THAT'S CLICHE.
(FIONA, HOLLY J,
AND ANYA LAUGH)
OH MY GOD,
I'VE GOT IT!
ALICE IN WONDERLAND.
WE COULD DO EXOTIC TEAS
AND MINIATURE CAKES.
ANYA:
I DON'T KNOW,
FOR MY 18TH BIRTHDAY,
I WAS PICTURING SOMETHING
A LITTLE LESS...
JUVENILE?
HAVE YOU SEEN
THE TIM BURTON VERSION?
OH! I GOT IT!
BIANCA: DON'T SAY IT.
ANYA: PARIS!
ARGH!
IT'S CLASSIC!
HOLLY J:
YOU REALLY WANNA RELIVE
WHAT YOU AND SAV
WENT THROUGH LAST YEAR?
OH, THAT'S IN THE PAST,
HOLLY J.
AND IN A FEW MONTHS,
I'LL BE OFF AT TORONTO U,
DATING DR. CHRIS.
FIONA:
SHOULD I ADD ONE MORE
TO THE GUEST LIST?
WHY DON'T WE ASK HIM?
FINE.
DR. CHRIS:
DR. CHRISTOPOULUS.
(FIONA MAKES KISSING NOISES)
DR. CHRIS:
UH, HELLO?
UH, HI, IT'S ANYA.
DR. CHRIS:
HI! I'VE BEEN MEANING
TO CALL YOU.
HE'S BEEN MEANING
TO CALL ME!
(HOLLY J AND FIONA GIGGLE)
DR. CHRIS:
AM I ON SPEAKER PHONE?
UH, NO, I'M SORRY,
MUST'VE JUST HAD
A BAD CONNECTION.
ANYHOO, UM...
MY BIRTHDAY IS IN TWO DAYS,
AND I WAS JUST CALLING
TO REMIND YOU
THAT I'M HAVING A LITTLE PARTY
WITH A VERY CLASSIC THEME.
OH.
OKAY.
HE CAN'T MAKE IT.
I'M SO SORRY.
SO HE ASKED ME OUT
TOMORROW NIGHT!
HE CAN'T EVEN WAIT
UNTIL MY BIRTHDAY!
(ANYA, HOLLY J AND FIONA LAUGH)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Oooh ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
AND THAT IS A NEGATIVE
FOR BROMIDE.
YOU DID THE SODIUM
AND POTASSIUM TEST?
ARE YOU QUESTIONING
MY METHODOLOGY?
(LAUGHS)
I'LL JOT DOWN THE RESULTS.
AT ANOTHER TABLE.
WAS IT WAS SOMETHING I SAID?
GIRLS ARE STILL
A MYSTERY TO ME.
ANYA:
OKAY, SO DATE WARDROBE ADVICE,
PLEASE!
THIS ONE -
LOOK AT ME, I'M EIGHTEEN -
OR... THIS ONE -
(SEDUCTIVE FRENCH ACCENT)
LOOK AT ME, I'M EIGHTEEN.
(FIONA AND HOLLY J LAUGH)
OH YEAH!
ANYA:
(DISGUSTED SIGH)
GIRL, YOU HAVEN'T UPDATED
YOUR STATUS.
UNIVERSITY ACCEPTANCES
STARTED ARRIVING YESTERDAY,
AND EVERYONE'S POSTING
THEIR STATUS ONLINE!
WELL, I'M SURE MY ACCEPTANCE
IS ON ITS WAY,
BUT RIGHT NOW I HAVE
MORE IMMEDIATE WORRIES,
LIKE WHAT I'M GONNA WEAR
ON MY DATE TONIGHT.
HOLLY J:
YOU COMING TO CLASS?
ANYA:
YEAH, I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
SO, I HEAR SOMEONE
HAS A BIRTHDAY COMING UP.
NEED HELP MAKING IT
MEMORABLE?
THANKS, BUT THAT POSITION'S
ALREADY BEEN FILLED.
BY WHO?
UH, YOU WOULDN'T KNOW HIM.
HE'S A DOCTOR.
OKAY, WELL,
IF YOU'RE NOT INTERESTED,
JUST SAY SO!
NO NEED TO MAKE UP
IMAGINARY BOYFRIENDS.
DR. CHRIS IS VERY REAL.
SO WHAT,
HE'S LIKE, FORTY?
TWENTY-SIX!
YOU GUYS MUST HAVE
A LOT IN COMMON.
I FEEL SORRY FOR YOU.
NEXT YEAR, I'LL BE OFF AT T.U.
DATING MY DOCTOR,
AND YOU'LL STILL BE
A TOTAL PIG.
OKAY, WELL,
IF THINGS DON'T WORK OUT,
YOU'VE GOT MY NUMBER!
(MOUTHS "CALL ME")
(WHISPERS)
HANNAH!
(WHISPERS LOUDLY)
(BELL RINGS)
HANNAH, WAIT UP!
HANNAH, HANNAH!
WHAT IS IT,
CONNOR?
IN SCIENCE CLASS
YOU GAVE ME THIS LOOK
THAT PEOPLE GIVE
WHEN THEY'RE ANGRY.
UM, DID I DO ANYTHING
TO MAKE YOU ANGRY?
YOU WERE STARING
AT MY CHEST!
SO? WESLEY DOES IT
ALL THE TIME.
NO, I DON'T!
I HAVE MATH CLUB.
I'LL ESCORT YOU!
♪ It's an old song
playing on the radio ♪
OKAY, SO MY MOM THINKS THAT
I'M SPENDING THE NIGHT HERE,
AND IF SHE CALLS...
YOU'RE IN THE BATHROOM.
AND, UH, TEXT MY PHONE,
AND I WILL CALL HER BACK.
HOLLY J:
I HATE TO BE
A COLD SHOWER HERE,
BUT DON'T YOU THINK
IT'S A LITTLE SOON
FOR SLEEPOVERS?
HE'S TWENTY-SIX,
HOLLY J.
YEAH, BUT YOU HAVEN'T SEEN
EACH OTHER IN A WHILE.
THINGS COULD BE...
DIFFERENT.
OKAY, YOU'RE REALLY NOT
HELPING MY BUTTERFLIES.
WHY IS IT SO HARD
FOR EVERYBODY TO BELIEVE
THAT DR. CHRIS COULD BE
INTERESTED IN A GIRL LIKE ME?
FIONA:
IT'S NOT; LOTS OF GIRLS
I KNEW IN NEW YORK
DATED WAY OUTSIDE THEIR LEAGUE.
BUT THERE'S NO NEED
TO RUSH THINGS.
IF THIS DOESN'T WORK,
THERE ARE OTHER GUYS.
IT'S OKAY, HOLLY J,
I'M AN ADULT NOW,
AND I CAN TAKE CARE
OF MYSELF.
WHEW!
(SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
(DOOR SHUTS)
COULD YOU TELL ME
I'M NOT GOING TO JAIL.
I MEAN,
IT-IT WAS SELF-DEFENCE!
DREW,
LET THE LAWYER TALK.
LAWYER:
I'VE READ YOUR STATEMENT.
MOSTLY IT CHECKS OUT,
EXCEPT FOR CERTAIN
INCONSISTENCIES.
LIKE WHAT?
YOU CLAIM YOU WERE
ON THE GROUND,
ON YOUR BACK,
BEING BEATEN FROM ABOVE.
BUT THE REPORT SHOWS
THE VICTIM WAS HIT
ON THE BACK OF THE HEAD.
THE GIRL WHO WAS WITH YOU...
BIANCA.
SHE KNEW YOUR ASSAILANT?
DID SHE HAVE ANY REASON
TO WANT TO HURT HIM?
HE WAS HARASSING HER,
AND SHE...
I ONLY HIT HIM TO STOP HIM
FROM HURTING US.
IT HAPPENED SO FAST,
I DIDN'T MEAN TO KILL HIM.
OKAY.
GOOD.
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
YOU SAVED
YOUR GIRLFRIEND'S LIFE.
SELF-DEFENCE WILL STICK.
WHAT ABOUT ANSON'S FRIEND,
VINCE -
THE GANG GUY
WHO THREATENED ME?
THE POLICE HAVE HIM
IN CUSTODY.
AND THEY'LL PUT HIM AWAY
FOR A LONG TIME?
LAWYER:
WITH THE INFORMATION
YOU GIVE THEM,
I'M SURE THEY'LL DO
EVERYTHING THEY CAN
TO KEEP HIM
OFF THE STREETS.
OKAY?
OKAY.
(SIGHS)
(CARS RUMBLE)
♪♪♪
♪ Gas bar, county line ♪
♪ Population 109 ♪
♪ How'd we end up here? ♪
SORRY I'M LATE,
THERE WAS AN EMERGENCY BIOPSY.
GOD, I HATE IT
WHEN THAT HAPPENS.
(BOTH LAUGH AWKWARDLY)
UH...
Y-YOU DON'T NEED TO WORRY,
I WILL BE 18 AT MIDNIGHT.
(LAUGHS SHYLY)
OH. OH, GOD.
UM, HOLLY J WAS RIGHT!
I DON'T FOLLOW.
SO HAVE YOU MET
SOMEONE ELSE?
IS IT A NURSE,
OR...
OR THAT BLONDE,
AT THE FRONT DESK?
SUZY?
HOW LONG HAS IT BEEN
GOING ON?
ANYA,
THERE'S NO ONE ELSE.
POSITIVE?
YEAH, UNLESS I HAVE
A SPLIT PERSONALITY.
OKAY, STUPID NERVES.
CAN WE REWIND
AND START AGAIN?
WHY DON'T WE GRAB
A SEAT,
YOU KNOW, HAVE SOME DINNER,
CATCH UP.
PERFECT.
(BOTH LAUGH)
SO, UH, DO YOU REALLY
THINK SUZY'S INTO ME?
(LAUGHS)
JENNA:
WELL, OUR LITTLE MAN'S
OUT COLD.
HERE'S TO THREE HOURS
OF PEACE AND QUIET!
AWESOME!
THAT'S JUST ENOUGH TIME FOR ME
TO CATCH THE HEAT-LAKERS GAME
AT CASA DAVE!
JENNA:
WAIT, YOU'RE GOING OUT?
I HELPED, DIDN'T I?
YEAH, BUT I JUST THOUGHT
THAT WE COULD SPEND
SOME TIME TOGETHER.
(SIGHS) RIGHT.
WELL, I GUESS WE HAVE
A TV HERE, TOO.
HOW ELSE WOULD WE WATCH
"DANCING WITH THE STARS"?
THE FINALS ARE ON TONIGHT!
OH. GREAT.
I THINK THERE'S LIKE
A RETIRED BASKETBALL PLAYER
COMPETING OR SOMETHING.
(FLAMENCO MUSIC PLAYS ON TV)
UNIVERSITY ACCEPTANCES
ARE ARRIVING SOON.
I SHOULD HEAR
FROM T.U. ANY DAY.
WHAT ABOUT OTHER SCHOOLS?
I DIDN'T APPLY ANYWHERE ELSE,
I WANTED TO BE CLOSE TO HOME.
FOR YOUR MOM.
AND...
FOR HER DREAMY DOCTOR.
MARISOL:
CAN I TAKE YOUR DESSERT ORDER?
UH, THE FRIED ICE CREAM HERE
IS SCRUMPTIOUS.
UH, I'M PRETTY FULL.
UH, WE CAN GO HALFSIES.
I'LL GIVE YOU TWO
A SECOND.
I'M SORRY,
WAS I PUSHING DESSERT ON YOU?
THAT'S FINE, UM...
BUT IT'S A SCHOOL NIGHT,
WE SHOULD PROBABLY BE
GETTING YOU HOME.
NO NEED.
UM... I'M COVERED.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
UM...
YOU'RE A GREAT GIRL.
BUT?
I PROBABLY SHOULDN'T HAVE
PUT THIS OFF.
I'VE BEEN OFFERED A JOB
WITH "DOCTORS
WITHOUT BORDERS",
IN KENYA.
(SIGHS)
LIKE, AFRICA?
I LEAVE IN A FEW DAYS.
HOW LONG WILL YOU BE GONE?
A YEAR.
(SIGHS)
YEAH, I-I WISH I COULD
BRING YOU WITH ME.
YEAH, WELL, MAYBE WE CAN SEE
EACH OTHER WHEN YOU GET BACK.
SURE!
(SIGHS) YEAH,
THAT SOUNDS LIKE A PLAN.
YEP.
(SIGHS)
(STUDENTS TALK QUIETLY)
OWEN:
SO...
HOW WAS YOUR BIG DATE?
YOUR DREAMY DOCTOR PROPOSE?
(BOOKS SLAM SHUT)
HOLLY J:
HEY!
BIRTHDAY BLUES?
(ANYA SNIFFLES)
WELL, YOU CAN CANCEL MY PARTY
BECAUSE HE ENDED IT.
WAS IT THE AGE THING?
PLEASE TELL ME
HE DIDN'T MEET SOMEONE ELSE!
NO, HE'S GOING TO AFRICA.
HE WANTS TO SAVE THE WORLD.
THAT BASTARD!
(BOTH LAUGH)
SORRY, I TRIED.
HOW COULD I HAVE BEEN
SO STUPID?
YOU'RE NOT.
IF HE WAS STAYING PUT,
IT COULD'VE WORKED.
YEAH, HE DID SAY HE WANTED
TO TAKE ME WITH HIM.
SEE?
AND A YEAR ISN'T SO LONG.
IT'LL FLY BY!
YOUR FINAL FEW MONTHS
OF HIGH SCHOOL,
SUMMER,
YOUR FIRST SEMESTER
AT UNIVERSITY.
AND THEN HE'LL BE BACK
AND WE CAN TRY AGAIN.
OKAY,
GIRL'S NIGHT AT FI'S.
MOVIES AND MUSHU.
(BELL RINGS)
I'VE GOT STUDENT COUNCIL,
BUT IF YOU NEED ME...
I'LL FIND YOU.
PROMISE!
(SIGHS)
WHEW!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(KEYS CLICK)
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
ANYA:
OH MY GOD, I...
I DIDN'T GET IN!
I DIDN'T GET IN.
(SIGHS)
HOLLY J: (OVER PA)
IMOGEN MARINO,
REPORT TO THE OFFICE,
IMOGEN MARINO.
(CONNOR SIGHS)
CONNOR:
HEY.
UM...
DO I HAVE TO FIND
ANOTHER LAB PARTNER?
NAH, I MANAGED TO SMOOTH
THINGS OVER WITH HANNAH,
CONVINCED HER
IT WAS AN ASPIE THING.
LOOK, MAMMARIES
ARE JUST ANOTHER BODY PART,
AND I DON'T HAVE ANY,
SO...SO OF COURSE
I'M CURIOUS!
YEAH, OKAY,
BUT YOU CAN'T STARE!
I MEAN,
GIRLS THINK IT'S WEIRD.
THEN WHY DO THEY WEAR
TIGHT SHIRTS?
SOME SORT OF TEST,
I GUESS?
NO, LOOK, CONNOR,
IF YOU DON'T STOP STARING,
YOU'LL NEVER GET A GIRLFRIEND.
BUT I DON'T WANT
A GIRLFRIEND.
EVERYONE WANTS A GIRLFRIEND!
I MEAN, DOUBLE DATES,
LATE NIGHT STUDY BUDDIES?
I KNOW WHERE
YOU CAN GET ONE!
I MEAN,
ARE YOU FREE TONIGHT?
LOOK, I DON'T THINK
THIS IS SUCH A GOOD IDEA.
OH, HAVE I EVER LED YOU
ASTRAY BEFORE?
TWICE.
(DREW SIGHS HEAVILY)
SO IT'S REALLY OVER?
YOU WERE RIGHT.
THE LAWYER SAID
IT WAS SELF-DEFENCE,
CUT AND DRIED.
(BIANCA LAUGHS)
TIME TO CELEBRATE.
MY MOM WILL KILL ME
IF I SKIP.
IT'S NOT SKIPPING...
IF YOU HAVE A NOTE
FROM MOM.
(BELL RINGS)
(BIANCA GIGGLES)
(TYSON CRIES LOUDLY)
HE'S BEEN CRYING
SINCE I GOT HOME FROM SCHOOL!
MAKE HIM STOP!
OKAY, MY PARENTING BOOK
SAYS BABIES MAINLY CRY
FOR THREE REASONS:
HUNGER, EXHAUSTION...
OR A CODE BROWN.
WE-WE JUST CHANGED HIM!
MAYBE HE FORGOT!
GRAB THE NEW PACK
OF DIAPERS?
(TYSON WAILS)
JENNA:
SHHH! COME ON, IT'S OKAY.
IT'S OKAY.
SHHH...
CRAP.
IT'S THE LAST ONE.
THEY WERE ON YOUR LIST!
I-I FORGOT!
IT WAS A LONG LIST.
BUT IF YOU WANT,
I CAN GET SOME NOW.
YOU'RE LEAVING ME ALONE
WITH THIS?!
I WON'T BE LONG!
(TYSON CRIES)
(DOOR SLAMS)
(PATIENTS CHATTER)
(PHONE RINGS)
(MUFFLED CHATTER IN THE HALLS)
DR. CHRIS:
ANYA, HEY.
ANYA:
HI! UM...
ARE YOU HAVING A PARTY?
UH, SORT OF.
UM, SHOULDN'T YOU BE
CELEBRATING
YOUR BIRTHDAY
WITH YOUR FRIENDS?
UM, I JUST WANTED TO...
FLOAT AN IDEA BY YOU.
WHAT IF I CAME
TO AFRICA TOO?
UM...
I MEAN, I KNOW WE'VE ONLY
KNOWN EACH OTHER
FOR A SHORT PERIOD OF TIME,
BUT I REALLY THINK
IT WOULD BE UNFAIR
TO NOT TO GIVE US
A CHANCE.
UH, WHAT ABOUT HIGH SCHOOL?
OH, GRADUATION'S ONLY
TWO MONTHS AWAY.
AND UNIVERSITY?
WILL BE HERE
WHEN WE GET BACK.
OKAY, YOU...
YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS!
WE-WE'VE BEEN ON ONE DATE,
WE BARELY KNOW EACH OTHER.
(CHOKED SIGH)
YOU... YOU WERE NEVER
SERIOUS ABOUT ME.
(SIGHS)
YOU ARE A SMART...
DON'T.
♪ I know that we have
not yet been perfected ♪
(SOUNDS OF BALL GAME ON TV)
♪ And are missing parts of us
that are required ♪
(CROWD BOOS,
WHISTLE BLOWS)
♪ I know that we will never
fully heal ♪
HEY.
SO, YOU'RE HIRING?
YOU SURE YOU WANNA SPEND
YOUR NIGHTS
SCRUBBING NACHO CHEESE?
RIGHT NOW?
THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
THEN I'LL GET YOU
AN APPLICATION.
♪♪♪
♪ Just a mess of broken glass
and shorted wires ♪
AUDRA:
YES, I UNDERSTAND.
THANK YOU.
(PHONE BEEPS)
UM...
THE DETECTIVE PHONED,
AND HE SAID THAT HE...
COULDN'T HOLD VINCE.
SO...SO HE'S OUT THERE?
WELL, WE'VE FILED
A RESTRAINING ORDER.
HOW IS A PIECE OF PAPER
GOING TO PROTECT ME?
WELL, IT'S THE BEST
WE COULD DO.
AUDRA:
(FRIGHTENED BREATH)
I WARNED YOU
ABOUT THAT GIRL!
MOM,
THIS ISN'T BIANCA'S FAULT!
SOMEONE DIED
BECAUSE OF HER.
BIANCA'S CHANGED!
WELL, SHE CAN'T UNDO
HER PAST,
AND NOW,
NEITHER CAN YOU.
I JUST WISH EVERYTHING
COULD GO BACK TO NORMAL.
(SIRENS WAIL)
ANYA:
FIONA?
(DOOR CLICKS SHUT)
HOLLY J?
GUYS? I THOUGHT WE WERE
HAVING A GIRLS' NIGHT.
ALL:
SURPRISE!
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
WHAT IS THIS?
FIONA:
WE COULDN'T LET YOUR 18TH
GO UNCELEBRATED!
BUT WE DECIDED AGAINST
A PARISIAN THEME.
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT MAD.
ANYA:
UM, ME? MAD? NO!
GOOD, 'CAUSE THERE'S
THIS GUY FROM T.U.
I REALLY WANT YOU
TO MEET!
I ALREADY CHECKED,
HE HATES TO TRAVEL.
SHALL I INTRODUCE?
UH, SURE,
JUST LET ME FRESHEN UP.
SO, HOW DID YOU SCORE
AN INVITE
TO THIS GRADE 12 PARTY?
I TOLD YOU,
ANYA AND I ARE TIGHT.
HER FRIENDS ARE PROBABLY
JUST TRYING TO FILL THE ROOM.
I SHOULD PROBABLY GO
WISH HER HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
HANNAH: I'LL COME WITH.
CONNOR: UH, ME TOO!
NO, NO! THIS IS WHERE YOU
FIND YOURSELF A GIRLFRIEND.
LOOK AT ALL
THESE FINE LADIES!
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
HI.
UH...DID YOU KNOW
THAT CHEESE
HAS FOUR TYPES OF BACTERIA?
HOLLY J, CAN WE TALK...
ABOUT ANYTHING?
I THINK HE WAS TRYING
TO FLIRT WITH ME!
(HOLLY J AND FIONA GIGGLE)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(DOOR SLAMS)
(SIGHS)
(WATER SPLASHES)
(DRAWER RASPS)
(DOOR CLICKS)
GET OUT, PLEASE?
(MUFFLED SOB)
(CRYING)
♪ I'll save you ♪
♪ Oh I'll save you ♪
(TYSON CRIES)
JENNA:
SHHH...
AW, SHH!
MY MOM'S ALREADY ASLEEP!
SHE HAS THE EARLY SHIFT.
HE'S HUNGRY;
CAN YOU FEED HIM?
OKAY, I'LL HEAT UP
THE BOTTLE.
OKAY, THAT'S GOOD.
(TYSON CRIES)
THERE MUST BE
AN EASIER WAY!
WE CAN'T AFFORD
AN ELECTRIC BOTTLE WARMER.
(TYSON COOS AND WHIMPERS)
REMEMBER I WAS THINKING
ABOUT GETTING A JOB?
THERE'S A DISHWASHER SPOT
AT LITTLE MISS STEAKS.
PART-TIME, EVENINGS.
OH.
WE COULD USE THE MONEY,
RIGHT?
OF COURSE.
YEAH, BUT I KNOW
YOU GET LONELY,
SO IF YOU REALLY DON'T
WANT ME TO...
NO.
GO GET A JOB.
YOU'LL BE OKAY
ON YOUR OWN?
AS LONG AS I KNOW
YOU'RE WORKING FOR US,
IT'S OKAY.
THANK YOU.
(SIGHS)
♪ How would you cope
if the world decided ♪
♪ To make you suffer
for all that you were ♪
♪ How could you dance
if no one was watching ♪
♪ And you couldn't even
get off the floor ♪
♪ What would you do
if you couldn't even feel ♪
(DOOR CLICKS SHUT)
OWEN:
IT'S YOUR PARTY,
AND YOU'LL CRY IF YOU WANT TO.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
ESCAPING YOUR LAME-ASS
FRIENDS.
ALL THEY TALK ABOUT IS
WHAT THEY WANNA MAJOR IN
NEXT YEAR.
WELL THEN, LEAVE.
CAN'T.
WHY?
OWEN:
WELL, SEE,
THAT WOULD SERIOUSLY
DECREASE MY CHANCES
OF HOOKING UP WITH YOU.
(SCOFFS)
YOU ARE SUCH A PIG!
FAIR ENOUGH.
BUT I'M NOT THE PIG
MAKING YOU CRY.
NO, HE'S OFF TO AFRICA.
HIS LOSS.
♪ Everything you say
is higher ♪
♪ Don't you know people
write songs
♪ About girls like you ♪
♪ See it in the grey
you crier ♪
♪ About girls like you ♪