(KIDS CHATTER)
(BASKETBALLS BOUNCE)
(VAN IDLES QUIETLY)
AUDRA:
YEAH, GOODBYE!
I'LL PICK YOU UP
WHEN YOU'RE DONE.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO FOLLOW ME AROUND!
REALLY?
WELL, THINK ABOUT THAT
THE NEXT TIME YOU SNEAK OUT
TO GO TO A CONCERT!
BYE, MOM!
(VAN RUMBLES AWAY)
(SIGHS)
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
I'M SORE,
BUT I'LL LIVE.
I MAY NEED HELP
PLANNING MY ESCAPE
FROM PARENTAL ALCATRAZ.
WHAT'S WRONG?
WE HAVE BIGGER PROBLEMS
THAN YOUR MOM.
(DREW GASPS)
BIANCA:
IT'S HIM.
DREW:
"RUSHED TO THE HOSPITAL
WITH HEAD INJURIES,
ANSON WELLS WAS DECLARED DEAD
ON ARRIVAL."
(GASPS FEARFULLY)
OH MY GOD,
WHAT DO WE DO?
OKAY, SLOW DOWN,
WE DON'T NEED TO PANIC.
REALLY? WE NEED
TO GO TO THE COPS!
DREW, WE NEED TO RELAX
AND THINK THIS THROUGH.
OH MY GOD,
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS!
A GUY TRIES TO RAPE YOU!
WE DID THE ONLY THING
WE COULD!
WE HAVE TO LIVE OUR LIVES
LIKE NOTHING HAPPENED.
(POLICE CAR RUMBLES)
WHY SHOULD WE TURN OURSELVES IN
IF NO ONE'S LOOKING FOR US?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(I can make it)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
("THE ONE YOU CALL"
BY KEKE PALMER PLAYS)
YOU DO KNOW
SHE WROTE THAT SONG
BEFORE SHE MET YOU,
RIGHT?
I JUST CAN'T GET OVER IT.
I MET KEKE PALMER.
NOW SHE'S GONE.
SHE WAS NEVER HERE!
IN THE SENSE OF ACTUALLY
BEING IN YOUR LIFE.
YEAH, BUT SHE INVITED ME
TO HER SHOW.
SHE EVEN PULLED ME UP
ON STAGE!
THAT'S GOTTA BE SOMETHING,
RIGHT?
SHE DID SEEM BIZARRELY
INTO YOU.
I HAVE TO SEE HER.
WELL, DID YOU GET
HER NUMBER?
(SIGHS)
WELL,
THAT WAS POOR PLANNING!
IT'S NOT LIKE I COULD...
AMBUSH HER AT HER HOTEL.
WHO DOES THAT SORT OF THING?
GROUPIES, STALKERS...
I SHOULD CHANGE.
NO, IT'S FINE,
GO!
(LAUGHS)
OFFICER TURNER:
AFTER YOU FINISH WITH THIS,
YOU COME HOME,
HELP ME IN THE GARAGE,
THEN YOU CAN HEAD OUT TONIGHT,
OKAY?
DAVE:
OKAY.
DREW:
DAVE!
HEY, SO I GUESS YOU
PATCHED THINGS UP WITH BIANCA
AFTER THE KEKE SHOW?
YEAH, IT WAS A BIG
MISUNDERSTANDING, MY FRIEND.
BIANCA:
HE'S SO PARANOID.
HEY, DID YOU GUYS HEAR ABOUT
THAT GUY WHO GOT KILLED
LIKE A BLOCK AWAY FROM US?
YEAH, IT WAS ANOTHER MURDER
IN THE CLUB DISTRICT,
RIGHT, POPS?
OH, IT WAS A MURDER?
WE DON'T KNOW THAT
FOR SURE.
YEAH, BUT PEOPLE DON'T USUALLY
SMASH THEIR OWN HEADS IN.
YOU GUYS HAVE ANY, LIKE,
LEADS?
WE'RE WORKING ON IT.
I GOTTA RUN, SON.
OKAY. BYE, POPS.
LATER.
(CAR STARTS)
(DOOR SLAMS)
YOU KNOW, IT'S PROBABLY
GANG STUFF OR SOMETHING.
OH YEAH,
NO DOUBT.
DAVE:
YEAH, THEY'LL PROBABLY FIND
THE GUYS WHO DID IT
LIKE DEAD NEXT WEEKEND.
(LAUGHS)
ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
LET'S SHOOT AROUND!
MAYBE CHARLIE
WON'T RECOGNIZE ME.
FIFI, ALL YOU DID
WAS LIE TO CHARLIE
ABOUT HAVING
A PLUMBING EMERGENCY,
AND IT WAS...
VERY SMOOTH.
(GROANS)
I KNOW!
JUST MAYBE I SHOULD AVOID...
CHARLIE!
SO, HOW'S THE PLUMBING?
GREAT.
IT'S GREAT.
UH...
JUST SOME BACKED UP PIPES.
SO BORING.
CHARLIE:
RIGHT...
UM, I DIDN'T SEE
YOUR SCOOTER OUT THERE.
OKAY, I LIED.
I DON'T HAVE ONE.
WHY LIE?
TO IMPRESS YOU?
I'M LESBIAN.
A-A LESBIAN?
IT'S A RECENT REVELATION,
IN CASE YOU HAVEN'T NOTICED.
I WONDERED, I ADMIT.
EVER SINCE I CAME OUT,
I HAVEN'T REALLY HUNG OUT
WITH ANY NON-STRAIGHT
TYPE GIRLS,
WOMEN, UH...
PEOPLE LIKE US,
I MEAN, IF YOU ARE.
CHARLIE:
OH, OKAY.
BREATHE.
(TAKES A DEEP BREATH)
I AM.
UM...
EVERYONE'S GOTTA START
SOMEWHERE, RIGHT?
YOU'RE DOING GREAT!
(BOTH LAUGH)
(KIDS HOLLER AND LAUGH)
DREW:
IT'LL BE OKAY.
WE'RE GONNA GET AWAY
WITH THIS.
WE JUST NEED
TO STICK TOGETHER.
(GASPS)
WHERE'S YOUR BRACELET?
I-I DON'T KNOW.
LAST TIME I WORE IT...
I-I WORE IT TO THE CONCERT!
THEN?
YOUR NAME
IS ENGRAVED ON IT!
IF THE POLICE FIND IT
IN THE ALLEY-
I KNOW!
WE NEED TO GO.
SAV:
HEY, KEKE.
CAN I GET AN AUTOGRAPH?
SHOULD I GET RID
OF HIM?
OH, ONE AUTOGRAPH,
IT'S FINE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
UM... NOT STALKING YOU?
(BOTH LAUGH)
OBVIOUSLY,
YOU'RE REALLY BUSY.
I HAVE TO GET OUT OF HERE.
EXCUSE ME?
EVERY SECOND OF MY LIFE
IS SCHEDULED.
I HAVEN'T HAD A MOMENT
TO MYSELF.
IT NEVER STOPS.
OKAY, UM...
WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO DO?
(SIGHS)
RUN.
WHAT?!
RUN. NOW!
♪♪♪
FIONA:
SO NOW WHAT? COFFEE?
I HAVE DIALYSIS.
RAIN CHECK?
SURE.
CHARLIE:
SO, YOU HAVE A GIRLFRIEND?
UH, HOLLY J?
UM, UH...
IN THE PLATONIC,
NON-LESBIAN SENSE.
(BOTH LAUGH AWKWARDLY)
SO WHAT'S IT LIKE?
YOU'VE NEVER RIDDEN ONE?
LUCKY FOR YOU
I CARRY AN EXTRA HELMET.
DO YOU GIVE A LOT OF GIRLS
RIDES ON YOUR SCOOTER?
MMM...
ONLY SPECIAL ONES.
(ENGINE REVS)
♪ We can do this together
we can ♪
♪ Yeah me and you ♪
(FIONA LAUGHS)
♪ When you hold me
I can see ♪
♪ This is exactly
where I wanna be ♪
♪ You're the harmony ♪
♪ To my heartbeat, baby ♪
VINCE:
SORRY I COULDN'T HELP YOU.
MAYBE WE SHOULD
JUST TURN OURSELVES IN,
TELL THE COPS EVERYTHING.
NO!
I CAN'T.
I HAVE A RECORD.
WHAT KIND OF RECORD?
I BEAT UP SOME GIRL
AT A CLUB
AND I'M STILL ON PROBATION!
BUT THIS WAS SELF-DEFENSE!
HE ATTACKED YOU!
YOU KNOW THAT!
I KNOW THAT.
BUT THE COPS ARE ALREADY
TALKING MURDER.
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
(POLICE CAR RUMBLES)
(SIGHS)
THEN LET'S FIND
YOUR BRACELET.
(CARS RUMBLE,
HORN HONKS)
NICE AND CHILL,
GOOD COFFEE...
YOUR HANGOUT'S
THE BUSINESS!
YEAH, THE DOT'S NORMALLY
INFESTED WITH HIGH SCHOOLERS,
BUT DURING SPRING BREAK,
GHOST TOWN CENTRAL.
I'M GLAD YOU SHOWED UP.
CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
WHY ME?
YOU SEEM NICE.
BUT FOR REAL THOUGH.
I MEAN...
YOU'RE THIS FAMOUS SINGER
AND I'M JUST A REGULAR GUY.
YOU'RE SPECIAL, SAV.
PLEASE.
I'M NO JET-SETTING,
CLUB-ROCKING,
HIT-MAKING SUPER DIVA!
IT'S JUST NICE TO GET A COFFEE
WITH A DOWN-TO-EARTH GUY,
ONCE IN A WHILE.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
THAT WAS QUICK.
STUPID GPS PHONE.
BODYGUARD:
YEAH, I'LL GET HER
TO REHEARSAL.
MS. PALMER,
IT'S TIME TO GO!
I GUESS THIS IS IT.
AT LEAST YOU HAVE
MY AUTOGRAPH.
(SIRENS BLEAT REPEATEDLY)
BIANCA:
FORGET IT!
IT'S NOT HERE!
TWO MORE MINUTES,
JUST TO BE SURE.
VINCE:
LOOKING FOR SOMETHING?
THE NAME'S VINCE,
AND YOU ARE BIANCA L. DESOUSA.
THAT'S NOT MY NAME.
VINCE:
YOU SHOULDN'T PUT SO MUCH
PERSONAL INFO ONLINE, BIANCA!
AND YOU MUST BE THE BOYFRIEND,
DREW.
SO YOU TWO GO TO DEGRASSI,
HUH?
WHAT DO YOU WANT, MAN?
YOU GONNA GO TO THE COPS?
YOU GOT NO IDEA
WHAT YOU GOT YOURSELF INTO,
DO YOU?
NEXT TIME I SEE YOU,
PAYBACK.
(KIDS HOLLER AND LAUGH)
THERE'S A GUY OUT THERE
WITH A GUN.
WHAT IF HE COMES AFTER
MY FAMILY
OR MY FRIENDS?
OR YOU?
I CAN'T LIVE LIKE THIS!
DREW, PLEASE!
WE CAN'T GO
TO THE POLICE.
I KNOW.
THAT'S WHY WE NEED TO FIND
THAT VINCE GUY.
SO HE CAN SHOOT US?
NO. SO I CAN TALK
TO HIM!
I DON'T THINK VINCE
IS THE TYPE OF GUY
WHO LISTENS TO REASON.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY
TO GET OUT OF THIS!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
I KNOW A GUY
WHO CAN TRACK HIM DOWN.
THANK YOU.
I HOPE YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
ME TOO.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(CARS RUMBLE)
HOLLY J:
WHAT'S THE EMERGENCY?
FIONA:
ISN'T IT PRETTY?
HOLLY J:
OH, RIGHT.
YOUR NEW OBSESSION.
CHARLIE TOOK ME FOR A RIDE
AND IT MADE ME FEEL FREE.
SO I'M GETTING MY LICENCE
AND PICKING IT UP TOMORROW!
NOT TO BE A BUCKET
OF WATER,
BUT YOU SURE YOU AND CHARLIE
ARE GONNA SCOOTER OFF
INTO THE SUNSET TOGETHER?
WELL, SHE CERTAINLY ENJOYS
MY COMPANY;
SHE'S COMING TO MY PLACE.
OH? WHAT ARE YOU GALS
GONNA DO?
SKETCH.
JUST THE TWO OF YOU?
ALONE?
OH MY GOD...
WHAT IF SOMETHING HAPPENS?
YOU WANTED A SPRING FLING,
RIGHT?
(SIGHS HAPPILY)
(SIRENS WAIL IN THE DISTANCE)
(CRICKETS CHIRP)
YOU'RE SURE HE'S COMING?
THAT'S WHAT I HEAR.
ANY HINTS ABOUT
WHAT YOU'RE GONNA SAY?
I DON'T WANT YOU TRYING
TO CHANGE MY MIND.
(DOG BARKS)
VINCE:
WHAT'S UP, DEAD MEAT?
THIS BETTER BE WORTH MY TIME.
DREW:
THEN I'LL MAKE IT QUICK.
LOOK, I GET THE WHOLE
EYE FOR AN EYE THING.
BUT YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND,
THIS WAS PURELY SELF-DEFENSE.
AND I'M REALLY,
REALLY SORRY
FOR WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR FRIEND.
ANSON WASN'T MY FRIEND;
HE WAS USEFUL.
HE HELPED ME GET PAID.
SO NOW YOU OWE ME.
NO!
IT'S OKAY.
VINCE:
I COULD USE SOMEBODY LIKE YOU -
SQUEAKY CLEAN,
POPULAR HIGH SCHOOL DUDE.
LOTS OF POTENTIAL CUSTOMERS.
LIKE FOR DRUGS?
THIS WAS YOUR PLAN
ALL ALONG.
WELL, IF YOU AND YOUR BOY
WANNA KEEP FROM GETTING SHOT.
FINE, I'LL DO IT.
FIRST, YOU GOTTA PROVE
I CAN TRUST YOU.
YOU WANT ME
TO SHOOT SOMEONE?
YOU IN OR YOU OUT?
(GUN RATTLES)
VINCE:
IT'S GONNA GO DOWN TOMORROW.
I'LL CALL YOU WITH THE NAME
AND WHERE TO FIND HIM.
THIS IS YOUR ONE CHANCE,
BRO!
(DOG BARKS)
(STREETCAR RUMBLES)
NICE PAD YOU'VE GOT HERE.
FIONA:
IT'S COMFY.
SO, WHAT SHOULD WE DRAW?
FRUIT?
ANOTHER BANANA?
FIONA, I'VE TAKEN 7 LEVELS
OF STILL LIFE CLASSES.
WHERE DO YOU WANT ME?
OH!
UH...
YOU'RE GONNA MODEL?
CHARLIE:
YEAH!
I MODEL FOR YOU,
YOU MODEL FOR ME.
OKAY.
(LAUGHS AWKWARDLY)
(SIGHS)
(LAUGHS)
ARE MY SHOULDERS
REALLY THAT POINTY?
FIONA:
OH NO, YOU DON'T LIKE IT?
NO, I DO.
I LOVE IT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN THERE?
WHEN I FOUND OUT MY SPRING BREAK
TRIP WAS CANCELLED,
I THOUGHT I'D NEVER GET
A CHANCE TO WEAR THIS.
THE SUSPENSE IS KILLING ME.
FIONA:
(LAUGHS)
DO YOU LIKE IT?
IT'S CUTE.
SO NOW IT'S YOUR TURN
TO SKETCH.
WHERE DO YOU WANT ME?
(SIGHS)
RIGHT THERE.
LIKE THAT.
THE WAY THE LIGHT HITS YOU,
RIGHT THERE...
THAT HAS TO BE ONE
OF THE MOST BEAUTIFUL THINGS
IN THE WORLD.
♪ ...things off my chest ♪
♪ The end... ♪
♪ Of broken hearts ♪
♪ Lies, lies
to fight for our lives ♪
I'M SORRY, UH...
CAN WE JUST SKETCH?
I'M REALLY SORRY.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(SIGHS)
I'M GONNA NEED YOU
TO STAND STILL.
(SIGHS)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(SONG PLAYS ON COMPUTER)
HEY, SOUNDS GREAT!
IS THAT KEKE?
NO, IT'S ME!
ALLI:
YOU'RE WRITING SONGS AGAIN?
DOES THIS MEAN
YOU'RE NOT BUMMED?
NO, I-I'M NOT DELUDED,
ALLI!
I WAS ONE DEGREE
FROM KEKE PALMER!
THAT COULD'VE BEEN
A WHOLE SEMESTER OF CRED!
YOU KNOW WHAT
THE BEST PART IS?
I HAVEN'T THOUGHT ABOUT HOLLY J
FOR A WHOLE DAY.
(COMPUTER CHIMES)
WHOA... WHAT'S THIS?
WHOA! HEY!
SAV?
KEKE!
HOW DID YOU FIND ME?
I HAVE PEOPLE.
YOU OKAY?
YEAH! I MEAN,
I'M-I'M KEEPING BUSY,
WORKING ON SONGS,
AND WORKING ON MY DEMO.
KEKE:
I'VE BEEN WORKING
ON SOMETHING TOO!
SAV, I'M SORRY
I HAD TO RUN.
I HOPE YOU DIDN'T THINK
I WAS PLAYING WITH YOU.
SAV:
NAH, IT'S FINE.
IT WAS FUN
WHILE IT LASTED.
TRUTH IS,
I NEEDED THE PICK ME UP.
KEKE:
SO DID I.
SAV:
SO, CAN I HEAR IT?
YOUR NEW TRACK?
WELL, IT'S JUST A MELODY,
BUT I CAN WING IT.
WELL, THAT WOULD BE AWESOME.
(KEKE LAUGHS)
♪ YOU CAN PUSH ME
TO THE EDGE ♪
♪ I'LL COME BACK
LIKE AN AVALANCHE ♪
♪ I'M READY ♪
♪ GOT BOTH MY FEET
ON THE GROUND ♪
♪ THE WORLD IS WAITING FOR ME ♪
♪ I'LL PUT THE STARS
IN THE SKY ♪
♪ IN MY HAND
AND INTO MY POCKET ♪
♪ BUILD A CASTLE WAY UP HIGH ♪
♪ COME DOWN ON ROCKETS ♪
YES!
CAN YOU TURN THAT OFF?!
ADAM:
NO WAY!
I'M SLAUGHTERING THESE GUYS!
YOU WANNA PLAY?
NO.
HOLLY J:
WELL, HOW WAS YOUR SKETCH DATE?
SKETCHY?
IF HUMILIATION HAD A FACE,
THIS WOULD BE IT.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WE KISSED.
HOLLY J:
FIONA CELESTINE ARABELLA COYNE,
YOU NAUGHTY LITTLE MINX!
SO, ARE WE TALKING
SPRING FLING,
OR SHOULD I MAKE NEW PLANS
FOR CHICK TV NIGHT?
WELL, I KISSED HER,
AND THEN SHE KISSED ME,
AND KEPT KISSING ME,
AND THEN I TOTALLY
CHICKENED OUT.
REJECTION IS HARSH.
FOLLOWED BY THE MOST
AWKWARD HOUR OF SKETCHING
SINCE THE INVENTION
OF CHARCOAL.
(FIONA SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
ARE WE SKIPPING
ART CLASS?
NO,
I HAVE TO FACE THIS.
HEY, CHARLIE.
LOOK, IF YOU HATE ME,
I GET IT.
LAST NIGHT,
I MIGHT HAVE MOVED FASTER
THAN I SHOULD HAVE.
I LIKE YOU,
IT'S JUST...
THIS IS ALL SO NEW TO ME,
AND I JUST WANNA MAKE SURE
WE'RE FRIENDS.
FRIENDS FIRST,
BENEFITS MAYBE LATER.
IT MAKES SENSE.
WE'LL ONLY GO FAST
ON THE STREET...
IF A FRIEND CAN GIVE
ANOTHER FRIEND A RIDE.
I DON'T SEE WHY NOT.
(RELIEVED SIGH)
WELL, I HOPE THE BRAKES
ON YOUR CRUSH
ARE AS GOOD AS THE ONES
ON HER SCOOTER.
THEY'RE NOT.
(LAUGHS) COME ON.
♪ Tell me everything
that happened ♪
♪ Tell me everything you saw ♪
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THIS.
I'M DOING IT FOR YOU.
THERE HE IS.
IT'S TIME FOR ME
TO PROVE MYSELF.
♪ They moved forward
and my heart died ♪
♪ Please, please tell me
what they looked like ♪
♪ Did they seem afraid of you? ♪
♪ They were kids
that I once knew ♪
DAVE:
YO, DREW, WHAT'S UP?
I NEED TO TALK TO YOUR DAD.
YOU ALL RIGHT, SON?
THAT GUY IN THE ALLEY -
THE ONE THAT WAS KILLED -
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
AND HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
HE ATTACKED MY GIRLFRIEND.
HE WAS GOING TO RAPE HER,
SO I HIT HIM OVER THE HEAD
WITH A BRICK A COUPLE OF TIMES
AND THEN WE RAN.
I KILLED HIM.
THERE'S ALSO THIS.
ONE OF HIS GANG BUDDIES
GAVE IT TO ME.
I'M SUPPOSED TO SHOOT SOMEONE
TO SAVE MYSELF.
I'LL TELL YOU EVERYTHING.
OKAY.
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN?
THERE'LL BE LOTS
OF QUESTIONS,
BUT YOU'RE DOING
THE RIGHT THING.
♪ They were kids
that I once knew ♪
(CAR DOOR SLAMS)
♪ They were kids
that I once knew ♪
♪ Now they're all dead hearts
to you... ♪
(CAR STARTS)
♪ They were kids
that I once knew ♪
that I once knew... ♪