♪ Oh really ♪
♪ So you're sittin' at home ♪
♪ Got bored
and you called me up ♪
♪ You're so silly ♪
♪ Did you think that
I'd be hanging around ♪
♪ Just waiting on you ♪
RADIO ANNOUNCER:
ALL RIGHT,
IT'S SPRING BREAK, KIDS!
AND JUST BECAUSE
YOU CAN'T GET TO THE BEACH
DOES NOT MEAN YOU HAVE
TO SPEND IT HOME ALONE!
♪♪♪
RADIO DJ:
IT'S ABOUT FUN,
IT'S ABOUT FLINGS,
AND WE'VE GOT THE PERFECT THING
TO GET YOU STARTED!
I'VE GOT SIX KEKE PALMER
CONCERT TICKETS
FOR THE FIRST FREESTYLER
THAT CAN RAISE OUR TEMPERATURES
UP HERE!
HOLD THIS.
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
DO YOU WANT THOSE TICKETS
OR NOT?
DREW AND DAVE: OH!
KC: OH YEAH, BIANCA!
DREW:
YEAH! WOO!
(CROWD CHEERS AND WHISTLES)
♪♪♪
(CROWD CHEERS WILDLY)
DREW:
WOO!
(CROWD CHEERS AND CLAPS LOUDLY)
(DAVE AND DREW HOLLER)
BIANCA:
TWO FOR YOU,
AND...TWO FOR US!
SWEET!
SO HOW ARE WE GOING
TO CELEBRATE MY BIG WIN?
BY GETTING ME HOME
BEFORE CURFEW.
YOU HAVE CURFEW
ON SPRING BREAK?!
ONLY TWO MORE WEEKS!
ANSON:
LOOKING GOOD, B!
LOOKING REAL GOOD.
SORRY,
CAN'T TALK RIGHT NOW!
HEY, DON'T BE A STRANGER!
(SIGHS ANGRILY)
HE'S A FRIEND OF YOURS?
BIANCA:
ANSON? NO.
HE'S JUST A THUG
I USED TO HANG OUT WITH.
WISH WE DIDN'T HAVE
TO SAY GOODBYE.
MAYBE WE DON'T.
(BIANCA GIGGLES)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(I can make it)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(DREW AND BIANCA
MOAN PASSIONATELY)
(KISSING)
(LAUGHS)
WOW! IT'S 4 A.M.
I SHOULD GO.
WAIT.
OPEN IT.
IT'S FOR OUR TWO MONTH.
IF YOU HATE IT,
I'LL-
I DON'T!
I LOVE IT.
THEY ENGRAVED IT
FOR FREE.
BIANCA L. DESOUSA.
AUDRA:
DREW? ARE YOU UP?
OH MY GOD!
MY MOM!
GET UP!
(UNCLEAR WHISPER)
OW!
I HEARD VOICES.
MUST'VE BEEN THE TV.
I JUST TURNED IT OFF.
TELL YOUR FRIEND TO GO HOME,
AND THEN WE'LL TALK.
AND MAKE SURE
SHE DOESN'T FORGET THIS.
(BIANCA SQUEAKS)
(DOOR SLAMS)
FIONA:
THANK YOU,
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
BON VOYAGE!
HERE, A PARTING GIFT.
SPF 75.
I'LL WEAR IT PROUDLY.
(BOTH LAUGH)
ONLY SIX HOURS TILL LONG WALKS
ON THE BEACH,
AND UNLIMITED
STRAWBERRY DAIQUIRIS.
VIRGIN, OF COURSE.
OH, SO SOMEBODY'S HOPING
FOR A SPRING FLING.
HER NAME IS TARA,
OR TISHA.
MAYBE HILARY.
SHE GOES TO A SMALL
LIBERAL ARTS COLLEGE,
AND WE'LL MEET WHEN THE SPA
DOUBLE BOOKS US FOR PEDICURES.
SHE'LL LET ME HAVE IT.
OF COURSE.
AND THEN ONCE MY NAILS
ARE PERFECTLY POLISHED,
WE'LL STROLL DOWN
TO A SECLUDED COVE
AND THAT'S WHERE WE'LL SHARE
OUR FIRST KISS.
HOLLY J:
SO YOU'RE JUST GONNA WING IT?
(LAUGHS)
YOU ARE NOT GOING
TO LIKE THIS.
FIONA:
WHAT? THE SPA'S ALL BOOKED?
MRS. COYNE:
A VOLCANO ERUPTED IN ST. KITTS!
ALL FLIGHTS IN AND OUT
OF THE CARIBBEAN
HAVE BEEN CANCELLED!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
SO WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO
FOR SEVEN DAYS?
HOLLY J:
OOH! I'M TAKING AN ART CLASS.
YOU SHOULD COME!
AND SPEND SPRING BREAK
STARING AT A BOWL OF FRUIT?
(SIGHS DRAMATICALLY)
KILL ME NOW.
(SIGHS)
(PAINT ROLLERS RASP)
(ALLI SIGHS HAPPILY)
MOM AND DAD'LL LOVE IT.
FRESH NEW WALLS
JUST IN TIME FOR SPRING,
AND WE DID IT!
YEAH, WELL,
I DID IT WHILE OTHER GUYS
ARE OUT HAVING FUN
WITH THEIR GIRLFRIENDS.
(SIGHS)
(STRUMS MELANCHOLY CHORD)
OKAY, I KNOW YOU'RE STILL
DOWN ABOUT HOLLY J,
BUT YOUR GUITAR MOPING
IS LIKE HARSHING
MY SPRING BREAK HIGH!
FINE,
I'LL TAKE IT UPSTAIRS THEN.
NO! WHAT YOU NEED TO DO
IS GO OUTSIDE,
AND SOAK UP SOME VITAMIN D!
(SIGHS MOURNFULLY)
IT'S SO BRIGHT OUTSIDE THOUGH.
COME ON, EMO BOY!
YOU ARE GONNA HAVE FUN
THIS SPRING BREAK,
WHETHER YOU LIKE IT
OR NOT!
COME ON!
DAVE:
TEN BUCKS AN HOUR
TO TEACH
LITTLE TEN-YEAR-OLDS
HOW TO DRIBBLE.
THIS IS THE BEST
SPRING BREAK JOB EVER!
KC:
WITH THE EXTRA MONEY
I CAN BUY BABY GUTHRIE
SOMETHING SPECIAL.
YOU GUYS WANNA SEE PICTURES?
(PHONE BEEPS)
OH YEAH,
SHE LOOKS LIKE JENNA.
WELL, SHE'S A HE.
UH...
HE LOOKS LIKE YOU, TOO!
DAVE:
OKAY, SO,
ENOUGH BABY TALK!
WHAT DID Y'ALL
GET UP TO LAST NIGHT?
OKAY, LAST NIGHT,
ME AND BIANCA WERE
RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE OF...
DAVE:
(CLEARS THROAT)
DREW:
SO WE WERE MAKING...
DAVE:
MAKING A SANDWICH.
YES.
A PRETTY AWESOME SANDWICH,
WHEN MY MOM WALKED IN.
DAVE AND KC:
OH!
(LAUGHS)
DAVE: GROUNDED?
DREW: A MONTH.
SO, ARE YOU GONNA SELL
YOUR CONCERT TICKETS?
NAH. BIANCA'S GOING
WITHOUT ME.
HAVE YOU SEEN
YOUR GIRLFRIEND?
(LAUGHS)
ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
HEY, LET'S GO.
(BASKETBALLS BOUNCE)
(CHURCH BELLS RING)
YEAH,
THESE ARE GREAT.
LET'S GO HOME.
ALLI:
SAV! YOU ALREADY OWN
A PAIR LIKE THAT.
YEAH, SO WHY MESS
WITH WHAT WORKS?
BECAUSE SOMETIMES
WHEN YOU TAKE A RISK,
GOOD THINGS
CAN HAPPEN.
WELL, ALLI,
WHEN A GIRL RIPS
YOUR HEART OUT,
AND THROWS IT
ON THE GROUND,
AND STEPS ON IT
A LITTLE BIT,
IT'S HARD TO PRETEND
TO JUST GET OVER SOMETHING
LIKE THAT.
YOU GOT YOUR HEART BROKEN?
(SIGHS)
YEAH, SORT OF.
I'M SORRY TO HEAR.
THANKS.
UH...I'M SAV.
KEYANA.
IS THIS WHAT YOU DO
ON SPRING BREAK?
SUNGLASSES SHOPPING?
SAV:
I-I WAS WORKING ON A SONG,
BUT UH...
MY SISTER FORCED ME OUT.
BODYGUARD:
KEYANA!
WE GOTTA ROLL!
SAV:
JEEZ, DADDY'S GOTTA GO
WHEN DADDY'S GOTTA GO, RIGHT?
UH, HEY, ARE...
A-ARE YOU FREE TONIGHT?
I'M WORKING
AT THE SOUND GARAGE.
OH YEAH,
THE-THE SOUND GARAGE.
YEAH, I LOVE SEEING
SHOWS THERE.
WH-WHO'S PLAYING?
BODYGUARD:
KEYANA!
I'LL LEAVE YOUR NAME
AT THE DOOR.
COOL!
(KEYANA LAUGHS)
(LAUGHS)
ALL RIGHT,
HERE YOU GO.
OKAY,
THAT WAS A GOOD TRY,
BUT...
WHEN YOU SHOOT,
YOU WANNA KEEP YOUR HAND...
IN THE COOKIE JAR.
♪ Whoa,
this girl got me like whoa ♪
♪ I can't believe she's so ♪
♪ Like whoa ♪
♪ This girl is so ♪
♪ This girl got me like whoa ♪
WOW.
IT'S FOR THE CONCERT.
YOU LIKE?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I-I WAS THINKING.
MAYBE YOU DON'T WANNA GO
TO THE CONCERT
DRESSED LIKE THAT.
YOU MIGHT ATTRACT
TOO MUCH ATTENTION.
YOU ARE TOO CUTE
WHEN YOU'RE JEALOUS.
(LAUGHS)
WE NEED TO MOTOR
IF WE WANT TO MEET
THE GIRLS IN TIME.
YOU'RE STILL GOING?
I'LL CALL YOU
WHEN I GET HOME.
AND DON'T WORRY,
I WON'T FLIRT... MUCH.
♪ A real smart thing
with a free type stroll ♪
♪ Do what she'd like
not do what she told ♪
♪ That's what a girl
that the brother's like whoa ♪
♪ Whoa! This girl got me
like whoa ♪
♪ I can't believe she's so ♪
♪ Like whoa ♪
HOLLY J:
LOOK, JUST TRUST ME,
ART CLASS WILL BE SO FUN!
FIONA:
I'M SIGNING UP,
THOUGH I STILL DON'T KNOW
WHY YOU DID!
HOLLY J:
MY CV IS LACKING
IN THE VISUAL ARTS,
MY DOCTOR SAYS IT'S RELAXING,
AND THERE MIGHT BE CUTE GUYS!
OR GIRLS.
FIONA:
HOLLY J, I'VE ACCEPTED MY DREAM
OF A SPRING FLING
IS OFFICIALLY...
DEAD.
WELL, SHE LOOKS
VERY MUCH ALIVE.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD GO
INTRODUCE YOURSELF
AND SAY HELLO,
MY NAME'S FIONA.
I LIKE GIRLS.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
WELL, YOU MIGHT WANT
TO WORK UP TO THAT.
HEY.
HI.
DID I STEAL YOUR SKETCH PAD?
IT'S ALL YOURS.
SEE?
I'M SUCH A NEWB.
HOLLY J:
OH, COME ON,
"DID I STEAL YOUR SKETCH PAD?"
THAT IS CLASSIC PICK-UP LINE!
ART TEACHER:
CLASS,
I'D LIKE TO INTRODUCE YOU
TO TODAY'S SUBJECT.
MEET CHARLIE.
AND IT LOOKS LIKE
YOU'LL HAVE SOMETHING
TO TALK ABOUT.
(GROANS)
(SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
(SIGHS)
I SAID NO, DREW!
DREW:
BUT EVERYONE IS GOING
TO BE AT THE SHOW!
AND DID EVERYONE SNEAK
A GIRL IN PAST CURFEW?
WEREN'T YOU EVER SIXTEEN?
YEAH, WHAT IF I DON'T GO
TO THE SHOW
AND...AND SHE MEETS
SOMEONE ELSE?
HOW WELL DO YOU KNOW
THIS GIRL?
HER NAME IS BIANCA!
THE GIRL WHO WOULDN'T DANCE
WITH YOUR BROTHER
IN BALLROOM CLASS?!
NO, THAT WAS
A MISUNDERSTANDING.
SHE'S A GOOD PERSON,
MOM!
WELL, THEN YOU HAVE NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
DON'T STAY UP TOO LATE.
(FRUSTRATED GROAN)
WHO'S A GOOD PERSON?
NEVER MIND.
OKAY, WELL AS LONG
AS YOU'RE GROUNDED,
DO YOU WANNA FIRE UP
THE X-BOX?
I'M GOING OUT.
I CAN'T GET ANY MORE GROUNDED.
(WHISPERS)
ACTUALLY, YOU CAN!
(SIGHS)
KC:
READY?
BIANCA:
WHERE ARE THE GIRLS?
KC:
INSIDE.
BIANCA:
LET'S GET IN THERE!
(BASS HEAVY DANCE MUSIC PLAYS)
(CONCERT GOERS CHATTER)
ALLI:
FREE TICKETS
TO THE KEKE PALMER CONCERT?
SAV, YOU HAVE GOT
TO LOCK THIS GIRL DOWN.
NOW, WHAT'S HER NAME AGAIN?
KEYANA.
SHE SAID SHE WAS WORKING,
I DON'T KNOW WHERE SHE IS.
WHO CARES?
THE CONCERT'S ABOUT TO START!
(FANS CHEER AND CLAP)
♪♪♪
KEKE:
♪ OOH OOH ♪
♪ RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ I NEED TO BREAK DOWN ♪
♪ COULD YOU FEEL IT TOO ♪
WOO!
♪ WHAT IF I WAS YOU? ♪
♪ I GOT ONE LIFE ♪
ALLI! ALLI!
ALLI.
THAT'S HER.
THAT'S KEYANA!
NO...
THAT WAS KEKE PALMER!
♪ I WANNA LIVE IT UP ♪
(SQUEALS)
♪ I NEED TO LIVE IT UP ♪
♪ UNTIL THE WALLS
COME TUMBLING DOWN ♪
♪ SO, DJ, TURN IT UP... ♪
ANSON:
HEY, B!
WHAT A COINK-I-DINK!
ARE YOU STALKING ME?
I'M A BIG KEKE FAN.
YOU KNOW,
I THOUGHT ABOUT YOU LOTS
WHEN I WAS LOCKED UP.
WE USED TO HAVE
SO MUCH FUN.
ANSON, DON'T.
WHOA.
TOO GOOD FOR ME NOW?
I HAVE A LIFE.
A BOYFRIEND.
WHO? THAT KID
I SAW YOU WITH?
HIS NAME'S DREW.
NO, HE SEEMED
LIKE A NICE GUY.
I BET PEOPLE WOULD BE
REAL TORN UP, YOU KNOW,
IF HE GOT HURT.
YOU THIRSTY?
YEAH. SURE.
GOOD.
LET ME BUY YOU A DRINK.
♪ SO, DJ, TURN IT UP ♪
♪ AND ARE THE SPEAKERS ON? ♪
♪ UNTIL THE WALLS
COME TUMBLING DOWN ♪
FIONA:
HOW DO I EVEN KNOW
IF SHE'S GAY?
HOLLY J:
TALK TO HER.
I'M SURE YOU HAVE SOME SPECIAL
LESBIAN-DAR THING.
(FIONA SIGHS)
OH! I CAN'T!
DEEP BREATH.
OKAY, MOVE YOUR LIPS,
WORDS WILL COME OUT.
GO!
(SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
(NERVOUS BREATH)
SO, WERE YOU INSPIRED
TO SKETCH?
OH, NOT REALLY.
OH, MODEL SUCKED.
I HATE WHEN THAT HAPPENS.
OH NO,
THE MODEL WAS GREAT.
YOU WERE GREAT.
(LAUGHS SHYLY)
CUTE SCOOTER.
MMM. IT GETS ME AROUND.
YOU LIKE?
I LOVE.
OH, AWESOME.
DON'T TELL ME
YOU HAVE ONE TOO?
ME? OH, YEAH.
I HAVE SCOOTERS...
THAT'S PLURAL.
MORE THAN ONE.
WOW! ANOTHER FANATIC.
WE SHOULD GO RIDING
TOGETHER SOMETIME.
WE SHOULD?
YEAH!
IT'D BE FUN.
UM...WHAT ARE YOU DOING
TOMORROW AFTER CLASS?
RIDING SCOOTERS
WITH YOU?
CHARLIE:
SOUNDS GREAT!
(ENGINE STARTS)
(SCOOTER REVS AND BUZZES AWAY)
HOLLY J:
HOW'D IT GO?
WE NEED TO GO SHOPPING.
HOLLY J:
ACCESSORIES?
KINDA.
KEKE:
SO YOU THINK YOU CAN
JUST CALL ME LIKE THIS?
NO, NOT ME.
♪♪♪
♪ YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ NAH-AH-AH-AH NAH ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
THAT IS THE GIRL
THAT I MET WHILE SHOPPING
FOR SUNGLASSES!
WELL, BELIEVE IT!
AND WHEN YOU TWO
GET TOGETHER,
MAYBE KEKE CAN INTRODUCE ME
TO TAYLOR LAUTNER!
NO, NO, NO,
TOO DREW-LIKE.
MAYBE JUSTIN BIEBER!!
NO...
NO, ALLI,
THAT'S NEVER GONNA HAPPEN!
SH-SHE'S A ROCK STAR.
♪ SO I WENT THROUGH YOUR PHONE
JUST TO SEE WHO PICKED UP ♪
♪ BUT IT WON'T BE ME ♪
A ROCK STAR WHO WANTS YOU
UP ON STAGE!
JUST GO!
(SQUEALS EXCITEDLY)
(SCREAMS AND CLAPS)
♪ I FORGOT ALL ABOUT YOU ♪
♪ WHY YOU ALL ON ME ♪
♪ YOU SHOULD REALLY GO BACK
TO HER ♪
♪ 'CAUSE RIGHT NOW
YOU WORKING ON MY NERVE ♪
(CROWD CHEERS WILDLY)
♪ 'CAUSE I'M NOT GONNA BE ♪
♪ NOT, NOT GONNA BE
THE ONE YOU CALL ♪
WHOO! YEAH!
♪ SO YOU DON'T LISTEN ♪
♪ DID YOU NOT GET THE HINT ♪
♪ WHEN I SAID
I'M NOT INTERESTED ♪
♪ WITH ME
YOUR TIME'S RUN OUT ♪
♪ DON'T YOU THINK
YOU SHOULD GIVE UP NOW ♪
♪ WHO ARE YOU KIDDIN'? ♪
OH, MAN!
SAV IS SO LUCKY!
BUT...NOT AS LUCKY AS ME.
HEY, DIDN'T YOU GUYS
JUST HAVE A BABY?
KC:
YEAH.
MY MOM HAD THE NIGHT OFF.
BEST GRANDMA EVER!
YEAH, I'LL BE LUCKY
IF I CAN STAY AWAKE
FOR ANOTHER HOUR!
(ALL LAUGH)
♪ WHY YOU ALL ON ME? ♪
♪ WHY YOU CALL? ♪
♪ YOU SHOULD REALLY
GO BACK TO HER ♪
THIS IS SO CRAZY...
THIS IS SO CRAZY!
DREW:
HEY, GUYS!
ALL:
HEY!
DAVE:
LOOK WHAT THE CAT DRAGGED IN.
YOUR MOM
LET YOU OUT?
UH, NOT EXACTLY.
WHERE'S B?
HAVEN'T SEEN HER
IN A WHILE.
KEKE:
♪ BUT WHAT GIVES YOU THE RIGHT ♪
♪ TO THINK THAT
I'M GONNA WAIT UP ♪
♪ DON'T YOU SEE THAT
YOU'RE PLAYING YOURSELF ♪
HEY, UH, B,
I'M AT THE SHOW
AND I WAS HOPING
THAT YOU'RE STILL...
HERE.
YOU'RE UNBELIEVABLE,
YOU KNOW THAT?
OH MY GOD!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I SNEAK OUT TO FIND YOU HERE
WITH ANOTHER GUY!
DID YOU PLAN THIS,
DID YOU TELL HIM
TO MEET YOU HERE?
OF COURSE NOT!
OH, SO IT'S JUST
ONE BIG COINCIDENCE?!
WE USED TO DATE, OKAY?
HE'S STALKING ME.
THERE'S NOTHING
I COULD DO ABOUT IT!
THEN COME WITH ME!
HE'S DANGEROUS, DREW!
HE'S IN A GANG,
HE THREATENED TO HURT YOU!
WHAT'S HE GONNA DO?
SHOOT ME?
YOU KNOW,
I THOUGHT YOU'D CHANGED.
DREW, STOP!
I BET YOU'VE BEEN
HOOKING UP WITH HIM
THE ENTIRE TIME
WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER.
PRETTY MUCH!
KEKE:
♪ NO IT WON'T BE ME ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU MISSED OUT
ON A GOOD ONE ♪
♪ NOW YOU'RE FEELIN'
LONELY... ♪
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
OKAY, THANK YOU.
(PHONE BEEPS)
ARGH!
APPARENTLY THERE'S NO WAY
I CAN LEARN
TO RIDE A SCOOTER
BY TOMORROW!
IT'S BABY BLUE.
HOW HARD COULD IT BE?
FIONA:
BEFORE YOU CAN EVEN
GET ON A SCOOTER,
YOU NEED A LEARNER'S PERMIT
AND A LICENCE.
AND THERE'S NO WAY YOU CAN GET
ALL THAT BY TOMORROW AFTERNOON?
SO I'M TOLD.
I GUESS THERE'S ONLY
ONE THING TO DO.
HOLLY J:
TELL CHARLIE THE TRUTH?
FIONA:
AND LET HER KNOW
I'M AN INEXPERIENCED DORK
WHO CAN'T TALK TO A GIRL
WITHOUT TURNING PATHOLOGICAL?
YOU'RE NOT GONNA CANCEL.
IS "PLUMBING EMERGENCY"
A VIABLE EXCUSE NOWADAYS?
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYS)
I'M OFF.
YOU FIND BIANCA?
YEAH, WITH ANOTHER GUY,
SOME EX.
SHE MADE UP SOME CRAP
ABOUT HIM BEING IN A GANG.
NOT EVERYONE LIVES
IN A NICE HOUSE
OFF THE PARK, DREW!
THERE WERE TONS OF GUYS
IN THE GROUP HOME
MIXED UP WITH STUFF
LIKE THAT.
IT'S NOT EASY TO GET OUT!
YOU THINK SHE'S TELLING
THE TRUTH?
HAS SHE EVER LIED
TO YOU BEFORE?
NO.
SHE COULD BE IN TROUBLE.
(CARS RUMBLE)
(PHONE BUTTONS CLICK)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(BUTTONS BEEP)
YOU'RE NOT HIDING FROM ME,
ARE YOU?
(BIANCA SIGHS)
I NEED TO GET HOME.
CURFEW.
OH, COME ON,
WE BOTH KNOW
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
(CRIES OUT)
(WHIMPERS FEARFULLY)
DON'T WORRY, OKAY?
I WON'T MAKE YOU DO ANYTHING
YOU HAVEN'T DONE BEFORE.
(SIRENS WAIL)
OH, COME ON.
PICK UP!
PICK UP, PICK UP!
(PHONE RINGS)
DAMN IT!
(FRUSTRATED SIGH)
AHHHHH!
LET GO OF ME!
(SCREAMING)
SHH! SHH! SHH!
HELP ME!
(PANICKED SCREAMING)
ANSON:
SHH! SHH! SHH!
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
HELP ME!
(MUFFLED SCREAMS)
(SCREAMING AND SOBBING)
DREW:
GET OFF HER!
ANSON:
MIND YOUR OWN BUSINESS, HUH?
(FIGHTING GRUNTS)
BIANCA:
(SCREAMING)
STOP IT!
STOP!
GET OFF OF HIM!
STOP!!
UNGH!
BIANCA:
PLEASE!
(DREW GROANS)
ANSON:
GET UP!
GET UP!!
(BIANCA SCREAMS,
BRICK THUNKS)
(PANTING)
OH GOD!
OH! ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH.
VINCE:
HEY!
BIANCA:
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE!
(RUNNING FOOTSTEPS THUD)
(BRACELET CLINKS)
BIANCA:
(PANTING)
OH MY GOD.
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
I'LL NEVER DOUBT YOU,
I'M SO SORRY.
YOU FOUGHT FOR ME.
(BIANCA SOBS)