FIONA:
LET'S GO.
IT'S TIME TO STRIKE.
IMOGEN:
COOL!
ARE WE ON A MISSION?
RUMOUR IS KATIE HAS
A LITTLE PILL PROBLEM
AND NOW SHE'S MISSING SCHOOL
FOR REHAB.
WOW! AND WE DIDN'T EVEN
HAVE TO DO ANYTHING.
WE'VE BEEN WAITING
PATIENTLY
SINCE KATIE AND MARISOL
BACKSTABBED US,
AND NOW THE USELESS
CHEERLEADER-JOCK
STUDENT COUNCIL'S
RIPE FOR THE TAKING.
MARISOL:
GUYS! GUYS!
UNTIL KATIE GETS BACK,
I'M ACTING PRESIDENT.
SO TAKE A NUMBER
AND I WILL GET TO YOU!
THIS IS GONNA BE EASIER
THAN I THOUGHT.
YEAH, WELL, KATIE SAID
THAT SHE'D ASK MR. SIMPSON
ABOUT THE UNIFORMS?
WELL, SHE'S NOT KATIE,
IS SHE?
FIONA:
YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
MARISOL, YOU'RE CLEARLY IN
WAY OVER YOUR HEAD,
SO IMOGEN AND I WOULD
LIKE TO HELP.
WE HAVE AN IDEA
FOR AN ERA-DEFINING
END-OF-SEMESTER EVENT.
WE DO?
MARISOL:
YOU KNOW I'M SOCIAL CONVENER.
AND WE'VE HAD, WHAT,
ZERO DANCES?
NO MOVIE NIGHTS.
REMIND ME, HAS ANYTHING FUN
HAPPENED THIS YEAR?
STUDENTS:
NO...
HMM...
THE COFFEE HOUSE?
AN IDEA YOU STOLE
FROM ME.
LISTEN, MS. KNOW-IT-ALL,
SINCE VEGAS NIGHT AND PROM
BOTH ENDED IN VIOLENCE,
SIMPSON HAS BANNED ANYMORE
AFTER-SCHOOL EVENTS.
SO YOUR JOB'S BEEN
PRETTY EASY, THEN.
AND IF YOU THINK
I'M GONNA PLAY DEAD
JUST BECAUSE KATIE'S
NOT HERE,
GIRL, YOU'RE FOOLING
YOURSELF.
PLEASE REMOVE
THIS RICH BRAT
AND HER LITTLE SIDEKICK
FROM MY FACE.
ME?
MO: SORRY, LADIES.
FIONA: WHAT? NO.
HEY! LET GO!
THIS IS ASSAULT!
I HAVE LAWYERS!
SO... NOW WHAT?
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh... ♪
(Oh-oh-oh)
♪ I can make it through ♪
(I can make it!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
CLARE:
HEY, GUYS, SORRY I'M LATE!
BUT I'VE GOT MY ARTICLE ON
THE HOLIDAY FOOD DRIVE ALL SET.
WHERE'S KATIE?
LIAM:
UH, SHE'S DEALING
WITH SOME PERSONAL ISSUES,
SO SHE'S NOT GONNA BE BACK
UNTIL THE END OF THE BREAK.
SO I'VE DECIDED TO POSTPONE
THE PAPER UNTIL THEN.
EVERYBODY ENJOY YOUR TIME OFF!
CLARE:
(SCOFFS) THIS IS CRAZY!
WE'RE ALL JUST GIVING UP
BECAUSE KATIE'S NOT HERE?
LIAM:
IT'S ONE LESS THING TO DO
BEFORE THE HOLIDAYS.
BUT THE HOLIDAY EDITION
OF THE DEGRASSI DAILY
IS LIKE AN INSTITUTION!
THINK OF HOW AWESOME IT'D BE
TO PULL IT OFF.
CLARE, THE TEAM
NEEDS A BREAK.
THEN I'LL DO IT MYSELF.
YEAH?
EVERY ARTICLE -
NEWS, ARTS, SPORTS?
SPORTS?
YEAH.
AND THEN THERE'S
THE OPINION PIECE,
LAYOUT,
PROOFING TEAR-SHEETS.
THEN MAYBE I'LL JUST HAVE
TO HIRE A WHOLE NEW TEAM.
BY THE END OF THE WEEK?
SURE.
I CAN DO ALL THAT.
OKAY, OKAY.
GOOD LUCK.
(BELL RINGS)
I UH... CAN DO ALL THAT.
ELI:
SO YOU HAD ONE MINOR SETBACK.
FIONA:
YEAH. ADDED TO AN ENTIRE
SEMESTER OF SETBACKS.
I WISH I COULD OFFER
SOMETHING MORE
THAN JUST MORAL SUPPORT.
FIONA:
THANK YOU,
ZEN MASTER GOLDSWORTHY.
WE'LL THINK OF SOMETHING.
AND IN THE MEANTIME,
MAYBE A LITTLE
ONLINE SHOPPING
AT LUNCHTIME?
OH, YOU ALWAYS KNOW
HOW TO MAKE ME
FEEL BETTER.
IT'S A GIFT!
I'M ITALIAN.
CIAO!
(GIGGLES)
WHEN ARE YOU TWO
GONNA MAKEOUT ALREADY?
(LAUGHS)
YEAH, I WISH.
I MEAN- WHAT?
OH, SHUT UP!
I WAS JOKING...
ARE YOU BLUSHING?
NO... I'M NOT!
YOU'RE CRAZY!
OH MY GOD!
YOU HAVE A CRUSH ON HER!
I SET YOU AND IMOGEN UP,
REMEMBER?
I LIKE HER
AS A FRIEND
AND BESIDES, SHE'D NEVER
RETURN THE FEELINGS,
SO JUST DROP IT!
(CHUCKLES) WELL,
THAT EXPLAINS A LOT.
THIS OBVIOUSLY GOES
IN THE VAULT.
YOUR SECRET'S SAFE
WITH ME.
GOOD. I DON'T WANT
MY STUPID CRUSH
GETTING IN THE WAY
OF TAKING MARISOL DOWN
A NOTCH OR FOUR.
DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING
UP YOUR SLEEVE?
SHE WON'T EVEN
TALK TO ME.
WHY DON'T YOU
JUST GO OVER HER HEAD?
SEE?
YOU ARE GOOD AT THIS!
HMM.
(SCHOOL BAND PLAYS
"ODE TO JOY")
(TRISTAN FLUBS A NOTE)
SORRY!
MS. OH:
IT'S OKAY.
CATCH UP. IT'S FINE.
(MAYA IMPROVISES HER PART)
MAYA?
OKAY, EVERYONE, STOP.
STOP! STOP!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
JUST IMPROVISING A BIT.
WELL, YOU'RE DISTRACTING
THE OTHERS.
PLEASE,
JUST FOLLOW THE NOTES.
I LEARNED THIS SONG
WHEN I WAS SIX.
MS. OH:
THEN YOU SHOULD HAVE NO PROBLEM
PLAYING IT
AT THE HOLIDAY RECITAL.
AND BEING HUMILIATED
IN THE PROCESS.
MS. OH:
LOOK, IF YOU'RE NOT HAPPY
IN THIS CLASS,
THERE'S A TIME AND PLACE
TO DISCUSS THAT.
WE HAVE THREE DAYS
TO GET THIS DOWN,
SO PLEASE FALL IN LINE
OR I'LL HAVE TO DOCK MARKS.
OKAY, EVERYBODY,
ONE MORE TIME FROM THE TOP.
AND ONE, TWO, THREE.
(CLASS BEGINS TO PLAYS)
FIONA:
MARISOL HAS NO RIGHT
TO EXCLUDE OTHER STUDENTS
FROM DECISION MAKING.
SHE'S THE VICE PRESIDENT.
IN THE ABSENCE OF THE PRESIDENT,
THE VICE TAKES OVER.
SHE HAS THE RIGHT.
FIONA:
TO RUN STUDENT COUNCIL LIKE
IT'S HER OWN LITTLE CLIQUE?
ISN'T THIS SUPPOSED TO BE
A DEMOCRACY?
SIMPSON:
(SIGHS) LOOK,
I KNOW YOU HAVE YOUR ISSUES
WITH KATIE AND MARISOL,
BUT IN THE SPIRIT
OF THE HOLIDAYS,
DO YOU THINK MAYBE
YOU CAN JUST TRY TO GET ALONG?
WELL, THAT'S IT!
IMOGEN AND I WANT TO SPREAD
HOLIDAY SPIRIT,
BUT MARISOL KEEPS LOCKING US
OUT OF ROOMS!
THEN HOW ARE YOU PLANNING
ON DOING THIS?
WELL, WE HAVE A PROPOSAL
FOR AN END-OF-SEMESTER
HOLIDAY CARNIVAL!
DID MARISOL MENTION THE BAN
ON AFTER-SCHOOL EVENTS?
FIONA:
EASY WORK-AROUND:
CLASSES LET OUT EARLY
ON FRIDAY,
SO WE CAN HAVE A FUN-FILLED,
DAYTIME CARNIVAL
THAT THE WHOLE SCHOOL
CAN ENJOY.
OH, FIONA...
THINK OF THE POINTS
IT'LL SCORE
WITH THE STUDENT BODY!
I'LL PUT UP MY OWN MONEY
SO WE CAN KEEP TICKET
PRICES LOW,
AND IT WON'T COST
STUDENT COUNCIL A THING!
PLEASE, SIR?
AND YOU THINK YOU CAN MANAGE
TO PULL THIS OFF BY FRIDAY?
I'VE PLANNED
A BLACK-TIE GALA
ON TWO HOURS NOTICE
WITH MY MOM.
IT'S KINDA MY THING.
AN AFTERNOON
DEGRASSI-ONLY EVENT,
AND I WANT YOU TO WORK OUT
YOUR DIFFERENCES WITH MARISOL
AND PLAN IT TOGETHER.
I'D LOVE TO.
THANK YOU, SIR!
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
DAVE: (OVER PA)
MISSED THE LATEST MANO-A-MANO
WITH DAVE AND ADAM,
PODCAST IS AVAILABLE ONLINE.
CHECK IT OUT!
CLARE:
HEY, GUYS!
UM, I'VE BEEN APPOINTED
THE INTERIM EDITOR
OF THE DEGRASSI DAILY
AND I WAS HOPING TO CONVINCE
SOME OF YOU TO JOIN MY TEAM.
IT'S AN EASY
EXTRA-CURRICULAR
AND YOU CAN WRITE
ABOUT ANYTHING.
ISN'T THERE ALREADY
A NEWSPAPER STAFF?
THEY TOOK AN EARLY HOLIDAY.
I COULD USE ALL THE HELP
I CAN GET.
AND WHY SHOULD WE
HELP YOU?
UM...
(STREETCAR RUMBLES)
MOM?
YOU HERE?
LARA:
I CAN NEVER FIND
MY PASSPORT!
YOU GOING SOMEWHERE?
LARA:
I'M FLYING HOME
FOR MORE ACCOUNTANT MEETINGS.
OH, VOILA!
FIONA:
ARE THOSE TAX PEOPLE
STILL PUNISHING YOU
FOR BEING GOOD
AT FUNDRAISING?
LARA:
WITH THE MONEY
WE GIVE TO CHARITY,
THEY SHOULD BE THANKING ME.
THE LAWYERS SAY
IT'LL ALL BE OVER SOON.
I'LL BE BACK
IN A FEW DAYS.
OKAY, UH... BEFORE YOU GO,
JUST LISTEN.
FIRST SEMESTER'S
ALMOST OVER,
AND I HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING
I SET OUT TO ACCOMPLISH
THIS YEAR.
WELL, IT'S NEVER
TOO LATE TO START.
EXACTLY.
SO THAT'S WHY I WANNA THROW
A SCHOOL CARNIVAL
TO SHOW EVERYONE
WHY I DESERVE A SEAT
ON STUDENT COUNCIL.
SO I JUST NEED AN ADVANCE
ON MY TRUST FUND
SO I CAN PAY
FOR THE CARNIVAL RIDES.
IT'S NOT POSSIBLE,
SWEETHEART.
I'LL PAY YOU BACK
THE DAY I TURN EIGHTEEN!
LARA:
I'M SORRY.
YOU'RE JUST GONNA HAVE
TO FIND ANOTHER WAY
TO IMPRESS DEGRASSI
THAT WON'T DRAIN OUR SAVINGS.
I'M NOT DRAINING ANYTHING!
WHY ARE YOU BEING
SO WEIRD ABOUT THIS?
IT'S FINAL, FIONA.
THE LIMO'S WAITING.
I LOVE YOU.
(MAYA PLAYS BACH'S
SUITE NO. 1 IN G FOR CELLO)
♪♪♪
MR. MATLIN:
MAYA! MAYA!
SHHH...
YOUR SISTER'S SLEEPING.
MAYA:
ALREADY?
KATIE SPENT ALL DAY IN REHAB
AND NEEDS HER REST.
PRACTICE QUIETLY?
PRACTICE CRESCENDI
AND DIMMINUENDI QUIETLY?
IT KINDA DEFEATS THE PURPOSE,
DAD.
PLEASE, HONEY.
FINE!
MR. MATLIN:
UH, (CLEARS THROAT)
EXCUSE ME!
WHAT'S WRONG?
GRADE NINE BAND
HAS BEEN TERRIBLE.
IT'S LIKE I'M PLAYING
WITH A BUNCH OF IDOL REJECTS.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU'RE SO TALENTED.
NO, WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU'RE SO TALENTED
IS YOU GET SENT
TO ARTS SCHOOL.
BUT SINCE I'M STUCK
AT DEGRASSI,
KATIE'S CHOICE OF SCHOOL,
I SHOULD AT LEAST
BE BUMPED
INTO AN OLDER BAND.
HAVE YOU TALKED
TO MS. OH?
SHE DOESN'T TAKE ME
SERIOUSLY.
YOU GIVING HER ATTITUDE?
FIONA:
UH-HUH... MM-HMM...
OKAY, SO YOU'LL HAVE EVERYTHING
SET UP AT DEGRASSI ON FRIDAY?
EXCELLENT!
YEAH. I'LL HAVE THE DEPOSIT
COURIERED OVER IN THE MORNING.
THANKS.
(PHONE BEEPS OFF,
SOMEONE KNOCKS AT THE DOOR)
DOOR'S OPEN!
(SIGHS) I BROUGHT PAINTS,
MARKERS, STENCILS,
AND ENOUGH BRISTOL BOARD
TO COVER THE ENTIRE SCHOOL.
PLEASE TELL ME
WHAT WE'RE MAKING SIGNS FOR!
OKAY, SIMPSON GAVE US
THE GO-AHEAD
TO HOLD
THE HOLIDAY CARNIVAL.
A FESTIVAL OF FROST?
NO!
A FROSTIVAL?!
WITH COTTON CANDY,
PONY RIDES, A CAROUSEL?
SURE. WHY NOT?
A FERRIS WHEEL?!
PLEASE!
OHMYGOD! OHMYGOD!
PLEASE DON'T LET ME WAKE UP
AND HAVE THIS BE A DREAM!
YOU ARE THE BEST!
WELL, WE HAVE A LOT
OF SIGNS TO MAKE!
DAMN, DO WE EVER!
WE MIGHT BE HERE
ALL NIGHT!
OKAY.
MARISOL:
WELL, WELL, WELL.
YOU WON SIMPSON OVER.
AREN'T YOU A HERO!
I'M GONNA NEED TO TAKE
OVER STUDENT COUNCIL
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
AND YOU'RE GONNA PAY
FOR A PARKING LOT
FULL OF CARNIVAL RIDES
AT TWO BUCKS A TICKET?
I'M COMING IN
WITH A HEAVY SUBSIDY.
OH, OF COURSE,
YOUR ONLY TRICK -
THROWING MOMMY'S
MONEY AROUND.
HAVE YOU EVER HAD TO WORK
FOR ANYTHING?
SERIOUSLY,
IF YOU WEREN'T RICH,
WHO WOULD YOU EVEN BE?
SHUT UP, MARISOL.
MARISOL:
OH! AND THROWING MONEY AROUND
TO IMPRESS YOUR LITTLE
GIRLFRIEND!
IMOGEN:
HEY!
PATHETIC!
OKAY, THAT'S IT!
TIME OUT! SHOO! SHOO!
OW! WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
WORKING TOGETHER!
THEN GO UPDATE THE MARQUEE
AND LEAVE THE REST TO US.
BYE.
IMOGEN:
CLASSIC LOCKOUT!
HEY!
FIONA:
SEE HOW SHE LIKES IT.
HELLO!
OPEN THE DOOR!
WHAT?
OH NO, SORRY.
WE'RE WORKING.
YEAH.
BYE.
(LAUGHING)
UH, MISS?
GOOD MORNING, MAYA.
I WAS WONDERING
IF THIS WOULD BE
THE TIME OR THE PLACE
TO TALK.
SURE.
MAYA:
AS YOU CAN PROBABLY TELL,
I'VE BEEN FRUSTRATED
IN BAND CLASS.
YEAH, YOUR SARCASTIC COMMENTARY
HASN'T BEEN APPRECIATED.
I KNOW,
AND I'M SORRY.
BUT I'VE HEARD
THE GRADE ELEVEN BAND
AND THEY'RE REALLY GOOD,
SO I WAS JUST WONDERING-
LOOK,
I KNOW YOU'RE TALENTED.
BUT RIGHT NOW,
BUMPING YOU UP
IS JUST NOT POSSIBLE.
MAYBE NEXT FALL.
THAT'S ALMOST
A YEAR AWAY!
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO
UNTIL THEN?
MAYBE I CAN FIND YOU
SOME MORE CHALLENGING
PROJECTS.
YOU COULD SIT ASIDE
AND STUDY THEORY
FOR THE REST OF THE YEAR.
SO I WOULDN'T BE PLAYING
WITH THE BAND?
WELL, THEY'LL MISS YOU,
BUT IF IT'LL MAKE YOU HAPPY.
WHEN DO I START?
CONNOR:
THAT'S NICE.
KC:
MAYBE MAKE THOSE...
THOSE HEADLINES BOLD.
(COMPUTER KEYS CLACK)
ARE YOU GUYS HERE
FOR NEWSPAPER?
KC:
YOU DID MENTION
EASY EXTRA-CURRICULARS, RIGHT?
(RELIEVED LAUGH)
THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR COMING.
WHAT IS THAT?
CONNOR:
IT'S A MOCK-UP OF A NEWSPAPER
FROM THE LATE 19TH CENTURY.
WE'RE THINKING A COOL
OLD SCHOOL LOOK
FOR THE HOLIDAY EDITION.
VERY IMPRESSIVE.
IT'S NICE TO KNOW
I HAVE SOME FRIENDS
I CAN COUNT ON.
KC:
WHAT HAPPENED BETWEEN YOU
AND ALLI, ANYWAY?
CONNOR:
THEY HATE EACH OTHER SINCE
ALLI KISSED JAKE OR SOMETHING.
AND JENNA'S BEST FRIENDS
WITH ALLI,
AND ALLI'S DATING DAVE...
I THINK IT'S JUST GONNA BE
THE THREE OF US.
WELL, WE NEED WAY MORE HELP.
CAN'T YOU JUST TALK TO ALLI
AND WORK THINGS OUT?
YOU SAW FOR YOURSELF,
WE'RE NOT EXACTLY
ON SPEAKING TERMS.
(KC SIGHS)
CONNOR:
IT'S TOO BAD
WE CAN'T ALL BE FRIENDS
LIKE WE USED TO BE.
IMOGEN:
THE REACTION ACHIEVED
IS A) MILD,
B) MODERATE,
AND C) VIGOROUS.
WELL, COMPARED TO THE ONE
WE GOT FROM MARISOL?
I'D SAY MILD AT BEST.
YOU KNOW, THIS YEAR WOULD'VE
BEEN PAINFUL WITHOUT YOU.
I'M GLAD
YOU'RE ON MY SIDE.
SO WAS THERE ANY TRUTH
TO WHAT MARISOL SAID?
I'M NOT GONNA APOLOGIZE
FOR USING MY MONEY-
NO! I MEAN, WHAT SHE SAID
ABOUT IMPRESSING ME -
WHICH YOU ARE NAILING,
BY THE WAY.
(GIGGLING)
I'D CALL THAT
A VIGOROUS REACTION.
OOPS!
WE NEED MORE REACTANT.
IMOGEN'S QUITE IMPRESSED,
I'D SAY.
SOUNDS LIKE SHE'S HOLDING
THAT CRUSH DOOR WIDE OPEN.
YEAH. VERY FUNNY.
WHAT?
IT COULD MEAN SOMETHING.
OR IT COULD JUST BE
IMOGEN BEING IMOGEN.
WOULD YOU HATE ME
IF ANYTHING HAPPENED?
SHE AND I ARE BETTER
AS FRIENDS.
AND ALL I KNOW IS THAT
LIFE IS TOO SHORT
TO WONDER WHAT IF.
WELL, ALL I KNOW IS
THAT I WANT TO BUY HER
LOTS OF NICE THINGS.
THE CARNIVAL'S
A GOOD START.
BY THE WAY,
I'M GONNA NEED SOME
OF THOSE TICKETS.
REALLY? I NEVER PEGGED YOU
FOR THE CARNIVAL TYPE.
BRINGING SOMEONE SPECIAL,
PERHAPS?
YEAH,
NOW WHO'S BEING FUNNY?
(PLAYING "ODE TO JOY")
♪♪♪
HOW'S DECIPHERING
MAJOR SCALE NOTES?
CHALLENGING,
YET FUN.
PERFECT.
♪ Walking shoulder to shoulder ♪
♪ We've been thinking it over ♪
♪ Are we wasting
our days away ♪
♪ Yeah, we're getting
much older ♪
♪ Heard it over and over ♪
♪ Time to wake up
and find our way ♪
♪ But sometimes we need
to get a little bit crazy ♪
♪ Chill and be
a little bit lazy... ♪
CLARE:
ALLI...
WAIT! CAN WE TALK?
YEAH. I DON'T REALLY HAVE
ANYTHING TO SAY.
I WAS MAD AT YOU
FOR KISSING JAKE,
BUT I WAS A HYPOCRITE.
I BLAMED YOU
AND LET JAKE OFF THE HOOK.
IT WASN'T FAIR.
CLARE, DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT I WAS GOING THROUGH
LAST SUMMER?
YOU AND DAVE,
YOU WERE FIGHTING.
DAVE CHEATED ON ME.
HE HAD SEX
WITH ANOTHER GIRL,
AND YOU CALLED MY PROBLEM
"PEDESTRIAN."
I DIDN'T KNOW.
AND AFTER I FOUND OUT,
I STUPIDLY KISSED JAKE.
BUT YOU WERE
SO SELF-OBSESSED,
YOU NEVER REALIZED
YOUR BEST FRIEND
NEEDED YOU.
AND NOW THE ONLY REASON
YOU'RE EVEN APOLOGIZING
IS BECAUSE YOU NEED HELP
WITH THE NEWSPAPER.
THAT'S NOT TRUE,
ALLI.
I JUST...
I WISH AFTER ALL THE YEARS
WE'VE BEEN BEST FRIENDS,
YOU'D AT LEAST GIVE ME
ANOTHER CHANCE.
HEY, MOM,
I KNOW YOU'RE BUSY,
BUT I HAVE HAPPY THINGS
TO TELL YOU!
I HOPE YOUR BORING
WORK STUFF
IS WORKING OUT TOO.
CALL ME BACK.
LOVE YOU!
I'VE ALREADY CALLED 911!
SHERM:
FIONA!
LISTEN, THERE'S NO NEED
TO WORRY!
FIONA:
SHERM, WHO ARE THESE PEOPLE?
WHAT ARE THEY DOING
TO MY STUFF?
SHERM:
WELL, IT'S EVIDENCE.
THERE'S BEEN SOME ISSUES
WITH THE FOUNDATION'S FINANCES.
FIONA:
YEAH, I KNOW.
MY MOM'S BEEN DEALING WITH IT
IN NEW YORK FOREVER.
SHERM:
WELL, YOU KNOW, NOW THE COURT
THINKS THEY HAVE A CASE.
LISTEN, YOUR MOM ASKED ME
TO LET THEM IN.
BUT YOU'RE OUR LAWYER!
CAN'T YOU STOP THEM?
THE POLICE HAVE
A WARRANT.
OKAY, THIS IS INSANE.
I'M CALLING MY MOM.
FIONA, PLEASE.
ALL RIGHT, YOUR MOM DOESN'T
HAVE A PHONE WITH HER.
(SIGHS)
THE INVESTIGATION HAS LED
TO YOUR MOM'S ARREST.
SHE'S BEING QUESTIONED
BY POLICE RIGHT NOW,
AND SHE SHOULD BE RELEASED
BY TONIGHT.
BUT JUST HANG IN THERE,
OKAY?
HANG IN THERE
UNTIL SHE CALLS YOU.
OKAY?
KC:
LOOK WHO WE FOUND!
DEGRASSI MINIONS
AT YOUR SERVICE.
(MOUTHS)
THANK YOU.
CONNOR:
IT'LL BE FUN!
IT'S ABOUT TIME
YOU TWO BURIED YOUR GRUDGE.
JENNA:
YEAH. IS IT OKAY
IF I HELP TOO?
YOU'RE NOT STILL MAD AT ME,
ARE YOU?
OH PLEASE, I GOT OVER
THAT KC THING AGES AGO,
AND JAKE CAN SEE
WHOEVER HE WANTS.
JAKE AND I ARE
JUST FRIENDS.
SO WHERE DO WE START?
I GUESS WE'LL START
WITH ASSIGNMENTS.
CONNOR:
LAYOUT!
KC:
I'LL TAKE SPORTS.
JENNA:
OH! DIBS ON MUSIC REVIEWS.
I CAN TAKE PHOTOS.
CLARE:
GREAT!
WHO CAN COVER THEATRE?
THE GRUNDY NOMINATIONS
JUST CAME OUT.
NO? NOBODY WANTS
TO COVER THEATRE?
ALLI:
YEAH. AND I DON'T THINK
ANYONE ELSE
IS WALKING THROUGH
THAT DOOR, CLARE.
JENNA:
YEAH, IS THERE ANYONE ELSE
YOU STILL HAVE TO MAKE UP WITH?
ELI:
(COUGHS)
ARE YOU STILL LOOKING
FOR WRITERS?
IF YOU NEED SOMEONE
TO COVER THE ARTS,
I'M YOUR GUY.
ALLI:
PERFECT!
ELI WILL COVER
THE GRUNDY AWARDS.
THE AWARDS THAT SNUBBED
MY PRODUCTION
OF LOVE ROULETTE?
WHICH WAS UNDERSTANDABLE.
SURE.
WELL, LET'S DO THIS!
IF THAT'S OKAY WITH YOU?
OF COURSE!
YEAH.
FIONA:
STRANGE MEN IN MY HOME
TAKING OUR STUFF...
MOM, IT WAS SO SCARY.
I'M SO SORRY ABOUT THAT.
FIONA:
NO, THIS IS MY FAULT.
I FORGED A FOUNDATION CHEQUE
TO PAY FOR THE CARNIVAL RIDES.
I'M SO SORRY!
HONEY, THE FOUNDATION
IS FACING FRAUD CHARGES
THAT GO WAY BEYOND
A FORGED CHECK.
BUT THE FOUNDATION IS YOU.
AND I MAY HAVE MADE
A MESS OF THINGS.
I'M UNDER HOUSE ARREST.
BUT CAN'T YOU DO SOMETHING
ABOUT THIS?
THEY'RE TREATING YOU LIKE
SOME KIND OF CRIMINAL!
LARA:
UNTIL THE COURTS
DECIDE I'M NOT,
ALL OF OUR ASSETS ARE FROZEN.
OUR CASH, OUR INVESTMENTS,
OUR TRUST FUNDS.
SO WE HAVE NOTHING?
WE HAVE OUR FAMILY.
BUT YOU'RE
FIVE HUNDRED MILES AWAY.
AND YOU SHOULDN'T BE ALONE,
SO I'VE SENT SOMEONE
TO KEEP YOU COMPANY.
WHO? DAD? DECLAN?
DECLAN'S ON HIS WAY HERE.
I'VE SENT-
HOLLY J:
FIONA? HELLO!
PERFECT TIMING AS ALWAYS.
FIONA:
HOLLY J?!
HOLLY J:
STILL HAVE MY KEY!
OH, I'M SO GLAD
YOU'RE HERE.
IT'S GONNA BE OKAY.
HEY, MRS. COYNE.
HI, SWEETHEART.
HOLLY J'S GOING TO HELP YOU
GET THINGS ORGANIZED
BEFORE YOU COME HERE.
RIGHT. I MIGHT SQUEEZE IN
A QUICK VISIT
WITH MY PARENTS TOO.
MOM, I CAN PACK
A WEEKEND BAG BY MYSELF.
IT'S GONNA BE A LITTLE BIT
LONGER THAN THAT.
WHAT? WHY?
LARA:
OUR FAMILY'S IN TROUBLE,
FIONA.
I CAN'T HAVE YOU
LIVING IN ANOTHER CITY
WITHOUT A SUPPORT SYSTEM.
I'M BRINGING YOU BACK
TO NEW YORK.
YOU'RE MOVING HOME.