♪♪♪
(TRUCK RUMBLES TO A STOP)
GLENN:
SO, JAKE, WHEN DO I GET TO MEET
THIS GIRLFRIEND OF YOURS?
GIRLFRIEND?
I DON'T HAVE A GIRLFRIEND.
RIGHT, SO WHO HAVE
YOU BEEN TEXTING
SINCE WE LEFT THE HOUSE?
WHA... IT'S...
CLARE:
UH, WE SHOULD PROBABLY
GET GOING.
WE DON'T WANNA BE LATE
ON THE FIRST DAY.
YEAH. SEE YA, DAD.
GLENN:
SEE YA.
♪ I don't know what it is ♪
(TRUCK HORN HONKS)
(LAUGHS)
LONGEST CAR RIDE EVER.
GROSS!
THOSE TWO ARE
STEP SIBLINGS.
SHOULDN'T THAT BE ILLEGAL?
KATIE:
DON'T KNOW, DON'T CARE.
I HAVE A WELCOME BACK SPEECH
TO DELIVER,
AND THANKS TO MY SISTER,
I'M LATE.
MARISOL:
RELAX, MADAME PRESIDENT,
IT'S THE FIRST DAY.
YEAH. THERE'S A 199 MORE LIKE IT
TILL SUMMER.
MAYA, I KNOW YOU WANTED TO GO
TO AN ARTS SCHOOL,
BUT I PROMISE
YOU'LL LIKE IT HERE.
IS THAT AN ORDER?
DON'T WORRY.
YOU'LL HAVE FRIENDS
IN NO TIME.
♪ Yeah, it's all I want,
it's all I want ♪
I DON'T RECOGNIZE A SOUL.
REGRETTING YOUR DECISION
TO SPEND ANOTHER YEAR
IN DEGRASSI BLUE?
FIONA:
THIS IS MY FRESH START.
PEOPLE BARELY KNOW ME.
I'M NOT DECLAN'S FREAKY SISTER,
OR HOLLY J'S SHADOW.
OH, FIONA,
YOU WERE NEVER A FREAK.
(SIGHS)
THE KIDS AT SCHOOL THOUGHT SO.
BUT THIS YEAR
WILL BE DIFFERENT;
I CAN BE ANYBODY.
LIKE HEAD CHEERLEADER?
MAYBE.
REHAB TAUGHT ME
I HAD NO LIMITATIONS...
EXCEPT ALCOHOL.
ALL I NEED ARE
A FEW NEW FRIENDS.
♪ To see it, to see it ♪
♪ To see it again ♪
♪ Oh yes, I will,
yes, I will ♪
(EXHALES, EXCITED)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh... ♪
♪ I can make it through
(Oh-oh-oh...) ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
(I can make it!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
KATIE:
WELCOME BACK, DEGRASSI!
TODAY IS THE DAY
YOU SET THE TONE
FOR THE REST OF THE YEAR;
THE DAY YOU DECIDE
WHO YOU WANT TO BE.
FOR FRESHMEN,
IT'S TIME TO MAKE NEW FRIENDS,
WHETHER IT'S SIGNING UP
FOR A CLUB,
JOINING A TEAM,
OR SAYING HELLO TO THE STRANGER
SITTING NEXT YOU
IN SCIENCE CLASS.
HEY, FIONA.
HOW WAS YOUR SUMMER?
TRANSFORMATIVE.
HOPE YOU DIDN'T CHANGE
TOO MUCH!
MINE WAS PRETTY NORMAL.
UH... I WENT-
FIONA:
I'M GONNA GRAB A SEAT.
HOW ABOUT RIGHT HERE?
IMOGEN, I WOULD LOVE,
LOVE, TO SIT WITH YOU,
BUT I UH...
PROMISED THAT GIRL.
MARISOL:
AND, UH, DON'T YOU DARE
DITCH ME. (CHUCKLES)
(AWKWARD CHUCKLE)
BYE.
FIONA:
THANKS.
MARISOL.
NO PROBLEM.
WHO WANTS TO BE STUCK
WITH THAT LOSER?
ANNOUNCEMENT:
REMINDER TO GRADE 9
BAND STUDENTS:
YOUR INSTRUMENTS ARE PROPERTY
OF DEGRASSI.
PLEASE TREAT THEM
WITH CARE.
HEY, CONNOR.
WELCOME BACK.
HOW WAS YOUR PROGRAM?
IT WAS HELPFUL.
THANKS FOR ASKING.
UM, SHOULDN'T YOU BE
SITTING WITH ALLI?
I MEAN, YOU ALWAYS SIT
WITH ALLI.
NOT SINCE SHE TRIED
TO STEAL MY BOYFRIEND.
DID SHE SUCCEED?
NO, OF COURSE NOT;
HE'S NOT THAT SHALLOW.
THEN WHO'S
YOUR BEST FRIEND NOW?
WELL,
I GUESS IT'S JAKE.
OH. OKAY.
(LOW HUM OF CHATTER)
(BELL RINGS)
MAYA:
(SIGHS, FRUSTRATED)
WHERE ARE YOU,
MUSIC CLASSROOM?
ZIG:
UM, IF YOU COULD SAVE A LIFE,
WOULD YOU?
UM, I THINK YOU HAVE ME
CONFUSED WITH SOMEONE ELSE.
JUST PRETEND
YOU'RE MY GIRLFRIEND.
WHAT?
I'LL EXPLAIN IN A MINUTE,
JUST...
UM, OKAY.
I CALLED YOU, LIKE,
TEN TIMES LAST NIGHT!
YOU WERE WITH BETHANY,
WEREN'T YOU?
(GASPS)
YOU... YOU SCOUNDREL.
SCOUNDREL?
HEY, IT'S NOT LIKE
I GOT A REHEARSAL.
WELL, UH...
THANKS FOR THE COVER.
I'M ZIG NOVAK.
HI.
OH. UM, I'M MAYA.
MATLIN.
ANY CHANCE YOU KNOW WHERE
THE MUSIC ROOM IS?
I'VE BEEN LOOKING
FOR THE ART CLASS
SINCE THE BELL RANG.
OKAY, WELL, I GUESS
I'LL SEE YOU AROUND.
ZIG:
UM, HEY.
I HEARD ABOUT THIS PLACE
CALLED THE DOT,
AND, UM, I WAS GONNA GO
CHECK IT OUT AFTER SCHOOL.
YOU SHOULD COME.
I MEAN, IF...
IF YOU'D WANT TO.
MAYBE I WILL.
'KAY.
(SIGHS)
THEORY OF RELATIVITY.
UGH!
I AM NOT EINSTEIN.
DON'T WORRY.
MY FRIENDS WHO TOOK
THIS CLASS LAST YEAR
SAID IT'S A BREEZE
AS LONG AS YOU DO
THE ASSIGNMENTS.
USEFUL ADVICE.
ONE OF THE ADVANTAGES
OF OFFERING A SEAT
TO A STRANGER.
STRANGER? YOU?
OH WOW,
THAT'S A JOKE!
YOU'RE KIND OF FAMOUS.
OH NO.
WITH ALL THE RUMOURS,
I HAD NO IDEA
WHAT TO EXPECT.
SHUT-IN SOCIALITE...
STUCK-UP SNOB...
LIPSTICK LESBIAN...
WELL,
THE LAST ONE'S TRUE.
EXCEPT I ONLY WEAR
LIP GLOSS.
GREAT!
THERE'S ENOUGH COMPETITION
FOR THE LIMITED MALE TALENT
AT DEGRASSI.
I'M JUST GLAD
YOU'RE NOT A WEIRDO.
KATIE:
DON'T WORRY.
THAT'S MARE'S ATTEMPT
AT A COMPLIMENT.
(LAUGHS)
THANKS FOR SAVING ME
A SEAT.
I'M KATIE.
YES, OUR FEARLESS PRESIDENT.
GREAT SPEECH.
MARISOL:
AND I'M VICE!
WE'RE BFFS!
HEY, DO YOU GUYS HAVE
LUNCH PLANS?
WE HAVE A STUDENT
COUNCIL MEETING.
FIONA:
WELL, WHAT ABOUT TONIGHT?
I KNOW IT'S LAST MINUTE,
SO IF YOU ALREADY
HAVE PLANS THEN...
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
UH... MAYBE HAVE SOME PEOPLE
OVER TO MY LOFT.
WE COULD GET IT CATERED,
MAYBE A DJ.
MY MOM WILL FOOT THE BILL.
AND THE GUEST LIST?
IS STILL A WORK
IN PROGRESS.
I'D NEED YOUR ADVICE,
OF COURSE.
YOU GUYS IN?
A CATERED PARTY
WITH A DJ?
HELLS YEAH!
(GIRLS LAUGH)
WELL, GREAT.
I'LL SET EVERYTHING UP.
MS. OH:
AND BEFORE YOU KNOW IT,
WE'LL ALL BE MAKING
BEAUTIFUL MUSIC TOGETHER.
NEXT ORDER OF BUSINESS:
CHOOSING OUR INSTRUMENTS.
I'M SO SORRY
I'M LATE.
I COULDN'T FIND
THE CLASSROOM.
AND YOU ARE...?
MAYA MATLIN?
CLASS, WE HAVE
AN AWARD-WINNING ARTIST
IN OUR MIDST.
MAYA, I ASSUME
YOU WANT THE CELLO.
SURE. THANKS.
TORI:
HE'S NOT IN THIS CLASS?
THEN WHERE IS HE?
TRISTAN:
RELAX.
I'LL GET INTEL
ON ZIG'S WHEREABOUTS.
OH, ZIG NOVAK?
HE HAS ART NOW.
IS HE A FRIEND OF YOURS?
ZIG NOVAK IS NOT A FRIEND.
TORI:
HE'S A JERK WHO USES GIRLS,
THEN BREAKS THEIR HEARTS.
IF YOU'RE SMART,
YOU'LL STAY AWAY.
TRISTAN:
FAR, FAR AWAY.
MS. OH:
TRISTAN, RIGHT?
UH, WE NEED A VOLUNTEER
FOR THE FRENCH HORN.
TRISTAN:
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
FIONA:
SUSHI FOR TWENTY.
YOUR USUAL SPREAD
IS ALWAYS PERFECT,
MR. ICHIRO.
IT'S GONNA BE A GREAT PARTY.
THANKS!
A PARTY?
I GUESS MY INVITE
GOT LOST IN CYBERSPACE.
UH, IT'S JUST A SMALL
GET TOGETHER.
DIDN'T THINK
YOU'D BE INTERESTED.
YOU THOUGHT RIGHT;
I HAVE SPINNING CLASS TONIGHT.
SPINNING CLASS?
STARTED EXERCISING
THIS SUMMER.
AND ALTHOUGH
I WOULD RATHER SWEAT
THAN ATTEND YOUR SOIREE,
I'M SURE THAT IMOGEN
WOULD LOVE TO GO.
IMOGEN:
THAT'S OKAY, ELI.
I'M SURE I'M NOT INVITED
TO FIONA'S FETE.
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
FIONA WOULD NEVER
EXCLUDE YOU.
IT'S JUST A FEW
CLOSE FRIENDS.
BUT, OF COURSE,
IMOGEN IS WELCOME.
FOR REALSIES?!
WANNA KNOW A SECRET?
I'VE BEEN HOPING
WE'D BE FRIENDS
SINCE WE DID
THAT PLAY TOGETHER.
YOU HAVE?
IMOGEN:
MOST GIRLS AT SCHOOL
TREAT ME LIKE CRAP.
YOU PROBABLY
COULDN'T IMAGINE.
YOU'D BE SURPRISED.
WHEN I FIRST CAME
TO DEGRASSI,
I COULDN'T MAKE A FRIEND
IF MY LIFE DEPENDED ON IT.
FIONA COYNE?
FIONA:
YEAH, IT WAS... SO LONELY,
I STARTED DRINKING.
A LOT.
I SPENT THE SUMMER
IN REHAB,
AND THAT'S WHERE I DECIDED
THINGS WOULD BE DIFFERENT;
THAT THIS WOULD BE
THE BEST YEAR EVER.
AND NOW YOU'RE FRIENDS
WITH THE MOST POPULAR GIRLS
AT SCHOOL.
FRIEND-LY.
I STILL HAVE A LONG WAY
TO GO.
MAYBE I SHOULD GO
TO REHAB.
(LAUGHING)
LISTEN, WHY DON'T YOU
COME OVER BEFORE?
WE CAN GET READY
TOGETHER.
(DRAMATICALLY)
SOMEBODY PINCH ME!
OR NOT.
(LAUGHS)
(ELI AND FIONA CHUCKLE)
DREW:
FEELS LIKE YESTERDAY
WE WERE UP AT YOUR CABIN.
LIFE'S NOT SO BAD
IN THE CITY.
LIVING WITH
YOUR GIRLFRIEND
MIGHT HAVE SOMETHING
TO DO WITH THAT.
OWEN:
SO HOW MANY ROOMS
YOU GUYS DONE IT IN?
(LAUGHING)
CLARE:
IT IS SO NICE TO SEE
A FRIENDLY FACE
AFTER A MORNING OF DEFLECTING
DEATH STARES
FROM ALLI AND JENNA.
OWEN:
OH, HI, CLARE.
UM, JAKE WAS JUST UPDATING US
ON YOUR LIVING ARRANGEMENTS.
DON'T YOU GUYS HAVE
SOMEWHERE TO BE?
DREW:
UH, YEAH,
WE'LL, UH...
CATCH UP WITH YOU,
LATER.
OWEN: I GOT YA, BRO.
DREW: THANKS, MAN.
OKAY,
WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
WELL, THE GUYS THINK THAT
NOW WE'RE LIVING TOGETHER,
WE'RE DOING
OTHER THINGS TOGETHER.
YOU MEAN SEX.
I DIDN'T SAY WE WERE.
BUT YOU MUST'VE THOUGHT
ABOUT IT.
I KNOW YOU'RE NOT READY,
AND PROBABLY WON'T BE
FOR A LONG TIME, SO...
WE SHOULD TALK.
OKAY... OKAY.
UH, HOW ABOUT TONIGHT?
SOUNDS GOOD.
FIONA:
SO WHEN IT COMES TO PARTIES,
THE BIGGER,
THE BETTER, RIGHT?
WRONG!
WE SHOULD KEEP
THE GUEST LIST EXCLUSIVE.
ONLY THE BEST
DEGRASSI HAS TO OFFER.
SO... BOYS?
DREW, OF COURSE,
OWEN...
MAYBE A FEW OTHER
FOOTBALL GUYS?
WE'LL NEED MORE GIRLS
TO EVEN OUT THE NUMBERS.
FIONA:
RAMONA SEEMS NICE,
AND, YOU KNOW,
MAYBE IMOGEN?
IMOGEN?
SERIOUSLY?
I THOUGHT MAYBE
IF WE GAVE HER A CHANCE-
SHE'D STOP DRESSING
LIKE A CIRCUS PERFORMER?
(GIRLS LAUGH)
YOU ALREADY INVITED HER,
DIDN'T YOU?
SHE OVERHEARD ME
ON THE PHONE.
I GOT BACKED
INTO A CORNER.
LET'S JUST CONSIDER IT
A SOCIAL EXPERIMENT.
MARISOL:
WELL, AT LEAST WE WON'T HAVE
TO WORRY ABOUT ENTERTAINMENT.
KATIE:
SORRY I'M LATE.
STUDENT COUNCIL STUFF.
THAT'S OKAY.
(TYPING)
OOH!
ZIG NOVAK IS CUTE.
DOES MY LITTLE SISTER
HAVE A CRUSH?
WE'RE JUST FRIENDS -
BARELY.
HE'S THE ONLY DECENT PERSON
I MET TODAY.
SO THEN
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
THIS GIRL IN MY BAND CLASS
THINKS HE'S THE DEVIL.
SHE SOUNDS JEALOUS.
OF ME?
KATIE:
HARD TO BELIEVE,
ISN'T IT?
WHEN I STARTED HANGING OUT
WITH DREW,
ALL THESE GIRLS TOLD ME
HE WAS A STUPID JOCK
WHO ONLY CARED ABOUT SE-
SPORTS.
WELL, ISN'T HE?
NO, HE'S THE SWEETEST GUY
IN THE WORLD
AND I WOULDN'T KNOW THAT
IF I LISTENED TO ALL THE GOSSIP.
SO YOU THINK ZIG'S
PROBABLY OKAY?
I THINK YOU SHOULD FIND OUT
FOR YOURSELF.
OKAY.
KATIE:
WELL, WE BETTER GET
A MOVE ON,
I HAVE A PARTY
TO GET READY FOR.
AND IF ZIG PULLS
ANY FUNNY BUSINESS,
TELL HIM YOUR SISTER'S
SCHOOL PREZ
AND I COULD MAKE
HIS LIFE HELL.
FIONA:
OH, DON'T PUT
THE SUSHI OUT YET!
I'M TRYING TO MAKE FRIENDS
NOT POISON THEM.
(DOORBELL BUZZES)
TA-DA!
WOW! (LAUGHS)
THAT IS QUITE
A DRESS!
IMOGEN:
YOU LIKE?
FIONA:
I LOVE.
BUT, YOU KNOW, I HAVE A DRESS
THAT WOULD LOOK EVEN BETTER.
TAKE A LOOK.
OH, UM...
THAT DRESS
IS VERY ELEGANT.
IMAGINE IT
WITH YOUR HAIR DOWN.
IMOGEN:
WHAT'S WRONG WITH MY HAIR?
NOTHING.
I LOVE YOUR HAIR.
I WAS JUST THINKING
ABOUT THE DRESS.
I KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TRYING TO DO.
YOU'RE TRYING
TO CHANGE ME
SO I DON'T EMBARRASS YOU
AT YOUR PARTY.
THE DRESS WOULD BE
ONE LESS THING
FOR PEOPLE TO MAKE FUN OF...
AND SOME OF THE GIRLS
I INVITED
WERE A LITTLE SURPRISED
THAT YOUR NAME
WAS ON THE GUEST LIST.
I DON'T CARE
WHAT PEOPLE THINK.
BUT IF YOU DID,
WE COULD HAVE
A LOT OF FUN THIS YEAR -
ALL OF US,
TOGETHER.
THEN LET'S SEE
IF THE DRESS FITS.
GREAT.
YOU CAN CHANGE
IN HERE.
♪ Turn your smile on ♪
♪ Turn smile on bright ♪
(APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS)
(CLOCK TICKS)
WHAT?
I WAS JUST...
I WAS JUST WAITING.
FOR...?
UH, THE TALK
THAT YOU MENTIONED EARLIER,
ABOUT BEING READY FOR...
SEX?
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
I THINK IT COULD BE GREAT.
I USED TO THINK
I WOULDN'T BE READY
UNTIL I WAS MARRIED.
BUT THEN AFTER
MY PARENT'S DIVORCE,
MARRIAGE SEEMED LESS...
PERMANENT?
I FEEL CLOSER TO YOU
THAN I HAVE TO ANYONE.
AND IF SEX IS SOMETHING
I WANT,
WHY WAIT?
SOUNDS LOGICAL TO ME.
SO...
DO YOU WANT TO...?
OH, TONIGHT?
NO, WE HAVE TO...
WE HAVE TO MAKE SURE
WE'RE PREPARED.
WHAT, YOU MEAN, LIKE,
PROTECTION?
NO. I MEAN, LIKE,
EMOTIONALLY.
SURE. I MEAN,
WHATEVER YOU NEED.
YEAH, I'M HERE.
OKAY. GREAT.
I'LL GO GET
THE MAGAZINE.
PERFECT.
♪ You gotta get it ♪
♪ Oh, go out and get it ♪
♪ Yeah, you gotta get it,
get it, get it ♪
♪ Oh, oh-oh oh ♪
♪ You gotta get it ♪
♪ Oh, go out and get it ♪
♪ Yeah, you gotta get it,
get it, get it ♪
MARISOL:
LOOKS LIKE WE'VE FOUND
OUR CHAIR
FOR THE SOCIAL COMMITTEE.
I'D SAY IT'S A LOCK.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU PUT THIS TOGETHER
IN A DAY!
MARISOL:
OH MY GOD.
IS THAT IMOGEN?
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYS)
FIONA:
DOESN'T SHE LOOK GORGEOUS?
TOTALLY!
(QUICKLY)
IF THAT'S YOUR TYPE.
NICE SAVE.
IMOGEN:
GREETINGS AND SALUTATIONS.
SO I THINK WE SHOULD
PLAY A GAME
TO GET THE PARTY STARTED.
IMOGEN:
WHAT ABOUT CHARADES?
OH... MAYBE AFTER THAT
WE CAN BRAID EACH OTHER'S HAIR.
(DERISIVE LAUGHTER)
IMOGEN WAS JUST KIDDING.
RIGHT, IMOGEN?
YEAH. TOTALLY.
WE SHOULD PLAY ANYTHING
BUT CHARADES.
MARISOL:
UH-HUH... LIKE WHAT?
TRUTH OR DARE?
DREW AND OWEN:
(SNAP FINGERS)
DOWN!
(FIONA CHUCKLES)
SO WHAT'S THE PURPOSE
OF THIS QUIZ?
TO DETERMINE
IF WE'RE EMOTIONALLY READY.
OKAY, LET'S START.
"DESCRIBE YOUR FEELINGS
TOWARDS YOUR PARTNER."
MY PARTNER?
THAT'S ME.
OH. OKAY.
UM, CAN YOU REPEAT
THE QUESTION?
JAKE, THIS ISN'T A TEST.
THERE'S NO RIGHT ANSWER.
RIGHT. OKAY, UM...
WELL,
I THINK YOU'RE COOL.
AND?
KISSABLE.
COME ON,
THIS IS IMPORTANT.
DO YOU CONSIDER ME
YOUR SOUL MATE?
SOUL MATE?
WHO MAKES UP THIS STUFF?
BUT YES, YES,
I SUPPOSE I DO.
GOOD.
UH, WHAT DO YOU WANT OUR FIRST
SEXUAL EXPERIENCE TO BE LIKE?
SEXY?
JAKE, THINK.
WELL, YOU SAID
THERE WAS NO RIGHT ANSWER.
THERE ISN'T,
BUT IT DOESN'T FEEL LIKE
YOU'RE TAKING THIS SERIOUSLY.
THINK OF OUR FIRST TIME TOGETHER
AND DESCRIBE IT TO ME.
WELL, UM...
YOU KNOW, I...
IT WOULD BE WITH YOU,
OBVIOUSLY - OBVIOUSLY!
UM, I THINK
IT WOULD BE GREAT
IF IT WAS IN A BED.
AND EMOTIONALLY?
HOW DO YOU WANT TO FEEL?
SATISFIED.
SATISFIED?
I DON'T KNOW, CLARE.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO SAY?
HOW YOU FEEL!
LIKE THESE QUESTIONS
ARE STUPID.
(SIGHS)
HOW ELSE AM I SUPPOSED
TO FIGURE OUT
IF I'M READY FOR SEX?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU JUST...
YOU JUST FEEL IT.
THEN I GUESS I DON'T,
AND IT WAS A MISTAKE
THINKING I DID.
♪♪♪
♪ I saw it written
in a magazine ♪
♪ That there's a one
in five chance ♪
♪ That you might make my heart
a mess  ♪
ZIG:
HEY!
MAYA:
OH!
SORRY, I'M LATE.
HAVE YOU BEEN WAITING LONG?
NO. NO,
I JUST GOT HERE.
IT'S PRETTY BUSY.
YEAH. OH!
THOSE GUYS ARE LEAVING.
HEY, SORRY, NINERS.
THIS TABLE'S TAKEN.
ZIG:
OH. OKAY.
THAT'S OKAY.
I LIKE STANDING.
(LAUGHS)
UM... SO,
HOW WAS YOUR FIRST DAY?
DID YOU MEET
ANY COOL PEOPLE?
A FEW.
WELL, I MET SOME KIDS
FROM YOUR JUNIOR HIGH.
OH YEAH? WHO?
TORI AND TRISTAN.
OH...
YEAH, THEY KINDA
HATE YOUR GUTS.
UH, YEAH.
CAN I EXPLAIN WHY?
(EXHALES)
OKAY.
WELL, UH, YOU STAY PUT.
I'LL GO SCORE US
A TABLE.
OWEN:
OKAY, UH... TRUTH.
IF YOU COULD KISS
ONE GIRL IN THIS ROOM,
WHO WOULD IT BE?
OWEN:
JUST ONE?
ALL RIGHT, UM...
THAT WOULD PROBABLY
HAVE TO BE YOU.
WHADDYA SAY?
UH, TEMPTING BUT...
IT'S YOUR TURN.
OWEN:
ALL RIGHT.
(DECIDING WHO TO CHOOSE)
MM, MM, MM...
YOU, TRUTH OR DARE?
DREW:
GIRLS ALWAYS PICK TRUTH.
DARE.
OH! OKAY.
OOH!
CHUG THAT.
WHAT IS IT?
THIS IS TEQUILA.
BROUGHT IT FROM HOME.
(CLUCKING LIKE A CHICKEN)
BAWK-BAWK-BAWK.
(EVERYONE LAUGHS)
LEAVE FIONA ALONE.
SHE'S AN ALCOHOLIC!
AN ALCOHOLIC?
MARISOL:
THAT'S NOT FUNNY,
IMOGEN!
YEAH, IMOGEN,
WHY WOULD YOU MAKE THAT UP?
OWEN:
WELL, IF IT'S NOT TRUE,
CHUG! CHUG! CHUG!
(EVERYONE STARTS CHANTING)
SO I CAN HURL AT MY OWN PARTY?
NO THANK YOU.
GUYS, THIS IS THE FIRST WEEK
BACK AT SCHOOL.
WE SHOULD DO
SOMETHING MEMORABLE.
MARISOL:
LIKE WHAT?
A SENIOR PRANK!
SNEAK INTO THE SCHOOL.
DO SOMETHING TO LEAVE
OUR MARK.
SHOW EVERYONE WHAT THIS YEAR'S
GRAD CLASS IS CAPABLE OF.
KATIE'S GOT
A SIDE-DOOR KEY
FOR SOME STUDENT
COUNCIL STUFF.
COME ON...
(PARTY GUESTS
SHOUT ENCOURAGEMENT)
FINE.
TO DEGRASSI WE GO!
(PARTY GUESTS CHEER)
YOU COMING?
♪ You won't regret it ♪
♪ When you want it,
you get it ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm sugardaddy's
little girl ♪
♪ Sugar, sugar, sugar ♪
♪ I'm sugardaddy's girl ♪
♪ Sugar, sugar, sugar... ♪
(FOIL RUSTLES)
IMAGINE THE LOOK
ON PEOPLE'S FACES
WHEN THEY SEE THIS.
MARISOL:
WE'LL BE LEGENDS!
EVERYONE WILL BE TALKING
ABOUT WHAT WE DID.
WITHOUT KNOWING
IT WAS US.
IMOGEN:
THIS IS MAGICAL -
THE EMPTINESS, DARKNESS,
THE ECHOING HALLWAYS...
I WANNA EXPLORE.
WHO'S COMING?
IMOGEN, THAT'S NOT
A GOOD IDEA.
WE SHOULD STICK TOGETHER.
IMOGEN:
WHO KNOWS WHAT SECRETS
THE SCHOOL HIDES AT NIGHT?
LET'S GO EXPLORE,
IMOGEN.
DON'T WORRY.
WE WON'T GO FAR!
AFTER YOU.
WE COULDN'T HAVE STARTED
THIS YEAR OFF
WITH A BIGGER BANG.
I'M GLAD WE'RE GETTING
TO HANG OUT.
MOI AUSSI.
DREW:
GUYS, GUYS, GUYS!
CLEANING STAFF
IN THE BUILDING!
DREW: LET'S GO!
OWEN: LET'S GO!
FIONA:
IMOGEN AND MARISOL!
KATIE: SHOOT! I'LL CALL MARE.
MARISOL: NO NEED. I'M HERE.
WHERE'S IMOGEN?
MARISOL:
I DON'T KNOW!
SHE SKIPPED OFF DOWN THE HALL!
I TOLD HER NOT TO.
OWEN:
WE GOTTA GO!
KATIE:
MARE, FIONA - VAMANOS!
WE NEED TO FIND IMOGEN.
KATIE:
WE DON'T HAVE TIME.
COME ON!
(SIGHS, TORN)
GUESS SHE'S ON HER OWN.