♪♪♪
YOU'RE REALLY MILKING
THAT LIMP.
MY FOOT IS STILL BROKEN,
AND I'D CALL IT
MORE OF A STRUT.
DON'T LOOK NOW,
BUT YOUR EX IS ON THE PROWL.
I'D SAY "RUN", BUT...
I'LL BE FINE.
CLARE EDWARDS.
I WAS HOPING
TO RUN INTO YOU.
I GOT A JOB
ON THE SCHOOL PAPER.
CONGRATULATIONS.
CLARE:
THANKS.
BUT THAT'S NOT WHAT
I WANTED TO TELL YOU.
WHOA, SOUNDS SERIOUS.
CLARE:
I HAVE TO WRITE AN ARTICLE
ON THE SCHOOL PLAY.
AND YOU NEED TO INTERVIEW
THE PLAYWRIGHT.
CLARE:
IF YOU SAY NO,
I'LL UNDERSTAND.
I'LL GIVE YOU
A KILLER ARTICLE.
(RELIEVED SIGH)
THANKS, ELI.
WELL PLAYED.
THANKS TO YOUR
MAGIC PILLS?
THEY'RE MY ANTI-ANXIETY
MEDS.
YEAH, SO WHAT EXACTLY
IS WRONG WITH YOU AGAIN?
(SIGHS)
THE DOCTORS HAVEN'T
FIGURED THAT OUT YET.
BUT UNTIL THEY DO,
I HAVE THESE.
(GULPS)
I CAN HANDLE ANYTHING.
EVEN A HEAD TO HEAD
WITH THE EX?
CLARE REJECTED ME,
SO I'M GONNA GET OVER HER.
HOW?
THE PLAY'S THE THING!
ALL I HAVE TO DO
IS DELIVER A HIT.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(CAR RUMBLES)
(BIRDS CHIRP)
(SEATBELT CLICKS)
YOU KNOW MA,
MY BIRTHDAY'S COMING SOON.
AND I WAS THINKING
YOU, ME, AND PA...
WE COULD CELEBRATE!
WE'LL SEE.
IN A FEW MONTHS,
I LEAVE FOR UNIVERSITY.
ARE YOU GONNA FREEZE ME OUT
UNTIL I GO?
FREEZE YOU OUT?
WHERE DO YOU GET
THESE IDEAS?
THERE MUST BE SOMETHING
I CAN DO.
MRS. ANDOPOLOUS' DAUGHTER
WOULD LIKE TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT SPORTS SCHOLARSHIPS.
BUT I TOLD HER THAT
YOU'RE PROBABLY TOO BUSY.
NO, NO,
I'D LOVE TO TALK TO HER.
I'LL SET SOMETHING UP
FOR TONIGHT.
TONIGHT?
SHE'S A GOOD LOOKING GIRL,
THAT ATHENA.
UNLESS YOU HAVE PLANS.
I'LL CANCEL THEM.
YOU'RE A GOOD BOY,
RILEY.
ANYTHING FOR YOU, MA.
THANKS.
MS. DAWES:
CONFLICT!
ALL GREAT STORIES
ARE BORN OF CONFLICT.
THE HIGHER THE STAKES,
THE GREATER THE DRAMA.
NOW I WANT YOU
TO DIVIDE INTO GROUPS,
DISCUSS,
WHAT WERE THEIR GOALS?
FRAU DIRECTOR,
I'VE GOT IDEAS FOR CASTING,
PICTURE THIS:
HEATHER POULETTE
AS THE TROLL QUEEN.
CART BEFORE HORSE,
GOLDSWORTHY.
YOU PITCHED A CONCEPT.
COSTUMES, CASTING,
CRAFT SERVICES,
WE CAN'T MOVE FORWARD
'TIL WE HAVE THE SCRIPT.
WHICH WILL BE EXACTLY
THE SAME
AS THE CONCEPT I PITCHED.
ABOUT THE CONCEPT.
I HAVE A FEW CONCERNS.
WHOA, WE ARE NOT TWEAKING
THE CONCEPT,
IT'S PERFECT!
HONESTLY,
A POST APOCALYPTIC PLAY
ABOUT THE LAST MAN ON EARTH
SEARCHING FOR A REASON
TO GO ON?
IT'S A RUMINATION
ON THE HUMAN CONDITION!
A PARABLE FOR LONELINESS
IN THE MODERN ERA!
IT'S DEPRESSING.
THAT'S ONE OPINION.
LET'S SEE WHAT DAWES THINKS.
(BIRDS CHIRP)
TAKE HIM?
I'M LATE FOR SCHOOL.
I REEK LIKE FERMENTED
SPIT UP!
JUST LET ME TAKE
A SHOWER.
NEED HELP?
I'M PRETTY GOOD WITH
A SCRUB BRUSH, YOU KNOW.
VERY FUNNY.
FIVE MINUTES.
IT'S GREAT YOU'RE
OFF TONIGHT.
YOUR MOM'S WORKING HER USUAL
TUESDAY DOUBLE SHIFT,
SO AT LAST WE'LL HAVE
SOME ALONE TIME!
WE CAN FINALLY GET THROUGH
ALL THAT LAUNDRY.
I CAN'T TONIGHT, WORK.
I THOUGHT YOU HAD
TUESDAYS OFF.
YEAH, BUT THE OTHER
DISHWASHER'S SICK.
WE NEED THE MONEY, RIGHT?
I'M ALONE ALL DAY,
WHY NOT ALL NIGHT, TOO?
(DOOR SLAMS)
THEN OUR HERO, HOPING THAT
HE'S NOT THE ONLY VOICE
LEFT IN THE UNIVERSE,
WAITS.
HE BITES THE LAST
REMAINING APPLE,
WATCHING AS IT SLOWLY,
SLOWLY, BROWNS.
LIGHTS FADE OUT...
THE END.
MS. DAWES: IT'S BLEAK.
ELI: MM-HMM.
MS. DAWES: IT'S DREARY.
ELI: OH, YEAH.
IT'S NOT...
YOUR STRONGEST WORK.
IT'S A RUMINATION
ON THE HUMAN CONDITION!
TRUE, BUT UM,
IT LACKS THE NUANCE
THAT I'VE COME
TO EXPECT FROM YOU.
WHAT DOES CLARE THINK
OF THIS CONCEPT?
I WOULDN'T KNOW.
WE BROKE UP.
MS. DAWES:
OH, THAT-THAT'S TOO BAD.
ELI...
I'M OVER IT.
MAYBE YOU COULD FIND
SOMEONE ELSE
TO BRAINSTORM
A NEW CONCEPT WITH?
A NEW CONCEPT?!
MS. DAWES: YEAH.
I'M HALFWAY THROUGH
THE SCRIPT!
MS. DAWES:
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY,
WRITING IS REWRITING.
(SIGHS)
GODSPEED, ELI.
(PANTING)
HEY, DID YOU GET MY TEXT?
SIMPSON'S HEALTH INITIATIVE?
PRETTY SWEET HE CAME TO US
TO GET THE WHOLE SCHOOL
EXERCISING!
YEAH, THE ONLY STUDENT TO EVER
GET A SPORTS SCHOLARSHIP,
AND THE HANDSOMEST KICKER
ON THE FOOTBALL TEAM.
WHO ELSE WOULD HE GO TO?
GOOD POINT, BUT...
HOW EXACTLY DO WE GET
EVERYBODY DOING
10,000 STEPS A DAY?
ZANE:
BEATS ME!
HOW ABOUT UH... WE BRAINSTORM
TONIGHT AT MY PLACE?
UH...YEAH,
I CAN'T TONIGHT.
BUT WE HAD PLANS
TO HANG OUT.
MY MOM ASKED ME
FOR A FAVOUR.
SHE'S TALKING
TO YOU AGAIN?
IN FULL SENTENCES
FOR THE FIRST TIME
SINCE I TRIED
COMING OUT TO HER.
WELL, I GUESS I CAN'T BE
THAT MAD AT YOU THEN,
FOR... DITCHING ME.
I'LL MAKE IT UP TO YOU!
(LAUGHS)
YEAH.
ADAM:
AND NOW, A SPECIAL DEDICATION
TO MY CO-HOST DAVE TURNER,
WHO'S AT HOME
WITH THE SNIFFLES.
GET WELL, BIG GUY.
SORRY DUDE,
I'D LOVE TO HELP,
BUT RADIO'S A CRUEL
MISTRESS.
WHO ELSE AM I SUPPOSED
TO BRAINSTORM IDEAS
FOR THE PLAY WITH?
CLARE.
THE INTERVIEW!
OH, I'M SO NOT READY!
UH, DIDN'T YOU ALREADY
TAKE ONE OF THOSE TODAY?
I CAN TAKE UP TO THREE
A DAY.
AND RIGHT NOW,
I NEED ONE.
DON'T WORRY,
YOU THRIVE UNDER PRESSURE.
JUST... MAKE IT UP.
(KNOCKING)
READY FOR OUR INTERVIEW?
OF COURSE!
LET'S GET STARTED.
SHOULD WE GO SOMEWHERE?
UH, WHY DON'T WE DO IT
RIGHT HERE?
ADAM:
I'M ON AIR
IN TWO MINUTES.
MAKE IT QUICK.
PERFECT.
OKAY.
SO...
WHAT'S THE PLAY ABOUT?
IT'S UM, SUSPENSEFUL.
UH, TEAR JERKING.
UH, DAZZLING.
I'M SURE IT IS,
BUT I REALLY NEED TO REPORT
WHAT THE PLAY IS ABOUT.
LIKE PLOT, STORYLINE?
AND I'D LOVE TO SHARE
THAT WITH YOU,
BUT I-I REALLY HAVE
TO GET BACK TO WRITING.
UM, FIONA'S REALLY IMPATIENT
FOR A FIRST DRAFT,
SO WE'LL-WE'LL TALK LATER.
(LOUD CLATTER)
ELI:
UH...HEH.
♪♪♪
♪ Whoa I'm still
gonna find you ♪
♪ I'm still thinking
About what went wrong ♪
TWO WATERS.
THANK YOU.
(DISHES CLATTER)
HEY, LIGHTEN UP THERE,
PARTNER!
(LAUGHS)
JENNA WANTED ME
TO GET A JOB,
BUT NOW THAT I HAVE ONE,
SHE COMPLAINS I'M WORKING
ALL THE TIME.
IT'S LIKE I CAN'T DO
ANYTHING RIGHT.
WELL, I CAN'T FIX
THAT PROBLEM,
BUT I CAN TAKE
YOUR MIND OFF IT.
HOW?
BY PLAYING A LITTLE GAME.
LOOK AT THAT COUPLE
OVER THERE.
IT'S A FIRST DATE.
THEY MET ONLINE,
HE DOES NOT LOOK ANYTHING
LIKE HIS PROFILE PIC,
BUT... SHE'S FARSIGHTED,
SO IT MIGHT WORK OUT.
(LAUGHS)
YOUR TURN.
JUAN:
KC!
IT'S PILING UP
BACK THERE!
KC:
YEAH, I'M ON IT.
(LAUGHS)
THANK YOU.
SO I'M THINKING
OF T.U. SOME DAY.
THEY HAVE A REALLY GREAT
SWIM PROGRAM.
HAVE YOU CONSIDERED SCHOOLS
SOUTH OF THE BORDER?
I HEAR THEY'RE
COMPETITIVE.
HEY, I GOT IN.
CUTE, AND MODEST.
I SHOULD'VE AGREED
TO THIS SET UP AGES AGO.
I SHOULD'VE KNOWN.
WHAT?
THIS IS A DATE,
ISN'T IT?
OH... YOUR MOM
DIDN'T TELL YOU?
I HOPE YOU DON'T MIND.
TO BE HONEST,
THINGS WITH ME ARE A LITTLE...
COMPLICATED RIGHT NOW.
YOU'RE IN A RELATIONSHIP.
YEAH.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO PASS ON
THAT INFO TO YOUR MOM.
SO, WHAT'S SO COMPLICATED
WITH THE GIRLFRIEND?
CAN YOU KEEP A SECRET
FROM OUR FAMILIES?
MY LIPS ARE SEALED.
MY GIRLFRIEND
IS A... BOYFRIEND.
YOU'RE GAY?
AND YOU HAVEN'T COME OUT?
I TRIED TO,
TO MY MOM.
BUT EVER SINCE THEN,
WE'VE BARELY SPOKEN.
TRADITIONAL PARENTS?
THEY JUST DON'T GET IT.
I DON'T WANNA SPEND THE LAST
FEW MONTHS BEFORE COLLEGE
FIGHTING WITH THEM.
MY FOLKS WOULDN'T EVEN
LET ME LOOK AT A BOY
'TIL I TURNED SIXTEEN.
SO WHAT'D YOU DO?
I'D INTRODUCE BOYFRIENDS
AS STUDY BUDDIES.
THEY'D COME OVER,
DO HOMEWORK,
HANG OUT IN MY ROOM.
AND YOUR FOLKS
NEVER CAUGHT ON?
THEY SEE WHAT
THEY WANNA SEE.
I'M THEIR OBEDIENT
DAUGHTER.
AND I'M THEIR STRAIGHT
SPORTS STAR.
(LAUGHS)
BEST OF BOTH WORLDS,
RIGHT?
(STAFF CHATTER)
WHERE YOU GOING,
DISH PIG?
HOME.
(LAUGHS)
STAY A BIT.
KC:
CAN'T, I'VE GOT LOTS
TO TAKE CARE OF.
(SIGHS)
LITTLE SECRET.
ONCE WE CLOSE,
THIS PLACE?
OURS!
PLUG IT IN,
CRANK IT UP!
(LAUGHS)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU'RE ALWAYS IN SUCH
A RUSH TO GET HOME,
YOU MISS THE AFTER HOUR
CLEAN UP PARTY.
COME ON,
GET OVER HERE,
AND DANCE!
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYS)
(STAFF LAUGH AND HOLLER)
OKAY, MAYBE FOR JUST
A LITTLE BIT.
♪ Get loose ♪
♪ Everybody on the floor ♪
♪ Leave your trouble
at the door ♪
♪ Get loose ♪
(FIST THUDS)
(KEYS CLACK)
♪ There was a house
halfway 'round the world ♪
♪ And I was invited in ♪
♪ For a small taste of gin ♪
♪ There was a hall
with a thousand birds long ♪
♪ But the biggest one
of them all ♪
♪ Was in a cage too small ♪
♪ I asked the caretaker
'cause he was the Maker ♪
♪ He looked at me
and laughed ♪
♪ Took another sip
from his glass ♪
♪ And said open up
your ears and hearts ♪
♪ You put a big bird
in a small cage ♪
♪ And he'll sing you
a song ♪
♪ That we all love
to sing along ♪
♪ To the sound of the bird ♪
♪ That mourns ♪
♪ Bah bah-bah-bah ♪
(KNOCKING)
RISE FROM THE DEAD,
KIDDO.
WHAT TIME IS IT?
BULLFROG:
TIME TO GET AT 'ER,
HEAD TO SCHOOL.
YOU LOOK GREEN.
IS EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT?
EVERYTHING'S SCRAMBLED.
OH.
I-I-I'VE BEEN TRYING
TO WRITE, AND I CAN'T.
I'M IN A CREATIVE SLUMP!
MAYBE YOU SHOULD LIMIT
YOUR STRESSES RIGHT NOW.
YOU WANT ME TO QUIT
THE PLAY?
WOULD IT BE THE END
OF THE WORLD?
I'M A WRITER, DAD!
IT'S THE ONLY THING
THAT MATTERS TO ME RIGHT NOW.
LOOK, ELI.
WHEN I GOT THE CALL
THAT YOU CRASHED MORTY,
IT HIT ME.
I MIGHT LOSE YOU.
AND I WOULD DO ANYTHING
TO NEVER GET THAT CALL AGAIN.
THERE'LL BE TIME FOR WRITING
WHEN YOU'RE BETTER.
OKAY.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(DOOR CLICKS SHUT)
(PILLS RATTLE)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
MRS. STAVROS:
MRS. ANDOPOLOUS TALKED
MY EAR OFF ALL NIGHT!
YOU MADE A BIG IMPRESSION
ON HER DAUGHTER!
ATHENA'S A REALLY
NICE GIRL, AND SMART.
AND EASY ON THE EYES!
YEP,
SHE'S QUITE A LOOKER.
I TALKED YOUR FATHER.
IT TURNS OUT HE COULD
MAKE IT TO A BIRTHDAY DINNER.
UH, MAYBE YOU COULD
INVITE A FRIEND,
WE'LL MAKE IT A PARTY.
(SHOCKED LAUGH)
I LOVE YOU, MA!
THANKS!
DON'T LET THE BOYS AT SCHOOL
HEAR YOU SAY THAT.
(CAR DOOR SLAMS)
(CAR STARTS)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
MY LETTER OF RESIGNATION.
(HALF LAUGHS)
FUNNY!
DOES IT LOOK
LIKE I'M JOKING?
I'M SORRY, IS THIS
'CAUSE I PASSED
ON YOUR ROTTING APPLE IDEA?
LOOK, I JUST BROKE UP
WITH MY EX.
IT'S THE BEST I'VE GOT.
I WILL NEVER UNDERSTAND
THE POWER CLARE EDWARDS
HAS OVER MEN.
LOOK, I THOUGHT
YOU WANTED THIS.
I DO, I JUST...
CAN'T DO IT.
NOT RIGHT NOW.
I'M SORRY.
FINE.
THEN I GUESS I'LL JUST
HAVE TO FIND
SOMEONE ELSE TO WRITE IT.
YOU MENTIONED CLARE.
SHE WRITES, YES?
UH, WELL UM...
LET'S NOT DO ANYTHING
DRASTIC!
I MEAN...
IT'S JUST WORDS.
RIGHT, SO HOW HARD
COULD IT BE?
I KNEW YOU'D COME AROUND.
SO REMEMBER,
NO DEADLINE EXTENSIONS,
TICK TOCK!
JENNA: (ON PHONE)
SOMEONE CAME HOME
LATE LAST NIGHT.
YEAH, I-I DIDN'T WANT
TO WAKE YOU,
AND TYSON WAS TOTALLY OUT.
POOR GUY,
WORK MUST'VE BEEN BUSY.
YEAH, IT WAS...
IT WAS CRAZY.
LOTS OF DISHES, THEN?
KC:
SORT OF.
THERE WERE "SORT OF"
A LOT OF DISHES?
DOESN'T SOUND THAT CRAZY.
THERE WAS MUSIC,
DANCING.
DANCING? WITH WHO?
KC:
NOBODY!
YOU-YOU KINDA
HAD TO BE THERE.
SOUNDS LIKE YOU'D RATHER
BE AT WORK WITH "NOBODY,"
THAN AT HOME WITH ME.
WHY, BECAUSE I HAVE
FIVE MINUTES OF FUN
AFTER A LONG DAY,
OR IS THAT NOT ALLOWED?
(SIGHS)
I-I GOTTA GO.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
CIVICS CLASS MAY BREAK OUT
INTO A DANCE PARTY.
(BEEPS PHONE OFF,
SIGHS ANGRILY)
(FRUSTRATED SIGH)
GIRL: (ON PA)
OUR HEALTH IS OUR PASSION,
DEGRASSI!
SIGN UP FOR A HEALTHY LIVING
ACTIVITY TODAY!
AND THEN IT HIT ME,
WHAT ABOUT AN INTRAMURAL
DODGE BALL TOURNAMENT?
TOTALLY FUN,
ANYONE CAN DO IT,
PEOPLE WOULD GET
10,000 STEPS, EASY!
SIMPSON WILL LOVE IT.
SO, HOW WAS LAST NIGHT?
LAST NIGHT?
YOU KNOW,
WITH YOUR MOM?
THE REASON YOU BAILED
ON OUR MOVIE PLANS?
OH, RIGHT.
SHE HAD SOME STUFF
I HAD TO LIFT.
AND THEN WE TALKED,
YEAH, IT WAS GOOD.
YEAH?
YOU TALKED?
WELL, NOT ABOUT THAT,
JUST BIRTHDAY STUFF.
SO DO YOU THINK
YOU'LL HAVE THAT TALK AGAIN?
MAYBE WITH YOUR DAD?
MAYBE...
AFTER MY BIRTHDAY.
RIGHT, BABY STEPS.
I NEED TO DO
SOME THINKING.
SAVE MY SPOT?
I MIGHT BE A WHILE.
YEAH, OKAY.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
GOT A SPOT?
AREN'T YOU SUPPOSED
TO BE ON THE RADIO?
NAH, I'M TOO STUFFED UP.
WHAT'S WITH THE HOMEWORK?
LUNCH TIME'S FOR LUNCH.
I'VE GOTTA MANAGE
MY DAYS BETTER.
SCHOOL WORK AT SCHOOL,
WORK AT WORK,
AND JENNA AT HOME.
WHEW!
FULL SCHEDULE.
YOU'RE MAKING TIME
FOR YOURSELF THOUGH, RIGHT?
YOU KNOW,
TIME FOR FUN?
YOU REMEMBER FUN,
RIGHT?
WORK IS FUN.
IS THAT WEIRD?
YOU WASH DISHES, RIGHT?
YEAH.
YEAH, THAT'S WEIRD.
I HAD SO MUCH FUN
AT WORK LAST NIGHT.
ME TOO.
AREN'T YOU GLAD
YOU DECIDED TO STAY?
♪ Get loose ♪
DAVE:
OH...
WORK, HUH?
OKAY.
♪ Leave your trouble
at the door ♪
♪ Get loose ♪
♪ Like you've never
done before ♪
♪ Get loose ♪
♪ Feel the music
in your soul ♪
♪ And get loose ♪
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
COME ON.
JUST KEEP IT TOGETHER.
(KEYS CLACK)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(CHAIR CRASHES)
(GRUNTS WITH EFFORT)
(MONITOR BUZZES)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
UH...
MS. OH'S COMING!
HIDE THE EVIDENCE!
HOW?
IMOGEN: UH...
I GOT IT!
(LOUD THUD)
MS. OH:
(GASPS) WHAT HAPPENED?
WHAT DO YOU THINK HAPPENED?
I TRIPPED OVER
A LOOSE CORD,
THIS PLACE IS A DEATH TRAP!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
I'LL BE OKAY.
MY NOSE JUST HURTS
A LITTLE.
LET'S GET YOU
TO THE NURSE'S OFFICE.
YOU KNOW YOU HAVE TO TELL ME
IF YOU WANNA PLAY
HIDE AND SEEK, RIGHT?
YOU'D KNOW ALL ABOUT
HIDING.
WHOA,
DID I DO SOMETHING?
BE HONEST, RILEY.
ARE YOU CHEATING ON ME?
WHAT IS YOUR PROBLEM?
(GASPS)
YOU STOLE MY PHONE?
YEAH, CHECK YOUR TEXTS.
IT SOUNDS LIKE
YOUR MYSTERY DATE
IS DOWN FOR ROUND TWO.
UNLESS THIS
IS FROM YOUR MOM.
(DOOR SLAMS)
(PHONE BEEPS)
ELI:
HEY, HOLD UP!
HOW'S YOUR NOSE?
IT'S FINE,
BUT I MIGHT NEED A SMELLING
NOSE DOG FOR A WHILE.
THEY HAVE THOSE, RIGHT?
I REALLY DON'T THINK SO.
COULD...
YOU SMELL FOR ME?
QUICK QUESTION.
WHO ARE YOU?
IMOGEN MORENO,
PLEASED TO MEET YOU.
LIKEWISE, BUT...
WHO ARE YOU?
OH, NOBODY REALLY.
I'VE BEEN GOING TO DEGRASSI
FOR A COUPLE OF YEARS NOW.
YOU'RE ELI GOLDSWORTHY.
DATED CLARE EDWARDS
LAST SEMESTER,
CRASHED YOUR HEARSE
INTO A WALL FOR HER.
AND YOU'RE AN AMAZING
WRITER.
YEAH, THAT LAST PART,
THE WRITER PART?
MIGHT NOT BE SO TRUE
ANYMORE.
HENCE THE COMPUTER
VANDALISM.
OH.
HOLD THIS FOR A SECOND?
O-KAY...
SO WHAT MEDS
ARE YOU TAKING?
I SAW YOUR VIAL.
UH NOTHING,
JUST ANTI-ANXIETY STUFF.
AH, THAT'S WHAT COULD BE
DULLING YOU OUT.
THEY CAN MAKE IT HARD
TO CONCENTRATE SOMETIMES.
REALLY?
THEY CAN DO THAT?
ABSOLUTELY.
ADAM:
HEY, WHO'S YOUR FRIEND?
WHOA! UH, WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR NOSE?
NO NEED TO WORRY,
ADAM TORRES.
ELI GOLDSWORTHY JUST
PUNCHED ME IN THE FACE!
DON'T PROVOKE HIM,
HE'S AN ANIMAL!
I DID NOT HIT HER.
THAT GIRL IS PSYCHO.
YEAH.
TOTALLY.