♪ I spin vinyl, ooh... ♪
ATTITUDE!
IMAGINE THERE'S A GUY
DOWN FRONT
WHO JUST DUMPED YOU!
MAKE HIM REGRET IT.
IT'S NOT BAD,
BUT WE CAN DO BETTER.
LET'S AIM HIGHER.
CHANTAY?
I GOT THIS.
♪ Music is fashion,
fashion ♪
♪ Press play for action ♪
FIONA:
OKAY, TERRIFYING.
HOLLY J:
LET'S KILL THE MUSIC.
♪ Demand a reaction... ♪
OKAY, LOOK, GUYS,
I'M NO MODEL,
BUT HERE'S WHAT I'M LOOKING FOR,
OKAY?
(SHORT EXHALE)
CONFIDENT.
NOT ANGRY.
SEE? OWN IT.
AND- OW! AGH! MY LEG!
OW! OW! OW!
GIRL:
OH MY GOSH!
FIONA:
WHAT HAPPENED?
GIRL:
IS SHE OKAY?
MUSCLE CRAMPS. DIALYSIS.
OW! OW! OW!
FIONA:
OKAY, LET'S GET HER UP.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
HOLLY J:
NO, I CAN'T!
(GASPING IN PAIN)
JUST BREATHE THROUGH IT.
HOLLY J:
(GASPING)
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh... ♪
(I can make it)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(ANNOUNCEMENT OVER HOSPITAL PA)
DOCTOR MITCH:
ALL RIGHT, THIS SALINE DRIP
WILL TOP UP YOUR FLUID LEVELS.
HOLLY J:
SO THAT'S ALL IT WAS?
DEHYDRATION?
IN ITS EXTREME FORM,
YES.
HMM, WELL I'VE BEEN NAGGING
HER TO DRINK MORE WATER.
YOUR BLOOD PRESSURE'S LOW.
WELL, THAT'S A GOOD THING,
RIGHT?
WELL, IN AN ELDERLY PATIENT
WITH A HEART CONDITION, YES,
BUT IN YOUR STATE
IT'S A SIGN
OF POOR RENAL FUNCTION.
TELL ME HOW YOU'VE BEEN FEELING.
HOLLY J:
TIRED.
NAUSEOUS SOME OF THE TIME.
UH...
FUNNY TASTE IN MY MOUTH
ALL THE TIME,
MY MEMORY'S TOTALLY SHOT,
AND ANOTHER THING?
MY MEMORY IS TOTALLY SHOT.
THAT WAS A JOKE.
I WISH I HAD BETTER NEWS.
WHAT'S WRONG?
HER KIDNEYS ARE ON
A STEEPER PATH OF DETERIORATION
THAN I FEARED.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
IT MEANS YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO START DOING DIALYSIS
EVERY DAY,
AND START THINKING SERIOUSLY
ABOUT A TRANSPLANT.
FAMILY MEMBERS ARE
THE MOST LIKELY MATCH, RIGHT?
ABSOLUTELY.
WELL, WE'RE ALL PREPARED
TO DO WHATEVER IT TAKES.
SO WE JUST NEED TO ARRANGE
FOR BLOOD TESTS -
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
DAVE:
HEY, HEY, EVERYONE,
YOU'RE LISTENING
TO "MANO-A-MANO"
WITH DAVE AND ADAM.
ADAM:
AND A SPECIAL GUEST,
KATIE MATLIN,
EDITOR OF DEGRASSI DAILY!
SO, TELL US, KATIE,
WHAT'S GOOD?
WELL, IT'S GOOD TO PUT A FACE
TO THAT VOICE, ADAM.
I HAVE TO SAY,
I'M A FAN OF YOUR SHOW.
SO, KATIE,
WHY DON'T YOU TELL US
ABOUT THE PROM FUNDRAISER
FASHION SHOW COMING UP?
LET ME GUESS,
YOU'RE A MODEL?
I AM,
AND IT'S GONNA BE AWESOME.
TICKETS ARE ONLY
SEVEN DOLLARS
AND ALL PROCEEDS
GO TO THE PROM FUND.
DAVE:
HMM. TALK ABOUT A WORTHY CAUSE.
AND WHO MIGHT THE HOT,
FUNNY AND TALENTED HOST BE?
OH, IT'S ME,
ISN'T IT?
KATIE:
YES.
BUT WE'RE STILL LOOKING
FOR MORE GUYS
TO WALK THE RUNWAY.
OH, WELL,
GOOD THING I'M AVAILABLE.
AMAZING.
YOU SHOULD SIGN UP!
REALLY?
REALLY.
WELL, IN THAT CASE,
LET ME PRACTICE MY MANLY STRUT
TO THIS NEXT TRACK.
(MUSIC STARTS)
THANKS,
THAT WAS GREAT.
CAN'T WAIT TO SEE THAT STRUT
ON THE CATWALK.
♪ This music is fashion ♪
WHOA.
IMOGEN:
ELI!
JUST READ YOUR NEW PAGES
FOR THE NEW PLAY.
(BREATHLESS)
SO GOOD. SO SO GOOD!
YOUR WORDS HIT ME
RIGHT HERE.
DID YOU FEEL THAT?
IT'S MY HEART.
I'M GONNA NEED THAT BACK,
IMOGEN.
I JUST WANTED TO ASK YOU
WHO YOU SAW
IN THE ROLE OF CLARA.
ANYONE IN DRAMA CLASS
CROSS YOUR MIND?
IF YOU WANT TO AUDITION,
JUST SIGN UP.
DONE. ANY TIPS?
I REALLY WANT TO NAIL
THIS PART!
WELL, IF YOU WANT
TO NAIL CLARA,
YOU HAVE TO FULLY UNDERSTAND
THE COMPLEX CREATURE
I BASED HER ON.
CLARE EDWARDS IS A...
A RIDDLE,
WRAPPED IN A MYSTERY,
STUFFED INSIDE
OF AN ENIGMA.
SHE SOUNDS LIKE A BURRITO,
AND NOW I'M HUNGRY.
YEAH, UM,
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
♪ I just need some air
to breathe ♪
♪ I need some air to breathe ♪
GIRLS ON CATWALK:
(GASP) OH!
OKAY, CHANTAY'S GONNA
KILL SOMEONE.
SHOULD I CUT THE MUSIC?
HOLLY J?
(MUSIC STOPS)
OKAY, TAKE FIVE,
EVERYBODY.
DON'T GO FAR.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
IT'S OFFICIAL,
DIALYSIS IS NOT WORKING.
I NEED A TRANSPLANT.
BUT SOMEONE IN YOUR FAMILY
WILL BE A MATCH THOUGH, RIGHT?
THERE'S NO GUARANTEE,
AND THE PUBLIC WAITING LIST
IS MILES LONG.
(SIGHS)
OKAY, YOU NEED TO GO HOME,
REST.
(SIGHING HEAVILY)
OKAY, WELL...
CAN YOU TAKE OVER?
YOU'RE A PRO
AT THIS STUFF.
AGREED, BUT I STILL HAVE
MY PLAY DUTIES
AND BEING BY YOUR SIDE 24-7
IS REALLY GONNA EAT UP
MY FASHION SHOW TIME.
THANKS, FI.
I MIGHT NEED YOU.
OKAY, WELL,
I BETTER GET HOME TO REST.
ATTENTION, MODELS!
FROM NOW ON
YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN.
ANY CHANCE YOU WANT TO ADD
"FASHION SHOW CONSULTANT"
TO YOUR RESUME?
I'M HANDING YOU THE REINS.
OH, GREAT,
I'LL TAKE IT FROM HERE.
THANKS.
OKAY, BREAK A LEG.
DAVE:
HEY, WHAT'S UP, LL COOL A?
I JUST CHECKED THE FASHION SHOW
SIGN-UP SHEET.
FUNNY.
I DIDN'T SEE
YOUR NAME ON IT.
BECAUSE MY NAME'S NOT
LL COOL A.
WELL, I DIDN'T SEE
"A. TORRES" EITHER.
COME ON, MAN,
YOU KNOW, KATIE?
SHE THREW YOU SIGNALS.
SHE WAS JUST BEING NICE
FOR RADIO SAKE.
NO, NO, NO,
TRUST ME.
I KNOW WHEN A GIRL'S
FLIRTING.
SO, I MEAN,
ARE YOU INTO HER OR WHAT?
I WOULDN'T MIND GETTING
TO KNOW HER BETTER.
ALL RIGHT,
THEN GO FOR IT!
I TOOK A CHANCE
WITH ALLI.
I DON'T NOW IF I'M INTO
TAKING CHANCES
WITH GIRLS ANY MORE.
LOOK, SERIOUSLY, BRO,
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
YOU'RE A DUDE.
ALL RIGHT? SO MAKE A MOVE
AND BEFORE YOU KNOW IT
IT'S GONNA BE ME, YOU,
KATIE AND ALLI
ALL HANGING OUT
DOUBLE-DATE STYLE.
MAYBE I'LL JUST BE
UP FRONT
ABOUT WHAT LIES BENEATH
AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
GOTTA SET THE TABLE
BEFORE YOU EAT, RIGHT?
OKAY, WHO TEACHES YOU
TO SAY THESE THINGS?
IT'S ALL ME.
P.A. ANNOUCEMENT:
ATTENTION
"DEGRASSI DAILY" STAFF,
PLEASE SUBMIT YOUR ARTICLES
TO THE PAPER
NO LATER THAN 4PM TODAY.
THANK YOU.
CAN I HELP YOU?
YES.
I'M STUDYING YOU.
I WANT TO BE YOU.
OKAY...
BUT I'M TAKEN BY ME.
(SMALL LAUGH)
YOU'RE FUNNY.
I DON'T WANT TO BE YOU,
EXACTLY.
I WANT TO BE CLARA.
AH.
YOU'RE AUDITIONING
FOR ELI'S PLAY.
CLARE,
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
THERE'S A LITTLE VOICE INSIDE
MY HEAD SAYING, "BAD IDEA."
YOU HEAR VOICES TOO?
CLARE, PLEASE.
YOU'RE MY ONLY HOPE
OF IMPRESSING ELI.
I NEED THIS.
YOU LIKE HIM.
YOU'RE NOT JEALOUS?
NO, I HAVE A BOYFRIEND.
I'VE MOVED ON.
I'D BE HAPPY
IF ELI DID TOO.
OKAY, I'LL HELP YOU.
OH MY GOD, CLARE,
THANK YOU!
JUST DON'T TELL ANYONE,
OKAY?
HEY, AM I TOO LATE
TO VOLUNTEER?
UH, DEPENDS.
DO YOU MIND WEARING
A SILLY T-SHIRT?
UH, IS THIS
THE BIGGEST SIZE?
THE GUYS WANT THEM
FORM FITTING.
OH, OH, OKAY.
NOT A PROBLEM.
GREAT, I'LL PAIR YOU UP
WITH ONE OF THE GIRLS.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
ME? SURE.
WARNING YOU IN ADVANCE,
YOU MAY BE UPSTAGED.
I DO A MEAN ZOOLANDER.
OH YEAH?
LET'S SEE YOUR "BLUE STEEL".
BOTH:
(LAUGHING)
YOU KNOW I'M TRANS,
RIGHT?
YEAH, I KNOW.
DID I DO SOMETHING WRONG?
NO,
IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
I WAS JUST MAKING SURE.
I GUESS I WAS JUST
THINKING OF YOU
AS ONE OF THE GUYS.
HOLLY J:
DO YOU HAVE NEWS?
DOCTOR MITCH:
I DO.
YOUR FATHER, MOTHER AND SISTER
ARE ALL TYPE AB,
BUT YOU'RE TYPE A.
SO THEY CAN'T GIVE ME
A KIDNEY?
WAIT, HOW CAN I HAVE
A DIFFERENT BLOOD TYPE?
WELL, IT'S POSSIBLE,
BUT IT'S HIGHLY UNLIKELY.
I'M GONNA RUN
THE TESTS AGAIN.
THERE MIGHT HAVE BEEN
AN ERROR AT THE LAB.
SWEETIE,
WE'LL FIND SOMEONE.
I KNOW.
I HOPE.
YOU DON'T THINK IT'S WEIRD
ABOUT THE BLOOD TYPES?
I NEVER GOT
HOW THAT WORKS,
EVEN BACK IN
GRADE TEN BIOLOGY.
BUT YOU HAVE
ALWAYS BEEN MORE TYPE A
THAN THE REST OF US.
IT'S A BLESSING
AND A CURSE.
WE'LL BROADEN OUR SEARCH -
AUNTS, UNCLES, COUSINS.
SURE.
SOMEONE'LL BE A MATCH.
'CAUSE WE'RE ALL FAMILY,
RIGHT?
HELLO, CLARE.
ALREADY RETURNING
MY STUFF?
YUP.
I STAYED UP ALL NIGHT
READING CLARE'S FAVOURITES.
WAIT, YOU READ ALL
MY TOP HEMINGWAYS?
EVERY WORD.
NOW AS WE DISCUSSED BEFORE,
CAN I BORROW
SOME OF YOUR CLOTHES?
NOT SO FAST.
I WILL HELP YOU
GET THIS PART,
BUT I NEED SOMETHING
IN RETURN.
I'LL KNIT YOU A SWEATER,
BUY YOU A MONKEY,
FOOT MASSAGE -
ANYTHING!
ONLY THIS:
IF YOU DO GET THE PART,
TRY TO MAKE CLARA
A BIT MORE SYMPATHETIC.
I'M CONCERNED WITH ELI'S
PORTRAYL OF ME.
DEAL.
HOLLY J:
FIONA, IF YOU WEREN'T CUT FROM
THE SAME CLOTH AS YOUR FAMILY,
YOU'D KNOW IT, RIGHT?
FIONA:
WELL, IT'S HARD TO SAY.
I MEAN, I'M A TWIN,
SO THERE'S A MALE COPY OF ME
OUT THERE
AND SOMETIMES I THINK MY MOM
AND I SHARE THE SAME BRAIN.
WAIT, IS THIS ABOUT
THE BLOOD TESTS?
HOLLY J:
I LOOKED IT UP.
IT IS REALLY WEIRD
THAT NOBODY IN MY FAMILY
IS A BLOOD-TYPE MATCH.
FIONA:
WEIRD AS IN IMPOSSIBLE?
SUPER, SUPER UNLIKELY.
WELL,
SINCE IT'S COME TO THIS,
I WANNA HELP.
I WANNA TAKE THE TEST,
FIND OUT MY BLOOD TYPE.
THERE'S MORE TO IT
THAN THAT.
THERE'S HUMAN LEUKOCYTE
ANTIGENS-
YOU'RE NOT GONNA TALK ME
OUT OF IT.
YOU'RE LIKE A SISTER TO ME,
HOLLY J.
YOU KNOW THAT.
MORE THAN MY SISTER
EVER WAS.
YOU AND HEATHER
ARE SIX YEARS APART.
I DUG THIS OUT
OF MY BASEMENT.
I'VE SEEN PICTURES
OF TODDLER ME,
BUT I DON'T REMEMBER
EVER SEEING
ANY BABY-ME PICTURES.
I'VE NEVER PAID MUCH ATTENTION
TO THE DATES,
BUT LOOK, 1993.
OH, THAT WAS
MY FIRST CHRISTMAS.
WE WERE IN BRUSSELS.
MY MOM TOOK LIKE
A THOUSAND PICTURES
OF DECLAN AND ME SURROUNDED
BY BABY GIFTS.
RIGHT, IT WAS MY FIRST
CHRISTMAS TOO,
SO I SHOULD BE IN
EVERY PHOTO IN HERE.
IS THAT HEATHER?
PRE-NOSEJOB.
THERE'S MY MOM, DAD...
GRANDMA.
EVEN HEATHER'S PET TURTLE.
WHERE AM I?
NAPPING?
FIONA, I WASN'T THERE.
WHY WASN'T I THERE?!
ELI:
YOU'RE TEARING ME APART,
CLARA.
JUST TELL ME WHAT YOU WANT.
SADIE:
I'LL SHOW YOU,
BUT NOT WITH WORDS.
ELI:
AND SCENE.
THANK YOU.
NOT ONE ACTOR HAS
EVEN COME CLOSE.
(DEJECTED SIGH)
(DISMISSIVE SIGH)
(KNOCKING AT THE DOOR)
YEAH, COME IN.
WE'RE READY...
TO BE DISAPPOINTED.
I'M HERE TO AUDITION,
BUT BEFORE YOU GET
TOO EXCITED
KNOW THAT WE CAN'T
BE TOGETHER
BECAUSE ALL WE WOULD DO
IS SPIRAL INTO ANOTHER
EPIC VORTEX
WHICH ENDS WITH YOU CRASHING
A HEARSE INTO A WALL!
WE ARE ALL
A LOST GENERATION.
SO LET'S JUST FOCUS ON THE PLAY
AND GET FOUND.
♪ I just need some air
to breathe ♪
♪ I need some air to breathe ♪
CROWD:
(CHEERS LOUDLY)
♪ I'm just gonna set me free,
I'm gonna set me free ♪
DAVE:
OKAY, OKAY,
NEXT UP WE HAVE CHANTAY
IN A FASHION CRIMES
BLACK AND WHITE BEAUTY,
ACCOMPANIED BY
MR. PRESIDENT HIMSELF,
SAV BHANDARI!
(MUSIC THUMPS,
CROWD CHEERS)
YOU LOOK GREAT.
THANKS.
I'M NERVOUS.
NOT BIG ON STANDING IN FRONT
OF A WHOLE BUNCH OF PEOPLE.
ME NEITHER.
CROWD:
(CHEERS WILDLY)
♪ I just need some air
to breathe ♪
♪ I need some air to breathe ♪
♪ Oh and another thing... ♪
DAVE:
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT.
NEXT UP, PEEPS, WE'VE GOT...
WHAT'S WRONG?
NOTHING.
DAVID:
IN A STRAPLESS IVORY NUMBER
WITH GOLD EMBELLISHMENTS,
ACCOMPANIED BY MY MAIN MAN,
ADAM!
CROWD:
(CHEERS WILDLY)
HOLLY J:
I GO TO FAMILY REUNIONS
EVERY YEAR
AND NOBODY'S EVER TOLD ME,
"HOLLY J,
YOU LAUGH LIKE YOUR DAD
OR YOU HAVE YOUR MOM'S EYES."
FIONA:
COME ON, THERE HAS TO BE
A SIMPLE EXPLANATION.
HOLLY J:
EXPLAIN THIS! MY NOSE?
HOW COME I ESCAPED THE WRATH
OF A SINCLAIR SCHNOZ
AND HEATHER DIDN'T?
YOU GOT LUCKY.
HOLLY J:
MY HANDS?
THEY DON'T LOOK ANYTHING
LIKE MY MOM'S OR MY DAD'S!
FIONA:
THEY'RE JUST HANDS!
YOU'RE FLIPPING YOURSELF OUT.
YOU NEED TO SIT,
DRINK SOME AQUA,
AND CHILL.
(SMALL LAUGH)
THE FUNNY THING IS I USED
TO LIKE BEING ONE-OF-A-KIND.
THOUGHT IT MADE ME ORIGINAL,
BETTER.
DRINK.
YOU KNOW,
IF I'M RIGHT ABOUT THIS,
IT MEANS MY PARENTS HAVE
BEEN LYING TO ME
FOR ALMOST 18 YEARS.
YOU KNOW, THERE MIGHT BE
A SILVER LINING HERE.
TWO NEW BIRTH PARENTS EQUALS
FOUR POSSIBLE KIDNEYS.
IT'S VEGAS NIGHT,
A NIGHT WHEN DREAMS COME TRUE,
BUT IS THIS A DREAM, ARI,
OR A NIGHTMARE?
YOU'RE TEARING ME APART,
CLARA.
JUST TELL ME WHAT YOU WANT!
I'LL TELL YOU...
BUT NOT WITH WORDS.
♪ You won't recognize yourself ♪
♪ The things that youth does ♪
♪ And you're too cold to melt ♪
♪ And you've come undone ♪
♪ I would give it all for you ♪
SCENE.
DAVE:
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY,
THAT WAS ONE HOT SHOW!
NOW PUT YOUR HANDS TOGETHER
AND GIVE IT UP FOR OUR MODELS!
CROWD:
(CHEERS AND CLAPS WILDLY)
♪ Let's get it tonight
(Music is fashion) ♪
♪ This is our runway ♪
(Music is fashion)
♪ Put it on on tight! ♪
♪ Put it on,
on-on on-on replay! ♪
ADAM:
YOU'RE A SUPERSTAR.
KATIE:
I'M JUST GLAD IT'S OVER.
WE SHOULD CELEBRATE.
YEAH, UH, COOL.
I JUST GOTTA TALK
TO SOMEONE
AND THEN I'LL FIND YOU.
DON'T FORGET
ABOUT TOMORROW.
ADAM:
MARISOL, HEY.
MARISOL:
HI, ADAM.
YOU AND KATIE LOOKED
GREAT UP THERE.
THANKS.
SO, KATIE,
SHE'S LIKE YOUR BFF, HUH?
MM-HMM.
SO, YOU KNOW HER THOUGHTS
ON CERTAIN THINGS,
CERTAIN PEOPLE?
SHE TALKED TO ME
ABOUT YOU.
SHE DID?
DID SHE TELL YOU
WE'RE GOING TO
A BOOK SIGNING TOMORROW?
YEAH, SHE THINKS
YOU'RE A PRETTY...
INTERESTING PERSON.
INTERESTING.
THAT'S A GOOD THING,
RIGHT?
WAIT, YOU LIKE HER,
LIKE HER?
WELL,
TO BE SORT OF REALISTIC,
UNLESS YOU WERE
PHYSICALLY DIFFERENT...
I DON'T THINK
YOU'RE HER TYPE.
SORRY.
(CAR DOOR SHUTS)
MARY KATE:
SO, OFF TO DIALYSIS.
SHOULD WE STOP AND GRAB YOU
SOMETHING TO SNACK ON?
NO, IT'S-IT'S OKAY.
I'M FINE.
YOU OKAY, SWEETIE?
WELL...
OKAY,
I'M JUST WONDERING
WHY THERE'S NOT
ANY BABY PICTURES OF ME.
(SIGHS)
MOM?
(EMOTIONAL SIGH)
YOUR DAD AND I WANTED TO WAIT
UNTIL YOU HAD TURNED 18 TO-
FOR WHAT?!
TO TELL YOU THAT,
WHEN YOU WERE 11-MONTHS-OLD,
WE ADOPTED YOU.
SO...
(INCREDULOUS SIGH)
OKAY, SO YOU LIED TO ME
FOR MY WHOLE LIFE?
WE NEVER WANTED YOU
TO QUESTION
WHERE YOU BELONGED.
WE WANTED YOU TO FEEL
100 PERCENT SINCLAIR.
GOD, THIS IS INSANE!
OKAY, WHAT ABOUT HEATHER?
WELL, THERE WERE COMPLICATIONS
WITH HER BIRTH.
I COULDN'T CARRY
ANOTHER CHILD
SO WE ADOPTED YOU.
THE BEST DECISION
WE EVER MADE.
WHO ARE MY BIRTH PARENTS?
I DON'T KNOW,
BUT YOUR DAD AND I HAVE
LOOKED INTO IT
AND IT MIGHT BE POSSIBLE
TO FIND OUT ONLINE.
SO YOU LOOKED INTO IT
BECAUSE OF THE KIDNEY THING?
YES, WE WERE GONNA TELL YOU
THE TRUTH
IN THE NEXT DAY OR TWO.
OH, SWEETIE,
I AM SO SORRY YOU HAD
TO FIND OUT LIKE THIS.
NO MATTER WHAT,
YOU ARE...
AND YOU ALWAYS WILL BE
OUR DAUGHTER.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
DAVE!
LOOK AT MY CHEST.
WHAT?
COME ON,
WE'RE FRIENDS, RIGHT?
WHICH MEANS WE DON'T LOOK
AT EACH OTHER'S PARTS.
FRIENDS TELL EACH OTHER
THE TRUTH.
COME ON, THESE JUST LOOK
LIKE MAN BOOBS, RIGHT?
NO, I'M NOT DOING THIS.
COME ON, JUST LOOK!
DAVE:
OKAY, JUST GET THOSE
OUTTA MY FACE!
DAVE, PLEASE.
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
LIKE THIS ISN'T
THE WEIRDEST THING
THAT'S EVER HAPPENED
IN MY LIFE -
ME LOOKING AT YOUR CHEST.
SHOULDN'T BE THAT WEIRD.
THERE'S NOT MUCH
TO LOOK AT, RIGHT?
OKAY, ADAM,
I KNOW YOU'RE TRYING YOUR BEST,
BUT LET'S KEEP IT REAL,
ALL RIGHT?
BOOBS ARE HAPPENING.
SO, I GUESS YOU HAVE A TRIP
TO A SUPER-BORING
GOVERNMENT OFFICE
TO LOOK FORWARD TO.
I'M TRYING TO AVOID
THAT IF I CAN.
I READ THAT THE GOVERNMENT
HAS OPENED ADOPTION RECORDS.
LOTS OF PLACES HAVE.
SO, ALL I NEED TO DO
IS FILL OUT THIS FORM
AND PRESS SEND.
SO LONG AS MY BIRTH PARENTS
CONSENTED TO DISCLOSING
THEIR NAMES,
I SHOULD BE ABLE
TO FIND THEM.
FIONA:
WAIT, NOW?!
HOLD ON,
DIDN'T YOU JUST GO THROUGH
A MAJOR LIFE-ALTERING
EXPERIENCE?
YEAH, AND NOW I MIGHT HAVE
A MUCH BETTER CHANCE
AT LIVING A NORMAL LIFE.
(SIGHS)
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
YOU'RE READY.
I'M STILL ME.
MY PARENTS ARE MY PARENTS.
BEING ADOPTED
CHANGES NOTHING.
YEAH, BUT WHAT IF-
FIONA, PLEASE!
JUST DON'T "WHAT IF" ME
TO DEATH.
THIS IS HUGE.
TAKE YOUR TIME.
ABSORB.
STOP BEING SO TYPE-A!
WELL, IT IS MY BLOOD TYPE.
AND RIGHT NOW...
TIME IS A LUXURY
I DON'T HAVE.
♪ I don't dream of flying ♪
♪ But I dream of fallin' ♪
♪ Home, take me home ♪
SO, YOU FIND OUT THE NAMES
OF YOUR BIRTH PARENTS.
THEN WHAT?
TRACK THEM DOWN?
AND ASK THE HARDEST QUESTION
YOU COULD EVER ASK:
WOULD YOU SACRIFICE
A VITAL ORGAN
FOR SOMEONE
YOU'VE JUST MET?
♪ Take me home ♪
♪ Tell me which way
did I come from... ♪