♪ Run... ♪
♪ Whirlwind run ♪
♪ Further and further away ♪
♪ Into the sun ♪
(SIGHS)
(KNOCKING)
GOOD MORNING,
HASLETT UNIVERSITY GIRL.
WELL, I DIDN'T GET IN YET.
IT'S JUST AN INTERVIEW.
HOW DID THE ESSAY GO
LAST NIGHT?
(SIGHS) GREAT.
I GOT A LOT DONE.
I DIDN'T KNOW THE DOT
WAS OPEN SO LATE.
UH, YEAH,
THERE WAS A BUNCH OF US
THERE WORKING.
REALLY?
YEAH, REALLY.
OKAY.
WELL, DON'T DILLY DALLY.
YOU'RE GONNA MAKE ME LATE
FOR WORK.
(SIGHS)
PAM:
ANYA, I'M LEAVING.
YOU BETTER BE FOLLOWING ME
OUT THE DOOR!
YEAH,
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh... ♪
(I can make it!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
OWEN, WAIT UP!
I CAN'T,
THE TEAM'S WAITIN'.
ANYA:
OKAY, LAST NIGHT WAS BAD.
I DIDN'T LIKE US
FIGHTING LIKE THAT,
BUT YOU SAID
SOME MEAN THINGS
AND I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO.
SO YOU GOT ALL COKED UP
AND GRINDED
WITH ANOTHER DUDE
IN FRONT OF MY FACE?
SORRY. I WASN'T MYSELF
LAST NIGHT.
YEAH,
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
YOU'RE NOT THE SWEET,
CUTE GIRL
I THOUGHT YOU WERE.
ARE WE BREAKING UP?
OKAY, MAYBE WE CAN TALK
WHEN YOU GET BACK.
YEAH.
GOOD LUCK ON YOUR TOURNAMENT.
(SIGHS)
THE TIPPING POINT?
ANY GOOD?
I LIKE IT, YEAH.
WERE YOU OUT AGAIN
LAST NIGHT?
UM, NO.
I WAS PREPPING
FOR MY INTERVIEW.
GOOD. THOSE THINGS
CAN BE KILLER.
MY YALE INTERVIEW WAS BY FAR
THE HARDEST 45 MINUTES
OF MY LIFE.
I PERSPIRED.
YOU MEAN,
YOU DON'T JUST SHOW UP
AND GO, "HERE I AM!
CHECKED OUT YOUR WEBSITE,
LOVE YOUR SCHOOL!"
NOT AT ALL.
(LAUGHS)
OKAY.
SINCE YOU'VE READ
EVERY UNIVERSITY PREP BOOK
IN EXISTENCE,
WOULD YOU MIND
COACHING ME?
OF COURSE.
THANK YOU.
BOTH:
(GIGGLE)
SIMPSON: (OVER PA)
A MALE WAS SEEN IN THE GIRLS'
CHANGE ROOM YESTERDAY.
POLICE ARE INVESTIGATING
THE INCIDENT...
IT'S PROBABLY THE PERV
WHO'S BEEN STEALING
GIRLS' UNDERWEAR.
GROSS!
I HOPE THEY CATCH
THE CREEP.
(LAUGHS) IMAGINE
IT'S SOME FLASHER?!
BOTH:
(CHUCKLE)
EVEN WORSE?
IT COULD BE A STUDENT.
IT COULD BE ANYONE
IN THE SCHOOL.
HEY.
LOOK, I DON'T WANT
TO TALK TO YOU.
YOU THINK IT WAS ME?
OKAY, WHO ELSE IS
SNEAKING AROUND STEALING...
(WHISPERS) STEALING
GIRLS' UNDERWEAR?
I HAVE AN ALIBI.
I WAS IN THE COMPUTER LAB
AFTER SCHOOL,
WORKING ON THE APP,
OKAY?
ASK MR. SIMPSON,
CHECK MY LOGINS.
OKAY,
IF YOU'RE LYING...
(BELL RINGS)
(SIGHS)
HANNAH'S WAITING.
LET'S GO PRESENT.
HANNAH:
HOW MANY OF YOU
HAVE SPENT HOURS
AGONIZING OVER
WHAT TO WEAR?
WE HAVE A SOLUTION
TO YOUR PROBLEM.
OUR TOUCH APP IS CALLED
"DRESS MATCH".
USERS SNAP PICTURES
OF TOPS,
BOTTOMS,
SHOES AND ACCESSORIES
USING THEIR CAMERA PHONE.
WESLEY:
IN THE DATA ENTRY FIELD,
YOU TYPE IN
HOW YOU'RE FEELING
OR WHERE YOU'RE GOING.
CONNOR:
THE ALGORITHM COMPUTES
AND YOU HAVE AN OUTFIT!
THAT'S AN ADVANCED ALGORITHM,
GUYS.
WESLEY:
ALL THANKS TO CONNOR.
MS. OH:
THEN HE DESERVES
A ROUND OF APPLAUSE.
CLASS:
(APPLAUDS)
WELCOME TO YOUR INTERVIEW,
ANYA!
THANK YOU!
CAN I GET YOU A COFFEE
OR A TEA?
DON'T ASK
IF THEY WANT ANYTHING.
I'M BEING POLITE!
YOU'LL BE IN THEIR OFFICE,
NOT A CAFE!
SIT.
OKAY
'KAY
WHERE DO YOU SEE YOURSELF
IN TEN YEARS?
JEEZ, I DON'T KNOW.
UM, I WANTED TO BE A VET,
BUT THOSE PROGRAMS
ARE IMPOSSIBLE TO GET INTO
WITH MY GPA.
I GAVE UP THAT DREAM,
SO...
HAPPY?
MAYBE YOU NEED
A CARD TO PLAY.
SCHOOLS LOOK FOR ALL KINDS
OF DIVERSITY.
TALK ABOUT MY DYSLEXIA?
THAT'S REALLY GOOD!
AND HOW I HELPED MY MOM
THROUGH CANCER.
THAT'S AMAZING,
ANYA!
SO DO YOU SEE YOURSELF
AS MORE OF A LEADER
OR A FOLLOWER?
FOLLOWER.
BUT I'M TRYING TO LEAD MORE
IN MY OWN LIFE,
DO MY OWN THING,
YOU KNOW?
IT'S IMPORTANT
TO HAVE A PATH.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO GET
OUT OF YOUR DEGREE?
I WOULD LIKE TO HELP PEOPLE
AND MAKE THE WORLD
A BETTER PLACE.
YOU GOTTA THINK UNIVERSITY,
NOT MISS UNIVERSE PAGEANT.
BE SPECIFIC.
I LOVE BEING HANDS-ON,
AND I LIKE WORKING
WITH PEOPLE.
OKAY, WELL, YOU'RE APPLYING
FOR A MINOR IN ENGLISH.
WHAT'S YOUR FAVOURITE BOOK?
A BOOK.
ANY BOOK.
DO MAGAZINES COUNT?
OKAY, WE ARE GOING
TO THE NATIONAL APP
CHAMPIONSHIPS!
I MUST BE DREAMING.
YOU'RE NOT,
IT'S REAL!
I'M GOING TO GO WORK OUT
BUGS IN THE CODE.
I'LL SEE YOU GUYS LATER.
OKAY, SEE YA LATER,
YOU ULTIMATE PROGRAMMER!
HEY, CAN I SEE THAT
FOR A SECOND?
UM...
MY NANIMA KNIT THAT FOR ME.
CUTE!
BUT HOW DID IT
GET IN HERE?
I LEFT IT IN THE LOCKER ROOM
DURING THE BEACH VOLLEYBALL
THING.
THE GUY IN
THE LOCKER ROOM.
FEELING READY?
I THINK SO.
YOU'LL DO GREAT.
CAN YOU COME TO THE INTERVIEW
WITH ME AND KEEP ME COMPANY?
LIKE THAT WON'T BE WEIRD?
NO, IT WON'T BE WEIRD
AT ALL!
HONEY!
THEY NEED TO SEE HOW BRIGHT
AND INDEPENDENT YOU ARE.
YOU CAN DO THIS,
YOU SILLY GOOSE.
(SNIFFLES) YEAH,
I DON'T THINK I CAN.
I CAN'T HEAR YOU.
(SIGHS)
WHAT IS WRONG WITH ME,
MOM?
I USED TO BE
SO CONFIDENT.
NOTHING IS WRONG
WITH YOU.
YOU CALLED THIS SCHOOL
AND GOT THE INTERVIEW
ALL ON YOUR OWN!
YOU CAN DO ANYTHING,
AS LONG AS YOU WANT IT
BADLY ENOUGH.
OKAY.
OKAY. (SIGHS)
(WAKING GROAN)
OEUF-A-LA-COQ FOR BREAKFAST?
SOUNDS DELICIOUS!
DON'T GET EXCITED.
IT'S JUST
A SOFT-BOILED EGG.
HEY, SINCE WE'RE
BED-BUG FREE,
HOW ABOUT WE CELEBRATE TONIGHT?
JUST YOU AND ME,
SOME CHEAP CHAMPAGNE?
CHAMPAGNE.
CHARLIE:
I KNOW YOU'RE UNDERAGE,
BUT JUST A LITTLE SOMETHING
TO WET OUR LIPS.
(SIGHS)
CHARLIE:
YOU'VE NEVER TRIED IT.
I'M SORRY,
I ASSUMED WITH EUROPEAN CHATEAUX
AND ALL.
OH, I'VE TRIED IT.
IT'S JUST...
I LIKE YOU SO MUCH.
I FELL FOR YOU
LIKE THE FIRST TIME
I SAW YOU.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO
MESS IT UP.
I'M FALLING FOR YOU, TOO...
SO HARD IT'S CRAZY.
BUT IF YOU WANNA
TAKE THINGS SLOW...
CHARLIE,
I'M DONE WITH SLOW.
(LOUD THUMP)
HI, UH...
UH, MY NAME'S ANYA MACPHERSON.
I KNOW.
COPY OF YOUR TRANSCRIPT?
OH, UH, I EMAILED IT OVER
WITH MY APPLICATION.
WE EXPECT YOU TO BRING ONE
WITH YOU.
NOW, OFFICIALLY,
WE'RE ALL FILLED UP,
SO I WOULDN'T GET
MY HOPES UP.
OKAY.
I'LL GET YOUR TRANSCRIPT.
DON'T TOUCH ANYTHING.
(SIGHS)
ANYA: (SPEAKING QUICKLY)
AND THEN I WENT THROUGH
THIS LARPING PHASE -
LIVE ACTION ROLE-PLAYING.
I LED MY FACTION TO VICTORY.
IT ACTUALLY REQUIRES A LOT
OF LEADERSHIP AND IMAGINATION.
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH!
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
I TALK REALLY FAST
WHEN I'M NERVOUS.
ACTUALLY, IT'S A BAD HABIT.
IT'S MY WORST QUALITY.
IF YOU WERE TO ASK ME
WHAT MY WORST QUALITY IS...
I WOULD SAY TALKS FAST
WHEN NERVOUS.
(LAUGHS)
I'LL CROSS THAT OFF
MY LIST.
YOU APPLIED FOR LIBERAL ARTS.
WHERE DO YOU SEE THIS
TAKING YOU?
UM... A PHD?
I MEAN, MY PHD.
WITH A PERIOD,
NOT A QUESTION MARK.
I SEE MYSELF AS A PROFESSOR;
THAT'S MY PATH.
WHAT CHALLENGES
HAVE YOU OVERCOME?
UM...
I STRUGGLE WITH DYSLEXIA.
AND YEAH, THAT'S TOUGH.
I MEAN, PEOPLE JUDGE ME,
BUT I FIGHT THAT.
I WANT TO BE AN EXAMPLE
FOR STUDENTS,
A TRAILBLAZER.
YOUR TRANSCRIPT IS AVERAGE,
AT BEST,
ESPECIALLY THIS LAST TERM.
WELL, I SPENT EVERY MINUTE
WITH MY MOM
WHEN SHE WAS BATTLING CANCER,
AND I GOT TO LEARN A LOT ABOUT
THE MEDICAL COMMUNITY,
AND THE EXPERIENCE
MADE ME STRONGER.
OUTSIDE OF ACADEMIA,
ANY INTERESTS?
I LIKE BOOKS.
UH...THE TIPPING POINT?
EXCELLENT READ.
I'D HIGHLY RECOMMEND IT.
SOUNDS LIKE YOU JUGGLE
A LOT.
THAT'S ME.
YOUR BASIC HIGH SCHOOL
OVER-ACHIEVER.
I CAN'T TALK FOR LONG,
I HAVE TO WORK ON MY APP.
CLOSE THE DOOR.
STUDENTS HAVE BROUGHT
TO MY ATTENTION
THAT YOU WERE IN THE GIRLS'
CHANGE ROOM.
I WASN'T.
IT WAS SOMEONE ELSE.
WE HAVE PROOF, CONNOR.
ALLI RECOGNIZED HER CLOTHES
IN THE APP.
OKAY, FINE.
IT WAS ME.
BUT I DIDN'T MEAN
TO DO ANYTHING WRONG.
CONNOR,
YOU PUSHED ALLI OVER.
I DIDN'T!
I WENT IN THE CHANGE ROOM
TO TAKE PICTURES OF CLOTHES
FOR THE APP.
SHE GOT IN MY WAY,
THAT'S IT.
STUDENTS AND FACULTY HAVE BEEN
REPORTING MISSING UNDERWEAR.
I STOPPED, I PROMISE!
SO IT WAS YOU?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT A CRISIS YOU'VE CAUSED
FOR THIS SCHOOL?!
I'M WORRIED ABOUT YOU,
CONNOR.
AND I'VE BEEN SO BUSY
THAT I HAVEN'T BEEN
AROUND LATELY,
SO THIS IS PARTLY MY FAULT.
CAN I GO WORK ON
MY APP NOW?
NO, NO, NO.
WE'RE NOT DONE TALKING.
CAN I GO WORK ON
MY APP NOW!?
CAN I GO WORK ON MY APP?!
LET ME GO WORK ON MY APP!
CALM DOWN, CALM DOWN.
CALM DOWN. RELAX.
JUST TAKE A SEAT,
OKAY?
I'M SORRY I YELLED.
MS. DAWES:
THE MEISNER TECHNIQUE.
KNOWN FOR IT'S INTENSE
REPETITION EXERCISES,
AND THE GOAL OF THE EXERCISE
IS TRUTH.
(WHISPERING)
SOMEONE'S GLOWING.
(LAUGHS)
(WHISPERING)
CHARLIE AND I TOOK
THE NEXT STEP.
YOU FINALLY GOT
TO KNOW EACH OTHER?
QUITE INTIMATELY.
DETAILS, PLEASE.
AS IF.
I LIKE HER SO MUCH.
SO WHY THE ANGST?
SHE WANTS TO CELEBRATE BEING
BED-BUG FREE TONIGHT
WITH SPARKLING WINE.
MINOR PROBLEM
FOR AN ALCOHOLIC.
IT'S THE ONE THING
I DIDN'T TELL HER.
I'M GOING AGAINST EVERYTHING
MY REHAB SPONSOR ADVISES.
SO TELL HER.
IF SHE LIKES YOU ENOUGH,
SHE'LL DEAL.
NOT EVERYONE'S A DESPERATE
ROMANTIC LIKE YOU,
MR. I-WRITE-PLAYS-
FOR-MY-EXES.
WHAT IF I SCARE HER OFF?
YOU WANT ME TO WRITE
A PLAY FOR HER?
(SIGHS)
I DIDN'T THINK
IT WOULD HURT ANYONE.
I MEAN, I LIKE LOOKING
AT GIRLS' UNDERWEAR.
(SIGHS)
I KNOW IT'S WRONG.
WELL, NO.
YOU'RE EXPRESSING VERY NORMAL
TEEN HORMONES.
SO THEN?
BUT IN
AN UNACCEPTABLE MANNER.
THEN WHAT SHOULD I DO?
WELL, THERE'S LOTS OF WAYS
THAT TEEN BOYS
DEAL WITH THEIR HORMONES.
BUT IT'S HARDER FOR ME
BECAUSE I HAVE ASPERGERS?
(SIGHS)
THAT'S WHY WE THINK
IT'D BE BEST
IF YOU ENTERED AN ACADEMIC
BEHAVIORAL PROGRAM
DURING YOUR SUSPENSION
FROM DEGRASSI.
I'M BEING SUSPENDED?
YEAH, BUDDY.
REGULAR SCHOOL MEANS
REGULAR CONSEQUENCES.
WHEN YOU RETURN,
YOU'LL BE BETTER EQUIPPED
TO DEAL WITH YOUR FEELINGS.
HOLLY J:
IF YOU CAN FIND TWO NUMBERS
THAT YOU ADD TOGETHER
TO GET B,
AND MULTIPLY TOGETHER
TO GET C,
THEN IT'S FACTORABLE.
GET IT?
(SIGHS) HASLETT U SHOULD'VE
GOTTEN BACK TO ME BY NOW.
THEY SAID THEY'D LET ME KNOW
BY END OF DAY.
WELL, IT'S NOT
THE END OF DAY YET.
WELL, WHAT IF I WROTE
THE WRONG NUMBER DOWN
OR THEY CALLED THE HOME LINE
AND THE MESSAGE GOT ERASED?
ANYA, RELAX.
YOU SAID IT WENT WELL.
I'M SURE YOU HAVE NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
OKAY, WELL, IF THEY HAVEN'T
CALLED ME BACK TONIGHT,
I WILL STOP BY HIS OFFICE
IN THE MORNING.
ARE YOU SURE
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA?
YEAH,
IT SHOWS INITIATIVE.
I NEED THIS.
IT'S MY LAST HOPE
OF HAVING A BRIGHT FUTURE,
LIKE YOURSELF.
ANYA, YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
A BRIGHT FUTURE
AS LONG AS YOU STAY
ON TRACK.
LIKE NOW.
IS THIS FACTORABLE
OR NOT?
(BELL RINGS)
(PUFFS OUT HER BREATH)
SURE.
HOW ARE WE GONNA WIN
THE APP CHALLENGE?
WHO AM I GONNA TALK
COMIC-CON WITH?
YOU HAVE HANNAH.
(SIGHS)
IT'S NOT THE SAME.
OH, COME ON, WES,
DON'T BE SAD.
YOU KNOW I DIDN'T MEAN
TO DO ANYTHING WRONG.
I KNOW.
YOU WERE CURIOUS,
AND YEAH, GIRLS ARE CONFUSING -
FOR ME, TOO.
AND THAT'S WHY I'M LOOKING
FORWARD TO THE PROGRAM
I'M GOING TO.
IT'LL HELP ME DEAL BETTER
WITH THESE SITUATIONS.
THE SOURCE CODE -
EVERYTHING YOU'LL NEED TO WIN
THE APP CHAMPIONSHIP.
I CAN'T TAKE IT.
IT'S YOUR WORK.
I DID IT FOR US.
NOW, I'M OFF TO BOLDLY GO
WHERE NO ONE HAS GONE BEFORE.
STAR TREK. NICE.
WILL I EVER SEE YOU
AGAIN?
(LIKE THE TERMINATOR)
I'LL BE BACK.
(LAUGHS)
TERMINATOR.
♪ And falling through
the fields ♪
♪ And hiding everyday ♪
♪ What have we done,
my brother? ♪
♪ Have we all gone away? ♪
YOU MADE DINNER?!
I TOLD YOU,
WE'RE CELEBRATING!
I KNOW IT'S NOT
THE EXPENSIVE KIND
THAT YOU'RE PROBABLY
USED TO,
BUT IT'LL DO.
(CORK POPS)
(SIGHS)
I DON'T WANT THIS
TO CHANGE.
WHY WOULD IT?
BECAUSE...
I'M AN ALCOHOLIC.
WOW.
RECOVERING ALCOHOLIC.
I HAVEN'T HAD A DRINK
IN WEEKS - MONTHS!
OKAY, THIS IS HEAVY.
YOU'RE SEVENTEEN.
WHEN DID YOU...?
SO YOU CAN'T BE AROUND
ALCOHOL EVER?
NO, I CAN!
I'M DOING GREAT!
I MEAN, I CAN HAVE
A SIP RIGHT NOW
AND IT WOULDN'T
EVEN AFFECT ME.
OH MY GOD.
I HAVE TO GO CALL
MY MOM.
♪ She said ashes to ashes ♪
♪ That was a long time ago ♪
(KNOCKING)
MR. COUTANCHE?
I'M ANYA.
DO YOU REMEMBER ME?
I BROUGHT YOU A COFFEE.
DO WE HAVE AN APPOINTMENT?
NO.
BUT I THOUGHT I WOULD
CHECK IN
BECAUSE I HADN'T
HEARD BACK YET,
AND YOU SAID END OF DAY
AND...IT'S TOMORROW,
SO...
ANYA MACPHERSON.
WELL, SINCE YOU'RE HERE,
I'LL GIVE YOU THE NEWS -
AND IT'S NOT GOOD.
WHAT?! NO, I THOUGHT
THE INTERVIEW WENT WELL.
IN PERSON,
YOU'RE COMPLETELY DIFFERENT
THAN THE PERSON
DEPICTED IN
YOUR ADMISSIONS ESSAY.
YOU WERE ERRATIC,
YOU WERE ALL OVER THE PLACE.
IF I DIDN'T KNOW BETTER,
I'D SAY YOU WERE ON DRUGS.
I WASN'T.
PLEASE,
I REALLY NEED THIS.
I'M SORRY.
(SIGHS) DO YOU REALLY WANT
TO BE THE PERSON
WHO RUINS MY ENTIRE LIFE?
ANYA, I DIDN'T BLOW
THE INTERVIEW,
YOU DID.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR TIME.
♪ Well, it's naked as we go ♪
♪ And naked as we leave ♪
(HARD ROCK MUSIC BLARES)
PAM:
ANYA? (KNOCKING)
UH, YEAH.
PAM:
ARE YOU CRYING?
YOU CAN'T BE SO HARD
ON YOURSELF.
OPEN UP.
ANYA:
JUST A SEC.
HEY.
OH, I THOUGHT YOU WOULD'VE
OUTGROWN THIS OLD THING
BY NOW.
DOES IT STILL HAVE
THE SAND IN IT?
UH, WHY WOULDN'T IT?
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOUR DAD AND I WERE TALKING
AND WE'RE THINKING THAT
MAYBE NOT GETTING
INTO HASLETT U
WASN'T THE WORST THING.
I MEAN. WE PUT SO MUCH
PRESSURE ON YOU
TO GO INTO
AN ACADEMIC PROGRAM.
MAYBE THAT WASN'T
THE RIGHT CHOICE FOR YOU.
THERE ARE SO MANY
OTHER OPTIONS.
DO WE REALLY HAVE
TO TALK ABOUT IT?
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT
WANT TO.
WELL, I DON'T.
AND I'M GOING OUT TONIGHT.
ON A SCHOOL NIGHT?
I THOUGHT WE'D SIT DOWN
AND FIGURE OUT
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
WITH YOUR LIFE.
I DON'T CARE.
(LAUGHS)
ANYA, YOU'RE NOT LEAVING
THIS HOUSE.
WATCH ME!
THANK-YOU.
HOW YA FEELING?
TALKING IT OUT
WITH MY THERAPIST HELPED.
WHAT DID SHE SAY?
THAT I'M NOT READY
TO BE AROUND ALCOHOL.
LIKE, AT ALL.
THAT MEANS
I CAN'T EITHER.
CHARLIE, I CAN'T ASK YOU
TO CHANGE.
YOU'RE IN COLLEGE;
IT'S PART
OF YOUR SOCIAL LIFE.
YET YOU WAITED UNTIL
I MOVED IN TO TELL ME...
UNTIL I LET MYSELF
GET CLOSE TO YOU.
THE FACT THAT I DIDN'T
TELL YOU SOONER
SHOWS THAT I'M NOT READY
TO BE IN A RELATIONSHIP.
I CAN FEEL IT MYSELF,
I'M NOT.
(SIGHS) I GUESS
I'LL BE MOVING OUT?
I'M REALLY SORRY.
WON'T BE THE FIRST TIME
I SHOW UP
AT MY MOTHER'S DOORSTEP.
(SIGHS)
SHE ALWAYS LOVES THAT.
I REALLY WANTED US
TO WORK.
WILL YOU BE OKAY?
I'M A BIG GIRL,
FIONA.
(LAUGHS)
MR. TUXEDO PANTS AND I
ALWAYS LAND ON OUR FEET.
SEE YA LATER, FIONA.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(CLUB MUSIC PLAYS)
♪♪♪