DAVE:
IT JUST FELT SO RIGHT,
GETTING THE WORDS OUT THERE.
BAM!
EVERYONE'S TALKING ABOUT IT.
WELL, THAT'S THE POINT,
RIGHT?
NO POINT IN HAVING
A RADIO SHOW
IF YOU CAN'T GET PEOPLE
TO LISTEN.
IT'S NOT EVERY DAY
THAT SOMEONE CALLS OUT
THEIR TRANSGENDER CO-HOST
ON-AIR.
(SIGHS) CAN YOU BELIEVE
ADAM BAILED?
LIKE I THOUGHT
HE COULD TAKE IT.
SURE, BUT...
DON'T YOU THINK YOU TOOK IT
LIKE A LITTLE TOO FAR?
HOW WOULD YOU FEEL
IF SOME DUDE WAS STARING AT YOU
WHILE YOU WHIZ?
OKAY, GROSS.
EXACTLY!
LOOK, I SAID HOW I FEEL.
FREEDOM OF SPEECH.
DAVE.
YOU ATTACKED ME
ON AIR
INSTEAD OF JUST
TALKING TO ME?
I EXPRESSED AN OPINION.
IF YOU CAN'T TAKE IT-
EXCUSE ME?
I'M JUST SAYING,
IF IT'S TOO INTENSE FOR YOU,
I'LL DO THE SHOW SOLO.
MAYBE WE SHOULDN'T HOST
THE SHOW TOGETHER.
THE LGBT CLUB HAS A PETITION
TO GET YOU KICKED OFF.
"REMOVE DAVE TURNER
FROM DEGRASSI'S AIRWAVES"?
DID YOU DO THIS?
NOPE, WASN'T MY IDEA.
BUT PRETTY SOON,
I'LL BE HOSTING THE SHOW SOLO.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
ZANE:
YEAH, GREAT, GREAT.
SO YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO, OKAY?
HEY. UH, ZANE, RIGHT?
OH.
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU?
YOU GUYS ARE PROTESTING ME?
YEAH, YOU USED THE WORD
"TRANNY" ON THE RADIO.
THAT'S HATEFUL LANGUAGE.
BUT...
NO, NO, I JUST ASKED
WHAT PEOPLE THOUGHT
ABOUT TRANSGENDERED GUYS
BEING IN THE BATHROOM.
YOU MADE IT CLEAR
YOU'RE AGAINST IT
FROM A POWER POSITION.
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING WRONG!
REALLY?
YOU REALLY THINK THAT?
ALLI:
YOU OKAY?
NO! KATIE WON'T GIVE ME
A CHANCE TO APOLOGIZE!
I'VE CALLED HER,
EMAILED HER!
WHAT ABOUT
A FRIENDLY TEXT?
I'M SORRY,
SMILEY FACE?
YEAH, THAT'LL PROVE
I'M NEWSPAPER MATERIAL!
WELL, MAYBE YOU CAN JOIN
A DIFFERENT CLUB.
THERE'S GOTTA BE
SOMETHING ELSE
WHERE YOU WON'T RUN
INTO ELI.
I-I REALLY WANTED
TO BE ON NEWSPAPER, ALLI,
AND I KNOW I'D BE GOOD
IF I COULD JUST...
ALLI:
CURB YOUR ENTHUSIASM?
(LAUGHS)
I NEED TO GET KATIE
TO TALK TO ME.
YOU'RE A SMART COOKIE,
YOU WILL.
(BOTH LAUGH)
HEY, SAV!
HAVE YOU HEARD ABOUT
THIS WHOLE PETITION THING?
OH, I'VE DEFINITELY HEARD.
IT'S RIDICULOUS, RIGHT?
LOOK, ALL I SAID
WAS IT'S STRANGE TO HAVE GIRLS
IN THE GUYS' BATHROOM,
AND PEOPLE ARE TALKING ABOUT ME
LIKE I'M SOME SORT OF CRIMINAL!
WHICH IS WHY I CAN'T LET YOU
BACK ON THE AIR.
WHAT?! I THOUGHT YOU SAID
I WAS GREAT!
REMEMBER?
FUNNY, CONTROVERSIAL?
YEAH,
BUT THERE'S A FINE LINE
BETWEEN CONTROVERSIAL
AND OFFENSIVE.
A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE PISSED,
MAN.
ESPECIALLY YOUR CO-HOST.
YOU-YOU CAN'T SILENCE ME
'CAUSE I HAVE AN OPINION!
ALL RIGHT,
I'M GOING TO SIMPSON.
(SCOFFS)
YEAH, GO TO SIMPSON.
BUT I WAS THE ONE
WHO CALMED HIM DOWN.
SIMPSON WANTED YOU
SUSPENDED!
SI-
SO YOU'RE CANCELLING
THE SHOW?
SAV:
NO.
WE'RE NOT CANCELLING THE SHOW,
YOU'RE JUST NOT HOSTING
ANYMORE.
AND ADAM IS?!
SO THAT'S HOW IT IS?!
ALL RIGHT.
GLOVES OFF!
DAVE.
(BELL RINGS)
FIONA:
SO MY MOM WENT COMPLETELY
MAMA BEAR ON ME FOR SKIPPING.
APPLY MYSELF AT SCHOOL,
OR IT'S BACK TO NEW YORK
I GO.
WHERE'D YOU TAKE OFF TO,
ANYWAY?
I JUST HUNG OUT
WITH CHARLIE.
AHA!
WE'RE JUST FRIENDS,
HOLLY J.
FOR NOW.
AT LEAST, WE WERE.
SHE STILL HASN'T CALLED ME BACK
SINCE MY MOM LOST IT
IN FRONT OF HER.
WHAT IF SHE DOESN'T?
WELL THEN, SHE'S NOT
A FRIEND WORTH HAVING.
BESIDES, YOU'RE WORRYING
TOO MUCH ABOUT HER.
YOU SHOULD BE KEEPING
YOUR PROMISE TO YOUR MOM.
I WILL,
ONCE I KNOW THAT EVERYTHING'S
OKAY WITH CHARLIE.
IF SHE'S NOT CALLING
YOU BACK...
THEN I SHOULD GO TALK
TO HER IN PERSON!
HOLLY J:
THAT'S NOT WHERE I WAS GOING
WITH THAT AT ALL!
(LOCKER SLAMS)
DAVE:
HEY, THANKS FOR COMING!
YOU GUYS ARE FREEDOM FIGHTERS.
HERE, PUT THESE ON.
THESE ARE DRESSES.
WHY ARE WE...
CONNOR, WAIT A SECOND!
DAVE:
NO, PUT IT ON!
LOOK, WE'RE GONNA DRESS UP
LIKE GIRLS,
HEAD INTO THE GIRLS WASHROOM,
AND YOU KNOW, GO.
WHAT?! WHY?
TO PROVE A POINT!
LOOK, JUST 'CAUSE YOU'RE DRESSED
UP AS THE OPPOSITE SEX
DOESN'T GIVE YOU THE RIGHT
TO USE THEIR WASHROOM.
ALL RIGHT?
HURRY UP!
CONNOR:
I NEED A DIFFERENT SIZE.
TAKE IT OFF!
OKAY,
HOW IS THIS A GOOD IDEA?
LOOK, I SPOKE THE TRUTH
ON THE RADIO
AND GOT SILENCED!
ALL RIGHT,
IT'S UNFAIR, WES!
YOU GET THAT,
RIGHT?
WE'RE TAKING A STAND,
COME ON!
I CAN'T, DAVE.
I'M SORRY.
NOT YOU, TOO!
YOU'RE A BUNCH
OF CHICKENS!
♪ Oh my love ♪
♪ I am with you now ♪
♪ Running the ghosts come out ♪
♪ They just keep coming ♪
♪ And they're rolling down ♪
♪ You're still running away ♪
♪ Give me one reason ♪
♪ You still keep moving ♪
♪ When the verdicts
keep coming ♪
♪ And they're falling out ♪
♪ Oh and I'm still wishing ♪
♪ I'm still wishing you'd stay ♪
♪ Wishing you'd stay ♪
HI, KATIE.
(KEYS CLICK)
DID YOU GET THE EMAIL
I SENT?
YOU'RE SHUNNING ME?
KATIE:
NO, I'M BUSY.
I HAVE TO POST THE NEW EDITION
ONLINE IN AN HOUR.
WELL, MAYBE IF YOU HAD
MORE HELP?
WHY DO YOU WANNA BE
ON THE NEWSPAPER SO BADLY?
(SIGHS)
CLARE:
LAST SEMESTER WAS A COMPLETE
TRAIN WRECK FOR ME.
MY BOYFRIEND...
MY EX-BOYFRIEND ELI AND I
HAD A TERRIBLE BREAK-UP.
ARE YOU SERIOUSLY CRYING
RIGHT NOW?
ALL I WANT IS TO MOVE ON!
OKAY, YOU CAN'T KEEP ME
OFF THIS PAPER
BECAUSE I MADE ONE MISTAKE.
I AM A GOOD WRITER!
IF YOU LET ME ON,
I WILL DO WHATEVER YOU SAY.
YOU'LL DO WHATEVER
I SAY?
YES! I PROMISE.
OKAY, THEN WIPE AWAY
THOSE DRAMA QUEEN TEARS
AND LEAVE ME ALONE
SO I CAN POST THIS PAPER!
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
DOES THAT MEAN YOU'LL GIVE ME
A SECOND CHANCE?
NO!
IT MEANS I NEED YOU
OUT OF MY FACE!
YOU HAD YOUR CHANCE,
CLARE.
BYE.
♪ You've got such a good ear ♪
♪ Why won't you listen ♪
(TAXI DOOR SLAMS)
HEY, CHARLIE.
HEY, FIONA,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I SAW THE FIGHT.
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH,
JUST SOME PERSONAL STUFF.
FIONA:
DO YOU WANNA TALK
ABOUT IT?
NO, I DON'T.
WE COULD GET LUNCH,
MY TREAT.
CHARLIE:
I CAN'T.
I HAVE SOME THINGS
I HAVE TO TAKE CARE OF.
YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU NEED A FRIEND.
THERE'S GOTTA BE SOMETHING
I CAN DO.
JUST GO BACK TO HIGH SCHOOL,
OKAY, FIONA?
(SIGHS)
PEOPLE SURE ARE RILED UP
WITH THIS WHOLE DAVE THING.
HOW'S YOUR DAY GOING SO FAR?
ANY BACKLASH?
MOSTLY AGAINST DAVE.
IT'S WEIRD,
IT'S LIKE I'M IN
THE MIDDLE OF A DEBATE,
AND I HAVEN'T SAID
A THING.
YOU'LL GET YOUR CHANCE
TO TALK,
ONCE YOU'RE ON THE AIR SOLO.
(GIRLS SCREAM)
GIRL: DAVE, GET OUT!
DAVE:
SO REMEMBER,
IF I'M DRESSED LIKE YOU,
IT'S ALLOWED!
(DOOR SLAMS)
ADAM:
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING
TO PROVE?
YOU'RE SMART,
FIGURE IT OUT.
YOU THINK DRESSING UP
IS WHAT THIS IS ABOUT?
THAT, AND GETTING
TO CHECK OUT DUDES' PACKAGES.
YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT ME!
I DON'T CARE ABOUT
YOUR STUPID JUNK!
NO, YOU CARE ABOUT
BEING A CRYBABY
UNTIL YOU GET
THE ONLY ACTUAL GUY
ON THE RADIO SHOW
KICKED OFF!
(DAVE HALF LAUGHS)
YOU KNOW, PEOPLE KNOW
YOU'RE NOT A DUDE, ADAM.
DAVE:
OOF!
HUH? WHAT?
GUY:
NOW, HEY! HEY! HEY!
(DAVE AND ADAM GRUNT)
STUDENTS:
(SURPRISED MURMURS)
HEY, GUYS! WHOA!
(DAVE GRUNTS)
ELI:
GUYS! SIMPSON!
ALL RIGHT! ALL RIGHT!
ALL RIGHT, YOU TWO,
WE'RE GOING TO MY OFFICE.
DAVE, I THINK YOUR DAD'S
HERE TODAY,
I THINK I'LL HAVE HIM
JOIN US.
(SIGHS)
MR. SIMPSON:
MY DECISION ON
THE BATHROOM STANDS.
AND FOR YOUR PART
IN THE FIGHT,
WE'LL SEE YOU AFTER SCHOOL.
ADAM:
OKAY. THANK YOU, SIR.
(DOOR SLAMS)
I WANNA SAY MY KID
WOULDN'T DO THIS,
BUT UH...
HERE YOU ARE IN A SKIRT.
SO MUCH FOR BEING
THE MAN.
MR. TURNER,
CARE TO EXPLAIN?
LOOK, I JUST TRIED
TO MAKE A POINT.
BY VIOLATING DRESS CODE
AND FIGHTING IN THE HALLWAY.
SIR, I GOT KICKED OFF THE AIR
FOR HAVING AN OPINION!
YOU GOT KICKED OFF THE AIR
FOR USING OFFENSIVE LANGUAGE.
LOOK, I JUST SAID
WHAT I THOUGHT!
FREE SPEECH!
THAT'S WHAT WE LEARN HERE,
RIGHT?
MR. SIMPSON:
YOU HAVE THE RIGHT
TO FREE SPEECH,
BUT THIS SCHOOL BELONGS
TO ALL OF US,
AND IT HAS TO BE A SAFE
AND COMFORTABLE PLACE
FOR ALL OF US!
YEAH, OR JUST THOSE OF US
THAT MATTER.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
ALL RIGHT,
YOU WERE IN
THE GIRLS' WASHROOM,
YOU WERE FIGHTING
IN THE HALLWAY,
AND WE'VE ALREADY DISCUSSED
THE RADIO INCIDENT.
YOU CAN THINK ABOUT THIS
IN DETENTION, ALL RIGHT?
SOUNDS ABOUT RIGHT.
AND WHAT,
ADAM GETS OFF SCOTT-FREE?
ADAM WILL BE PUNISHED
FOR FIGHTING TOO.
OKAY,
SO IF WE'RE BOTH WRONG,
THEN WHY CAN'T I GET
MY RADIO JOB BACK?
(SIGHS)
I DON'T THINK
IT'S A GOOD IDEA.
RIGHT.
I LOSE AGAIN.
(BELL RINGS)
KATIE: (OVER PA)
THE DEGRASSI DAILY
IS LOOKING FOR PHOTOGRAPHERS.
PLEASE SUBMIT YOUR PORTFOLIO
TO KATIE MATLIN.
HEY, THERE YOU ARE!
HOW'D TALKING IT OVER
IN PERSON GO?
I WAS REJECTED.
BRUTALLY REJECTED.
I AM SO STUPID.
YOU'RE NOT STUPID.
I THOUGHT THERE
WAS SOMETHING
BETWEEN CHARLIE AND ME,
BUT I WAS JUST A GIRL
HANGING ON.
I COULD DEAL WITH BEING
FRIENDLESS AT DEGRASSI
AS LONG AS I HAD ONE FRIEND
OUTSIDE OF SCHOOL.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
YOU FUNCTION BEST
WHEN YOU HAVE A PROJECT.
FORGET ABOUT MAKING FRIENDS
AND JUST FIND
SOMETHING TO DO.
HEY, IT'S BETTER THAN GOING
BACK TO NEW YORK, RIGHT?
RIGHT NOW,
I'M NOT SO SURE.
THANKS A LOT.
WE'RE OFF THE RADIO SHOW
AND IN DETENTION
BECAUSE OF YOU.
THAT'S WHAT YOU
CARE ABOUT?
DO YOU KNOW WHAT SIMPSON
SAID TO ME?
WHAT'D HE DO,
GIVE YOU A LOLLIPOP?
EVER SINCE I GOT HERE,
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO USE
THE GUYS' BATHROOM,
AND NOW I'M BACK
TO THE HANDICAP CRAPPER.
THANKS A LOT.
DAVE:
OOPS! TOUGH LIFE.
SORRY.
HOW COME EVERYONE ELSE
CAN DEAL WITH ME...
EXCEPT YOU?
DAVE:
BECAUSE WHY DO YOU GET
SPECIAL PRIVILEGES?
HOWEVER YOU CUT YOUR HAIR-
ADAM:
IF YOU WANT ME
TO GO INTO THE BORINGNESS
ABOUT TRANSGENDER
BRAIN DEVELOPMENT,
I'D BE GLAD TO.
(SCOFFS) WHATEVER.
EVERY DAY I FIGHT TO DO
THE THINGS YOU DO,
LIKE USE THE GUYS' BATHROOM,
PEE STANDING UP.
YEAH, WHICH YOU SUCK AT,
BY THE WAY.
YOU THINK USING THAT THING
IS EASY?
LOOK, NO ONE MAKES YOU,
ALL RIGHT?
SO YOU HAVE
A DIFFERENT BATHROOM,
BIG DEAL.
HOW WOULD YOU FEEL
IF IT WERE YOU?
I WOULD JUST FOLLOW
THE SIGN ON THE DOOR.
YEAH, WELL, 50 YEARS AGO,
THAT SIGN WOULD'VE SAID
"WHITES ONLY."
THAT'S DIFFERENT!
THAT'S RACISM.
ADAM:
OKAY, MAYBE IT'S NOT
EXACTLY THE SAME,
BUT STILL,
YOU DISCRIMINATED AGAINST ME
BASED ON SOMETHING
I DIDN'T CHOOSE
AND CAN'T CHANGE.
IT'S THE WAY I AM, DAVE.
BUT HEY,
IF YOU'RE OKAY WITH THAT.
♪♪♪
(BUS RUMBLES)
KATIE: (OVER PA)
THE LATEST ISSUE
OF THE DEGRASSI DAILY IS OUT.
PICK YOURS UP TODAY.
ALLI:
SO THAT'S IT?
SHE JUST WON'T LISTEN
TO REASON?
IT'S DEFINITE.
DEGRASSI DAILY'S EDITOR
HATES ME.
WELL, SHE SOUNDS LIKE
A TOTAL "B,"
WITH A SIDE ORDER
OF "ITCH".
OH, COME ON,
KATIE'S ON HONOUR ROLL,
SHE'S A REGIONAL
SOCCER CHAMP.
SHE RAISED THE MOST MONEY
FOR OUR "FREE THE CHILDREN"
CAMPAIGN LAST YEAR,
ALL BY HERSELF.
YOU DON'T GET
WHERE KATIE'S AT
BY LETTING YOUNGER STUDENTS
PUSH YOU AROUND.
WELL,
YOU'RE AN OLDER STUDENT,
NOT TO MENTION THE PRESIDENT
OF THE WHOLE FREAKIN' SCHOOL.
NOW CAN'T YOU GIVE KATIE
A TALKING TO?
MAN, YOU GRADE TENNERS
ARE WEARING ME OUT.
IT'S OKAY, SAV,
I'LL FIND SOME OTHER WAY
TO FILL UP MY SPARE TIME.
BY DOING WHAT?
(CLARE AND ALLI LAUGH)
FIONA!
THANK GOD YOU'RE HERE!
WE ARE FOUR DRAMA NERDS AWAY
FROM VOTING ON A PLAY...
ABOUT A REALITY TV SHOW!
A PLAY...
ABOUT A TV SHOW!
WHAT WOULD I DO?
TALK TO THEM!
YOU'RE THE ONLY PERSON HERE
WITH ANY TASTE!
YEAH,
BUT THEY DON'T KNOW THAT.
THEY DON'T KNOW ME
AT ALL.
PLEASE?
I DON'T WANNA SPEND
ALL SEMESTER
WORKING ON
A PIECE OF CRAP.
MS. DAWES:
OKAY...
LET'S START DISCUSSING
THE CONTENT OF THE PLAY,
THE REALITY...
TV SHOW...THING.
ANY COMMENTS?
PLEASE.
COULD I SAY SOMETHING FIRST?
FIONA, I SUPPOSE SINCE
YOU BOTHERED TO JOIN US
IN CLASS TODAY,
YEAH, GO AHEAD.
OKAY,
WHATEVER THE PLAY IS,
IT SHOULD BE REAL.
ABOUT STUFF THAT HAPPENS
TO PEOPLE OUR AGE.
LIKE BEING SCARED
YOU WON'T FIT IN,
FEELING ALONE,
OR BEING COMPLETELY AWKWARD.
LIKE I AM RIGHT NOW.
(A FEW STUDENTS LAUGH)
ELI'S THE BEST WRITER
IN THE CLASS.
IMOGEN:
OBVIOUSLY!
FIONA:
AND I THINK WE SHOULD
GIVE HIM A CHANCE
TO COME UP WITH SOME IDEAS.
I'M IN.
MS. DAWES:
I THINK WE'VE FOUND
OUR DIRECTOR.
FIONA:
ME?
OH, I'M NOT SURE...
I'M NOT MY BROTHER.
MS. DAWES:
THEN THIS IS THE PERFECT
OPPORTUNITY TO SHOW US
WHO YOU ARE.
CLASS, ALL IN FAVOUR
OF ELI, THE WRITER,
FIONA, THE DIRECTOR?
STUDENTS:
YEAH. FOR SURE! FINE.
GUY:
YEP.
OKAY, WE'VE GOT A LOT OF WORK
AHEAD OF US!
♪♪♪
♪ Window in ♪
♪ Window out ♪
♪ These are the wars
we are in doubt ♪
THINK YOU COULD HURRY UP
IN THERE?
WHAT'RE YOU STARING AT?
(SIGHS)
♪ Burning with truth ♪
♪ You're waking up under ♪
♪ As a fallen tree ♪
YOU'VE GOT FRIENDS
IN HIGH PLACES.
I'M SORRY?
I GOT REAMED OUT BY
THE STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT
FOR HAVING NO GRADE TENS
ON MY NEWSPAPER STAFF.
I DIDN'T ASK SAV
TO DO ANYTHING.
YOU DIDN'T ASK SAV
FOR A FAVOUR?
THE OLDER BROTHER
OF YOUR BFF?
WHAT DO YOU WANT, KATIE?
I WANT...
TO WELCOME YOU
TO THE STAFF
OF THE DEGRASSI NEWSPAPER.
NEXT MEETING'S TOMORROW
AT LUNCH.
(GASPS)
LOOK, I'M NOT ONE
TO HOLD GRUDGES.
TOMORROW'S A NEW DAY
FOR US, OKAY?
OKAY, AGREED.
GREAT!
AND HEY, I'VE GOT THE PERFECT
FIRST ASSIGNMENT FOR YOU.
LAY IT ON ME.
I JUST GOT A TEXT THAT
THE GRADE 11 DRAMA CLASS
HAS CHOSEN THE WRITER
FOR THE SCHOOL PLAY.
ELI SOMETHING OR OTHER?
YOU KNOW HIM,
RIGHT?
EX-BOYFRIEND, PERHAPS?
YEAH.
GOOD, BECAUSE YOU'RE GONNA
BE COVERING THE PLAY
FROM NOW UNTIL
CLOSING NIGHT.
BUT MAYBE-
WHAT?
IS THERE A PROBLEM?
NO.
THERE'S NO PROBLEM.
GOOD.
KEEP YOUR SCHEDULE OPEN.
YOU'RE GONNA BE SPENDING
LOTS OF TIME WITH ELI.
(SIGHS)
FIONA:
SO WICKED'S A FANTASY,
BUT STILL SO RELATABLE.
AND ELPHABA MAY BE A WITCH,
BUT SHE STILL HAD
THE SAME PROBLEMS
FITTING IN AT SCHOOL
AS WE DO.
ELI:
MAYBE THAT COULD BE OUR THEME.
(SCOOTER RUMBLES)
I...GOTTA GO.
WE'LL TALK MORE ABOUT THIS
TOMORROW, OKAY?
ELI:
GOT IT.
HEY.
HI.
I'M SORRY FOR SNAPPING
AT YOU,
I WAS HAVING...
A REALLY ROUGH DAY.
IT HAPPENS.
APOLOGY ACCEPTED?
YOU'RE LUCKY YOU'RE CUTE!
(LAUGHS)
SO, DID YOU...
MAKE UP WITH
YOUR GIRLFRIEND?
OH, ELISE ISN'T MY GIRLFRIEND.
SHE, UH,
SHE WAS MY ROOMMATE.
(SIGHS)
I HAVE ALL THIS SCHOOL DEBT,
AND I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO MAKE RENT IN A FEW MONTHS.
AND SHE KICKED ME OUT,
SO I HAVE NOWHERE TO GO.
YOU'RE HOMELESS?
THIS ISN'T YOUR PROBLEM,
AND I DIDN'T COME HERE
TO LAY MY CRAP ON YOU.
HEY, THAT'S WHAT FRIENDS
ARE FOR, RIGHT?
DO YOU WANNA GRAB A CUP
OF COFFEE AFTER SCHOOL,
AND TALK ABOUT IT?
I'D LOVE A COFFEE,
BUT I DON'T WANNA TALK
ABOUT IT.
FINE, WE CAN TALK ABOUT
SOMETHING ELSE.
I ACTUALLY HAD
AN AMAZING MORNING.
REALLY?
WHAT AMAZINGNESS HAPPENED?
WELL, UH, MY DRAMA CLASS
IS PUTTING ON THE SCHOOL PLAY,
AND GUESS WHO'S DIRECTING IT?
OKAY, DON'T BOTHER GUESSING!
IT'S ME!
(LAUGHS)
(MUSIC PLAYS)
(DOOR CLICKS SHUT)
(LOCK CLICKS)
SAV: (FROM CONTROL BOOTH)
DAVE! YOU CAN'T BE IN THERE!
I'VE GOT A SHOW TO DO.
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
(KEYS CLICK)
HEY, DEGRASSI, HOW ARE YOU?
IT'S DAVE TURNER.
I HAVE...
MR. SIMPSON:
DAVE? DAVE! OPEN THE DOOR!
LOOK, I HAVE SOMETHING
YOU'RE GONNA WANNA HEAR.
FIONA:
WE STILL ON FOR COFFEE
BEFORE MY CLASS?
MAYBE A SCOOTER RIDE BEFORE?
CHARLIE:
SURE, I'LL PICK YOU UP.
FIONA:
BYE, CHARLIE.
CHARLIE:
BYE, FI.
THAT'S A PRETTY CRAZY DANCE
THERE, CRAZY LEGS!
WELL,
IT WAS A CRAZY MORNING!
UH...
I HEARD YOU'RE DIRECTING
THE PLAY!
FIONA:
OH YEAH, THAT TOO!
THAT TOO?
YOU WERE RIGHT,
HOLLY J,
I JUST NEEDED
TO PUT MYSELF OUT THERE,
AND PEOPLE CAME TO ME.
I'M SO GLAD YOU HAVE
SOMETHING KEEPING YOU BUSY.
THIS WAY YOU WON'T SPEND
TOO MUCH TIME
PINING AFTER CHARLIE
FROM AFAR.
YEAH, WELL,
THERE'S NO NEED FOR PINING.
AND IT WON'T EXACTLY BE
FROM AFAR.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
CHARLIE'S LOSING
HER APARTMENT,
SO I SAID SHE COULD
MOVE IN WITH ME.
FRIENDS DON'T LET FRIENDS
BE HOMELESS, HOLLY J!
YOU HAVE A HUGE CRUSH
ON HER, FIONA!
HOW CAN YOU POSSIBLY LIVE
TOGETHER PLATONICALLY?
AND WHAT WILL
MAMA COYNE THINK?
SHE ALWAYS TAUGHT ME
TO BE CHARITABLE.
(LAUGHS)
FOR THOSE OF YOU
WHO DON'T KNOW,
THE OTHER DAY I TALKED ABOUT
HOW I WAS SURPRISED
THAT TRANSGENDERED KIDS GOT
TO USE THE REGULAR BATHROOM.
I RAN INTO THAT SITUATION,
AND I WAS FREAKED, OKAY?
I CAN ADMIT THAT.
I-I USED STUPID,
HATEFUL LANGUAGE,
AND I OFFENDED
A LOT OF PEOPLE -
MY CO-HOST,
IN PARTICULAR -
AND I'M REALLY SORRY.
I SHOULD'VE TOLD HIM
HOW I FELT,
AND, YOU KNOW,
STARTED A DIALOGUE.
ADAM:
SIR? JUST LET HIM FINISH.
DAVE:
AND IF YOU GUYS LET ME
KEEP DOING THE SHOW,
THAT'S WHAT I'LL DO.
TALK ABOUT THE TOUGH STUFF.
ASK QUESTIONS,
TRY AND UNDERSTAND,
INSTEAD OF JUDGE.
SO, ADAM TORRES,
YOU'RE DOWN FOR THIS?
UH... DEPENDS.
ARE YOU GONNA BE PULLING
ANY OTHER SKELETONS
OUT OF MY CLOSET?
DAVE:
NOPE, JUST WANT HONEST TALK.
SO THE QUESTION HERE IS...
WHAT MAKES YOU A GUY, EXACTLY?
TELL US.
NO, THE QUESTION IS...
WHAT MAKES YOU A GUY?
(LAUGHS)
OKAY, I DESERVED THAT.
LOOK, YOU KNOW
YOU'RE A GUY,
SO DO I.
BUT I GOT WRONG EQUIPMENT.
DAVE:
WHAT, YOU CAN'T EXCHANGE?
(LAUGHS)
MAYBE SOME DAY.
ENOUGH TALK,
THE PEOPLE WANT TUNES!
DAVE:
ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL BE BACK.
♪ I'll take you away ♪
♪ I can take you away ♪
♪ Take my hand don't be shy ♪
♪ Please don't beg,
please don't cry ♪
♪ I'll take you away,
I can take you away... ♪