AWW!
DAVE SAYS HE MISSES ME.
JENNA:
SINCE LAST NIGHT?
ALLI:
HEY, TWELVE HOURS IS FOREVER
WHEN YOU'RE IN LOVE.
OH, SO YOU'RE IN LOVE NOW?
MAYBE.
JENNA:
SO HOW'D DAVE TAKE IT
WHEN YOU TOLD HIM
YOU'RE SPENDING
THE WHOLE SUMMER AWAY
AT THAT SCIENCE PROGRAM?
ALLI:
UH, WELL...
ALLI,
YOU HAVE TO TELL HIM!
OKAY, BUT WE JUST
GOT TOGETHER!
HOW'S THAT GONNA LOOK?
(SCOFFS)
FINE.
I'LL TELL HIM SOON, OKAY?
I PROMISE.
DAVE:
HEY, YOU LADIES
ARE LOOKING FINE!
HMM... FLATTERER!
ANYWAYS, HOW'S THE NEW
ROOMMATE SITUATION?
ANY LATE NIGHT PILLOW FIGHTS
I SHOULD KNOW ABOUT?
IS THAT WHAT GUYS
THINK WE DO
WHEN THEY'RE NOT AROUND?
SO WHAT,
NO PILLOW FIGHTS?
MAYBE ONE.
DAVE:
YEAH, SEE, I KNEW IT!
YOU AND YOUR POPS
UP FOR SOME CARDS LATER ON?
AREN'T YOU TIRED
OF LOSING TO ME?
DAVE:
TO YOU? NEVER.
I CAN'T WAIT TO KEEP LOSING
TO YOU ALL SUMMER.
ALLI: (LAUGHS UNCOMFORTABLY)
DAVE: ANYWAYS, CATCH 'YA LATER.
MY LISTENERS AWAIT.
JENNA:
SO I GUESS YOU'LL TELL DAVE
SOME OTHER TIME THEN?
(MAKES A BLOWING SOUND)
HE'S GONNA FREAK.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Oh oh-oh... ♪
(Oh oh-oh...)
♪ I can make it through ♪
(I can make it!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
COACH ARMSTRONG:
OKAY, WE'RE SOLVING FOR X,
PEOPLE.
I WANT YOU TO PAIR UP
AND TACKLE THE PROBLEM.
PROBLEMS.
FUNNY THING,
THEY ALWAYS SEEM TO GET BIGGER
WHEN IGNORED.
I KNOW, IT'S JUST...
DAVE'S GONE ABOVE
AND BEYOND FOR ME.
HE EVEN MANAGED TO GET INTO
MY PARENTS' GOOD BOOKS.
YEAH,
BUT YOU CAN'T NOT GO!
THIS IS A ONCE
IN A LIFETIME CHANCE, ALLI!
I KNOW, I KNOW,
AND I'M DEFINITELY GOING,
IT'S JUST...
I NEED TO GET HIM ALONE,
YOU KNOW,
SO WE CAN TALK THINGS OVER.
MY PARENTS ARE GOING
TO A FUNDRAISER TONIGHT
AND SAV'S GOT THAT MUSIC THING
WITH MO.
RIGHT.
LOOKS LIKE I'LL BE STUDYING
AT THE DOT.
I HATE TO KICK YOU OUT,
BUT...
AFTER ALL THE DRAMA WITH KC
AND GIVING UP TY,
GIVING YOU SPACE
IS THE LEAST I COULD DO.
MAYBE IT WON'T BE
SO BAD.
COACH ARMSTRONG:
MS. BHANDARI?
I TRUST YOU AND JENNA ARE
WORKING ON THE PROBLEM?
UH, X EQUALS...
MINUS FORTY-FIVE OVER TWO.
YES.
WOULD YOU CARE
TO TAKE US THROUGH IT?
SURE.
(BELL RINGS)
MR. BETENKAMP:
WHAT IS A RUBE GOLDBERG MACHINE?
ANYONE? ANYONE... ANYONE...
YEAH.
AN OVERLY COMPLEX MACHINE
THAT PERFORMS A SIMPLE TASK.
FIVE POINTS
TO WESLEY-PEDIA!
NICE!
THIS IS LAST YEAR'S
WINNING MODEL.
THIS YEAR'S TASK:
TURN ON A LIGHT BULB.
YOU RESEARCH, YOU PLAN,
AND YOU BUILD.
AND THE GROUP
WITH THE BEST MACHINE
WILL REP DEGRASSI
IN THE CITY-WIDE COMPETITION.
LOOKS LIKE
IT'S JUST ME AND YOU
BUILDING OUR FIRST CHILD
TOGETHER.
ROOM FOR ONE MORE?
UM...
SURE!
LIAM:
AWESOME! PHYSICS PARTY!
I HOPE THREE ISN'T A CROWD.
UH, NO. HEH.
UH, THE MORE THE MERRIER!
HEY, YOU WANNA RALLY
TOGETHER?
YEAH, NO.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
COACH ARMSTRONG:
WELCOME TO VOLLEYBALL, LADIES.
I HAVE ONE RULE:
DO NOT KICK THE VOLLEYBALLS!
(GIRLS CHUCKLE)
MISS DESOUSA,
WHERE ARE YOUR GYM CLOTHES?
MUST BE IN THE WASH,
MR. A.
I'LL TAKE THE DETENTION.
IF YOU'RE NOT GONNA
PARTICIPATE,
YOU CAN DO THIS
HEALTH ASSIGNMENT.
I'D REALLY RATHER
HAVE DETENTION.
THE HEALTH ASSIGNMENT
IS OPTIONAL?
ONLY IF YOU'RE UNABLE
TO JOIN IN.
AGH!
THESE CRAMPS ARE KILLING ME!
DUE TOMORROW -
BOTH OF YOU.
OKAY,
LET'S WARM UP!
WANNA WORK TOGETHER
AFTER SCHOOL?
CAN'T.
I'M MEETING THIS GUY.
IT'S SCHOOL WORK.
JUST CANCEL!
TRUST ME,
I WISH I COULD.
(WHISTLE BLOWS REPEATEDLY)
WESLEY:
OKAY, LET'S BRAINSTORM.
ALL THE BEST RGM'S
HAVE A THEME.
HOW ABOUT,
UM, GRAVITY?
WESLEY:
HAH! OR, UH, SOMETHING GOOD.
HOW ABOUT THIS:
MONOPOLY.
WE'LL USE MODEL TRAINS
FOR THE STATION STEPS,
A WATER VALVE
FOR THE WATER WORKS,
AND THE FINAL LIGHT BULB
WILL BE THE ELECTRIC COMPANY!
WHOA, WHOA!
CAN'T WE DO SOMETHING SIMPLER?
I MEAN, HOW ABOUT THE CLASSIC
MARBLE WITH DOMINOES?
WESLEY:
UH, I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT YOU, LIAM,
BUT HANNAH AND I KINDA
WANT TO WIN THIS.
OF COURSE!
WE ALL WANNA WIN.
LOOK,
I'M JUST SAYING,
A CONCEPT BASED ON
A BOARD GAME,
THERE'S A LOT TO GO WRONG.
IT'S COMPLICATED!
OKAY, WELL,
COMPLICATED IS
THE WHOLE POINT!
I'M SURE IF WE PUT
OUR HEADS TOGETHER,
WE'LL COME UP
WITH A COMPROMISE.
YEAH, FINE,
TAKE HIS SIDE.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
OKAY, SO NEXT TOPIC:
MOVIES OR BASKETBALL?
BASKETBALL!
DEFINITELY BASKETBALL.
GREAT SHOW, GUYS.
ADAM:
YEAH, DAVE'S A NATURAL.
HE'S GOT A FACE FOR RADIO,
YOU KNOW?
DAVE:
(LAUGHS)
SO, WHAT'S UP?
WELL, MY PARENTS
ARE GOING OUT TONIGHT
AND I JUST WANTED TO KNOW
IF YOU WANNA COME OVER
FOR A NICE DINNER.
YOU KNOW, WE CAN HAVE
SOME ALONE TIME.
I REALLY WANT TO MAKE
TONIGHT SPECIAL.
SURE. SOUNDS FUN.
CAN I BRING ANYTHING?
UM... DESSERT?
D...
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
I'LL, UH,
I'LL SEE YOU THEN.
(ALLI AND DAVE LAUGH)
WHAT?
SEX DESSERT?
WHA-?
SHE DIDN'T MEAN THAT.
COME ON,
HER FAMILY'S OUT,
ALONE TIME?
MAKE TONIGHT
REALLY SPECIAL?
NO!
IT'S HAPPENING, MAN.
REALLY?
OH, MAN.
LIAM:
SO BY THE END OF THE WEEK
WE SHOULD HAVE A PRETTY
AMAZING MACHINE, HUH?
WESLEY: (LAUGHS)
LIAM: WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
OH! NO, NOTHING.
IT JUST WON'T BE
THAT INTERESTING
WITHOUT A WATER VALVE STEP.
DO WE NEED THAT?
WE'RE KIND OF RUNNING
SHORT ON TIME.
WE'LL STAY LATE!
LIAM AND I HAVE
A BUS TO CATCH.
YOU TAKE
THE SAME BUS?!
WE JUST REALIZED
WE LIVE LIKE TWO BLOCKS AWAY
FROM EACH OTHER!
YEAH.
ISN'T THAT INTERESTING.
I'LL COME WITH YOU GUYS!
WE'LL TALK ABOUT
THE MACHINE SOME MORE!
HANNAH:
ISN'T YOUR HOUSE
THE OTHER WAY?
(SIGHS)
YEAH, BUT...
DON'T WORRY, OKAY?
YOU'RE STILL MY NUMBER ONE
NEUTRON BOMB.
(HORN HONKS)
MR. BETENKAMP:
HOP IN, WES!
I'LL GIVE YOU A RIDE.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
DON'T OBSESS!
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
OKAY, I NEED DRIVING LESSONS,
UNCLE MIKE.
WHAT,
ALL OF A SUDDEN?
A MAN KNOWS WHEN HIS TIME
IS RIGHT.
CAN YOU DRIVE ME
TO GET MY LEARNER'S PERMIT?
WE DIDN'T HAVE
ALL THOSE LICENCING STAGES
BACK WHEN I GOT MY LICENCE.
HOW LONG TILL I'LL BE ABLE
TO DRIVE HANNAH HOME BY MYSELF?
WELL, AT LEAST SIX MONTHS.
THEN WE'D BETTER
GET STARTED.
ADAM:
EXPLAIN TO ME AGAIN
WHY YOU COULDN'T BUY
YOUR OWN PROTECTION?
DAVE:
I DON'T KNOW,
IT'S EMBARRASSING.
WHOA!
WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN RIBBED AND TEXTURED?
(BOX CLATTERS)
WELL!
BIG PLANS TONIGHT?
NO, UH...
NONE OF MY BUSINESS.
SMOOTH, DAVE.
VERY SMOOTH.
YOUR FIRST TIME'S
A BIG DEAL.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE READY?
LOOK, AFTER TWO YEARS
OF WAITING,
I'M FINALLY WITH ALLI.
ALL RIGHT,
I DON'T WANT TO MESS THIS UP.
I LOVE THAT GIRL.
YOU KNOW, IF SHE'S READY,
THEN I'M READY.
I JUST WANT IT
TO BE PERFECT.
(SIGHS)
(SIRENS WAIL IN THE DISTANCE)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
VINCE:
WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU MISS CHEERLEADING?
FUNNY.
DID YOU HAVE TO PARK
SO FAR AWAY FROM THE SCHOOL?
YEAH.
YOUR EX-BOYFRIEND'S
RESTRAINING ORDER AND ALL.
THAT STUFF IS BEHIND US NOW,
VINCE.
BIGGER AND BETTER THINGS,
RIGHT?
YOU GOTTA MOVE SOMETHING
FOR ME.
(SIGHS)
DOWNTOWN AGAIN?
I'M THINKING
OF ANOTHER OPPORTUNITY.
I CAN'T GET WITHIN
FIVE BLOCKS OF DEGRASSI,
BUT YOU CAN.
WE HAVE COPS AT SCHOOL
DOING RANDOM SEARCHES
EVERY WEEK!
YOU CAN HANDLE IT, B!
BESIDES,
WE HAVE A DEAL.
YOU KEEP UP YOUR END
AND EVERYBODY STAYS
IN ONE PIECE.
FINE.
GOOD GIRL.
(CRICKETS CHIRP)
DOUBLE PEP,
DOUBLE CHEESE?
YOU KNOW WHAT I LIKE.
AND YOU KNOW
WHAT I LIKE?
YOU.
IN FACT,
I LIKE YOU A LOT.
(LAUGHS SHYLY)
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT YOURSELF.
WELL, GOOD.
(LAUGHS)
BECAUSE I HAVE SOMETHING
TO SAY,
AND I-I DON'T REALLY KNOW
HOW TO SAY IT.
I-I-I KNOW WHERE
YOU'RE GOING WITH THIS.
UM, LOOK, I KNOW...
YOU'VE DONE THIS BEFORE
AND I HAVEN'T,
BUT, UH, I JUST...
UM, I WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT UH...
I'M READY...
TO UH...
CONDOMS?!
WHY DID YOU BRING CONDOMS?
YOU KNOW,
FOR... STUFF.
ALLI:
DID YOU REALLY THINK
WE WERE GONNA HAVE SEX TONIGHT?
WELL, I MEAN, YOU SAID
YOUR PARENTS WERE GONNA BE AWAY
AND YOU WANTED IT
TO BE SPECIAL.
I MEAN, WHAT AM I SUPPOSED
TO THINK?
YOU ARE JUST LIKE
EVERYONE ELSE!
MAYBE IT'S A GOOD THING
I'M GOING AWAY
FOR THE WHOLE SUMMER!
YOU'RE GOING AWAY?
I GOT ACCEPTED
INTO AN EXCLUSIVE
SUMMER SCIENCE PROGRAM.
I LEAVE IN THREE WEEKS,
AND THAT'S WHY
I INVITED YOU OVER.
SO I COULD TELL YOU
IN PRIVATE.
I JUST,
I JUST GOT YOU!
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
YOU'RE GOING AWAY?
IT'S ONLY TWO MONTHS!
THAT'S A LONG TIME!
ANYTHING CAN HAPPEN
IN TWO MONTHS!
SO WHAT,
TWO MONTHS IS TOO LONG
FOR YOU TO WAIT
TO HAVE SEX?
THANKS FOR TELLING ME.
ALLI:
YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET'S JUST TALK ABOUT IT
OVER DESSERT, OKAY?
UH, I... I SHOULD GO.
THIS...
(AT A LOSS FOR WORDS)
ALLI:
I DON'T KNOW,
I GUESS I JUST THOUGHT DAVE
WAS DIFFERENT, YOU KNOW?
JENNA:
HE'S JUST LIKE ALL GUYS.
ALL THEY WANT IS SEX.
RIGHT?
WELL, WHEN YOU SAID
YOU WANTED A SPECIAL NIGHT,
I MAY HAVE CONVINCED DAVE
YOU WANTED TO DO IT.
ADAM!
ADAM:
HE WAS INSECURE
WITH IT BEING HIS FIRST TIME.
ALL HE CARED ABOUT
WAS GIVING YOU A PERFECT NIGHT.
HE JUST WANTED
TO MAKE YOU HAPPY.
YEAH? SO WHY'D HE STORM OUT
LAST NIGHT?
WELL, YOU CAN'T TELL HIM
I TOLD YOU,
BUT HE WAS REALLY UPSET.
THE NEWS MUST HAVE
DESTROYED HIM.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
OKAY, BESIDES SEX,
UM, WHAT'S THE NUMBER ONE THING
ON A GUY'S MIND?
ADAM:
WELL, IF THAT GUY IS DAVE?
BASKETBALL.
DEFINITELY BASKETBALL.
OKAY!
I'M ALL IN.
JENNA:
I FOLD.
ADAM:
NOT ME!
READ 'EM AND WEEP!
I'VE GOT THAT JACK
YOU WANTED.
ADAM:
HOW DO YOU KNOW WHAT I WANTED?
ALLI:
I JUST REMEMBERED.
I TAKE A PICTURE
IN MY MIND
OF ALL THE CARDS
I'VE ALREADY SEEN,
AND THEN I JUST PLAY
THE PROBABILITIES.
YOU'RE COUNTING CARDS?
YOU MAKE IT SOUND
LIKE IT'S A BAD THING.
ADAM:
IF I COULD COUNT CARDS,
I'D MAKE IT WORK FOR ME.
I'D BE RICH!
HEY, CAN YOU GUYS DO ME
A FAVOUR?
POKER TOURNAMENT TODAY
AT LUNCH.
TEN DOLLAR BUY IN,
SPREAD THE WORD.
YOU KNOW SIMPSON PUT THE KIBOSH
ON GAMBLING AT SCHOOL!
SO MAKE SURE
HE DOESN'T FIND OUT!
(BELL RINGS)
(LAUGHS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
HOW'D THE MEETING
WITH THE BOY GO?
WE'RE NOT TALKING
ABOUT THAT, OKAY?
SURE. SORRY.
LET'S JUST SAY
I'D RATHER HAVE DETENTION.
IS THAT YOUR ASSIGNMENT?
BIANCA:
YUP. ALMOST DONE.
IMOGEN:
NO, YOU'RE NOT!
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
A FAVOUR.
COACH ARMSTRONG:
DID YOU FINISH
YOUR ASSIGNMENTS?
NO, MR. A.,
WE DIDN'T.
THEN YOU CAN FINISH THEM
IN DETENTION.
OKAY, SIR.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
(BOTH LAUGH)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
SO, UH, DID YOU AND HANNAH
DO ANY BRAINSTORMING
ON THE BUS HOME YESTERDAY?
NAH, WE JUST GRABBED
A SLICE.
YOU GOT PIZZA?
LIAM:
YEAH, AND TALKED
AND STUFF.
SHE'S PRETTY AWESOME.
I THINK I MIGHT GO FOR HER.
HANNAH AND I ARE DATING.
LIAM:
REALLY? SORRY, MAN.
SHE NEVER MENTIONED IT,
AND YOU GUYS DON'T EXACTLY
HAVE THAT VIBE EITHER.
WELL, WE ARE,
AND... YEAH, WE DO.
LIAM,
ARE YOU GETTING A CAR?
LIAM:
UH, SOME DAY.
A GUY CAN DREAM, RIGHT?
YEAH, I WAS THINKING
OF GETTING ONE.
PRETTY SOON,
IN FACT.
YOU HAVE YOUR LICENCE?
OF COURSE I DO.
WHO DOESN'T?
OH!
NO OFFENSE, LIAM.
WHEN WERE YOU
GONNA TELL ME?
WESLEY:
WELL, I WANTED IT
TO BE A SURPRISE.
SURPRISE!
(LAUGHS)
♪♪♪
♪ M-m-m-mah ♪
♪ I wanna hold 'em
like they do in Texas please ♪
♪ Fold 'em,
let 'em hit me ♪
♪ Raise it, baby, stay with me
(I love it) ♪
♪ Lovegame intuition ♪
♪ Play the cards
with spades to start ♪
♪ And after he's been hooked ♪
♪ I'll play the one
that's on his heart ♪
♪ Oh oh-oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh-oh oh-oh oh oh ♪
♪ I'll get him hot ♪
♪ Show him what I've got ♪
♪ Can't read my,
can't read my, ♪
♪ No, he can't read
my poker face ♪
♪ (She's got me like nobody) ♪
♪ Can't read my,
can't read my, ♪
♪ No, he can't read
my poker face ♪
♪ (She's got me like nobody) ♪
♪ My my my poker face ♪
♪ P-p-poker face ♪
♪ P-p-poker face
p-p-poker face ♪
♪ M-m-m-mah ♪
(GEAR GRINDS)
(ENGINE REVS,
TIRES SCREECH)
WELL, TERRIFIC CONTROL
ON THE STREETS.
MAYBE, UH, A TAD SLOW,
BUT NO WORRIES.
'CAUSE US BETENKAMPS
WE'RE BORN DRIVERS.
(TIRES SCREECH)
(NERVOUSLY)
UH, OKAY, LET'S UM...
LET'S SLIDE INTO THAT
OPEN SPACE.
(ENGINE REVS,
TIRES SCREECH)
(GARBAGE CAN CLATTERS)
WESLEY:
JUST A BIT OFF.
MR. BETENKAMP:
HEH! NO PROBLEM.
JUST, UH, BACK UP,
TRY AGAIN.
(TIRES SCREECH)
DREW:
WHOA! HEY, WATCH OUT, MAN!
SORRY! REAL SORRY!
FIRST TIME DRIVER!
CRAZY.
OKAY, NEXT TIME WE PRACTICE
IN AN EMPTY LOT.
AND...
YOU MIGHT BE ADOPTED.
(PHONE BUTTONS BEEP)
HEY,
DO YOU EVER GET HIGH?
RIGHT NOW,
IN DETENTION?
NO. JUST DO YOU WANNA
BUY SOME?
NO, NOT REALLY.
SORRY.
DON'T BE.
JUST THOUGHT I'D TRY.
WHERE'S ARMSTRONG?
I REALLY HAVE TO PEE!
DISTRACT ME!
HOW?
I DON'T KNOW,
TELL ME A STORY.
HOW PRINCESS BIANCA
MET HER PRINCE.
I'VE NEVER MET ONE.
NOT EVEN THE GUY
YOU'VE BEEN AVOIDING?
IS IT THAT OBVIOUS?
YOU WEREN'T EVEN MAD
WHEN I GOT US DETENTION.
WELL, LET'S JUST SAY...
IT'S COMPLICATED.
I HAD A THING
WITH A COMPLICATED GUY, TOO.
SOMETIMES I THINK
THE WHOLE THING WAS MY FAULT.
HOW DID YOU GET OVER IT?
I TOLD MYSELF
I DESERVE BETTER.
MAYBE ONE DAY
I'LL BELIEVE IT.
20 MINUTES LEFT.
HOW ARE THOSE ASSIGNMENTS
COMING, LADIES?
SIR, I REALLY,
REALLY HAVE TO PEE!
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
MR. ARMSTRONG:
MAKE IT QUICK.
BE RIGHT BACK.
♪♪♪
♪ Am I asking for too much
from you? ♪
♪ Did you get too bored of me? ♪
♪ If we could have
the conversation... ♪
LIAM:
SO THE MARBLE GOES DOWN
THIS TRACK,
WHICH SETS OFF THE DOMINOS,
WHICH SETS OFF
THE SPRING LOADED ARM,
WHICH TURNS ON THE LIGHT BULB.
COOL.
GREAT.
OUR MACHINE'S BORING.
YOU ARE NOT LETTING GO
OF THIS WATER VALVE STEP IDEA,
ARE YOU?
OKAY,
I'M JUST SAYING,
WE SHOULD AT LEAST BRAINSTORM
SOME INTERESTING STEPS.
HANNAH:
I'D LOVE TO,
BUT IT'S LIKE ALMOST FIVE.
MY GRANDMA'S COMING OVER
FOR DINNER, SO...
LIAM:
YEAH, WE BETTER HIT THE ROAD.
WELL, BUT THE MACHINE?
HANNAH:
WILL STILL BE HERE TOMORROW.
SEE YA, WESSER.
OR... OR I COULD GIVE YOU
A RIDE.
YOU'LL GET HOME
TO YOUR GRANDMA FASTER.
YOUR UNCLE LETS YOU
USE HIS CAR?
TOTALLY, I JUST HAVE
TO HAVE IT BACK
BEFORE HE'S DONE COACHING
THE GRADE NINE DEBATE TEAM.
AWESOME!
THANKS, WES.
OH! SORRY, LIAM.
UH, ONE PASSENGER PER RIDE.
UNCLE'S RULES,
YOU UNDERSTAND.
UM, READY TO GO?
HANNAH: YEAH!
WESLEY: COOL!
(SIGHS)
ALLI:
TWO SEATS,
CENTRE COURT IN THE REDS.
HOW'S THAT FOR AN APOLOGY?
JENNA:
WATCH THE JUMBOTRON.
I'D BE SURPRISED
IF DAVE DIDN'T PROPOSE.
YEAH.
WHOA!
THESE AREN'T THE CHEAP SEATS!
WELL, YOU AND ADAM
DID A FANTASTIC JOB
IN LINING UP MY VICTIMS.
YEAH, YOU'RE LUCKY
YOU DIDN'T GET CAUGHT.
(SCOFFS)
SO WHAT IF I DID?
GAMBLING IS PRETTY MUCH
LIKE APPLIED MATH,
WHICH WOULD MAKE THIS
ALL HOMEWORK.
AND ABOUT TAKING
PEOPLE'S CASH?
SO MUCH FUN.
CHECK THIS OUT:
I FOUND A POKER GAME
WITH REAL PEOPLE
PLAYING WITH REAL MONEY.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YOU'RE GONNA MEET UP
WITH A BUNCH OF STRANGERS
TO PLAY CARDS?
IT'S IN
A SECRET LOCATION!
ALLI, YOU COULD LOSE
A LOT OF MONEY.
I THINK WHAT YOU MEAN
TO SAY IS,
I COULD WIN A LOT
OF MONEY.
JENNA, I'M REALLY GOOD.
BESIDES, I'M DYING
FOR SOME REAL COMPETITION.
NO OFFENSE.
OKAY, SO SAY YOU WIN.
THERE'S GONNA BE
A BUNCH OF ANGRY GUYS
WATCHING YOU TAKE THEIR CASH.
YEAH, AND IT'S ALL PART
OF THE GAME!
ARE YOU SURE
THAT'S ALL IT IS?
OKAY...
POKER IS THE LAST THING
I THINK ABOUT
BEFORE I GOT TO BED,
AND THE FIRST THING
I THINK ABOUT
WHEN I WAKE UP
IN THE MORNING.
I KEEP COMING UP
WITH THESE STRATEGIES,
AND THIS IS
THE PERFECT OPPORTUNITY
TO TRY THEM ALL OUT!
(DOORBELL RINGS)
(SIGHS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
RIGHT ON TIME!
YOU GOT MY NOTE?
DAVE:
YEAH, I HEARD
THERE'S A "SUWPWISE."
(ALLI LAUGHS)
RAPTORS VERSUS THE KNICKS.
YOU GOT TICKETS?
YUP!
AND THIS!
SUIT UP.
NO YOU DIDN'T!
OH, YES, I DID!
THIS IS AMAZING!
NOW PUT IT ON.
WE'RE ABOUT TO HIT UP
SOME PREGAME WINGS, OKAY?
HELL YEAH!
♪♪♪
♪ All eyes they're on you ♪
♪ Don't deny you've got to ♪
♪ This is a call ♪
♪ That's all you'll ever
get from me ♪
♪ This is a call ♪
♪ It's all you'll ever
get from me ♪
♪ All eyes
they're on you ♪
♪ Don't deny you've got to ♪
♪ This is a call ♪
♪ That's all
you'll ever get... ♪
BUCKLE UP,
IT'S GONNA BE
A PLEASANT RIDE.
(SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
(STARTS CAR,
BLOWS OUT HIS BREATH)
(TIRES SCREECH)
EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT?
YUP!
YEAH, NO, THE SHIFTER,
IT'S JUST STICKY.
DRIVING WITH MY BOYFRIEND!
I COULD GET USED TO THIS.
(CAR RUMBLES)
DAVE:
OKAY, SO LET ME
GET THIS RIGHT.
YOU SCORED THESE TICKETS
BY FLEECING A FEW GUYS
AT POKER?
MORE THAN A FEW.
AND I MAY HAVE HAD
TO DIP INTO MY SAVINGS.
ALLI, YOU DIDN'T HAVE
TO DO ALL THAT.
AH, DON'T WORRY.
I'LL WIN IT BACK
IN A JIFFY.
YES, I DID HAVE TO.
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW
HOW MUCH YOU MEAN TO ME,
AND I WANT EVERY SECOND
WE SPEND TOGETHER
TO BE SPECIAL,
EVEN IF WE'RE NOT
DOING "IT."
OH, YEAH.
YOU KNOW, THERE'S NO RUSH
FOR ANY OF THAT STUFF.
SOME THINGS
ARE WORTH THE WAIT.
INCLUDING US.
YOU KNOW, I THINK
IT'S PRETTY AMAZING
THAT YOU GOT INTO
THAT SCIENCE PROGRAM.
AND WHAT'S TWO MONTHS,
RIGHT?
IT'LL FLY BY.
YEAH, BUT UH...
BEFORE YOU LEAVE,
YOU THINK YOU COULD
COME OVER TOMORROW NIGHT
FOR SOME PIZZA?
REALLY?
OF COURSE!
I TOLD MY FOLKS
ABOUT YOU.
THEY WANNA KNOW WHAT GIRL
I'M GONNA BE MISSIN'
LIKE CRAZY ALL SUMMER.
ABSOLUTELY!
TOMORROW IT IS.
OKAY!
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
LET'S GET TO THE GAME!
I'LL TAKE CARE
OF THE WINGS.
UH, OH NO,
I'VE GOT THESE.
ALLI, IT'S THE LEAST
I CAN DO.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
FINE.
(BOTH LAUGH)
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
TEXTING SOMEBODY?
(CLEARS THROAT)
ALLI:
UH NO, IT'S NOTHING.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)