JULIAN:
GIVING UP?
(GRUNTS) NEVER!
(GRUNTING)
JULIAN:
(GRUNTS IN PAIN)
(THUMPS HAND ON MAT)
WOO!
OWEN:
AND THE STUDENT
WHUPS THE MASTER!
NICE ESCAPE.
I THOUGHT I HAD YOU THERE.
THAT'S WHAT I WANTED
YOU TO THINK.
GUYS! ARMSTRONG!
EVERYTHING OKAY IN HERE,
GUYS?
YES, SIR.
EVERYTHING BUT MY BICEPS.
SHORTEN YOUR CURLS.
AND I NEED TO REMIND YOU GUYS
THAT THE WEIGHTROOM
IS FOR EVERYONE'S USE -
GUYS AND GIRLS.
OKAY?
UM, YOU GOT SOME...
JUST BIT MY LIP.
WHAT'S WITH LOCKING
PEOPLE OUT?
NOTHING.
IT'S JUST GUY STUFF.
AW, LOOK AT YOU GUYS
WITH YOUR CUTE LITTLE
SECRET BOY'S CLUB.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
OF COURSE YOU DON'T.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Oh oh-oh... ♪
(Oh oh-oh...)
♪ I can make it through ♪
(I can make it!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
OWEN:
SOON AS I SENT
THOSE GIRLS AWAY,
I KNEW THEY'D BLAB.
JULIAN:
WE NEED TO BE MORE CAREFUL.
DREW:
YEAH, LIKE PUTTING SOMEONE
WITH A BRAIN ON LOOKOUT.
JULIAN:
WE GOTTA LAY LOW.
NO FIGHTS.
C'MON.
ANYONE FINDS OUT
WE'RE WAILING ON EACH OTHER,
WE'LL GET SUSPENDED.
WE'RE TRAINING,
NOT FIGHTING.
FIGHTING IS FIGHTING.
ZERO TOLERANCE.
NO,
THERE'S A DIFFERENCE!
WE HAVE A WRESTLING TEAM,
BUT MMA TRAINING'S
NOT ALLOWED?
MAN,
THAT'S JUST BULL!
OWEN:
WHOA!
THROW A TANTRUM!
(BELL RINGS)
BETENKAMP:
AFTERNOON, CLASS.
JUST GIVE ME A MOMENT
WITH THESE PIPETTES...
YOU OKAY?
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE YOU GUYS
ARE SO READY TO GIVE UP.
IT IS WHAT IT IS,
ALL RIGHT?
MAYBE IT'LL BE BETTER
FOR YOU
TO CHILL FOR A BIT ANYWAY.
YOU KNOW I MISS YOU!
DAVE:
WE HAD LUNCH TOGETHER.
YEAH,
LIKE FIVE HOURS AGO!
DAVE:
OKAY, ALL RIGHT,
SO WHAT'S MY CUTE GIRL UP TO
AFTER SUPPER?
ALLI:
THE USUAL:
DISHES, HOMEWORK...
MISSING YOU MORE.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S REWORK THAT PLAN.
DISHES, HOMEWORK,
AND THEN WE HANG OUT.
YEAH,
NOW YOU'RE BEING CUTE.
YOU KNOW MY PARENTS
WON'T LET ME.
DAVE:
YOU ASKED ALREADY?
CAN I CALL YOU BACK?
(BEEP)
(CLEARS THROAT)
HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
I GOT AN EIGHTY-NINE
ON MY ENGLISH PAPER.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO NINETY?
ONLY TEASING.
GOOD GIRL.
YOU GOT ME.
HA!
HAVE I EVER TOLD YOU
HOW MUCH I LOVED
YOUR TIE?
(LAUGHS) IF YOU WANT
TO ORDER PIZZA,
JUST ASK ALLIA.
IT'S NOT THAT.
I WAS JUST WONDERING,
DO YOU THINK I COULD
GO OUT FOR A BIT
AFTER DINNER?
SURE.
IT'S NOTHING CRAZY,
I JUST...
YOU SAID, "SURE."
THANK YOU!
YOU HAVE BEEN
VERY RESPONSIBLE.
YOUR MOTHER AND I TALK ABOUT
HOW WELL YOU'RE DOING.
UH...
DID YOU OR MOM EVER DATE
IN HIGH SCHOOL?
(LAUGHS)
IS THIS A TRICK
QUESTION?
NO. I'M JUST CURIOUS.
AT YOUR AGE,
IT IS MUCH BETTER
TO MAKE GREAT FRIENDS.
RIGHT.
WHEN YOU SEE CLARE
TONIGHT,
TELL HER I SAY HELLO.
CLARE... YEAH.
WILL DO.
HOLLY J:
(CHUCKLES) NO.
YOU'RE THE ONLY GIRL
IN THE WORLD
WHO COULD PULL THIS OFF.
I SUPPOSE IT DOES TAKE A CERTAIN
JE NE SAIS QUOI.
THIS IS CUTE.
I DON'T EVEN FEEL
LIKE GOING TO PROM.
I'M SO DRAINED
FROM ALL THIS DIALYSIS,
AND I'M STILL PROCESSING
BEING ADOPTED.
NOT TO MENTION
THE TWENTY THOUSAND DOLLARS
YOUR BIRTH MOM WANTS
FOR HER KIDNEY.
YEAH, I'M DESCENDED
FROM A GOLD-DIGGER.
THE WHOLE THING
MAKES ME FEEL ICKY.
BUT I DON'T HAVE THE MONEY,
SO...
YES, YOU DO.
WHAT?
A PROM GIFT,
FROM ME TO YOU.
NO! FIONA, YOU CAN'T!
(SIGHS)
NOT LISTENING!
NO, MY PARENTS WILL SELL
THE CAR.
OUR LAWYER'S ALREADY SIGNING OFF
ON THE CHEQUE!
LOOK, I'D GIVE YOU
MY OWN KIDNEY IF I COULD,
SO JUST PUT
YOUR MORAL DILEMMAS ASIDE
AND GO GET THAT KIDNEY.
THANK YOU.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
OH, I THINK THAT'S HIM!
HI, SHERM?
SORRY?
BUT WE'RE NOT TRADING
IN ORGANS,
WE'RE JUST TRYING TO BUY
ONE LITTLE PINK KIDNEY!
(TAKEN ABACK CHUCKLE)
(SIGHS) OKAY.
THANKS, SHERM.
BYE.
WHAT'S WRONG?
APPARENTLY PAYING SOMEONE
FOR A KIDNEY
IS TOTALLY ILLEGAL.
(GASPS)
ADAM:
HEY, WHERE ARE
THE GAME CONTROLLERS?
I'M GONNA BLACK OP
YOUR BUTT INTO INFINITY.
(PANTING)
YOU KNOW,
THERE'S MORE TO LIFE
THAN JUST WORKING OUT.
I'M DOING SOME MIXED
MARTIAL ARTS
WITH OWEN AND JULIAN,
OKAY?
WHOA!
ULTIMATE FIGHTING?!
ADAM, IT'S AMAZING.
YOU GET, LIKE, THIS RUSH
THAT YOU CAN JUST...
TAKE ON ANYONE.
LIKE THE GUYS
WHO BEAT YOU UP?
WHAT? NO!
THE POINT IS... (PANTING)
IS THAT IT'S FUN.
WELL, AT LEAST IT WAS,
BEFORE WE GOT NARC'D ON
BY A BUNCH OF GIRLS.
NOW WE GOTTA FIND
SOMEWHERE ELSE TO TRAIN.
WELL, I'M GLAD
YOU FOUND SOMETHING
THAT MAKES YOU FEEL GOOD.
JUST GOTTA KEEP AT IT,
YOU KNOW?
HEY, FEEL LIKE STRAPPING ON
THE GLOVES?
YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
YEAH, ADAM.
'KAY, GOOD.
'CAUSE I LIKE
MY VIOLENCE VIRTUAL.
BRING IT.
(BELL RINGS)
'KAY, REMEMBER,
GRAB THE FULL KNEE
TO FLIP YOUR OPPONENT.
READY?
THREE, TWO, ONE...
GO!
(GRUNTING)
MATCH TO MO.
SPECTATORS:
(APPLAUD)
MO:
COME ON, COACH.
AGAIN?
GIVE ME A CHALLENGE!
ARMSTRONG:
WE'RE GONNA KEEP GOING
UNTIL SOMEBODY BEATS YOU.
ANYONE?
MR. TORRES?
HOW WOULD YOU LIKE TO ADD
ANOTHER SPORT TO YOUR RESUME?
(LAUGHS) NO THANKS, SIR.
I'LL PASS.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, IF ANY OF YOU
ARE INTERESTED
IN NEXT SEASON'S TRYOUTS,
COME SEE ME.
SO, UH, WHAT ARE YOU?
LIKE A HEAVYWEIGHT?
YOU MAKING FUN OF ME?
I'M WORKING ON IT!
NO, MAN.
I'M JUST SAYIN',
YOU'RE LIKE IN A LEAGUE
OF YOUR OWN.
YOU GONNA TRY OUT?
NAH.
I'M MORE OF AN MMA GUY.
OH YEAH.
TITO ORTIZ
IS THE MAN.
HE'S A MAN,
BUT IT'S ALL ABOUT GSP!
GEORGE ST. PIERRE?
OVERRATED!
OKAY.
SO WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE SETTLE THE MATTER,
HAND TO HAND?
WHEN AND WHERE?
(BELL RINGS)
SORRY OUR DATE WAS SO SPEEDY
LAST NIGHT.
A LITTLE ALLI
AND ICE CREAM
IS BETTER THAN
NO ALLI AND ICE CREAM.
MR. BETENKAMP:
DAVE T.
YOU FINALLY WATCH
THE ORIGINAL TRON?
I DID, I DID.
I HAVE THOUGHTS, MR B.
WE'LL TALK LATER?
YOU KNOW IT!
OKAY, ALL RIGHT!
WHAT, ARE YOU FRIENDS
WITH EVERY TEACHER?
I'M GOOD WITH ADULTS,
LIKE YOU ARE
WITH ADVANCED SCIENCE.
SEE YOU AFTER CLASS?
YEAH.
IF MY PARENTS ASK,
I WAS WITH YOU LAST NIGHT.
HASHTAG: DAUGHTER-OF-STRICT-
PARENT-DILEMMAS.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO ABOVE-BOARD BHANDARI?!
SHE CHICKENED OUT!
BOYFRIENDS ARE FORBIDDEN,
NON-NEGOTIABLE.
BUT YOUR PARENTS
HAVE COME SO FAR.
AND THAT'S JUST IT.
WE LAUGH,
THEY'RE PROUD OF ME.
I DON'T WANNA HAVE TO GO BACK
TO SQUARE ONE.
IT'S JUST I DON'T WANNA
HAVE TO LIE TO THEM ANYMORE.
OKAY, LET ME BLOW YOUR MIND HERE
FOR A SECOND.
WHAT IF YOU INVITED DAVE
OVER TO YOUR PLACE,
INTRODUCE HIM
AS YOUR FRIEND,
AND THEN, ONCE YOUR
PARENTS LIKE HIM,
YOU PULL BACK THE CURTAIN.
THE BOYFRIEND REVEAL.
THAT MIGHT BE AN EXPERIMENT
WORTH TRYING.
MO:
YOU SURE YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE GETTING YOURSELF INTO?
DREW:
I COULD SAY THE SAME FOR YOU.
YOU GOTTA WATCH
THE HANDS.
MO:
OH, YOU WANNA PLAY
LIKE THAT, EH?
(GRUNTS)
(HEAVY THUMP)
(GRUNTING)
MO:
ARRGH!
ALL RIGHT! ENOUGH!
GSP'S NOT OVERRATED!
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT!
BOOM!
♪ ...the cream of the crop ♪
♪ Now they call me that ♪
♪ The best - not a title -
a matter of fact ♪
THANKS.
IT'S ALWAYS GOOD
TO GET A JOLT OF CAFFEINE
BEFORE THE SCHOOL
DROP OFF.
YOU'RE NOT HAVING ONE?
NO, I NEED TO WATCH
MY LIQUIDS -
DIALYSIS AND ALL.
RIGHT.
BUT THAT'LL CHANGE, RIGHT?
SOON.
YEAH.
UM... ABOUT THAT.
JOSH, BREANNE.
C'MON,
EAT YOUR MUFFINS, GUYS!
LOOK, I CAN'T PAY YOU
FOR YOUR KIDNEY.
I KNOW I ASKED A LOT,
BUT-
NO, IT'S NOT THE MONEY,
IT'S UM...
IT'S ILLEGAL.
BUT IT'S NOT AGAINST THE LAW
IF YOU DONATE IT.
SO...
I'M BEGGING YOU.
HOLLY J,
MY LIFE IS NUTS.
AFTER I DROP
THESE MINI-MONSTERS OFF,
I'M AT WORK
FOR NINE HOURS.
OKAY, I'M ASKING THE WORLD,
I KNOW.
I HAVE A FRIEND
WHO'S AN RN.
SHE SAYS THAT IT WILL TAKE
THREE MONTHS TO RECOVER
FROM THE DONATION.
I'M A SINGLE MOM.
YOU'D BE GIVING ME
MY LIFE.
I CAN'T AFFORD TO TAKE
THAT KIND OF TIME OFF WORK.
THE DONOR LIST
WILL COME THROUGH.
YOU UNDERSTAND,
RIGHT?
I UNDERSTAND THAT
YOU'RE SO SELFISH
YOU'LL LITERALLY GIVE UP
A BABY WITHOUT A THOUGHT.
AND THEN WHEN YOU CAN
SAVE HER LIFE...
HOLLY J, PLEASE!
YOU LET HER DOWN AGAIN.
YOU REALLY SHOULDN'T
HAVE CHILDREN
IF YOU'RE NOT GONNA
BE THERE FOR THEM!
♪ On top of the world ♪
♪ Where you can find me at ♪
♪ The cream of the crop ♪
♪ Now they call me that ♪
♪ The best -
not a title - ♪
♪ A matter of fact ♪
♪ Now that I got the crowd ♪
♪ Ain't no giving it back ♪
WHAT'S UP, DREW?
NOT MUCH, KATIE.
I SAW YOUR LITTLE DISAGREEMENT
ABOUT GSP WITH MO.
GLAD TO KNOW YOU'RE A FAN.
SO, YOU GONNA RUN
AND TELL ARMSTRONG AGAIN?
FOR THE RECORD?
THAT WASN'T ME.
I SWORE OFF TATTLE-TALING
IN KINDERGARTEN.
I JUST WANT TO ASK
YOU SOMETHING.
IN THAT CASE,
YES, I AM FREE FOR PROM.
SO WHAT DO YOU
GET OUT OF IT?
I MEAN, DO YOU LIKE HURTING
PEOPLE OR SOMETHING?
DREW:
IT'S NOT ABOUT
HURTING ANYONE.
ME AND THE GUYS
DO A LOT OF SPORTS.
MOST SPORTS DON'T INVOLVE
WAILING ON EACH OTHER.
'KAY, WAIT.
WHY DO YOU CARE?
I'M WRITING SOMETHING
FOR THE PAPER
ON VIOLENCE
IN YOUTH CULTURE.
WHAT? NO.
YOU CAN'T-
DON'T WORRY,
IT'S ANONYMOUS.
AND MAYBE
I'M A LITTLE CURIOUS...
ABOUT YOU.
OKAY, LOOK,
WHEN I BEAT SOMEONE,
HAND-TO-HAND,
I KNOW THAT I CAN SURVIVE.
I KNOW THAT THEY HAVEN'T
COMPLETELY BEATEN ME DOWN.
AND WHO ARE THEY?
NOBODY.
JUST AN EXPRESSION.
OKAY. COOL.
OH, HEY CUTIE!
LET ME SPRING SOMETHING
ON YOU HERE:
HOW WOULD YOU FEEL ABOUT
MEETING MY PARENTS TONIGHT?
COOL.
YOU'RE GONNA BE GREAT,
YOU'VE NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
I'M NOT WORRIED.
I'M INTO IT.
OKAY, SO I'LL MEET YOU
AFTER SCHOOL
FOR A QUICK PREP SESSION.
(STUTTERS) PREP?
YOU KNOW, THE BASICS:
WHAT TO SAY,
WHAT NOT TO SAY.
AM I MEETING THE QUEEN
OF ENGLAND,
OR AM I MEETING
YOUR PARENTS?
YOU ALREADY KNOW
MOST ADULTS LOVE ME.
MY PARENTS AREN'T
MOST ADULTS.
LET'S JUST SAY
THEY'RE A LITTLE...
PARTICULAR.
BUT IF OUR MEETING
GOES WELL,
YOU AND I GET TO HANG OUT
AT MY PLACE WHENEVER WE WANT,
NO SNEAKING AROUND.
ALL RIGHT.
I LIKE THE SOUND OF THAT.
GOOD. AND REMEMBER,
NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
(GIGGLES)
I WASN'T WORRIED...
JULIAN:
PSST!
(WHISPERS)
WHERE WERE YOU AT LUNCH?
I WASN'T IN THE WEIGHT ROOM
TAKING DOWN THE MOST BAD-ASS
HEAVYWEIGHT WRESTLER
IN THE SCHOOL,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
YOU FOUGHT MO?
YEAH, I WHUPPED HIM GOOD,
AND NOTHING HAPPENED,
YOU CHICKENS!
SO NOBODY SAW YOU?
WELL, ONE GIRL,
BUT I THINK SHE LIKES ME.
NO, NO, NO,
NOT THE NEWSPAPER CHICK!
SHHH!
YEAH, KATIE.
I KNOW.
DON'T WORRY,
I'LL GET HER ON BOARD
AND WE CAN USE HER
AS A LOOKOUT.
ALL RIGHT. GOOD.
'CAUSE I JUST LEARNED A NEW MOVE
YOU WILL NOT SEE COMING,
PRETTY BOY.
WE JUST GOTTA KEEP IT LEGIT;
STICK WITH THE DISCIPLINE
AND WORK ON TECHNIQUE.
BETENKAMP:
GUYS!
I ASSUME YOU'RE DISCUSSING
THIS CHEMICAL COMPOUND?
DREW:
YES, SIR.
GREAT. DREW, WHY DON'T YOU
COME ON UP,
TALK US THROUGH IT.
DREW:
(SIGHS) O-KAY.
OOH! THAT LOOKS NASTY.
YOU OKAY?
NEVER BETTER, SIR.
ALLI:
SO DON'T SAY ANYTHING
ABOUT RAP MUSIC.
DAVE:
HOLLA!
BUT DO MENTION THAT
YOUR DAD'S A COP.
THOUGH YOU SHOULD PROBABLY
SAY POLICE OFFICER.
WHAT'S HIS RANK AGAIN?
UH, DETECTIVE CONSTABLE,
I THINK.
YEAH, SAY THAT.
THAT SOUNDS GOOD.
ARE YOU WRITING THIS DOWN?
NO? UM, IT'S OKAY,
I HAVE CUE CARDS.
I CAN WRITE IT DOWN FOR YOU.
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE READY
TO DO ALL THIS -
INTRODUCE ME AT HOME?
'CAUSE-
OF COURSE I AM.
WHY WOULDN'T I BE?
BECAUSE YOU'RE ACTING
LIKE I'M IN THE CIA.
I'M JUST YOUR BOYFRIEND.
WE CAN NOT USE THE B-WORD.
WHOA. HOLD UP.
I THOUGHT YOUR PARENTS
WERE MEETING YOUR BOYFRIEND.
LOOK, I'M SORRY,
I'VE JUST NEVER
DONE THIS BEFORE -
BROUGHT A BOY HOME.
SO YOU'RE NERVOUS.
MY PARENTS ARE TOUGH,
DAVE.
BUT I KNOW THEY'RE JUST
LOOKING OUT FOR ME.
SO, IF I JUST BARGE IN
WITH A BOYFRIEND...
THEY'LL PUT UP A FORCE FIELD?
BUT IF I INTRODUCE YOU
AS MY FRIEND,
THEY'LL GENUINELY LOVE YOU.
AND THEN WE CAN DROP
THE BF BOMB.
IS THAT ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, FOR YOU IT'S 'AIGHT.
(SIGHS)
SO WHAT DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT CRICKET?
UH...
HOLLY J:
GOD.
I MIGHT AS WELL BURN
MY YALE ACCEPTANCE
'CAUSE I'LL BE STUCK
TO THIS MACHINE
UNTIL I DIE!
I TAKE IT YOU DIDN'T MAKE
A CONNECTION WITH DAWN?
I CALLED HER SELFISH.
I SAID SHE NEVER SHOULD'VE
HAD CHILDREN.
YEESH!
BUT YOU'RE ALLOWED
TO BE MAD AT HER.
BUT I'M THE SELFISH ONE;
I NEVER EVEN TRIED
TO GET TO KNOW HER
AND NOW I NEVER WILL.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO TELL YOUR MOM?
I'LL HAVE TO TELL HER
SHE WASN'T A MATCH.
LISTEN, WE JUST NEED
TO HANG ONTO HOPE;
KEEP FIGHTING.
I'M TIRED.
BUT YOU'RE NOT DONE TRYING,
ARE YOU?
(KNOCKING)
ALLI: HI.
DAVE: HI.
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYS QUIETLY)
ALLI:
SO THIS IS MY FRIEND DAVE-ID.
NICE TO MEET YOU,
DAVID.
UH, AND YOU,
MR. BHANDARI.
PLEASE, SIT, DAVID.
THANKS.
I'VE MADE TEA.
OH, I'M FINE THANKS,
I DON'T-
I'D LOVE SOME.
THANK YOU.
ALLI:
DAVE AND I...
DAVID AND I SPEND
A LOT OF TIME TOGETHER.
WE'RE REALLY GOOD
STUDY BUDDIES.
YEAH.
ALLI'S BIG ON STUDYING.
SHE KEEPS MY GRADES UP.
IT'S NICE TO HEAR THAT
ALLI'S A GOOD INFLUENCE.
SO, WHAT DOES YOUR FATHER DO,
DAVID?
HE'S A DETECTIVE CONSTABLE.
MRS. BHANDARI:
OH, THAT'S VERY INTERESTING!
I NEVER MISS "NCIS", "CSI",
OR "THE MENTALIST".
LOVELY SHOWS.
DO YOU LIKE SPORTS,
DAVID?
YEAH, YEAH.
BASKETBALL'S MY GAME.
BUT LATELY I'VE BEEN
GETTING TO KNOW CRICKET.
AH!
DID YOU HAPPEN TO SEE
THE INDIA/SOUTH AFRICA GAME?
YEAH. YEAH, YEAH. I DID.
WITH UH...
VIRENDER.
VIRENDER SSS...
SEHWAG.
DAVE:
PHEW!
(SLURPS TOO QUICKLY
AND SPITS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
UM...
IT'S OKAY.
DREW:
SO I'M THINKING WE SEE IF MO
CAN RECRUIT A FEW MORE GUYS
FROM THE WRESTLING TEAM.
JULIAN:
PAIR A FEW GUYS UP,
AND COME NEXT WEEK...
OWEN:
YEAH! AND WE GOT OURSELVES
AN MMA TOURNAMENT!
ALL RIGHT.
HEY, SIR.
OH, YOU WANNA GET IN THERE,
FELLAS?
I JUST WANTED TO, UH,
GET A QUICK WORKOUT IN -
HEALTH INITIATIVE AND ALL.
IT'S USUALLY OPEN.
YEAH,
IT'LL BE OPEN AGAIN,
BUT WITH SUPERVISION
AND SIGN-UPS.
I'VE HEARD A FEW STORIES.
FROM WHO?
YOU KNOW I APPROVE
THE SCHOOL NEWSPAPER.
THE LATEST EDITION
THERE ARE REPORTS OF FIGHTING.
PERFECT.
WHATEVER SHE SAID
IS A LOAD OF CRAP, SIR.
DREW.
CAN YOU JUST LET US IN?
PLEASE?
WE NEED TO TRAIN!
LOOK, I KNOW YOU
FEEL STRONGLY-
DON'T TOUCH ME!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GOING TO LET YOU COOL DOWN
IN DETENTION.
I'M SORRY, SIR.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO-
WE'LL TALK TO HIM.
HE'S HAVING A HARD DAY.
(BELL RINGS)
YEAH.
WELL, IF I HEAR ABOUT
ANY MORE VIOLENCE,
I'LL KNOW WHO TO LOOK FOR.
THOUGHT YOUR GIRLFRIEND
COULD KEEP SECRETS.
(LAUGHS)
I WILL NEVER FORGET
MY FIRST LIVE GAME
AT BRABOURNE STADIUM
IN MUMBAI.
INDIA WAS PLAYING ENGLAND!
AS ALLI WOULD SAY,
IT WAS EPIC!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE SHOULD ALL WATCH
A GAME TOGETHER!
GREAT IDEA!
SHALL I GET YOU
SOME MORE TEA?
MOM?
COULD THIS BE
GOING ANY BETTER?
WHAT'S WRONG?
LOOK, I THOUGHT YOUR PARENTS
WERE SUPPOSED TO GET TO KNOW
THE REAL ME.
BUT IT'S GOING
SO WELL.
IT'S ALL FAKE!
NOT ALL OF IT.
YOU'RE BEING NICE
AND THE REAL YOU IS NICE!
YEAH, BUT THE REAL ME
WOULDN'T TUCK IN HIS SHIRT
AND DRINK TEA.
LET'S FACE IT,
THE REAL YOU WOULDN'T HAVE
LASTED A MINUTE!
OKAY, THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT.
NO...
MORE TEA?
SORRY, I ACTUALLY
GOTTA HEAD OUT;
MY DAD NEEDS HELP
IN THE YARD.
MRS. BHANDARI:
OF COURSE.
COME BACK AND VISIT AGAIN SOON.
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
(KEYBOARD KEYS CLACK,
DOOR OPENS)
DREW:
YOU LIED TO ME.
EXCUSE ME?
I JUST GOT OUT OF DETENTION.
YOUR STUPID PIECE
WASN'T ANONYMOUS!
THERE ISN'T A SINGLE
NAME IN IT.
SORRY, BUT I'M TRYING TO FINISH
THE INTRAMURAL ROUND-UP.
NOT A SINGLE WRITER
ON STAFF
HAS ANY INTEREST
IN SPORTS.
SIMPSON SHUT
THE WEIGHT ROOM DOWN.
YOU NEED TO SIGN UP
AND HAVE A TEACHER
SUPERVISE NOW.
SO THE PRINCIPAL
FINALLY FIGURED OUT
WHAT'S GOING ON
IN HIS OWN SCHOOL.
HOW IS THAT MY PROBLEM?
I THOUGHT YOU LIKED ME.
LOOK, I'VE HEARD STORIES
ABOUT YOU;
RUMOURS ABOUT
WHY YOU MISSED SCHOOL
AFTER SPRING BREAK.
IF YOU'RE HIDING
SOMETHING,
MAYBE I CAN HELP.
HOW?
BY PUTTING MY PERSONAL CRAP
IN YOUR PAPER?
WELL,
HERE'S THE STORY:
DREW TORRES IS AN IDIOT.
HE THOUGHT KATIE MALTIN
WAS SOMEONE HE COULD TRUST.
(CHAIR CRASHES)
(DOOR BANGS SHUT)