CLARE:
ALLI, ALL I SAID WAS HE'S TALL
AND HE HAS A TRUCK.
NO, I NEVER SAID JAKE MARTIN
IS HOTTER THAN MOLTEN LAVA.
WELL, HE CERTAINLY LACKS
HIS FATHER'S CHARM, BUT...
UH, GLENN...
YOU KNOW JAKE
IS A GREAT YOUNG MAN.
VERY... STRAPPING.
WELL, IF YOU WANT
TO SAY HELLO,
HE'S IN THE KITCHEN
CLEANING UP.
HE CAME OVER TO HELP ME
WITH THE RENO.
(EXHALES)
JAKE:
HOW LONG HAVE YOU
BEEN THERE?
A-A MINUTE.
LESS THAN A MINUTE.
LIKE, MORE LIKE A SECOND,
BUT...
DO YOU OFTEN GET CHANGED
IN OTHER PEOPLE'S KITCHENS?
I DIDN'T KNOW
I HAD AN AUDIENCE.
I WASN'T STARING,
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK.
(LAUGHS)
IT'S OKAY IF YOU WERE.
WELL, I WASN'T.
I HAVE HOMEWORK.
OKAY. SEE YOU AROUND.
OKAY.
(LOUD THUD)
UH... YEAH.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh... ♪
(I can make it)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
ALLI:
SO DID JAKE LOOK GOOD?
I BET HE DID.
CLARE:
ALLI, I HAVE ONE HOUR
TO FINISH MY ARTICLE
ON THE CONCEPT
FOR THE SCHOOL PLAY,
WHICH ACCORDING TO ELI
IS THE STORY OF CLARA,
A PSYCHOPATH WHO DESTROYS
EVERYTHING IN HER PATH.
SO I'M SO NOT IN THE MOOD
TO TALK ABOUT THIS RIGHT NOW.
FINE, BUT YOU'D BETTER
DRAW ME A PICTURE LATER.
BOTH:
(GIGGLE)
KATIE:
JAKE, SO GLAD YOU COULD BE PART
OF MY PROFILE ON NEW STUDENTS.
SO, TELL ME,
HAVE YOUR FIRST WEEKS
AT DEGRASSI BEEN EASY?
JAKE:
(SIGHS) WELL, SOME PEOPLE
HAVE SURPRISED ME.
KATIE:
THAT'S GOOD, ISN'T IT?
JAKE:
ABSOLUTELY!
BECAUSE AS A NEW STUDENT,
YOU FEEL NAKED.
LIKE ALL EYES ARE ON YOU,
STARING...
UNABLE TO LOOK AWAY.
KATIE:
SOUNDS LIKE
MY WORST NIGHTMARE.
WELL, DEPENDS ON
WHO'S LOOKING.
ALLI:
AH... FIRST MOVIE NIGHT
OF THE SEMESTER.
WE NEED A FILM
THAT'S EPIC AND ICONIC.
WHAT ABOUT GREASE?
WE COULD DO A SING-A-LONG.
SO WE'RE PLANNING
AN ALL-GIRLS MOVIE NIGHT?
AND WHAT DO YOU SUGGEST?
A KUNG-FU MOVIE?
NO, A CLASSIC COMEDY.
UH, MARX BROTHERS,
CHAPLIN...
WHAT ABOUT ZOMBIES?
OR ZOMBIES!
OF COURSE, ZOMBIES!
WHY'D WE STOP
HANGING OUT AGAIN?
'CAUSE YOU STARTED DATING
DREAMY TORRES.
RIGHT, NOT THE SMARTEST
DECISION EVER MADE.
WE SHOULD CATCH UP.
WANNA GO FOR WINGS,
TOMORROW NIGHT,
AFTER WE POSTER
FOR MOVIE NIGHT?
YEAH, SOUNDS GOOD.
I'LL HAVE TO CHECK
WITH SADIE THOUGH.
GOOD LUCK.
GIRLFRIENDS DON'T
LET BOYFRIENDS
HANG OUT WITH GIRL FRIENDS
'CAUSE THEY'RE AFRAID
THAT WILL HAPPEN.
WHAT? NO. KC AND MARISOL
ARE JUST FRIENDS.
LIKE US.
WHICH IS WHY SADIE
WILL HAVE NO PROBLEM
WITH US HANGING OUT.
TEN DOLLARS SAYS
YOU ARE WRONG.
SADIE TRUSTS ME.
THEN I'LL SEE YOU
TOMORROW NIGHT.
(CHUCKLES)
DO YOU HAVE
YOUR CELL PHONE?
OKAY, I PROGRAMMED
OFFICER TURNER'S NUMBER.
SO IF YOU NOTICE
ANYTHING SUSPICIOUS-
MA, ARE YOU GOING TO BE
LIKE THIS EVERY DAY?
HONEY, IT'S YOUR FIRST DAY
BACK AT SCHOOL SINCE-
ADAM:
THOSE GANG MEMBERS WENT
GRAND THEFT AUTO ON YOUR BUTT.
ADAM!
LISTEN, ONE MORE DAY
AT HOME WOULDN'T HURT.
I-I COULD CANCEL
MY MEETINGS.
I HAVE A NUMBER
OF A PSYCHOLOGIST-
OKAY, MOM, ENOUGH.
I SPENT A MONTH
DEALING WITH THE AFTERMATH
OF SPRING BREAK.
I WANT FUN,
I WANT FRIENDS,
I WANT MY OLD LIFE BACK.
(CHUCKLES)
YEAH, I KNOW DREW, BUT...
NO BUTS.
THE COPS ARE WATCHING
THE GUYS WHO BEAT ME UP.
IT'S TIME TO MOVE ON,
AND GOING BACK TO SCHOOL
IS THE BEST WAY I KNOW HOW.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
STUDENT:
WATCH IT!
I HATE HIM. I HATE HIM.
I HATE HIM.
ELI?
WHY CAN'T I STOP PICTURING
HIS HALF-NAKED BODY?
DEFINITELY NOT ELI.
IT'S LIKE HE KNOWS
WHAT I'M THINKING
AND HE'S MOCKING ME.
MAYBE HE LIKES YOU.
DON'T SAY THAT.
WHAT? HE'S CUTE,
SINGLE,
HE DOESN'T DRIVE
HEARSES INTO WALLS.
YOU DON'T KNOW THAT.
HE COULD BE
A HOMICIDAL MANIAC
WHO LURES GIRLS IN
WITH HIS SEXY SMILE. UGH.
OR THE PERFECT REBOUND.
OKAY,
MY EX HAS WRITTEN A PLAY
THAT PAINTS ME
AS A PSYCHOPATH.
MY MOM IS THROWING PARTIES
TO CELEBRATE HER DIVORCE.
GIVE ME ONE REASON
WHY I WOULD WANT TO START
A RELATIONSHIP WITH JAKE.
BECAUSE YOU CAN'T STOP
THINKING
ABOUT HIS SEXY SMILE.
WELL, I AM CERTAINLY
GOING TO TRY.
BETENKAMP:
OKAY, WE'VE COVERED
THE HEART.
ON TO THE REPRODUCTIVE ORGANS.
DREW:
INTRAMURAL DODGEBALL CAPTAINS,
MEET YOUR NEW MVP.
KC:
YOU ARE JUST IN TIME.
WE GOT SMOKED
IN OUR LAST GAME.
MARISOL:
YOU UH...
SURE YOU'RE UP FOR IT?
WORD IS THAT GANG
PRACTICALLY KILLED YOU.
THERE WERE, LIKE,
TEN GUYS, RIGHT?
ARE THEY STILL AFTER YOU?
(GASP) GOD, I BET THEY ARE.
YOU MUST BE SO SCARED.
I'M FINE.
REALLY?
C-CAUSE I'D BE TERRIFIED.
KC:
MARE...
GIVE US A SEC?
YEAH. SURE.
YOU OKAY, DUDE?
I'M FINE.
LOOK, YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE
WHO'S BEEN THROUGH STUFF.
BACK WHEN MY MOM
WAS ON DRUGS,
I WAS SCARED
ALL THE TIME.
I COULDN'T TRUST ANYONE.
I SAID I'M FINE.
HEY,
THAT'S WHAT I SAID TOO.
OKAY, WELL,
I'M NOT YOU.
(BIG CRASH)
CLARE:
MOM, I'M HOME!
(GASPS)
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
HELLO TO YOU, TOO.
(LAUGHS)
I THINK
IT'S A FAIR QUESTION.
DAD WANTED ME TO FINISH
WITH THE SINK.
WANNA HELP?
I CAN'T.
UM... I'VE GOT PLANS.
WITH MY MOM.
MRS. EDWARDS:
OH. SOUNDS LOVELY,
CLARE-BEAR,
BUT I'M MEETING A FRIEND
FOR DINNER TONIGHT.
WELL, THEN I'LL COME, TOO.
THE MORE, THE MERRIER!
I'M NOT SURE.
YOU SEE IT'S KIND OF A...
CLARE:
A DATE?
NO, NO.
MY FRIEND WANTS TO TALK
ABOUT TROUBLE WITH A SON.
WHY DON'T YOU AND JAKE
ORDER IN A PIZZA?
OKAY? MUAH!
YOU KNOW,
BEFORE THE DIVORCE
MY MOM WOULDN'T LET
A BOY IN THE HOUSE.
NOW SHE'S HAPPY TO LEAVE ME
ALONE WITH ONE.
WELL... WHAT'D SHE THINK
YOU'D DO?
HOMEWORK.
LOTS OF HOMEWORK.
SORRY I'M LATE.
MOVIE NIGHT STUFF.
THE TRIALS OF BEING
THE GIRLFRIEND OF A CLASS REP.
LOOK,
ONCE MOVIE NIGHT'S OVER,
YOU'LL HAVE
MY FULL ATTENTION.
OKAY, BUT EVEN THE MOST
DEDICATED POLITICIAN
NEEDS TO TAKE A BREAK.
ALL-YOU-CAN-EAT CHOCOLATE
FONDUE TOMORROW NIGHT?
COUPLES ONLY.
UH... TOMORROW?
WHO'S STEALING YOU AWAY
THIS TIME?
UH... ADAM.
WE'RE WORKING
ON THE RADIO SHOW.
BUT I CAN CANCEL FOR YOU.
THE POSSESSIVE GIRLFRIEND?
NOT EVERYBODY'S
FAVOURITE CHARACTER.
GO. HAVE FUN.
(LAUGHS)
UH... YOU'RE THE BEST.
CLARE:
ALLI, YOU NEED TO COME OVER.
MY MOM'S OUT
AND ALL I CAN THINK ABOUT
IS KISSING JAKE,
WHO IS IN MY HOUSE,
SWEATING.
SO? YOUR DAD'LL HAVE
ANOTHER BIRTHDAY NEXT YEAR.
JAKE:
CLARE? PIZZA'S HERE.
GOTTA GO.
I-I'M NOT HUNGRY.
UH... JUST DIG IN.
(KNOCKING)
EVERYTHING OKAY?
YOU SOUND MORE TENSE
THAN USUAL.
EVERYTHING'S GREAT.
'CAUSE IT SUCKED
WHEN MY PARENTS SPLIT.
(EXHALES)
MY FOLKS HAD
THESE OTHER LIVES
THAT I WASN'T A PART OF.
THEY WENT OUT ON DATES,
TOOK CARDIO FIT.
SOMETIMES I FELT
THAT THEY'D FORGOTTEN
ALL ABOUT ME.
♪ You're gonna start
11 steps behind me ♪
♪ You are the one for me,
boy, ♪
♪ You give me butterflies ♪
♪ From my head to my feet ♪
♪ And I knew from day one... ♪
H-HOW ABOUT THAT PIZZA?
I'M NOT THAT HUNGRY.
ME NEITHER.
♪ You give me butterflies ♪
♪ From my head to my feet ♪
CLARE:
I'M GOING STRAIGHT TO HELL.
FOR KISSING A CUTE BOY?
I HAVE RULES.
I CAN'T JUST MAKE OUT
WITH EVERY HUNK
WHO BARGES INTO MY LIFE.
DID YOU JUST USE
THE WORD HUNK?
OKAY,
SO NOT THE POINT.
I'D JUST HATE FOR YOU TO MISS
OUT ON A GREAT OPPORTUNITY
JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE SCARED.
OF WHAT?
GETTING HURT.
I'M NOT.
OKAY,
BUT CAN YOU BLAME ME?
I DON'T HAVE THE BEST
TRACK RECORD WITH GUYS.
CLARE,
YOU'RE AN AWESOME GIRL,
BUT NOT EVERY GUY
IS GOING TO CRASH A CAR
INTO A WALL FOR YOU.
I DID HAVE LOTS OF FUN
LAST NIGHT.
WHAT'S THE WORST
THAT COULD HAPPEN?
WE COULD JUST START SLOW.
NO NEED TO RUSH.
THAT'LL BE TEN DOLLARS.
WAIT, YOU'RE CHARGING ME
FOR ADVICE?
NO, MOVIE NIGHT TICKETS.
MIGHT BE A GOOD IDEA
FOR YOU AND JAKEY BOY
TO SPEND TIME
IN AN UPRIGHT POSITION.
HA-HA!
HEY!
(EXHALES)
ADAM:
SO, IS IT TRUE?
I DON'T KNOW,
I LEFT MY CRYSTAL BALL
AT HOME.
PEOPLE ARE SAYING
YOU WHOOPED KC
DURING INTRAMURALS
YESTERDAY.
IT WAS A MISUNDERSTANDING.
(LOCKER SLAMS)
YOU KNOW, GUY STUFF.
RIGHT... GUY STUFF.
I GOOGLED "SUDDEN RAGE".
IT'S COMMON AFTER TRAUMA
AND...
SO ARE NIGHTMARES.
I HEARD YOU SCREAMING
LAST NIGHT.
YOU MUST'VE BEEN DREAMING.
"PLEASE DON'T KILL ME."
DID MOM HEAR?
DUNNO.
I SWEAR,
IF YOU TELL HER...
MOM WAS RIGHT.
YOU HAVE, LIKE,
POST-TRAUMATIC STRESS DISORDER.
YOU NEED HELP.
NO, WHAT I NEED
IS FOR EVERYONE
TO GET OUT OF MY BUSINESS!
NOW, YOU'RE SCARING ME!
PUSHING KC WAS AN ACCIDENT.
I'M GOING TO APOLOGIZE,
THEN I'M GOING
TO MOVE ON.
AND IT WOULD BE A LOT EASIER
IF EVERYONE JUST DID THE SAME.
OKAY?
♪♪♪
♪ Saw you on the train ♪
♪ Except it wasn't you again ♪
♪ And I could not contain ♪
♪ That feeling
in my heart again ♪
♪ For what it's worth ♪
♪ I still love you ♪
♪ I still need you ♪
♪ And I just can't
let you go... ♪
ADAM:
FIVE MINUTES TILL SHOWTIME.
TODAY WE TAKE ON THE DELICATE
TOPIC OF FLATULENCE:
WHEN IS IT APPROPRIATE
TO LET ONE GO?
UH, HOW ABOUT NEVER?
(SNIFFS)
ESPECIALLY NOW.
BOTH:
(LAUGH)
HEY, IF SADIE ASKS,
YOU AND I HAVE A DATE TONIGHT.
I HAVE ABSOLUTELY
NOTHING TO WEAR.
HEH. YOU'RE HILARIOUS.
SO WHAT'S THE REAL REASON
YOU'RE LYING
TO YOUR GIRLFRIEND?
XBOX MARATHON?
BAREKNUCKLE BOXING?
UH, NO.
I'M MEETING UP WITH ALLI.
YOU'RE GOING ON A DATE?
NO, WE'RE JUST FRIENDS.
DIDN'T YOU HAVE
THE HOTS FOR HER?
YEAH, LIKE A MILLION
YEARS AGO.
REJECTED!
(LAUGHS)
IT WAS MUTUAL.
OH, SO NOW YOU GUYS
ARE JUST FRIENDS?
AND ONE FRIEND
SHOULD BE ALLOWED
TO HANG OUT WITH ANOTHER.
ABSOLUTELY.
BUT IF YOU AND ALLI
ARE JUST FRIENDS,
WHY DID YOU LIE
TO SADIE?
♪ And I just can't
let you go ♪
KATIE:
CLARE, ARE YOU DONE THIS WEEK'S
COVERAGE OF THE PLAY?
IT'S ON THE SERVER.
ELI STILL WON'T SHARE
THE SCRIPT,
BUT FIONA CONFIRMED THAT
AUDITIONS START NEXT WEEK.
I'LL SEE YOU
AT THE MEETING?
YEAH.
HEY, I MEANT TO ASK YOU
SOMETHING.
YOU HAVE EXPERIENCE
WITH JAKE MARTIN, RIGHT?
WHY?
WHAT DID HE SAY?
YOU SAID YOUR FAMILIES
WERE FRIENDS.
OH YEAH, WE USED TO RENT
A COTTAGE NEAR HIS.
IN YOUR OPINION...
IS HE A DECENT GUY?
UH, YEAH. SURE.
THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'S REALLY GOOD.
SO DO YOU THINK-
I-I HEARD HE'S INVOLVED
WITH SOMEONE.
THEN WHY DID HE AGREE TO GO
TO MOVIE NIGHT WITH ME?
I, I DON'T KNOW.
UM, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
I HAVE MORE QUESTIONS -
AT LEAST TEN.
I HAVE A MEETING
I HAVE TO CANCEL.
DODGEBALL TEAM:
(YELLING)
B-E A-G-G-R-E-S-S-I-V-E.
BE AGGRESSIVE! BE AGGRESSIVE!
BE AGGRESSIVE!
(CHEERING)
DREW:
IS THERE ROOM
FOR ONE MORE?
OKAY, I'M SORRY FOR FLIPPING OUT
ON YOU YESTERDAY.
ARE WE GOOD?
AS LONG AS YOU CHANNEL
SOME OF THAT AGGRESSION
ONTO THE COURT.
DEAL.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
♪♪♪
♪ Love me! ♪
♪ 'Cause misery loves company ♪
♪ It's a mystery ♪
♪ Why I let you do
these things to me ♪
CLARE:
CAN I HAVE
THAT NOTE BACK?
OH, UH, THIS NOTE?
SO YOU NO LONGER WANNA
HAVE FUN WITH ME TONIGHT?
SOMETHING CAME UP.
DID I DO SOMETHING
TO PISS YOU OFF?
I JUST THOUGHT THAT...
AFTER WE...
ARE YOU GOING TO MOVIE NIGHT
WITH KATIE?
YEAH, SHE ASKED ME.
I SAID YES.
GOOD. GLAD WE CLEARED
THAT UP.
HEY, BUT IT DOESN'T MEAN
I DON'T WANNA...
HANG OUT WITH YOU TOO.
SO WHAT?
I'M, LIKE, THE OTHER WOMAN?
YOU'RE ANOTHER WOMAN.
AFTER MY FOLKS SPLIT,
I GAVE UP RELATIONSHIPS.
IT'S TOO MUCH HURT.
AFTER YOUR MESSY BREAK-UP,
I THOUGHT YOU'D FEEL THE SAME.
I CAN'T JUST MAKE OUT
WITH YOU.
YOU DID LAST NIGHT.
YOU SEEMED TO ENJOY IT.
THAT WAS DIFFERENT.
HOW?
I DON'T KNOW.
IT JUST WAS.
OKAY.
WELL, IF YOU CHANGE
YOUR MIND...
YOU KNOW WHERE TO FIND ME.
(TRUCK ENGINE STARTS)
CROWD:
(CHEERS)
READY? SHOOT! NOW!
CROWD:
(CHEERS)
KC:
OKAY. THERE'S TWO OF US,
ONE OF HIM.
DREW:
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S TAKE HIM OUT.
CROWD:
(CHEERS)
DREW:
HEY, MAN,
WHY'S DAVE'S DAD HERE?
KC:
HE'S PROBABLY ON DUTY
AT THE SCHOOL TODAY.
DREW:
WHAT IF HE KNOWS SOMETHING
ABOUT THE GANG?
KC:
YOU PARANOID MUCH?
HEY! HEY, WE'RE IN
THE MIDDLE OF A GAME.
THIS CAN'T WAIT.
TELL ME WHAT YOU KNOW!
PARDON ME?
I SAID TELL ME
WHAT YOU KNOW!
SON,
I NEED YOU TO RELAX.
TAKE A DEEP BREATH.
I'M SORRY, SIR.
(LAUGHS) YOU INHALED
TWO POUNDS OF WINGS!
AND I'M JUST GETTING
STARTED.
NO, I BET YOU COULDN'T
EAT ANOTHER BITE.
HA... WANNA BET?
LET ME GUESS.
TEN BUCKS?
WELL, GOTTA MAKE
MY MONEY BACK SOMEHOW.
(LAUGHS)
I'M HAVING A LOT
OF FUN TONIGHT.
YEAH, ME TOO.
MARISOL:
DAVE AND ALLI, RIGHT?
AREN'T YOU A CUTE COUPLE!
UH... WE'RE JUST FRIENDS,
HANGING OUT.
ON COUPLES FONDUE NIGHT?
UH... MY GIRLFRIEND
HAD OTHER PLANS TONIGHT.
DON'T WORRY,
YOUR SECRET'S SAFE WITH ME.
NOT A SECRET!
AH, ANYWAY...
CHOCOLATE FONDUE FOR DESSERT?
IT'S UH...
IT'S GETTING KINDA LATE.
I SHOULD PROBABLY GO.
UH... SEE YOU AROUND.
(CLEARS HER THROAT)
THERE ARE A MILLION
REASONS...
WHY WE SHOULDN'T
BE DOING THIS.
(LANDS WITH A THUD)
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
(PHONE BEEPS ON)
(FOOTSTEPS THUD)
BOTH:
(GASP)
MOM!
CLARE,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING UP?
I THOUGHT SOMEONE
WAS BREAKING IN!
(LAUGHS)
WAIT, IT'S FOUR IN THE MORNING
AND YOU'RE JUST GETTING HOME?
OKAY. (GIGGLES)
I WAS OUT FOR A DRINK
WITH A MAN.
I WOULD'VE TOLD YOU
SOONER,
BUT THE BOOK SAID WAIT
UNTIL IT'S SERIOUS.
WHAT WERE YOU DOING?
CLARE, THAT'S NONE
OF YOUR BUSINESS.
THIS IS A CONFUSING TIME.
I WAS MARRIED TO YOUR FATHER
FOR SO LONG.
I SHOULD GET BACK TO BED.
CLARE...
I'M SORRY I WOKE YOU.
GOOD NIGHT.
(LAUGHS)
MY SON IS UP AT NINE
ON A SATURDAY.
MUST'VE KNOWN HIS MOM
NEEDED HELP FOLDING LAUNDRY.
WHAT'S UP?
I THINK THERE'S SOMETHING
WRONG WITH ME, MOM.
LISTEN, I HAVE THE NAMES
OF A FEW GOOD THERAPISTS.
I'LL FIND ONE
FOR YOU TO TALK TO...
TODAY EVEN.
THE GANG WILL
STILL BE OUT THERE.
HONEY, THE POLICE THINK
IT'S VERY UNLIKELY
THAT THEY'RE GONNA
COME AFTER YOU AGAIN.
BUT DOESN'T MAKE ME
ANY LESS SCARED!
DREW...
WHAT IF I'M GOING CRAZY?
OH, HONEY,
YOU ARE NOT GOING CRAZY.
LOOK AT ME.
LISTEN, I-I THINK
THAT MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST-
MOVE!
NO.
WE JUST NEED TO GET YOU AWAY
FROM ALL THIS TERRIBLE STUFF,
JUST FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
BUT MOM...
HONEY, LISTEN,
YOUR DAD AND I HAVE JOBS.
IT'S NOT LIKE WE CAN
JUST PICK UP AND GO.
HEY...
CLARE:
THANKS FOR COMING.
I TRIED TALKING TO ALLI,
BUT SHE DIDN'T REALLY
UNDERSTAND.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU CAUGHT YOUR MOM
SNEAKING IN AT 4 AM.
AND THEN SHE BASICALLY COPPED
TO A BOOTY CALL
WITH A STRANGER.
A STRANGER?
WELL, STRANGE TO ME.
SHE SPENT SIXTEEN YEARS
LECTURING ME
ON CHRISTIAN VALUES,
AND THEN JUMPS IN BED
WITH THE FIRST MAN SHE MEETS.
WHEN MY DAD STARTED DATING,
I FELT THE SAME WAY.
THEN I REALIZED
IT'S WHAT MADE HIM HAPPY.
SO... WE SHOULD JUST DO
WHAT MAKES US HAPPY?
IF IT DOESN'T HURT ANYONE,
WHY NOT?
THIS CASUAL THING...
HOW DOES IT WORK EXACTLY?
WE HANG OUT,
WE HAVE FUN.
THEN NO ONE GETS HURT.
I DON'T WANT TO FORCE YOU.
OH, SHUT UP.