SO, I'LL PICK YOU UP
AFTER SCHOOL FOR DIALYSIS,
AND DON'T FORGET...
MONITOR MY WATER INTAKE.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE GONNA BE OKAY?
YOU'VE HAD A LOT
TO DIGEST.
I JUST HEARD BACK
FROM THE MINISTRY OF RECORDS.
AND?
I GOT SOME
EXCITING NEWS.
YOU FOUND
YOUR BIRTH PARENTS?
MY BIRTH FATHER WITHHELD
HIS NAME, BUT...
I FOUND MY BIRTH MOTHER
AND SHE LIVES NEARBY,
SO...
WOW! THAT'S GOOD.
HER NAME'S DAWN.
SO, I'M GONNA CALL HER
THIS MORNING.
MOM, I KINDA FEEL WEIRD
ABOUT THIS,
LIKE I'M CHEATING ON YOU
OR SOMETHING.
I CAN'T IMAGINE
WHAT YOU MUST BE
GOING THROUGH.
I'LL BE FINE,
HONESTLY.
AS WEIRD AS IT IS
FINDING OUT I'M ADOPTED,
THERE'S A SILVER LINING
BECAUSE I MIGHT GET MY KIDNEY,
RIGHT?
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
FINGERS CROSSED.
YEAH.
MARY KATE:
HOLLY J?
JUST REMEMBER WE DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT THIS PERSON.
BE CAREFUL.
I'LL KEEP MY EYES OPEN,
MOM.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh... ♪
(I can make it)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
YOU KEEP TUGGIN'
AT YOUR SHIRT,
YOU'LL STRETCH IT OUT
OF SHAPE, ADAM
IT FEELS TIGHT.
I THINK ALL MY SHIRTS
ARE TOO TIGHT.
(CHUCKLES)
I CAN TAKE A HINT.
YOU WANT TO GO SHOPPING.
NO, IT'S NOT ABOUT
THE SHIRTS.
IT'S WHAT LIES UNDERNEATH.
STOP BEING CRYPTIC.
I WAS HOPING
WE COULD TALK SOME MORE
ABOUT CHEST
RECONSTRUCTION?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
AH...
YOU KNOW HOW I FEEL
ABOUT SURGERY.
WHICH IS WHY
I'M BRINGING IT UP AGAIN.
AND I RESPECT THAT
YOU FEEL LIKE A BOY-
I DON'T FEEL LIKE A BOY!
I AM!
YOU'RE FIFTEEN, OKAY?
YOUR BODY IS STILL CHANGING,
AND WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
REMOVING PARTS OF YOU.
YOU MAKE IT SOUND
SO HORRIBLE.
I'LL MAKE A DEAL
WITH YOU.
WE'LL SPEAK TO YOUR COUNSELLOR
ABOUT THIS.
REALLY?
SO, IF SHE OKAYS ME
FOR SURGERY...
THEN WE'LL HAVE SOME
DECISIONS TO MAKE.
OKAY. COOL.
COOL.
HOLLY J:
IT'S RINGING.
OH MY GOD,
WHAT IF I GET VOICEMAIL?
WHAT DO I SAY?
"HI, THIS IS YOUR BIRTH
DAUGHTER.
MAY I HAVE YOUR KIDNEY?"
HELLO? HI, DAWN?
I'M HOLLY J.
HOLLY J SINCLAIR.
NO, WAIT.
NO, I'M NOT TRYING TO SELL YOU
ANYTHING.
I ACTUALLY CALLED
TO ASK YOU SOMETHING.
DID YOU PUT A BABY
UP FOR ADOPTION IN 1994?
I KNOW IT'S A PRIVATE QUESTION.
I HAVE A GOOD REASON TO ASK.
THAT BABY IS...
THAT'S ME.
YEAH, I JUST FOUND
YOUR INFO ONLINE.
I THOUGHT
WE COULD MEET UP.
GREAT.
GREAT, YEAH.
UM...
THERE'S THIS PLACE
CALLED "THE DOT".
AFTER SCHOOL,
MAYBE 4:00?
OKAY, I'LL SEE YOU THERE.
YEAH. BYE, DAWN.
(PHONE BEEPS OFF)
(ASTONISHED EXHALE)
(GASPS)
I'M MEETING MY BIRTH MOM
FOR COFFEE?!
HOLLY J,
THAT IS SO AWESOME!
MS. DAWES:
FOR THOSE HOPEFULS
WHO AUDITIONED,
THE ROLES ARE NOW POSTED
ON THE BOARD.
GIRL:
(GASPS EXCITEDLY)
GOT IT!
(BREATHLESS)
YES.
I'M GOING TO BE CLARA!
THANK YOU SO MUCH,
ELI!
ELI:
YOU DESERVED IT.
YOU WERE AWESOME!
YOU CAN GET OFF ME NOW.
ELI, WE DON'T HAVE
TO PRETEND.
I KNOW I'M YOUR LEADING LADY
BOTH ON STAGE
AND IN YOUR HEART.
IMOGEN,
WE'RE NOT TOGETHER.
(CHUCKLES)
BUT YESTERDAY
YOU KISSED ME BACK.
I'M FLATTERED,
BUT...
I'M NOT IN
THE RIGHT PLACE,
EMOTIONALLY SPEAKING.
WHERE ARE YOU,
EMOTIONALLY SPEAKING?
WELL, I'M OFF MY MEDS
SO MY EMOTIONS
ARE A MOVING TARGET.
AND I'M JUST STARTING
TO FEEL A LITTLE BETTER -
GETTING OVER CLARE
AND SUCH.
I DON'T WANT TO MESS
WITH THAT.
YOU UNDERSTAND.
FIONA:
CONGRATS, IMOGEN.
KATIE:
I CAN'T BELIEVE RYAN LYNCH
TALKED TO ME FOR SO LONG.
ADAM:
WHAT DID HE WRITE IN YOUR BOOK?
KATIE:
"TO KATIE,
DON'T GIVE UP ON YOUR DREAMS
AND THEY WON'T GIVE UP ON YOU."
I TOLD HIM ABOUT MY DREAM
OF BECOMING A JOURNALIST.
ADAM:
THAT'S MY DREAM.
I'M SERIOUS!
I'M HOPING TO BE
A RADIO JOURNALISM MAJOR.
KATIE:
REALLY?
WELL, YOU DO HAVE QUITE
A PRESENCE ON-AIR.
WE COULD GO
TO THE SAME UNIVERSITY!
STUDY TOGETHER!
IT'D BE AWESOME!
ARE YOU ALWAYS
THIS ENTHUSIASTIC?
JUST HAPPY I GUESS.
I'M HAVING A FUN TIME
WITH YOU.
I LIKE YOU.
I LIKE YOU TOO.
IT'S JUST-
YEAH, I KNOW.
JUST SO YOU KNOW
I'M GONNA BE MAKING
SOME CHANGES.
REALLY?
WHAT KIND OF CHANGES?
YOU KNOW,
PHYSICAL STUFF.
SURE.
WHATEVER YOU NEED TO DO.
HEY, I'M STARVING.
YOU WANNA GRAB POUTINE?
FRIES, GRAVY AND CHEESE?
THOUGHT YOU'D NEVER ASK.
FIONA:
I BET SHE GAVE YOU UP
TO PURSUE THIS BRILLIANT CAREER,
MADE BIG MONEY,
CONQUERED THE BUSINESS WORLD.
LOOK,
IT'S GONNA BE TRIPPY,
BUT DON'T FORGET
WHY WE'RE HERE, OKAY?
HOLLY J:
LET'S DO THIS.
WHERE IS SHE?
NOPE. NOPE.
NO.
THERE SHE IS.
HI, EXCUSE ME,
I'M HOLLY J.
DO I KNOW YOU?
DAWN:
HOLLY J?
IT'S ME, DAWN.
YOU MUST HAVE MISSED ME
SITTING OVER HERE
WITH MY KIDS.
I GUESS I DID.
CLARE!
(GASPS)
DON'T DO THAT!
SORRY.
JUST REALLY WANTED
TO THANK YOU.
YOU GOT THE PART!
AND I GOT THE BOY.
REALLY?
WITHOUT YOU,
THERE'D BE NO ME AND ELI.
WELL, I'M GLAD
IT WORKED OUT.
ME TOO!
ME TOO.
SO, AS A TOKEN
OF MY ETERNAL APPRECIATION,
DINNER FOR TWO
AT THAT STEAK PLACE.
THOUGHT YOU COULD TAKE
YOUR BOYFRIEND
OUT ON A DATE.
REALLY?
WOW! THAT'S SO NICE,
IMOGEN.
JAKE'S A STEAK GUY.
I THOUGHT SO.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'LL CALL HIM,
SEE IF HE'S FREE TONIGHT.
EXCELLENT.
DAWN:
IT WAS MY FIRST YEAR
OF UNIVERSITY
WHEN MY BOYFRIEND -
YOUR FATHER,
I GUESS -
HEARD ABOUT MY SITUATION.
NEVER HEARD
FROM HIM AGAIN.
BY THE TIME THAT I KNEW
THAT I WAS PREGNANT,
I HAD TWO CHOICES:
DROP OUT,
RAISE A BABY,
OR GIVE UP THE BABY,
STAY IN UNIVERSITY
AND GET A CAREER.
IT WASN'T EASY.
IT TOOK ME NEARLY A YEAR
TO DECIDE TO GIVE YOU UP.
HOLLY J:
FOR THE RECORD,
I DON'T BLAME YOU.
YOU KNOW, HOLLY J'S QUITE
AMBITIOUS HERSELF.
SHE'S GOING TO YALE
THIS YEAR.
YALE?
THAT'S AMAZING!
I'M A WESTERN ALUMNI
MYSELF.
THAT'S AWESOME!
WHAT DID YOU MAJOR IN?
COMMERCE.
I WORK IN
THE FINANCIAL SECTOR.
I'M A SENIOR
ACCOUNTS ASSOCIATE.
SO YOU HANDLE
IMPORTANT ACCOUNTS?
WELL...
NOT SO MUCH THESE DAYS.
I'M REALLY JUST
A GLORIFIED BANK TELLER.
BUT THE HOURS ARE FLEX
AND BEING A SINGLE MOM,
THAT'S... THAT'S GOLDEN.
SO, HOLLY J,
I'M SURE DAWN WOULD LOVE
TO HEAR MORE ABOUT YOU.
YES, PLEASE!
WELL, I'M...
I ALREADY MENTIONED YALE.
UM, I GRADUATE
HIGH SCHOOL SOON,
SO I'M STOKED ABOUT THAT.
AND UM...
FIONA:
HOLLY J HAS SOMETHING
IMPORTANT TO ASK YOU.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
YEAH, WERE YOUR WISDOM TEETH
IMPACTED?
MINE WERE FINE.
IS THAT ALL?
NO, MY DENTIST THINKS
MINE MIGHT BE SO UH...
I JUST WANTED TO KNOW
MY HISTORY.
ANYWAY...
IT WAS REALLY GOOD
MEETING YOU,
BUT I THINK I SHOULD GO.
COME ON, FIONA,
WE'RE GONNA BE LATE.
YEAH, WOULDN'T WANT
TO WASTE VALUABLE TIME,
WOULD WE?
SO, DID I PASS?
IT'S NOT THAT
KIND OF TEST.
THE QUESTIONNAIRE
IS STEP ONE.
THERES SO MUCH MORE
TO COVER
BEFORE I CAN MAKE
A RECOMMENDATION ABOUT SURGERY.
GREAT.
SO, WHAT'S STEP TWO?
WELL, GENERALLY WE RECOMMEND
FURTHER COUNSELLING
BEFORE STARTING
HORMONE THERAPY.
I DON'T NEED
COUNSELLING!
AUDRA:
HONEY, WE JUST WANT
TO MAKE SURE.
WHAT IF YOU CHANGE
YOUR MIND?
I WON'T!
I JUST NEED TO FIX MY CHEST
SO I WON'T FREAK OUT
THIS GIRL!
AUDRA:
THIS IS ABOUT A GIRL?
NO, THAT'S NOT
WHAT I MEANT.
ADAM, YOUR BODY'S
STILL CHANGING.
I JUST WANT TO LOOK
LIKE HOW I FEEL,
AND I CAN'T BECAUSE
OF THESE.
STRAPPING THEM DOWN
ALL THE TIME ISN'T WORKING.
PEOPLE CAN TELL!
THAT I CAN HELP WITH.
THERE ARE ALTERNATIVES.
TAKE A LOOK.
(EMOTIONAL SIGH)
HOSPITAL P.A.:
DR. STODDARD, LINE TWO.
HOLLY J:
I'M SUCH A LOSER.
FIONA:
YOU'RE NOT A LOSER.
YOU CHOKED.
SO, I GUESS IT'S FINALLY
STARTING TO SETTLE IN.
I GUESS I'VE ALWAYS BEEN
MORE FOCUSED
ON WHERE I'M GOING,
BUT...
YEAH.
I WANT TO GET TO KNOW DAWN.
THERE'LL BE TIME
FOR ALL THAT
ONCE YOU ASK HER
TO GET TESTED.
WHAT IF I SCARE HER OFF?
WHAT'S MORE IMPORTANT -
HAVING A RELATIONSHIP
WITH YOUR BIRTH MOM
OR GETTING HEALTHY,
GOING TO YALE,
LIVING LIFE?
♪ I got a feeling
that's shaking the tree ♪
THANK YOU.
TRUST ME,
THIS IS SO MUCH BETTER
THAN MOVIE NIGHT
WITH OUR PARENTS.
HEY!
YOU SAID IN YOUR TEXT
YOU WANTED TO TALK
ABOUT CLARA?
YEAH, JUST SOME
BACKSTORY-TYPE QUESTIONS
I WANTED TO HASH OUT.
YOU LOOK FANTASTIC,
BY THE WAY.
COOL.
SO, SHOULD WE SIT DOWN?
UM, CAN WE GO SIT LIKE
BACK THERE?
ELI:
UH, 'KAY.
YOU KNOW, WE REALLY SHOULD
TELL THEM EVENTUALLY.
"HEY, MOM, I'M DATING
YOUR BOYFRIEND'S SON!"
(LAUGHING)
NO THANKS.
HOW ABOUT WE TRY NOT
TO THINK ABOUT IT.
IMOGEN:
OH, SORRY!
DIDN'T SEE YOU
TWO LOVEBIRDS.
AWKWARD!
COME ON, MUFFIN,
LET'S GO SIT.
ELI, YOU KNOW JAKE.
WHAT A COINCIDENCE,
HUH, IMOGEN?
JUST TRYING
TO BREAK THE ICE.
HOW'S IT GOIN'?
LET'S GO SIT DOWN,
OKAY, MUFFIN?
STOP CALLING ME THAT!
THE REAL CLARE EDWARDS
WOULD NEVER DO
WHAT YOU JUST DID.
WE BOTH KNOW
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
THE REAL CLARE EDWARDS
WOULD DO ANYTHING
TO GET WHAT SHE WANTS.
(RECEDING FOOTSTEPS)
ADAM:
HEY, KATIE.
LAST NIGHT
WAS CRAZY FUN.
WASN'T IT?
I WAS HOPING
FOR A REPEAT.
MAYBE WE COULD GO
TO A MOVIE FRIDAY?
YEAH, UM,
ADAM, I THINK MAYBE
YOU GOT THE WRONG IDEA?
WHAT IDEA IS THAT?
THAT I LIKE YOU
IN THAT WAY.
UH, NO.
KATIE, COME ON.
YOU'VE MISUNDERSTOOD.
DOCTOR MITCH:
OOH, BACK AGAIN, ARE WE?
HOLLY J:
YOU KNOW ME,
I CAN'T GET ENOUGH DIALYSIS.
ANY NEWS TODAY?
I DO HAVE THE RESULTS
OF YOUR FRIEND FIONA'S
BLOOD TESTS.
THEIR NEGATIVE,
I'M AFRAID.
OH. I'D NEVER ASK HER TO GO
THROUGH WITH IT ANYWAY.
DOCTOR MITCH:
AND THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE.
I'M LOOKING
AT YOUR LATEST TESTS,
AND, UH,
WE'D HOPED TO REALLY
SLOW THE PROCESS,
BUT I'M GONNA LEVEL WITH YOU.
YOUR RESULTS ARE SHOWING
END STAGE KIDNEY FAILURE.
I KNOW THAT'S NOT THE ANSWER
YOU WANTED TO HEAR.
BUT, UH,
I'VE PUT YOU ON
A TRANSPLANT LIST.
TYPICAL WAIT TIME'S
ABOUT 12 MONTHS,
COULD BE SOONER.
I'LL BE AT YALE BY THEN.
YOU MIGHT CONSIDER
DEFERRING YALE.
HEY. DON'T GIVE UP HOPE,
OKAY?
(SNORT OF DISBELIEF)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
DAVE:
HEY!
YOU WERE QUIET IN THERE.
DID YOU GOT THE LICENCE PLATE
OF THE GUY THAT RAN YOU OVER?
IT WAS A GIRL.
KATIE?
AH, SORRY, MAN.
I THOUGHT SOMETHING
WAS GOING ON.
DON'T WORRY,
WE'LL FIND YOU
A NEW FINE FEMALE.
I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, LOOK,
DON'T GET ALL DEFEATED ON ME,
ALL RIGHT?
THINGS WILL GET EASIER
WITH THIS NEW PROFILE
YOU GOT GOIN' ON.
YOU, UH,
TRYING SOMETHING NEW?
YEAH,
A COMPRESSION VEST.
AH, SOUNDS PAINFUL.
YEAH, KINDA.
IT'S BETTER THAN THE BINDING
I WAS USING BEFORE.
LOOK, I'M JUST SAYIN'
THAT THIS NEW
DE-BOOBING DEVICE WORKS.
YEAH, BUT WILL I EVER
BE FLAT ENOUGH
FOR THE KATIES
OF THE WORLD?
I DON'T HAVE
THE ANSWERS, MAN.
YEAH, I KNOW.
YOU'VE HELPED A LOT ALREADY.
I MADE YOU LOOK
AT MY CHEST.
YEAH, PLEASE,
NEVER AGAIN.
IT'S REALLY CONFUSING.
HOLLY J:
(NERVOUS SIGH)
THANKS FOR MEETING ME,
ESPECIALLY ON
YOUR LUNCH BREAK.
YOU...
YOU SAID IT WAS URGENT.
YEAH, UM...
WELL, HERE'S THE THING.
I HAVE A...
A MEDICAL ISSUE.
OH.
YEAH, I'VE GOT
A RENAL CONDITION,
SO MY KIDNEYS ARE IN...
END STAGE FAILURE.
WHAT DOES IT MEAN?
IT MEANS...
I'M GONNA NEED
A TRANSPLANT.
LOOK, I KNOW YOU HAVE
A TON ON YOUR PLATE,
BUT I'M WONDERING IF YOU'D
THINK ABOUT GETTING TESTED,
JUST TO SEE
IF YOU'RE A POSSIBLE DONOR?
I'M SUPPORTING TWO KIDS
ON MY OWN.
I KNOW. I FEEL SO ROTTEN
EVEN ASKING.
THAT'S...
THAT'S WHY I COULDN'T
LAST TIME.
WHAT'S THE RECOVERY TIME?
WELL,
I DON'T EXACTLY KNOW,
BUT MY DOCTOR CAN TELL YOU
EVERYTHING YOU NEED TO KNOW.
WELL...
I'LL GET TESTED
AND UH...
WE'LL TAKE IT
FROM THERE.
(EMOTIONAL EXHALE)
(ELECTRIC DRILL WHIRS)
FIONA:
SOMEONE WANTS TO SEE YOU.
I OWE YOU AN APOLOGY.
DON'T WORRY, I'M OKAY.
ARE YOU?
I'M GOOD.
I'M GREAT.
THAT'S AWESOME.
I'M SO GLAD TO SEE YOU
IN A BETTER PLACE NOW -
EMOTIONALLY.
JAKE:
UH, I'M GONNA GET MORE WOOD
FROM THE SHOP.
EXCELLENT.
JAKE'S WORKING
ON OUR SETS?
WE NEED A CARPENTER,
HE WANTS AN EXTRA CREDIT.
EVERYBODY'S HAPPY.
SO YOU'VE MOVED ON.
YOU KNOW, IMOGEN,
SEEING JAKE KISS CLARE
MADE ME REALIZE SOMETHING.
WHAT'S THAT,
ELI GOLDSWORTHY?
THAT I'M NOT OVER
CLARE AT ALL.
THAT'S WHY I ASKED
JAKE FOR HELP.
AS THE WARRIOR POET
SUN TZU SAID,
"KEEP YOUR FRIENDS CLOSE,
YOUR ENEMIES CLOSER."
MOM!
UH, THIS IS DAWN.
THANK YOU, DAWN.
THIS MEANS A LOT
TO OUR FAMILY.
YOU'VE DONE MORE
FOR HOLLY J
THAN I EVER COULD HAVE.
RESULTS TOMORROW.
FINGERS CROSSED.
HOLLY J:
YEAH, FINGERS CROSSED.
(CHUCKLES)
DAVE:
HEY, WASSUP, MY FRIEND?
ADAM:
QUICK, WHAT'S A GOOD
ONLINE NAME?
DAVE:
FOR...
ADAM:
I'M JOINING AN FTM SITE.
DAVE:
OH, FOR HOOKUPS?
YEAH, THAT'S MY MAN, OKAY.
NO, IT'S TO MEET
OTHER TRANS GUYS.
I'LL GET TO CHAT
WITH SOME DUDES
GOING THROUGH
SIMILAR THINGS.
DAVE:
WHOA!
(GASPS)
THAT'S INTENSE.
THAT'S MY LIFE.
DAVE:
THAT GUY STARTED OUT
AS A GIRL?
ADAM:
PHYSICALLY, YEAH.
AND THAT GONNA BE YOU
SOMEDAY?
SOMEDAY.
COOL.
DOES THIS MEAN
I'M FIRED NOW?
SHUT UP, MAN,
YOU'RE MY FRIEND,
LIKE IT OR NOT.
FIONA:
WATCHED POT DOESN'T
BOIL ANY FASTER.
HOLLY J:
WELL, IT DOESN'T BOIL
ANY SLOWER.
FIONA:
SHE'LL CALL YOU WHEN SHE HEARS.
I JUST FEEL LIKE EVERYTHING
IS AT A STANDSTILL
UNTIL I GET THE RESULTS.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
OH MY GOD,
THIS IS HER!
DAWN?
UH, THANKS FOR CALLING.
YEAH, I AM PRETTY DESPERATE
TO HEAR THE RESULTS.
YEAH,
MORE THAN YOU KNOW.
OH MY GOD,
THAT IS THE BEST NEWS!
WHAT?
UH...
OKAY. NO, I...
I GET IT.
YEAH, OF COURSE.
YOU HAVE TO DO
WHAT YOU HAVE TO DO.
OKAY, BYE.
SO WHAT?
SHE'S NOT GONNA DO IT?
NO, SHE WANTS TO DO IT.
SHE WANTS TO GIVE ME
HER KIDNEY.
SO, WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
SHE WANTS $20,000 DOLLARS.
♪ When there's no one
to hold onto ♪
♪ Stay strong like a lion
in the dark ♪