(BABY COOING)
KC, WAKE UP!
WAKE UP!
ONE OF US WAS SUPPOSED
TO STAY AWAKE TO MONITOR TYSON!
OKAY, HE'S AWAKE.
NO PROBLEM.
THE DOCTOR SAID THAT MEANS
HE'S PROBABLY NOT CONCUSSED.
I'M SO SORRY,
LITTLE GUY.
JENNA,
EVERYTHING'S OKAY.
WE'RE GONNA MAKE IT
THROUGH THIS, OKAY?
HERE, I'M GONNA TAKE TY
IN TO GRANDMA.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
HELLO?
YEAH, THIS IS HER.
(DOOR OPENS)
SORRY?
IT HAS TO BE TODAY?
RIGHT.
OKAY. YEAH.
BYE.
KC:
SHE'S GONNA GIVE HIM A BATH.
WE BETTER GET GOING.
I CAN'T.
THAT WAS CHILD SERVICES.
THEY'RE COMING HERE
THIS AFTERNOON.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYS)
AW MAN, THIS IS SO LEGIT!
CAN'T BELIEVE I HAD
TO BLACKMAIL YOU
TO GET YOU TO WORK
WITH ME.
YEAH, WELL, ONCE WE GET
JENNA'S PART IN THERE,
MS. OH'S GONNA LOVE THIS.
AND LOVE YOU.
SHE'LL PROBABLY SUGGEST
SOME MUSICAL INSTRUMENTATION
AND HARMONIES THAT I COULDN'T
EVEN IMAGINE.
AND SOME BEDROOM ACTIVITIES
YOU COULDN'T EVEN IMAGINE!
DUDE, SHE'S A TEACHER!
SO? ANYONE WHO WRITES A SONG
AS PASSIONATE AS - OH, GIRL,
OBVIOUSLY HAS STRONG
FEELINGS.
FOR THE LOVE OF GOD,
PLEASE STOP!
JAKE:
SO, YOU JUST WOKE UP
AND DECIDED YOU WANTED
TO WORK ON THE PLAY?
LETS US SPEND MORE
TIME TOGETHER!
WANNA TRY THIS ONE?
UH YEAH, SURE.
(DRILLING NOISE)
OOPS.
(SIGHS) IT'S OKAY.
WE CAN TOUCH THAT UP.
WHY ARE YOU HERE?
REALLY?
I WANNA MAKE SURE ELI
DOESN'T TRY AND HURT YOU.
(LAUGHS) HURT ME?
HE GETS JEALOUS
AND POSSESSIVE.
LAST SEMESTER,
HE POISONED FITZ!
THAT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
FITZ WASN'T SUPPOSED
TO DRINK IT.
ELI TOLD US.
AND YOU BELIEVED HIM?
ELI'S BEEN REALLY
NICE TO ME.
HIS NEW SCRIPT'S OUT,
AND HE WANTED ME TO READ
THE PART OF FRITZ
FOR THE READ-THROUGH LATER
(LAUGHS) CLAIRE, THERE'S
NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
YEAH,
YOU'RE PROBABLY RIGHT.
THERE'S MY EASY-GOING
CLARE-BEAR.
♪ RUNNIN' THROUGH
THE HALLWAYS OF MY HEART... ♪
THAT'S CATCHY.
WHAT IS THAT?
OH, I WROTE IT WITH SAV.
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO PRESENT
IT TODAY, BUT...
OH, WHAT ABOUT
THE OUTLETS?
IS CHILD SERVICES
GONNA BE MAD
WE DON'T HAVE THOSE LITTLE
PLUGGY THINGS?
I THINK TY'S
A LITTLE FOR THAT.
I JUST WANNA DO
EVERYTHING RIGHT.
(SIGHS) WE HAVE CLEANED
FOR TWO HOURS.
EVERYTHING'S SPOTLESS.
AND KC'S GONNA GET SUPPLIES
AT LUNCH, RIGHT?
BUT, WHAT IF THEY STILL
THINK I'M A BAD MOM?
THEY TOOK KC AWAY FROM ME
BECAUSE I LOCKED HIM IN
A CLOSET SO I COULD GET MY FIX.
YOU'RE A GOOD MOM.
THANKS.
I'M GONNA SCRUB THE FLOOR
ONE MORE TIME JUST TO BE SURE.
WHY DON'T YOU GO
PRESENT THAT SONG.
BUT THE MEETING...
ISN'T 'TIL 2.
I KNOW HOW HARD IT CAN BE
TO LOSE TOUCH WITH HIGH SCHOOL.
JENNA:
♪ I'M RUNNIN' THROUGH
THE HALLWAYS OF MY HEART ♪
♪ TO TRY AND SAVE MY LIFE ♪
♪ I'M RUNNIN' THROUGH
THE HALLWAYS OF MY HEART ♪
♪ FROM THE HUNTER'S KNIFE ♪
(CLAPPING)
SAV! ONCE AGAIN I AM IMPRESSED
WITH YOUR MUSICAL PROWESS!
YEAH. I COULDN'T HAVE DONE IT
WITHOUT THESE GUYS.
OKAY, WE'LL MEET AT LUNCH TO
GO OVER THE REST OF THE PLAY.
I HOPE WE CAN MAKE
SOME MORE MAGIC!
JENNA:
I'VE GOTTA GO, TOO.
I CAN'T WAIT TO TELL KC!
DID YOU HEAR THAT?!
PROWESS, MAGIC.
SHE LIKES YOU.
IT'S GO TIME!
NO MAN.
YES! YOU HAVE TO.
FOR EVERY DUDE WHO'S
EVER FANTASIZED ABOUT HER
DURING COMPUTER SCIENCE CLASS.
FOR THE STOCKY GUYS WHO
CAN NEVER GET DATES.
I JUST WANNA TALK MUSIC
WITH HER.
MAN, SHE'S A HOT TEACHER.
THINK ABOUT HOW AWESOME
IT'D BE?
WELL, YEAH, IT WOULD BE
PRETTY AWESOME...
RIGHT?
BUT I DON'T WANNA
MESS THIS UP.
(BELL RINGS)
UGH, FINE.
SEE YOU AT LUNCH...
(COUGHS) LOSER.
(SIGHS)
SUDDEN ONSET ASTHMA?
ELI'S WRITTEN SOME CRAZY
NEW DRAFT OF THE PLAY.
AND JAKE'S GONNA HEAR IT
TONIGHT AT THE READ-THROUGH.
THAT'S IT? YESTERDAY THIS
WAS A POTENTIAL MURDER PLOT.
IT STILL IS.
OF MY RELATIONSHIP.
ELI'S PLAY IS
HIS REVENGE FANTASY.
IT PAINTS ME AS
SOME EVIL SHREW.
HAVE YOU SEEN THE FLYER?
BASED ON A TRUE STORY.
IT'S ALL LIES!
WELL, TOO BAD THERE ISN'T
SOME TRUTH SUPERHERO
THAT COULD SWOOP DOWN
AND SET EVERYONE STRAIGHT.
CLARK KENT!
SUPERMAN'S ALTER-EGO,
WHO WAS ALSO A NEWSPAPER
REPORTER, JUST LIKE ME!
I HAVE TO COVER
THIS READ-THROUGH.
THIS'LL NEVER END,
WILL IT?
HEY, THANKS FOR TELLING ME
SAV NEEDED MUSIC HELP.
WE TOTALLY ROCKED IT!
ALLI:
YEAH, YOU SEEM LIKE
YOUR OLD SELF.
ALMOST.
JUST GOTTA GET THROUGH
A STUPID CHILD SERVICES
MEETING.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
IT WILL BE.
HAVE YOU SEEN KC?
I'M HERE TO SURPRISE HIM!
UH.
JENNA:
WHAT'S HE DOING
WITH MARISOL?
MAYBE HE ASKED FOR A RIDE?
REALLY?
DO THEY, LIKE, HANG OUT?
I-I REALLY DON'T KNOW.
IS SOMETHING GOING ON
BETWEEN THEM?
BETWEEN WHO?
KC AND MARISOL?
UH.
OH MY GOD, YOU KNOW!?
YEAH, I'M SORRY JENNA.
OH, SAV, SIT.
DON'T BE SHY.
UM, WHERE'S MO?
OH, HE EMAILED. SAID HE
COULDN'T MAKE IT.
GUESS IT'S JUST YOU AND ME.
SHOULD WE GET BUSY?
WHAT?!
TO GO THROUGH THE PLAY
TO DECIDE WHAT PLACES
NEED SCORE.
YEAH. RIGHT.
OF COURSE.
UM, I BROUGHT SOME TRACKS
THAT MO AND I ROUGHED OUT.
OH, IT'S OKAY.
MO EMAILED THE TRACKS.
HE DID?
YEAH. SO, FOR THE OPENING
IN THE DARKENED HALLWAY
TRACK 1,
(SAV'S SONG PLAYS)
THAT'S - THAT'S NOT IT!
IS THIS YOU?
IT'S REALLY GOOD!
UMM, I GOTTA ...I HAVE TO...
I...UH...
I HAVE TO GO TALK
TO SOMEONE.
SAV:
♪ YOU LOOK SO CUTE IN THOSE
TALL LEATHER BOOTS ♪
♪ OH YEAH, OH YEAH ♪
SUPPLIES!
HOW COULD YOU CHEAT ON ME?
I WOULDN'T-
TIME SHEETS!
YOUR SHIFTS END AT NINE,
BUT YOU COME HOME AT ELEVEN?
LOOK, DON'T JUMP
TO CONCLUSIONS.
DAVE TOLD ME!
I'M AT HOME, DEPRESSED,
MISSING MY LIFE-
WHILE YOU RUN AROUND
WITH MARISOL?
FINE.
LOOK, SOMETHING HAPPENED.
BUT I ENDED IT.
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT.
MY FAULT?
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO PRETENDED
YOU WEREN'T PREGNANT
UNTIL IT WAS TOO LATE.
YOU KNOW, I WAS TRYING TO MAKE
SOMETHING OF MYSELF.
MUSIC IS MY LIFE.
AND I'VE EVEN HAD
TO GIVE THAT UP.
WELL, YOU MANAGED TO GET
BACK TO IT LONG ENOUGH
FOR TY TO FALL OFF
THE CHANGE TABLE.
GOD FORBID YOU PUT YOUR GUITAR
DOWN FOR TWO SECONDS-
(SMASH)
(BABY CRYING)
(DOORBELL BUZZES)
OH MY GOD.
IT'S CHILD SERVICES.
TELL ME ABOUT
YOUR SUPPORT SYSTEM.
MY BROTHER JUST
MOVED AWAY.
I DON'T REALLY
HAVE ANYONE ELSE...
WE HAVE MY MOM.
UH, LISA GUTHRIE?
ACCORDING TO MY FILE,
SHE WAS RECENTLY INCARCERATED.
SHE STRUGGLES WITH ADDICTION?
SHE DID.
SHE'S DONE WITH THAT.
CASEWORKER:
YOU'RE SURE?
SHE'S BEEN OUT LESS THAN
A YEAR. RELAPSE IS COMMON.
BUT SHE WON'T.
UNTIL WE'RE SURE
THIS IS A SAFE ENVIRONMENT,
TYSON SHOULDN'T BE
LEFT ALONE WITH HER.
SO ONE OF US HAS
TO STAY HOME,
OR YOU'RE GOING TO TAKE HIM
AWAY FROM US?
WE DON'T LIKE TO REMOVE
CHILDREN FROM THEIR FAMILY,
BUT IN THIS CASE
THAT'S ON THE TABLE.
TYSON'S WELL-BEING
IS OUR FIRST PRIORITY.
IS YOUR HEAD OKAY?
I BUMPED IT IN THE SHOWER.
I'LL BE BACK
FOR REGULAR OBSERVATION.
I NEED TO MAKE SURE
THAT THIS IS A SAFE
AND NURTURING ENVIRONMENT.
SO WHO'LL BE STAYING HOME?
NINERS!
SCATTER.
YEAH, BUT I MEAN,
MAYBE I'LL THINK ABOUT IT
AND I'LL GET BACK TO YOU ON
LIKE TUESDAY OR WEDNESDAY, OR...
YOU WIN.
DO THE SCORE ON YOUR OWN.
OKAY, WAIT, WAIT.
I WASN'T TRYING TO WIN.
THEN WHY DID YOU RUIN
MY RELATIONSHIP WITH MS. OH?
RUIN IT? I WAS TRYING
TO MAKE IT HAPPEN!
BY SENDING HER MY SONG?!
WELL, I MEAN, NOW
SHE KNOWS HOW YOU FEEL.
THE BALL'S TOTALLY
IN HER COURT.
THERE IS NO BALL!
THERE'S NO GAME!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
I JUST WANTED TO BE
YOUR WING-MAN.
YEAH, WELL, NOW I CAN'T
EVEN LOOK HER IN THE EYE!
WHAT IF I HELP YOU
FORGET ABOUT HER?
OKAY?
I'VE GOT TICKETS
TO JUSTIN RUTLEDGE.
I'M LISTENING...
YOU LIKE THE OLDER LADIES.
THEY LIKE HIM.
YOU FIND A GIRL THAT
GETS YOU OVER MS. OH,
I WATCH THE MASTER
AT WORK.
(BELL RINGS)
FINE.
BUT ONLY BECAUSE
THE SHOW'S SOLD OUT.
YES!
THAT'S IT.
MY LIFE IS OVER.
C'MON.
IT'S ONLY FIVE YEARS
'TIL TY'S IN KINDERGARTEN.
I'LL NEVER MAKE IT
THAT LONG
WITHOUT GETTING
COMPLETELY DEPRESSED.
FINE. WE'LL FIND CHILD-CARE
AND GET YOU INTO SCHOOL.
HOW?
WITH WHAT MONEY?
I'LL TAKE MORE SHIFTS
AT LITTLE MISS STEAKS.
REALLY?
YOUR SOLUTION IS TO SPEND
MORE TIME WITH MARISOL?
NO!
THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT.
LOOK, JENNA, WE CAN
MAKE THIS WORK.
WE CAN'T EVEN
MAKE US WORK!
HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO RAISE A KID?
WHERE'RE YOU GOING?
HEY, WHAT ABOUT TY?
WATCH HIM!
(DOOR SLAMS)
(BABY CRIES)
ARI,
YOU CAN'T FIGHT FRITZ.
HE DRAGGED YOU INTO
THIS GODFORSAKEN CASINO.
HE STARTED IT.
BUT I WON'T BE ABLE
TO LIVE WITH MYSELF
IF HE FINISHES IT.
PLEASE.
CLARA CARESSES ARI'S CHEEK.
REALLY?
HE KISSES HER
AND TURNS AWAY.
FRITZ APPEARS
WITH A HUGE KNIFE.
NEVER TURN YOUR BACK
ON THE BLADE.
WHAT?
ARI TURNS,
WHISPERING TO CLARA:
TRAITOR.
OKAY, COME ON.
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
(SIGHS)
AS A REPORTER FOR
THE DEGRASSI DAILY,
I HAVE FEW QUESTIONS REGARDING
THE VERACITY OF THIS SCENE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
NONE OF THIS HAPPENED.
NOT THIS WAY!
I KNOW.
IT'S A PLAY.
THAT YOU'RE ADVERTISING
AS BASED ON A TRUE STORY.
CLAIRE.
IMOGEN:
WOW,
IF ANYONE'S STILL WONDERING
WHY ELI DUMPED YOU
IN THE FIRST PLACE-
YOU STAY OUT OF THIS.
OKAY, NEW POLICY-
NO MORE PRESS!
YOU'VE GOTTA GO.
SHOO, SHOO, SHOO!
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S KEEP GOING.
DUDE, IT'S LADIES CENTRAL!
WE'LL GET YOU OVER
MS. OH IN NO TIME.
YEAH.
OKAY, WHAT ABOUT HER?
SHE'S AT LEAST A NINE!
OKAY, I MEAN, HER FRIENDS
ARE A BIT WEAK,
BUT I'LL THROW MYSELF
ON A GRENADE IF I HAVE TO.
OKAY, YEAH, FINE.
YOU GOTTA START
SOMEWHERE, RIGHT?
RIGHT?
YOU FORGET HOW TO WALK?
LEFT FOOT, RIGHT FOOT,
THEN REPEAT.
OH... OH!!
YEAH, OH!
OF COURSE SHE'S HERE.
ALL I EVER DID WAS TRY
TO PROTECT ELI FROM HIMSELF.
I SET OFF ONE TINY STINK
BOMB AS A DIVERSION.
AND I DID NOT TRY
TO HAVE SEX WITH FITZ,
NOR DID I OFFER HIM DRY CLOTHES
TO SEE HIM NAKED. BUT I DID-
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
ELI IS USING HIS
PULPIT TO TRASH ME,
AND HE OBVIOUSLY WANTS
YOU TO HEAR IT,
SO I'M JUST COMING CLEAN
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
I KNOW THIS IS FICTION.
BUT ELI'S SUCH
A GOOD STORYTELLER,
IT'S SO EASY TO WANT
TO BELIEVE HIM.
IF ANYONE KNOWS,
I DO.
I WOULD NEVER BELIEVE
ELI OVER YOU.
YOU WOULDN'T?
(LAUGHS)
HE'S WEIRD.
HE WEARS EYELINER
AND WRITES PLAYS.
BOTH:
(LAUGH)
THIS MIGHT NOT BE
AS BAD AS YOU THINK.
♪ I AM A PAUSE
IN A STORM ♪
♪ ON A DARK STAIR ♪
♪ WHENEVER YOUR NAME
IS SPOKEN ♪
♪ I AM THE BIRTH OF A DAWN
THROUGH A CURTAIN ♪
♪ THE HURT OF A DAWN
MO:
YOU'RE NOT EVEN
GOING TO SAY HI?
DUDE, I JUST HAVE
TO GET OUTTA HERE.
BUT I CAN'T LEAVE
WITHOUT PASSING HER.
I KNOW A BACK WAY.
ALL RIGHT, COME ON.
KEEP YOUR HEAD DOWN.
OH.
SORRY.
SAV?
LATER PAL.
I WANT STORIES!
HI.
UM, I WAS JUST
TELLING THEM-
THIS IS THE GUY THAT WROTE
THAT SONG FOR ME.
AND ABOUT THAT.
I'M SO SORRY.
NO GUY'S EVER WRITTEN
A SONG FOR ME.
STILL, UM...
MISS OH,
I SHOULDN'T HAVE-
MISS OH? (LAUGHS)
WE'RE NOT IN SCHOOL.
CALL ME WINNIE.
ARE YOU ALONE?
WANNA WATCH WITH US?
YEAH, SURE...
WINNIE...
♪ BE A MAN ABOUT THIS ♪
♪ BE THE BOREDOM
OR THE BLISS ♪
♪ BE A MAN ABOUT THIS ♪
UH, I'M USUALLY BETTER
AT THIS.
I'M JUST OBSERVING.
PRETEND I'M NOT HERE.
OKAY.
COME HERE. OKAY.
THIS IS WHEN YOU NORMALLY
LEAVE FOR SCHOOL?
UH... YEAH?
YEAH, THIS IS WHEN
HE MAKES HIS ESCAPE
AND LEAVES ALL HIS BAGGAGE AT
THE DOOR UNTIL SCHOOL'S OVER.
(FRIDGE SLAMS)
ARE YOU GONNA BE ON US
LIKE THIS EVERY VISIT?
WE HAVE TO BE DILIGENT
TO PROTECT THE BABY.
YOU UNDERSTAND.
WHAT ABOUT ADOPTION?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
DISCUSSING OUR OPTIONS.
IT'S STILL AN OPTION,
RIGHT?
IT'S A VERY BIG DECISION.
WHOA! ARE WE ACTUALLY
TALKING ABOUT THIS?
I'M JUST ASKING
A QUESTION!
I CAN SET YOU UP WITH
OUR ADOPTION CONSULTANT,
IF YOU'RE SERIOUS.
WE ARE NOT!
SHHH.
IT'S OKAY. SHHH.
...IT WOULDN'T BE
GENTLEMANLY.
SCREW GENTLEMANLY.
YOU GOTTA TELL ME.
IT'S THE GUY CODE!
OKAY, WE WATCHED
THE WHOLE SHOW TOGETHER.
AND SHE TOLD ME
TO CALL HER WINNIE.
OH MY GOD!
YOU TOTALLY-
HAVE A SHOT!
THAT WAS A GREAT SHOW
LAST NIGHT, EH, WINNIE?
IT'S MS. OH.
OR NOT.
OUCH.
♪ I WANT TO BUY
YOU PRETTY THINGS ♪
♪ HORSES AND CASTLES
AND DIAMOND RINGS ♪
HEY,
I READ YOUR PLAY.
AND?
IT'S...
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
YEAH,
I MADE SOME CHANGES.
YOU MADE CLARA THE HERO.
THAT'S BECAUSE SHE IS
THE HERO.
♪ ...BREATH FOR ONE ANOTHER ♪
♪ THEY WILL NEVER
SUFFOCATE US ♪
♪ AND IF WE STAY CLOSE
TO EACH OTHER ♪
ARE WE REALLY
STILL NOT TALKING?
YOU AMBUSHED ME.
OKAY, WE SHOULD
HAVE TALKED FIRST.
BUT ADOPTION
IS AN OPTION.
I WON'T ABANDON MY SON.
I DON'T WANNA BE
A FAILURE...
BUT YOU ARE!
WE BOTH ARE.
WE'RE STRUGGLING.
WE'RE HURTING EACH OTHER.
AND YOU'RE NEVER HERE.
YOU DON'T PAY
ANY ATTENTION TO TY.
ADMIT IT. YOU DON'T
REALLY WANNA BE A DAD.
WE CAN GIVE HIM
A BETTER LIFE...
WE CAN GET BACK TO SCHOOL,
AND SPORTS, AND MUSIC.
WE CAN MAKE SOMETHING
OF OURSELVES.
IF WE GIVE TY UP,
THERE'S NO REASON
FOR YOU TO STAY HERE.
AND NO REASON FOR US
TO STAY TOGETHER EITHER.
♪ THEY WILL NEVER
SEPARATE US ♪
♪♪♪