ADAM:
YOU'RE GONNA WAKE UP
MOM AND DAD!
DID YOU HAVE
ANOTHER NIGHTMARE?
THAT WOULD ONLY HAPPEN
IF I GOT TO SLEEP,
SO NO.
SIMPSON SHUT
THE WEIGHT ROOM DOWN
'CAUSE KATIE WROTE SOMETHING
IN THE PAPER.
REALLY?
WHO WOULD TALK
TO LOIS LANE?
WHAT, DID SHE GIVE YOU
A POLYGRAPH?
NO, I WAS JUST AN IDIOT.
SHE WANTED ME
TO TALK TO HER,
AND I LIKED
TELLING HER STUFF
'CAUSE SHE'S COOL
AND KINDA TOUGH.
PLUS, SHE'S CUTE.
THE HONEY TRAP -
CLASSIC SPY LADY MOVE.
YEAH, PART OF ME
WAS EVEN THINKING
OF ASKING HER OUT.
BUT THEN I...
UH-OH.
I BLEW IT.
I FLIPPED OVER
A CHAIR.
ADAM,
I BASICALLY LOST IT.
I CAN'T EVEN GET THROUGH A DAY
WITHOUT FLIPPING OUT, ADAM.
SO YOU FIGURE OUT
HOW TO FIX YOURSELF FIRST.
I DON'T KNOW
IF THAT'LL EVER HAPPEN.
WELL, NOT IF FISTFIGHTS
ARE ALL YOU'RE TRYING.
LOOK, IF KATIE WANTS YOU
TO OPEN UP TO HER,
THAT'S GOTTA BE WORTH A TRY,
RIGHT?
MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Oh oh-oh... ♪
I can make it through
(Oh oh-oh...)
♪ I can make it through ♪
(I can make it!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
I HOPE YOU TAKE SUGAR.
WHAT'S THIS?
APOLOGY COFFEE.
CAN WE PLEASE FORGET
THAT I LOST IT ON YOU
YESTERDAY?
THAT WASN'T ME.
I COULD HAVE HIDDEN
THE DETAILS BETTER
IN MY ARTICLE.
I DIDN'T MEAN
FOR SIMPSON
TO SHUT YOU OUT OF
THE WEIGHT ROOM.
YOU WERE JUST DOING
YOUR JOB.
AND SPEAKING OF WHICH,
I HEAR YOU NEED
A SPORTS REPORTER.
(LAUGHS)
YOU'RE SERIOUS?
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR SOMETHING
LESS INTENSE TO DO.
MAYBE I'D BE GOOD.
I'VE BEEN IN
YOUR ENGLISH CLASSES
AND, UM...
HEY, I CAN WRITE ABOUT STUFF
I CARE ABOUT.
IF IT MEANS
YOU'RE FORGIVING ME
FOR ACCIDENTALLY NARC'ING
YOU OUT TO SIMPSON,
I'LL LET YOU TRY OUT.
TRY OUT.
THAT'S GENEROUS.
(LAUGHS)
THAT'S ME,
SUPER-GENEROUS.
THE ASSIGNMENT MEETING'S
RIGHT AFTER SCHOOL TODAY,
OKAY?
OKAY,
I'LL BRING MY A-GAME.
LOOK, I'M SORRY,
BUT I WISH YOU WOULDN'T
HAVE RUN OFF LAST NIGHT.
WELL, ACTUALLY,
THAT WASN'T ME.
THAT WAS DAVID
WHO APPARENTLY LIKES CRICKET
AND LOOSE LEAF TEA.
I JUST WANTED MY PARENTS
TO THINK YOU WERE GREAT
SO WE CAN SPEND
WAY MORE TIME TOGETHER.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE HAPPY
ABOUT BEING HONEST WITH THEM.
I AM.
SO THEN WHY
MAKE ME LIE?
LOOK,
IF YOU WEREN'T READY
FOR YOUR PARENTS
TO MEET YOUR BOYFRIEND,
THAT WOULDA BEEN FINE
WITH ME.
I WOULD'VE JUST DEALT
WITH YOUR CURFEW.
OKAY, WAIT.
STOP,
LET'S BAAAACK IT UP HERE...
(EXHALES)
AND START ALL OVER AGAIN.
DAVE TURNER,
DO YOU WANNA MEET
MY PARENTS?
OKAY, SORRY,
I JUST WANNA GET THIS CLEAR.
WHO EXACTLY
ARE YOU INVITING?
ACTUAL DAVE.
COME CRACK A FEW JOKES
MY PARENTS MIGHT NOT GET.
HECK, YOU COULD PICK THE RAISINS
OUT OF MY MOM'S BAKING,
IF YOU WANT.
CAN I BE YOUR BOYFRIEND
ALSO?
I'LL TALK TO MY PARENTS
ABOUT THAT.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
JULIAN:
I FOUND US ANOTHER ONE
OF THOSE CLUBS
THAT DON'T EXIST.
OWEN:
OH, GOOD!
NOW THAT PRETTY BOY GOT US
LOCKED OUT OF THE WEIGHT ROOM.
MY COUSIN'S FRIEND HOLDS
MMA MATCHES
A COUPLE NIGHTS A WEEK.
FOR REAL?
WAS I TALKING TO YOU?
COME ON, GUYS,
I'M SORRY THAT I BLABBED
TO KATIE,
BUT YOU CAN'T FREEZE ME
OUT LIKE THIS.
(SIGHS) ALL RIGHT.
I FOUND US SOME ACTION
SHE CAN'T SHUT DOWN.
AFTER SCHOOL TODAY
WE'RE GONNA GO CHECK IT OUT.
YOU IN?
I CAN'T.
WHY NOT?
I PASSED ON EVERYTHING
I'VE BEEN TAUGHT,
AND YOU'RE BETTER
THAN ME.
YOU'RE GOOD.
IT'S NOT THAT.
IT'S JUST I'M JOINING
A DIFFERENT CLUB.
WHAT, CHESS?
YEARBOOK?
(BELL RINGS)
I'LL SEND YOU THE ADDRESS
FOR WHEN YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND.
THANKS FOR MEETING ME AGAIN.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE AMBUSHED YOU
BY ASKING YOU FOR A KIDNEY.
AND YOU WERE REASONABLE
TO EXPECT SOME KIND
OF COMPENSATION.
YOU WEREN'T BEING SELFISH;
I WAS.
SO...
I GUESS I'M JUST...
ASKING FOR A SECOND CHANCE
AT A FIRST IMPRESSION.
YOU DON'T NEED TO ASK
FOR A SECOND CHANCE, HOLLY J.
ARE YOU OKAY?
I'M JUST GONNA WAIT
FOR A KIDNEY...
LIKE LOTS OF
OTHER PEOPLE DO.
LOOK, I JUST REALLY WANNA
STOP SAYING KIDNEY NOW.
I WANT TO HELP YOU,
I REALLY DO.
I'M TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO FIND A WAY
TO MAKE THE TRANSPLANT
HAPPEN.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO,
DAWN.
OH, I DO.
NO, REALLY, I HAD NO RIGHT.
THAT WAS... A STRANGE
AND SUPER INTENSE WAY
TO MEET THE DAUGHTER
YOU GAVE UP FOR ADOPTION.
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED
TO MEET YOU.
I FEEL LIKE THAT'S THE SECRET
GOOD PART OF ALL OF THIS.
NOW WE CAN JUST MEET,
TALK.
WHATEVER.
SO, UM...
MY GRAD'S COMING UP.
I REMEMBER MINE
LIKE IT WAS YESTERDAY.
AND PROM?!
THAT WAS ONE
OF THE BEST NIGHTS
OF MY LIFE.
MAYBE I'D BE MORE EXCITED
IF I COULD FIND A DRESS
THAT I ACTUALLY LIKED.
I'M NOT SURE WE'RE MAKING
THE STRONGEST CHOICE
EDITORIALLY.
CLAIRE:
WELL, WHAT ABOUT
A SPLIT-PAGE DEBATE?
KATIE:
THAT'S A LOT OF COLUMN WIDTH.
CAN'T WE AFFORD
THE REAL ESTATE?
KATIE:
WE'D HAVE TO PULL
THE SUDOKU
AND THAT MIGHT LEAD TO MUTINY.
IN THE STAFF ROOM, ANYWAY.
(KATIE'S VOICE FADES OUT)
DREW:
(PANTING)
PLEASE...
PLEASE DON'T KILL ME.
(KICKING GRUNTS)
(SIRENS)
(GASPS)
DREW? YOU OKAY?
I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO BORE YOU.
CAN I GET SOME KIND OF
SPORTS OPINION COLUMN TOMORROW?
SORRY, I GOTTA GO.
FIONA:
OKAY, LAST PIN...
THINK I HAVE A CAREER
AS A HUMAN MANNEQUIN?
IT LOOKS WAY BETTER ON YOU
THAN IT DOES ON ME!
IT'S YOURS.
I'LL GO SHOPPING.
HEY, I THINK I MIGHT MEET UP
WITH DAWN AGAIN.
MAYBE NEXT WEEK.
REALLY? WELL, I KNEW
YOU COULD DO IT.
I FINALLY GET HER.
WE'RE CONNECTING.
SO THANK YOU FOR MAKING ME TRY.
OH, I WANTED TO SHOW
YOU SOMETHING.
FIONA:
HOLLY J! POINTY PINS!
(GIGGLES)
YOU READY FOR A PROM
TIME MACHINE?
DAWN'S PROM PICTURES...
SHE SAID IT WAS
THE BEST NIGHT OF HER LIFE,
AND SHE STILL HAS THE DRESS.
OH MY GOD!
THAT'S IT!
WHAT?
YOUR BIRTH MOM'S DRESS
IS STUNNING;
I WANT IT.
DO YOU THINK DAWN
WOULD SELL IT TO ME?
I DON'T KNOW,
SHE SEEMED PRETTY ATTACHED.
I MEAN, YEAH,
IT'S HARD TO PUT A PRICE
ON VINTAGE...
PLUS SENTIMENTAL VALUE.
I'D SAY...
FI, NO...
TWENTY THOUSAND,
GIVE OR TAKE?
I CAN COME UP
WITH THE CASH.
UM...
SO WHAT'D YOU GUYS
THINK OF DAVE?
DAVE'S A VERY NICE
YOUNG MAN.
IT'S ALWAYS NICE
TO MEET YOUR FRIENDS.
YEAH, ABOUT THAT,
I HAVE A CONFESSION.
DAVE ISN'T MY FRIEND.
DAVID'S YOUR TUTOR?
HE'S A BOY...
AND HE'S A FRIEND,
AND IF YOU PUT THOSE
TWO WORDS TOGETHER,
YOU GET...?
HE'S YOUR FRIEND-BOY.
REALLY, MOM?
YOU KNOW WE DON'T LIKE
EITHER YOU OR SAV DATING;
IT'S A DISTRACTION.
YOU SHOULD FOCUS ON-
SCHOOL AND GOOD FRIENDS.
BUT DAVE IS MY GOOD FRIEND
AND I'M DOING WELL IN SCHOOL,
AND WE'RE GOOD PEOPLE.
I STILL DO NOT LIKE
THIS IDEA.
BUT I'M BEING HONEST!
I'M TELLING YOU THE TRUTH
SO I DON'T HAVE TO RUN AROUND
BEHIND YOUR BACK.
WE'RE GLAD THAT
YOU'RE BEING HONEST WITH US.
I GUESS IT WAS BOUND
TO HAPPEN AT SOME POINT.
SO DOES THIS MEAN
I CAN...
MAYBE HAVE DAVE COME OVER
AGAIN...
AS MY FRIEND-BOY?
(LAUGHS)
OKAY.
CROWD:
(CHEERING)
(GRUNTS)
CROWD:
(CHEERS)
REF:
THAT'S IT!
OWEN:
OKAY, NOT GOING IN THERE.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S GET OUTTA HERE.
HEY, GUYS,
YOU READY TO DO THIS?
NO, WE ARE NOT READY
TO DO THIS, ACTUALLY.
WE'RE GOING.
C'MON.
NO, NO, NO.
I JUST GOT HERE.
REF:
WHO'S NEXT?
DREW:
YEAH, RIGHT HERE.
JULIAN:
DREW! DREW!
CROWD:
(SHOUTING AND WHISTLING)
(SHOUTING)
C'MON! YEAH! LET'S GO!
REF:
COME ON, GUYS!
BRING IT ON!
CROWD:
(CHEERING AND SHOUTING)
(GRUNTS)
UNGH!
CROWD:
OOH...
HIT 'EM, MAN!
COME ON!
(GRUNTING)
COME ON, MAN!
COME ON!
ROLL, MAN, ROLL!
ALL RIGHT,
HE'S DONE!
LEE, HE'S DONE!
OWEN:
GET OUTTA MY WAY!
DREW!
HEY, HEY, HEY!
LOOK AT ME!
JULIAN:
DREW! DREW!
OWEN:
SNAP OUT OF IT.
COME ON.
JULIAN:
YOU DON'T TAKE A BREAK,
DO YOU?
DREW:
I JUST NEED TO GET STRONGER.
HE HAD YOU IN
A TRIANGLE HOLD!
I'M SURPRISED
YOU'RE STILL ALIVE.
WELL, HERE I AM.
SERIOUSLY, BRO?
YOU GOT A DEATH WISH
OR SOMETHING?
I LEFT MYSELF OPEN
FOR A CHOKE HOLD.
STUPID, I KNOW.
BUT I WANT TO BEAT HIM.
NO. YOU'RE DONE.
CLUB'S OVER.
JULIAN, C'MON.
LOOK, WEREN'T YOU JOINING
SOMETHING ELSE ANYWAY?
I DID; NEWSPAPER.
WELL, STICK WITH
THE PAPER.
GET THE GIRL,
STOP USING YOUR FISTS.
YOU'LL GET YOURSELF KILLED.
FINE.
(SIGHS)
IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN,
DAVID.
I PREFER DAVE.
DAVID NEVER STUCK.
OF COURSE.
UM, WHAT ABOUT YOU, MR. B?
HOW YOU BEEN?
IF YOU DON'T MIND,
I PREFER MR. BHANDARI.
(LAUGHS)
(LAUGHS) OF COURSE,
OF COURSE.
ANYWAYS,
I WANT YOU GUYS TO KNOW
THAT I REALLY CARE
ABOUT ALLI.
SHE'S AWESOME.
WOULD YOU LIKE
SOME TEA?
ALLI:
UM, NOT FOR DAVE.
YEAH,
I'M NOT A BIG TEA GUY.
YEAH... WHEW!
ANYWAYS, YOU GUYS WANNA PLAY
A GAME OR SOMETHING?
AN INTELLECTUAL GAME, MAYBE,
LIKE SCRABBLE?
OR CARDS?
MRS. BHANDARI:
OH NO, WE DON'T-
I DON'T THINK
WE EVEN HAVE A DECK OF...
POKER?
BUT YOU HAVE TO WATCH OUT,
DAVID.
I HAVE TO WARN YOU,
MY FRIENDS AND I PLAYED
FOR HOURS
BETWEEN CLASSES
AT UNIVERSITY.
I TRIED TO TEACH ALLI
YEARS AGO.
YEAH, I KNOW.
BORING!
DAVE AND MR. BHANDARI:
HOW CAN YOU SAY THAT?
I THOUGHT I'D SHAKE UP
OUR MEETINGS
WITH A LITTLE
FRESH AIR.
THANKS FOR LETTING ME BUY YOU
THE NON-DAIRY LATTE.
IT'S QUITE A TREAT,
ACTUALLY.
OKAY, UM...
THIS MIGHT SOUND WEIRD,
BUT MY FRIEND FIONA
WANTS TO BUY
YOUR PROM DRESS.
SHE'S A NUT FOR VINTAGE.
WELL, THAT'S SWEET,
BUT I CAN LEND IT TO HER.
SHE INSISTS SHE COULDN'T.
SHE SAID
IT'S EXTREMELY VALUABLE.
WELL, IT'S NICE, BUT-
SHE WANTS TO PAY YOU
TWENTY THOUSAND DOLLARS.
THAT AMOUNT SOUNDS FAMILIAR.
FIONA CAN'T HELP
HAVING FABULOUS
AND EXPENSIVE TASTE IN GOWNS.
AND THIS WON'T GET US
INTO TROUBLE?
SHE'LL PAY CASH.
(CLINK)
(SIGHS)
HEY, MR. TORRES.
BEEN LOOKING FOR YOU
ALL DAY.
JUST TRYING TO LAY LOW.
THAT'S WHAT WRITERS DO
WHEN THEY BLOW DEADLINES.
WHERE'S MY PIECE?
I'M TRYING TO DO IT.
BUT I CAN'T,
I'M SORRY.
YOU NEED TO FIND
SOMEONE ELSE.
SO I GUESS I'LL NEVER
FIND OUT, HUH?
THE BIG MYSTERY?
WHAT IS DREW TORRES
AFRAID OF?
IS THAT FOR
YOUR NEXT ARTICLE?
I'M NOT ASKING
AS A JOURNALIST.
♪ Stand tall and proud ♪
♪ You're a steep bow ♪
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
I HAVE NIGHTMARES,
AND THE ONLY ANSWER
IS FIGHTING.
SO THE RUMOURS ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED AFTER SPRING BREAK
ARE TRUE?
I GOT JUMPED...
BY A BUNCH OF GUYS.
KATIE, I THOUGHT
I WAS GOING TO DIE.
WHY DIDN'T YOU
JUST SAY THAT?
BECAUSE BEING SCARED
IS WEAK.
EVERYBODY'S SCARED
OF SOMETHING.
HAVE YOU EVER
THOUGHT ABOUT
TRYING SOME OTHER FORM
OF TRAINING?
SOMETHING STRUCTURED?
MAYBE WE COULD DO
SOMETHING TOGETHER?
♪ But it's okay ♪
♪ 'cause I fall asleep
with dignity... ♪
OKAY...
I'M SORRY,
THAT WAS WRONG.
NO, THAT WASN'T
A STOP SIGN.
NO, I CAN'T DO THIS
TO YOU.
I'M JUST GONNA MESS
EVERYTHING UP LIKE LAST TIME.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
DON'T FOLLOW ME.
ALL RIGHT,
TWO PAIR.
SHOW 'EM.
THREE OF A KIND,
SCARLET LADIES
ARE GOING TO A SHOW.
UM, I THINK I HAVE
A ROYAL FLUSH?
AGH!
I RAISED A CHEATER.
COME TO MAMA!
HA! BEGINNER'S LUCK!
LOOK, I'VE HAD ENOUGH,
BUT I DEMAND A REMATCH.
ANY TIME, MR. BHANDAR-
DAVE: OH!
MR. BHANDARI: WATCH!
DAVE:
ALMOST STEPPED ON A HEART.
YEAH,
BE CAREFUL YOU DON'T.
(SQUEALS)
I'M HAVING SO MUCH FUN!
I KNOW. I TOLD YOU,
PARENTS LOVE DAVE.
(SIGHS OF RELIEF)
THIS IS SUCH A RELIEF.
I MEAN,
DO YOU KNOW HOW AWESOME
OUR SUMMER'S GONNA BE?
WE CAN SPEND A WHOLE LOT
OF TIME TOGETHER.
I KNOW, IT'S GONNA BE
JUST YOU AND ME, GIRL.
(SIGHS) THANK YOU
FOR BEING SO NICE TO ME
THROUGH MY PARENT INSANITY.
YOU'RE A PRINCE.
YEAH, YOU'RE MY PRINCESS.
AWWW.
BOTH:
(GIGGLE)
ANNOUNCEMENT OVER P.A.:
DR. SWAN TO O.R. 3,
DR. SWAN TO O.R. 3.
I HURRIED OVER AS SOON
AS I GOT YOUR MESSAGE.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
BETTER THAN OKAY.
DAWN'S DONATING HER KIDNEY.
R-REALLY?
I'LL GIVE HER A CALL
TO THANK HER...
OR WE'LL SEND HER FLOWERS.
BOTH:
(GIGGLING)
OH! FIONA!
DAWN'S DONATING HER KIDNEY!
REALLY? (GASPS)
THAT'S THE BEST NEWS EVER!
MARY KATE:
AND WHAT'S THAT?
OH, I JUST PICKED UP
MY PROM DRESS.
LET'S SEE!
(GASPS) OH!
VINTAGE!
SUDDENLY I'M EXCITED FOR PROM!
WE SHOULD BOOK THAT LIMO THEN.
HAVE I MENTIONED
HOW MUCH I LOVE YOU GUYS?
CROWD:
(CHEERING AND SHOUTING)
REMATCH!
SORRY, PRINCESS.
I DON'T NEED
NO HOMICIDE CHARGE.
YOU GOT LUCKY
LAST TIME.
LET'S GO.
CROWD:
(SHOUTING AND WHISTLING)
REF:
YOU KNOW THE RULES!
NOW FIGHT!
(GRUNTS)
(CROWD CHEERS AND SHOUTS)
UNGH!
DREW:
UNNNGH!
(HARD THUMP)
WOO!
REF:
THAT'S IT!
HE'S TAPPED!
HE'S DONE!
GET OFF!
LET'S GO!
(PUNCHING GRUNTS)
KATIE:
DREW!
(GRUNTS)
C'MON, THAT'S ENOUGH!
AARRRGGGHHHH!
REF:
THAT'S ENOUGH!
GET THIS GUY
OUTTA HERE!
YOU WON'T SEE HIM
HERE AGAIN.
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
NOT TO COME.
I GUESS YOU CAN'T
TELL ME WHAT TO DO.
I GOT YOU.
(PANTING)
ALLI:
AND HE'S COMING OVER FOR DINNER
ON SUNDAY!
HO-LY.
WHEN'S HE MOVING IN?
HA! YEAH, RIGHT.
(SIGHS) I JUST CAN'T WAIT
FOR SUMMER, Y'KNOW?
BEING TOGETHER
FOR DAYS ON END...
THAT'S WHAT THE SUMMER'S
ALL ABOUT.
(GIGGLES)
MR. BETENKAMP:
MISS BHANDARI,
MAY I SEE YOU?
YES.
YOU REMEMBER THAT
SPALDING SCIENCE PROGRAM
YOU APPLIED TO?
LIKE FOREVER AGO?
YEAH, WELL,
THIS CAME FOR YOU.
AGH! ENOUGH SUSPENSE!
YOU GOT IN!
LOOKS LIKE SOMEONE'S GONNA
BE SPENDING THE SUMMER
IN OUR NATION'S CAPITAL!
I HAVE TO GO AWAY
FOR THE WHOLE SUMMER?
YEAH, IT'S EXCITING.
RIGHT?
GOOD FOR YOU!
SO MUCH FOR THE SUMMER
OF ALLI AND DAVE.
I'M GLAD YOU CAME.
DREW:
SORRY I'M LATE.
IT'S THE FIRST TIME
I'VE GEARED UP FOR TAE KWON DO.
LOVE THE BELT;
WHITE'S YOUR COLOUR.
HEY, WHY DO YOU
GET A GREEN ONE?
OH, YOU'LL SEE.
I GET THE FIGHTING,
YOU KNOW.
WHEN YOU'RE SCARED,
LEARNING TO DEFEND YOURSELF
BUILDS CONFIDENCE.
BUT IT TAKES DISCIPLINE,
CONTROL,
INNER CALM.
OKAY.
YOU READY?
DO YOU WANT TO CONQUER
YOUR FEARS?
THANKS FOR NOT
GIVING UP ON ME.
UH, THERE'S STILL TIME.
I'M NOT GONNA
MAKE IT EASY.
GOOD TO KNOW.
WHOA! UNGH!
HOW'D YOU DO THAT?
IT'S NOT MY FIRST RODEO.
DON'T MESS WITH ME.
OW.
I KNEW THERE WAS A REASON
I LIKED YOU.
♪ Yes I wonder ♪
♪ Will you always love me... ♪