A BUH BUH BABY -
MY LITTLE BABY.
YO MAMA'S IN THE SCHOOL
YOU'RE COVERED IN DROOL.
(LAUGHS)
HERE'S MY MAN
OF MANY TALENTS.
WHAT'S THE SMALL FRY
DOING AT SCHOOL?
WE KINDA NEED
TO COOL IT.
YEAH, I KNOW.
NOT AT SCHOOL.
BUT WE CAN HAVE FUN
AT WORK, RIGHT?
JENNA IS TALKING
TO SIMPSON.
SHE'S COMING BACK
TO DEGRASSI.
SO, MEXICAN NIGHT TONIGHT
AT WORK, EH?
WELL, I'LL BRING
MY SOMBRERO.
'KAY.
SO WHAT'D HE SAY?
CAN YOU COME BACK?
(SIGHS) NO.
I MEAN, I CAN,
IT'S JUST...
WE HAVE NO CHILDCARE.
SO I CAN'T.
IS THERE ANYTHING
I CAN DO?
STAY HOME WITH TY?
I DON'T REALLY HAVE
THE RIGHT EQUIPMENT.
DON'T CALL MY BOOBS
EQUIPMENT, KC.
MY MOM COULD WATCH HIM?
SHE TOLD US SHE WOULDN'T
BE A BABY-SITTER, REMEMBER?
OKAY, WHAT ABOUT
THE MOMMIES GROUP?
UGH, THOSE LADIES
ARE SUPER COMPETITIVE!
IT'S SO ANNOYING.
MAYBE YOU COULD ASK THEM
HOW THEY DO IT.
FINE, I'LL ASK.
BUT ONE WAY OR ANOTHER,
I NEED TO COME BACK
TO DEGRASSI.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
WE'RE STILL MISSING THE TWELFTH
SUPREME COURT JUDGE!
DID YOU KNOW
SHE'S A MUSICIAN?
RUTH BADER GINSBERG?
NO, MS. OH!
SHE PLAYED VIOLIN
IN SOME INDIE BAND.
THEY TOURED WITH ARCADE FIRE!
DID YOU KNOW THIS PRESENTATION
IS DUE NEXT PERIOD?
YEAH, I KNOW, ALL I'M SAYING
IS, YOU KNOW,
SHE'S PROBABLY THE COOLEST
TEACHER, LIKE, EVER.
DUDE, SET ASIDE YOUR TEACHER
CRUSH FOR ONE SECOND AND FOCUS!
THERE'S NO CRUSH!
I'M FOCUSED.
SAV!
I'M SUPERVISING THE SCORE
FOR THE SCHOOL PLAY
AND I WAS HOPING YOU'D
COME OUT FOR IT.
TODAY AT LUNCH?
SURE.
YEAH, IT'S A DATE!
OH YEAH,
NO CRUSH AT ALL.
NO, IT'S JUST LIKE...
YOU KNOW, I REALLY
HAVEN'T HAD ANYONE
TO TALK MUSIC WITH
IN A WHILE.
AND SHE'D MAKE
A GREAT MENTOR!
IS THAT WHAT THE KIDS
ARE CALLING IT THESE DAYS?
MENTOR?
(LAUGHS)
ANNOUNCEMENT:
TICKETS ARE ON SALE NOW
FOR THE GRADE 11
ORIGINAL THEATRE PRODUCTION,
LOVE ROULETTE.
BASED ON A TRUE STORY.
WHY THANK YOU, JAKE.
YOU ARE SO-
STRONG?
I WAS GONNA SAY
CHIVALROUS.
SO ANY NEW IDEAS ON HOW
TO AVOID OUR PARENTS?
WELL, I GUESS BEING IN DENIAL
THAT THEY'RE DATING
ISN'T GOING TO MAKE IT
GO AWAY.
(GROANS)
NOT SO FAR, NO.
(LAUGHS)
HOW 'BOUT YOU COME OVER
AFTER SCHOOL?
MY MOM'S WORKING LATE,
WE CAN RENOVATE MY BEDROOM.
MMM HOT.
BUT I CAN'T TONIGHT.
NO PROBLEM! SHE WORKS
LATE ALL WEEK.
SEE THIS IS WHY I LIKE YOU
CLARE, YOU'RE SO EASY-GOING.
I TRY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING TONIGHT,
ANYWAY? JUST ASKING!
OH, I DIDN'T TELL YOU?
I'M BUILDING THE SETS
FOR THE NEW PLAY.
THE SCHOOL PLAY?
WRITTEN BY
AND STARRING MY EX?
ELI?
YEAH. I GUESS SO.
IS THAT ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, YEAH.
TOTALLY.
COOL.
YOU KNOW, I'M GLAD I FINALLY
FOUND SOMETHING I LIKE TO DO
AT DEGRASSI.
YOU KNOW, BESIDES YOU.
(SIGHS)
HE'S SO LITTLE, BUT HE'S
ALREADY OUTGROWING
ALL HIS NEWBORN CLOTHES!
THANK GOD MY SISTER
AND I BOTH HAD GIRLS.
HAND-ME-DOWNS ARE A SAVIOR.
IT'S TOO BAD YOU HAD A BOY,
OR I COULD PASS IT ON.
OH, IT'S OKAY.
I'M A THRIFT-STORE
REGULAR.
YEAH, YOU CAN FIND SOME GOOD
STUFF. SAVE SOME MONEY...
SAYS THE MOM WITH
THE THOUSAND DOLLAR STROLLER.
(LAUGHS) I KNOW.
I'M THE WORST.
WHENEVER I SEE SOMETHING
I LIKE, I JUST HAVE TO BUY IT.
WHETHER IT'S A STROLLER,
TOYS, CLOTHES...
HER NANNY CAN BARELY KEEP UP
WITH THE LAUNDRY.
OH, YOU HAVE A NANNY?
YEAH, JUST AFTERNOONS.
WE'RE LOOKING FOR
A SHARE. SHE'S GREAT.
FOR MORNINGS?
REALLY? HOW MUCH?
ABOUT FOUR HUNDRED
A WEEK.
WHOA.
I GUESS IT CAN ADD UP,
BUT IF YOU CAN MAKE IT WORK,
THOSE COUPLE OF HOURS
OF ESCAPE ARE HEAVEN.
(SIGHS)
I'M SURE THEY ARE.
SAV!
YOU'RE EARLY!
UH YEAH, YEAH.
I BROUGHT MY FAVOURITE
MUSICAL SCORES-
TRON, SOCIAL NETWORK,
THERE WILL BE BLOOD.
SHOULD WE LISTEN?
WE SHOULD PROBABLY
WAIT A LITTLE.
RIGHT. YEAH.
PROBABLY TALK MUSIC FIRST.
SO, DID YOU REALLY TOUR
WITH ARCADE FIRE?
OH, YEAH.
YOU HEARD ABOUT THAT?
FUN TOUR.
TOUGH LIFE THOUGH.
MMM, YEAH.
UH, EXCUSE ME, THERE'S
A MEETING IN HERE.
YEAH!
FOR THE PLAY'S HIT SCORE.
BY YOURS TRULY,
MO MASHKOOOUUUUR!
MS. OH:
OKAY, THANK-YOU
ALL FOR COMING.
AS DEGRASSI'S MOST
TALENTED MUSICIANS,
ONE OF YOU WILL WRITE
THE SCORE TO THE PLAY.
(SNEEZING)
MO MASHKOUR.
AND SINCE THERE'S
SO MUCH INTEREST,
I'M MAKING IT
A COMPETITION.
AND THE WINNER WILL WORKSHOP
THE FINAL VERSION
WITH LITTLE OLD ME.
YOU'LL ALL PRESENT YOUR
ROUGH IDEAS TOMORROW.
IMPRESS ME!
I WILL, MS. OH!
(SNEEZES)
TEACHER'S PET.
SORRY. GOT A BIT OF
A TICKLE IN MY THROAT.
MS. OH:
NOW, SOME GUIDELINES:
THEY WANT SOMETHING MOODY,
HAUNTING...
DO YOU THINK ELI WOULD SABOTAGE
MY RELATIONSHIP WITH JAKE?
MY LIST OF THINGS ELI
WOULDN'T DO IS VERY SHORT.
AND WHY ARE WE TALKING
ABOUT ELI AGAIN?
ELI ASKED JAKE
TO BUILD HIS SETS.
JAKE'S A CARPENTER, RIGHT?
MAYBE IT'S FOR REALS.
ELI'S TAKING THE PLAY
PRETTY SERIOUSLY.
UH, ZINC?
JUST TELL ME
I'M BEING PARANOID.
YOU TOTALLY ARE.
UNLESS ELI ACTUALLY
WANTED TO POISON JAKE.
WHAT? HE POISONED FITZ
WITH IPECAC.
I MEAN, HE'S BEEN
OFF HIS MEDS A LOT.
BUT YOU DON'T THINK HE'D
ACTUALLY TRY AND HURT JAKE?
I'M TEASING.
C'MON, THEY'RE FINE.
ELI CAN CONTROL
HIS FEELINGS.
YOU'RE NOT HELPING,
YOU KNOW THAT?
UH, HOW MUCH ZINC
DID YOU PUT IN THERE?
I DON'T...
OH MY GOD!
(DEFLATING NOISE)
(BABY CRYING)
(DOOR OPENING)
JENNA?
JENNA!
OKAY, OKAY, TYSON.
SHHH.
IT'S OKAY.
I'M HERE.
YOU CAN'T LEAVE HIM
LIKE THAT.
I KNOW. I JUST-
I CAN'T GO TO SCHOOL,
I SPEND ALL DAY, EVERY DAY,
ALONE WITH HIM.
I NEED A BREAK.
IT'S OKAY.
(SIGHS)
IT IS TOUGH TO DO THIS
AT YOUR AGE.
I KNOW.
WHAT DID YOU DO?
WHEN DID YOU GO BACK
TO SCHOOL AFTER YOU HAD KC?
I ACTUALLY NEVER DID.
NEVER?!
HOW DID YOU COPE
WITH BEING ALONE?
NOT VERY WELL...
I WENT TO A REALLY
DARK PLACE.
BUT YOU ARE STRONG
AND BRIGHT.
I DON'T FEEL
THAT WAY ANYMORE.
YOU KNOW, THE OTHER MOMMIES
THEY HAVE SO MUCH HELP.
I'VE GOT A DEAD MOM,
A DEAD BEAT DAD.
EVEN MY BROTHER MOVED
BACK TO ALBERTA...
(SIGHS)
WELL, YOU'VE GOT US.
LISTEN, MY SHIFTS
ARE MOSTLY EVENINGS NOW.
SO WHAT IF I TOOK TYSON
IN THE MORNINGS?
AND THEN MAYBE YOU
COULD GO TO SCHOOL PART-TIME.
THAT'S TOO MUCH TO ASK.
JENNA, YOU NEED THE BREAK,
PLUS, IT'LL GIVE ME
SOME GRANDMA TIME.
REALLY?
YOU'RE SURE?
(ELECTRONIC MUSIC)
SOUNDS AWESOME!
(SLOW INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC)
DUDE, THAT'S YOUR SCORE?
YEAH.
YOU HEAR THE STRINGS?
MS. OH'S GONNA LOVE IT.
SURE, BUT LIKE, HAVE YOU
EVEN TALKED TO ANYONE
ABOUT THE PLAY?
IT'S ABOUT VEGAS NIGHT,
RIGHT?
(ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYS)
HEAR THAT MELODY?
HUH?!
AND IN THE BACKGROUND?
SLOT MACHINES. BOOM!
NO, IT IS PRETTY GOOD.
IF YOU WANT A CHANCE TO WORK
WITH AN OH-CALIBER HOTTIE,
YOU'VE GOTTA BRING
YOUR A-GAME, PAL!
OH, EASY. TABLE THREE DOESN'T
NEED ALL THOSE CALORIES.
THEY ALREADY HAD THE TRIPLE
CHEESE MAMMOTH NACHOS.
OKAY, MORE FOR YOU THEN.
(LAUGHS) AS IF YOU WANTED
THIS TO END.
WANTED TO END WHAT?
NOTHING, JUST A LITTLE
GAME WE PLAY. INSIDE JOKE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
SURPRISING YOU, SILLY!
ONCE YOU'RE DONE WORK,
WE CELEBRATE!
CELEBRATE...
I CAN GO BACK TO SCHOOL!
REALLY?
YOUR MOM'S GONNA TAKE TY
FOR THE MORNINGS.
I CAN DO TWO CLASSES,
PLUS LUNCH.
ISN'T THAT GREAT?
SO AT NIGHT YOU'LL HAVE
TO WATCH TY AND DO HOMEWORK?
WHEN I'M ALONE WITH TY,
I GET SO DEPRESSED.
I NEED TO SEE MY FRIENDS.
BE NORMAL.
I NEED THIS.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE'LL MAKE IT WORK.
IT'S GOING TO BE FUN!
SO FUN! I KNEW
YOU'D BE EXCITED.
JENNA!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
LEARNING, LAUGHING,
WHATEVER I WANT.
I'M BACK AT DEGRASSI!
R) REALLY?
L) FOR THE MORNINGS, AT LEAST!
WHERE'S TYSON?
ON THE CUTEST LITTLE
BABY VACAY?
HE'S WITH KC'S MOM.
BUT THIS IS MY VACATION.
SO, TELL ME EVERYTHING.
GOSSIP, STORIES,
WHADDAYA GOT?
HEY, J-ROCK, YOU'RE BACK!
HOW'S THE LITTLE MAN?
ANY NEW BABY PICTURES?
SERIOUSLY?!
WHAT?
BABIES ARE CUTE.
CAN WE TALK ABOUT
ANYTHING ELSE? ANYTHING!?
PERINO:
MORNIN' FOLKS.
TODAY, WE'LL BE DISCUSSING
VERY MODERN HISTORY.
PERFECT.
IN THE INTERNET AGE,
CAN NATIONS STILL KEEP
DIPLOMATIC SECRETS?
THAT IS THE QUESTION POSED
BY THE SCANDAL DU JOUR-
WIKILEAKS!
(WHISPERS)
JENNA.
UH... WIKILEAKS!
LIKE, WIKILEAKS...
YOUR LEAKAGE!
MS. MIDDLETON,
CAN I HELP-
OH MY GOD!
UH, I JUST NEED TO PUMP.
ALL RIGHT,
DO WHAT YOU GOTTA DO.
JUST DON'T DO IT HERE.
I DON'T WANNA MISS
THE LECTURE.
JENNA, PLEASE. WE'RE NOT
GONNA HAVE FUN WITHOUT YOU.
SO JUST, HERE,
HALL PASS.
K, RIGHT.
WHERE WERE WE...
WIKILEAKS.
CABLES...
(ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYS)
...AND FINALLY, I CALL IT
LOVE ROULETTE:
THE SO SO SWEET SUITE.
MS. OH:
VERY GOOD, MO.
AND GREAT TITLE.
SAV?
(EXPERIMENTAL MUSIC)
VERY NICE.
THANKS.
THE BASS REPRESENTS
ARI'S HEARTBEAT RACING
AS FRITZ CHASES HIM.
AND THE BRASS, CUTTING IN
HERE AND THERE,
SHOULD EVOKE FRITZ'S KNIFE.
MS. OH:
THAT'S JUST-
WOW.
MO:
(COUGHS) TRY HARD.
MS. OH:
MO, DO YOU NEED A LOZENGE?
I THINK WE HAVE A WINNER!
THE FIRST ORDER OF BUSINESS
IS TO BUILD THIS
INTO A THEME SONG WITH LYRICS
FOR THE OPENING.
I'D LOVE TO HEAR IT
TOMORROW.
WE CAN WORK ON THE REST
OF THE SCORE LATER, OKAY?
SURE. I COULDN'T BE
MORE STOKED,
AND SAV, YOU MIGHT WANT
TO THINK
ABOUT COLLABORATING
WITH MO.
HE HAD SOME PRETTY
GREAT IDEAS TOO.
YOU HEARD THE PRETTY LADY.
SORRY MO.
I WORK ALONE.
HEY, WHERE IS EVERYONE?
ALLI:
IN THE GYM WATCHING
DODGE BALL.
I'D BE THERE TOO,
BUT YOU KNOW, SCIENCE
PROGRAM APPLICATION!
I THOUGHT I WAS SUPPOSED
TO EAT LUNCH WITH KC.
DODGEBALL, REALLY?
UM, HE AND MARISOL
ARE CO-CAPTAINS.
HE DIDN'T TELL YOU?
NO.
NO ONE TELLS ME
ANYTHING ANYMORE.
HE'LL EAT WITH YOU
TOMORROW.
IF THERE IS A TOMORROW.
THAT'S A BIT DARK.
I HAD A LEAK IN CLASS,
ALLI.
MY LIFE IS JUST SO DIFFERENT
FROM EVERYONE ELSE'S.
HEY. YOU CAN DO THIS.
YOU JUST NEED TO FIND
SOMETHING FUN HERE!
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT FUN IS ANYMORE.
WELL, SAV'S BEEN
KILLING HIMSELF
TRYING TO WRITE
SOME MUSIC THING.
MAYBE YOU CAN HELP?
OKAY, MAYBE.
I'LL GET OUTTA
YOUR HAIR THEN.
WAIT.
I CAN DO THIS LATER.
WANNA HAVE LUNCH
WITH A FRIEND?
(LAUGHS) THANKS.
THAT SOUNDS FUN.
WE NEED A MOMENT EARLY ON
THAT SHOWS THE AUDIENCE
THAT CLARA LIKES ARI.
MAYBE SHE JUST STANDS IN
A DOORWAY, WATCHING HIM WORK.
WHOA,
THAT'S REALLY GOOD!
I'M GONNA LET YOU TWO TALK.
IT'S BAD ENOUGH THAT THIS PLAY
DRAGS MY NAME THROUGH THE MUD,
BUT CAN YOU PLEASE LEAVE
JAKE OUT OF THIS?
JAKE?
MY BOYFRIEND.
BUILDING YOUR SETS.
OH JAKE.
STRAPPING. HANDSOME.
GOOD WITH HIS HANDS.
GREAT HIRE.
JUST PROMISE NOT TO SAY
ANYTHING MEAN ABOUT ME
AROUND HIM.
WHERE IS THIS VENOM
COMING FROM?
IT'S NOT- UGH.
YOU'RE OFF YOUR MEDS.
YOU'RE UNSTABLE.
I'M FINE.
I'M THINKING CLEARLY.
THEN WHY DOESN'T THAT
MAKE ME FEEL ANY BETTER?
CLARE, I WOULD NEVER
BAD-MOUTH YOU...
ON PURPOSE.
BUT WHEN I'M IN HERE-
MY CREATIVITY
CAN'T BE CONTAINED.
DO YOU HATE ME SO MUCH YOU'D
YOU'D RUIN MY RELATIONSHIP?
CLAIRE,
I DON'T HATE YOU.
I JUST DON'T KNOW WHY
YOU'RE SO UPSET.
HE'LL BE OUT OF THE PICTURE
SOON ENOUGH.
WAIT.
OUT OF THE PICTURE?
WHAT IS THAT SUPPOSED
TO MEAN?
(LAUGHS) OH CLARE,
ALWAYS SO CURIOUS...
(LAUGHS)
(HUMS)
MAN!
(KNOCKING)
HEY!
I'VE HEARD YOU'VE GOT A...
THING?
JENNA!
THANK GOD YOU'RE HERE.
I HAVE TO WRITE A SONG
FOR THE SCHOOL PLAY
AND IT'S KILLING ME.
OKAY. WHAT DO YOU
HAVE SO FAR?
UH, OKAY.
HM HM HM HM HM HM HM
HUNTER'S KNIFE.
UM, ISN'T THAT
ROW ROW ROW YOUR BOAT?
YES! I'VE ALSO WRITTEN YMCA,
AND THE NATIONAL ANTHEM.
(LAUGHS)
YOU DO NEED MY HELP.
CAN YOU COME AND JAM
IN THE MUSIC ROOM?
NOW?
YEAH, UNLESS YOU HAVE
TO GET BACK TO THE BABY.
UH, NO.
I'LL CHECK IN
WITH GRANDMA.
I'M SURE SHE WOULDN'T MIND
WATCHING HIM A LITTLE LONGER.
PERFECT!
WORKS ALONE, MY ASS.
OH SAV, YOU REALLY SHOULD NOT
LEAVE YOUR THINGS UNATTENDED.
THERE'S HIS BAG.
YOU'RE SERIOUSLY GONNA
GO THROUGH HIS STUFF.
HE'S BEEN OKAY LATELY.
I KNOW HE'S UP TO SOMETHING
I JUST DON'T HAVE ANY PROOF.
ADAM:
WELL, IF YOU'RE SO WORRIED,
TALK TO DAWES OR SOMETHING.
AH-HA! IPECA-
HAND SANITIZER.
C'MON, LET'S GO BEFORE
JAKE CATCHES YOU
AND THINKS YOU'RE
THE CRAZY ONE.
JAKE:
HEY CLARE!
UP HERE!
JAKE?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
ELI ASKED ME TO HANG
SOME LIGHTS.
DON'T YOU THINK THAT STUFF
SHOULD BE SECURED?
NAW, IT'S STURDY.
HOW ABOUT I HOLD IT STEADY,
AND YOU BE A LITTLE
MORE CAREFUL, OKAY?
THINK I'M BEING
PARANOID NOW?
JENNA:
(HUMS) ♪ THE HALLWAYS
OF MY HEART... ♪
HELLO!
(SINGING)
OH, THAT'S IT!
♪ RUNNING THROUGH
THE HALLWAYS OF MY HEART ♪
(GUITAR SOUNDS)
♪ RUNNING THROUGH
THE HALLWAYS OF... ♪
♪ MY HEART ♪
(BANG)
(GASPS)
(BABY CRYING)
TY! OH MY GOSH!
TY!
IT'S OKAY, IT'S OKAY!
SHHH.
OH, IT'S FINE.
IT'S OKAY.
IT'S OKAY,
IT'S OKAY. SHHHH.
OH MY GOD! TY, YOU'RE
OKAY, YOU'RE OKAY.
SHHHH. IT'S OKAY,
IT'S OKAY. IT'S OKAY.
YOU'RE FINE.
YOU SURE YOU DON'T
NEED MY HELP?
FROM YOU? NO.
NOT EVEN HELP
FINDING THIS?
(SIGHS)
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
MAKE ME CO-COMPOSER.
OR WHAT? YOU'LL ERASE
THE HARD DRIVE?
I'D WOULD NEVER DELETE
AN ARTIST'S WORK.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE NOT
VERY GOOD AT BLACKMAIL.
OKAY, HOW'S THIS?
YOU MAKE ME CO-COMPOSER,
OR-
♪ OH GIRL,
YOU MAKE MY HEART BURN ♪
♪ YOU'VE GOT SO MUCH
TO TEACH ♪
♪ I'VE GOT SO MUCH
TO LEARN... ♪
PLEASE STOP.
♪ YOU DROP THE KNOWLEDGE
AND YOU SPEAK THE TRUTH ♪
♪ AND YOU LOOK SO CUTE
IN THOSE TALL LEATHER BOOTS ♪
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
YOU KNOW, THINGS'D PROBABLY
GET PRET-TY CRAZY
IF MS. OH OH OH OH GIRL
HEARD YOUR LITTLE
LOVE BALLAD.
OKAY FINE.
JUST PROMISE TO NEVER
SING THAT AGAIN.
BUT IT'S SO DAMN CATCHY!
(LAUGHS)
HOW IS HE?
IS HE OKAY?
DOCTORS ARE STILL
LOOKING AT HIM.
WHY DID I HAVE TO CALL
LITTLE MISS STEAK'S LANDLINE
TO REACH YOU?
I'VE BEEN HERE AN HOUR!
I WAS BUSSING TABLES,
I DIDN'T HEAR MY PHONE BUZZ.
WHAT DID YOU DO,
ANYWAY?
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT!
HE WAS ON THE CHANGE TABLE,
AND THEN-
THEN YOU ACCIDENTALLY
DROPPED HIM ON HIS HEAD?!
WERE YOU EVEN PAYING
ATTENTION?
DO NOT ACCUSE ME
OF BEING A BAD MOTHER!
I'M WITH HIM ALL THE TIME,
WHILE YOU'RE OFF HAVING FUN.
FUN? I WORK!
TO MAKE MONEY
FOR THIS FAMILY!
ARE YOU SAYING IT'S NOT WORK
TO STAY HOME WITH THE BABY?!
I DON'T KNOW, BUT IT MUST
BE NICE TO SIT AT HOME,
WATCH TV AND PLAY GUITAR,
WHILE OUR BABY FALLS OFF
A TABLE!
YOU'RE SUCH AN ASS!
EXCUSE ME?
GOOD NEWS.
TY'S GOING TO BE OKAY.
OH THANK GOODNESS.
NURSE:
HE PASSED ALL THE TESTS,
BUT HE MAY STILL
HAVE A CONCUSSION,
SO YOU'LL HAVE
TO MONITOR HIM.
WE CAN DO THAT.
THERE IS ONE OTHER THING.
OH GOD. WHAT?
GIVEN THE NATURE OF YOUR
BABY'S INJURIES AND YOUR...
...SITUATION,
I HAVE NO CHOICE BUT TO FILE
A REPORT TO CHILD SERVICES.
BUT WE DIDN'T DO ANYTHING
WRONG. IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
I'M SORRY.
THAT'S POLICY.