♪ You've got to watch them ♪
♪ You're rich enough
to take them down ♪
♪ You're breakin' new doors ♪
♪ Whatcha you think
you're looking for ♪
♪ You've got to watch them ♪
MR. TORRES, I'M CONDUCTING
A LITTLE EXPERIMENT.
I NEED TO SEE IF I CAN FUNCTION
WITHOUT TAKING THESE.
I HAVEN'T TAKEN THESE
SINCE YESTERDAY.
I BELIEVE THEY'RE RESPONSIBLE
FOR KILLING MY CREATIVITY -
WHICH IS GREAT WHEN
YOU'RE WRITING A PLAY.
COME ON, I'M ON-AIR
IN FIVE MINUTES.
PLEASE!
JUST TAKE THESE.
JUST FOR TODAY.
IF THE PILLS AREN'T
WORKING FOR YOU,
THEN TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR.
WHO ARE YOU, MY DAD?
MY UNCLE HAD TO TRY A FEW
DIFFERENT MEDICATIONS
BEFORE HE FOUND ONE
THAT WAS RIGHT FOR HIM.
A FEW MEDICATIONS?
I'M NOT A LAB RAT.
THE LAST COUPLE DAYS
HAVE BEEN A LIVING HELL.
YOU WANT ME TO DO THAT
OVER AND OVER AGAIN
UNTIL SOME QUACK
GETS IT RIGHT?
WELL, OBVIOUSLY NOT, BUT-
ARE YOU GOING TO HELP ME
OR NOT?
SORRY, IT'S SHOW TIME.
YOINK!
I'LL TAKE CARE OF THESE.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ If I hold out ♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
ABOUT THAT TEXT
YOU SAW ON MY PHONE-
YOU'RE BEING
TOTALLY RIDICULOUS.
YOU WERE CHEATING AND
I'M BEING RIDICULOUS. RIGHT.
LET ME EXPLAIN -
THAT DATE I WENT ON,
IT WAS WITH A GIRL,
NOT A GUY.
THAT MAKES ME FEEL
MUCH BETTER.
MY MOM TRICKED ME
INTO A SET-UP
WITH ONE OF HER
FRIENDS' DAUGHTERS.
SOUNDS LIKE THIS DAUGHTER
HAD A GOOD TIME.
IS THIS WHY YOU AND MOM
ARE BACK ON SPEAKING TERMS?
BECAUSE YOU'RE PLAYING INTO
HER HETERO FANTASIES?
THINGS ARE GOOD
WITH MY PARENTS.
WHATEVER KEEPS THEM HAPPY.
SEE,
I KNEW YOU'D CATCH ON.
EVEN IF THEY DON'T
ACCEPT YOU, RILEY?
WELL, I'M HOPE SOME DAY
THEY WILL.
BUT UNTIL I LEAVE
FOR COLLEGE,
I JUST WANT THINGS
BACK TO NORMAL.
WHY CAN'T YOU ACCEPT THAT?
RILEY,
YOU'VE MET MY FAMILY,
YOU'RE PART
OF MY WHOLE LIFE,
BUT I FEEL LIKE
A DIRTY SECRET.
THEN SAY YOU'LL COME TO MY
BIRTHDAY DINNER TONIGHT -
(LAUGHS)
WITH MY PARENTS.
BUT JUST AS FRIENDS?
BETTER THAN NOTHING,
RIGHT?
(BELL RINGS)
MS. DAWES:
AND, GENTLEPEOPLE,
THE PROPOSAL DEADLINE
FOR DEPARTMENT HEADS
IS FAST APPROACHING.
ASSUMING WE HAVE A PLAY
TO STAGE!
GOOD!
SO, WHAT'S THE NEW CONCEPT?
WE NEED A SCRIPT,
LIKE, YESTERDAY.
VERY SOON.
JUST A FEW TWEAKS.
I KNEW
I COULD COUNT ON YOU.
HOW'S IT COMING?
IT'S GREAT!
I'M TRYING A NEW APPROACH.
MS. DAWES:
VERY GOOD!
HAVE YOU FOUND SOMEONE
TO BOUNCE IDEAS OFF OF?
JUST CALL ME RUBBER...
TO BOUNCE THINGS OFF OF.
IDEAS.
OH, (LAUGHS)
JUST HAVE FUN WITH IT, ELI.
YOU STILL GOT
THOSE PILLS?
GOOD.
HEY, DISH PIG.
LOOKING FORWARD TO ANOTHER
FUN NIGHT AT WORK?
ALWAYS.
OH,
TONIGHT'S HAWAIIAN NIGHT.
EVERYBODY'S GETTING LEI'D!
(LAUGHS) LEIS-
LIKE THE FLOWER NECKLACE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I JUST SAID THAT.
(LAUGHS)
HEY, IS LITTLE MISS
STEAKS HIRING?
WHAT?
HEY, I'M JUST SAYING, I COULD
USE A GOOD HAWAIIAN NECKLACE.
(LAUGHS)
MAYBE WE SHOULD GET FLASH
CARDS TO INSPIRE YOU
OR, WE COULD DO SOME
WORD ASSOCIATION.
FORGET IT!
IT'S IS A BAD IDEA.
I NEED THOSE PILLS.
GIVE ME THOSE PILLS.
ELI, BE STRONG!
I'M FALLING APART HERE.
IT'LL BE OKAY.
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
PANICKY. SWEATY. SHAKY.
IF I'M GONNA STAY
AT THIS SCHOOL, I...
I NEED THOSE PILLS!
THEN WHY STAY?
LET'S SKIP!
DO YOU WANT ME
TO HELP YOU OR NOT?
OKAY.
WHERE TO?
HEY.
THIS SHOULD LAST US
THE WEEK.
THANKS.
HERE.
OH, I WASHED YOUR
WORK CLOTHES.
FOR SOMEONE WHO CLEANS THINGS,
THEY GET PRETTY GROSS.
(LAUGHS)
ABOUT THAT,
WE NEED TO TALK...
OOO - ME FIRST!
CHECK THIS OUT!
IT'S A BABY VIDEO MONITOR.
ON SALE THIS WEEK!
(GRUMBLES) TWO HUNDRED BUCKS
IS ON SALE?
(SIGHS)
IT WOULD MAKE THINGS
SO MUCH EASIER.
AND WE CAN AFFORD IT.
THAT'S WHAT I WANTED
TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
I NEED TO QUIT THE JOB
AT THE RESTAURANT.
OH, BUT I THOUGHT
YOU LIKED IT.
I KNOW, BUT I SLEPT
THROUGH MY CLASSES TODAY.
IT'S JUST TOO MUCH.
I'M GOING TO TELL
THEM TONIGHT.
DO WHAT YOU NEED TO DO.
YOU'RE TOTALLY MY HERO
EITHER WAY.
WOW. THIS WATCH
MUST'VE COST HEAPS.
AH WELL, MY SON ONLY TURNS
EIGHTEEN ONCE.
YOU KNOW, WHEN I CAME
FROM GREECE,
I IMAGINED A BETTER LIFE
FOR MY KID.
BUT AN ATHLETIC SCHOLARSHIP
FROM AN AMERICAN UNIVERSITY?
I NEVER DREAMED THIS BIG!
YOU'RE THE ONE THAT TAUGHT ME
TO THROW A FOOTBALL, DAD.
HEY, NEVER FORGET THAT.
DO YOU PLAY FOOTBALL,
ZANE?
JUST THE KICKER.
SOCCER'S MY GAME.
I'M BETTER WITH MY FEET.
ENOUGH SPORTS! YOU'RE BORING
ATHENA AND HER MOM.
ATHENA'S AN ATHLETE TOO.
HEY, YOU AND RILEY
HAVE KIDS,
YOU PICK YOUR SPORT,
YOU'RE SET FOR LIFE.
EVERYONE:
(LAUGHS)
RILEY'S GIRLFRIEND MAY HAVE
SOMETHING TO SAY ABOUT THAT.
RILEY!
YOU HAVE A GIRLFRIEND?!
YEAH,
SHE'S REALLY PRETTY.
BUT YOU SAID THINGS
WERE COMPLICATED.
THEY SURE ARE.
SHE JUST NEEDS TO RELAX.
DOES SHE, NOW?
MR. AND MRS. STAVROS,
THANK YOU FOR DINNER,
BUT I SHOULD GO.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I CAN'T PLAY ALONG,
RILEY.
WHY ARE YOU SO STRESSED?
JUST HAVE FUN WITH IT!
(WHISPERS)
THERE'S NOTHING
FUN ABOUT THIS.
ZANE, PLEASE-
CAN I GO HOME NOW?
WE'VE BEEN WANDERING
THE STREETS FOR HOURS.
ALL DONE!
SEE,
BEING CREATIVE IS EASY!
YOUR TURN.
DO ME!
WRITING WAS A PASSION
THAT CLARE AND I SHARED.
AND NOW THAT WE'RE
NOT TOGETHER, I'M BROKEN.
HOW COULD YOU STILL BE
IN LOVE WITH SOMEONE
WHO HURT YOU SO MUCH?
I DON'T WANT TO BE!
I WANT TO BE OVER HER!
I CAN HELP WITH THAT.
HOW?
EASY.
YOU NEED TO CONFRONT
CLARE.
COME WITH ME.
MARISOL:
HEY THERE,
READY TO GET
YOUR GROOVE ON TONIGHT?
NOT EXACTLY.
I'VE GOTTA QUIT.
AW, BUT WE HAVE
SO MUCH FUN!
YEAH,
BUT I'D MAKE AS MUCH
BEING AT HOME WITH MY KID
ON WELFARE.
SO, LET'S JUST GET YOU
PROMOTED TO BUSBOY THEN.
JUAN,
I'VE GOT A PROPOSAL.
KC'S TALENTS ARE WASTED
IN THE DISH-PIT.
HE'S BUSBOY MATERIAL
AT LEAST.
IS THAT SO?
HE'S CUTE, PERSONABLE,
AND HE'S GOT A KID TO FEED.
ALL RIGHT. LET'S TRY IT OUT
FOR A SHIFT AND SEE.
THIS IS SO STUPID.
JUST PRETEND I'M CLARE.
YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
COME ON! YOU HAVE SO MUCH YOU
NEED TO GET OFF YOUR CHEST!
YOU AND CLARE'S RELATIONSHIP
WAS AN EMOTIONAL ROLLERCOASTER
AND YOU'RE LETTING HER
GET AWAY WITH IT SCOT-FREE.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT TO LOSE?
OKAY!
IF WE DO THIS
CAN YOU LET IT GO?
I'M CLARE EDWARDS.
I'M SO SMART.
NO ONE WILL EVER UNDERSTAND
YOU LIKE I DO, ELI.
OKAY.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
I NEVER REALLY LOVED YOU.
I WAS ONLY PLAYING YOU
BECAUSE I KNEW YOU'D
LET ME GET AWAY WITH IT.
AND LOOK!
I WAS RIGHT!
I DID EVERYTHING
TO MAKE YOU HAPPY!
I'M STILL IN LOVE WITH YOU
AND I HATE MYSELF FOR IT.
AND I HATE YOU, ELI.
I ALWAYS HAVE.
DON'T SAY THAT.
YOU DON'T MEAN IT.
I DO.
I NEVER LOVED YOU.
YOU'RE A LOSER.
AND YOU ARE
A MANIPULATIVE WITCH.
YOU USED ME AND YOU
TOSSED ME AWAY.
I HATE YOU. I HATE YOU.
I HATE YOU!
EXCELLENT!
NOW GO USE THAT EMOTION
AND WRITE YOURSELF A PLAY.
BOTH:
(LAUGH)
HEY.
WAS YOUR BIRTHDAY
A HAPPY ONE?
HARDLY.
YOUR EIGHTEENTH IS SUPPOSED
TO BE SPECIAL!
TELL THAT TO ZANE.
HE AGREED TO COME TO DINNER
AS A FRIEND,
BUT HE COULDN'T HANDLE IT.
HE JUST KEPT PUSHING
FOR MORE.
IT'S BECAUSE HE CARES
ABOUT YOU SO MUCH.
DOES HE?
HE WANTS ME TO CHOOSE
BETWEEN HIM AND MY FAMILY.
BUT IF I TRY TO DROP
THE GAY BOMB AGAIN,
THAT'S IT. MY WHOLE FAMILY
WOULD BE OVER.
WELL, AND IF YOU DON'T,
YOU LOSE ZANE.
BOTH OPTIONS BITE.
WELL, HONESTY IS USUALLY
THE BEST POLICY.
THAT'S WHAT
THEY TELL ME, ANYWAY.
SINCE WHEN?
GOOD POINT.
I THINK WHAT
I'M TRYING TO SAY,
IS THAT ZANE'S PUT UP
WITH A LOT.
AND YOU STAYING
IN THE CLOSET-
REALLY ISN'T FAIR TO HIM.
WELL, DO WHAT YOU GOTTA DO.
MY NEW CONCEPT
WILL EXPAND HORIZONS.
ELEVATE CONSCIOUSNESS.
IT'S BRILLIANT, ELI.
I CAN ALREADY HEAR
THE STANDING OVATION.
YOU WERE RIGHT. THOSE PILLS
WERE THE PROBLEM.
THANKS TO YOU,
I'M FINALLY FREE.
CLARE:
ELI?
CLARE.
DO YOU KNOW IMOGEN?
HI.
HELLO, CLARE EDWARDS.
I STILL NEED
THAT INTERVIEW.
AND I WANT TO GIVE IT
TO YOU.
I PITCH MY NEW CONCEPT
TO FIONA IN THE MORNING.
HOW ABOUT LUNCH?
SOUNDS GREAT.
IT'S A DATE.
I COULDN'T QUIT WHEN THEY
OFFERED ME THE RAISE.
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT MAD?
ARE YOU KIDDING?
I AM SO PROUD.
IN THIS UNIFORM?
(LAUGHS)
YOU WORK SO HARD FOR ME
AND TYSON,
CLIMBING THE CORPORATE
LADDER.
BOTH:
(LAUGH)
I CAN'T TAKE ALL THE CREDIT.
THIS GIRL AT WORK REALLY
WENT TO BAT FOR ME.
THIS GIRL AT WORK?
YEAH, MARISOL.
OH, HOW NICE OF HER.
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
I USED TO BE ON POWER SQUAD
WITH MS. FLIRTY FLIRT, KC.
I KNOW HER TYPE.
I USED TO BE HER TYPE.
JENNA,
SHE GETS OUR SITUATION.
AND SHE JUST WANTS
TO HELP US.
(SIGHS)
(CRYING BABY)
TO A BAGGAGE-FREE FUTURE!
AND BY BAGGAGE
I MEAN CLARE.
YOU KNOW, I HAVE TO HAND IT
TO YOU, YOUR METHODS WORKED.
JUST WAIT UNTIL YOU SHARE YOUR
BRILLIANT PLAY IDEA WITH HER.
(LAUGHS)
SHE'LL REALIZE LOSING ME
IS THE BIGGEST MISTAKE
SHE EVER MADE.
SHE'LL NEVER DOUBT
YOU AGAIN.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU KNOW, JUST ALWAYS SEEMED
LIKE SHE SECOND GUESSED YOU.
(LAUGHS)
LIKE WHEN?
LIKE VEGAS NIGHT.
WHEN SHE TOOK FITZ'S SIDE
INSTEAD OF YOURS.
IT WAS SO CLEAR
FITZ WAS PLAYING CLARE
AND YOU WERE ONLY
LOOKING OUT FOR HER
BUT SHE WOULDN'T LISTEN.
THAT HAPPENED MONTHS AGO.
(LAUGHS)
HOW DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT THAT?
YOU KNOW,
IT'S COMMON KNOWLEDGE.
LIKE THE GOTHIC FICTION
FESTIVAL
YOU WERE GOING
TO TAKE CLARE TO.
HAVE YOU BEEN
STALKING ME?
NO.
I'M JUST A KEEN OBSERVER
OF HUMAN BEHAVIOUR.
OKAY,
YOU NEED TO BACK OFF.
DEEP BREATHS, ELI.
DEEP BREATHS.
DON'T LET THE CRAZY
GET THE BEST OF YOU.
THAT'S WHAT CLARE WANTS.
GOOD.
NOW LET'S GET READY TO PITCH
FIONA YOUR CONCEPT.
I KNEW YOU'D LOOK CUTE
IN A KERCHIEF.
THANKS.
YOU KNOW, IT'S TOO BAD
MY MP3 PLAYER'S BROKEN,
SO THERE WON'T BE
A DANCE PARTY TONIGHT.
WELL,
I CAN'T MAKE IT ANYWAY.
GOTTA GET HOME TO TAKE CARE
OF MY KID AND BABY MAMA.
GOTCHA.
MARISOL?
I GUESS I KINDA
OWE YOU, HUH?
DON'T BE SILLY.
I'M JUST GLAD I COULD HELP,
BUSBOY.
(LAUGHS)
COME HERE.
THANK YOU.
HEY.
GLAD YOU CAME.
LEAST I COULD DO.
I GOT YOUR TEXT ABOUT
THE BIG DECISION, SO...
WHAT'S THE PLAN?
PLAN?
YEAH, WE'LL NEED A STRATEGY
TO COME OUT TO YOUR FOLKS,
SO THINGS DON'T END UP
LIKE LAST TIME, RIGHT?
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
TAKE A SEAT.
ABOUT DINNER YESTERDAY,
I CAN'T KEEP PUTTING YOU
THROUGH STUFF LIKE THAT.
I'M SORRY.
SEE?
YOU CAN'T HAVE IT
BOTH WAYS.
THAT'S WHY
WE SHOULD BREAK UP.
WHAT?
I KNOW YOU'RE NOT HAPPY
THE WAY THINGS ARE.
SO WHY DON'T WE CHANGE
THE WAY THINGS ARE?
WHY DON'T WE STOP
PLAYING PRETEND
AND COME OUT TO YOUR PARENTS
TOGETHER?
YOU KNOW WHY!
AND JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE
IN SOME SORT OF HURRY,
DOESN'T CHANGE ANYTHING!
I'VE MADE MY DECISION.
I'M SORRY IF YOU
CAN'T RESPECT IT.
SO THIS-
THIS IS HOW IT ENDS?
IT HAS TO.
ELI:
AND THEN- BAM!
OUR HERO COLLAPSES,
A CROWD GATHERS,
SIRENS BLARE.
AND THE TRUTH IS LAID NAKED,
FOR ALL TO SEE.
LIGHTS DIM.
CURTAINS.
APPLAUSE.
I HAVE CHILLS.
CHILLS!
I KNEW YOU COULD DO IT.
THANK YOU.
NOW ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS WRITE IT.
DO YOU THINK DAWES
WILL LIKE IT?
LEAVE THAT TO ME.
IMOGEN:
BRA-VO. BRA-FREAKIN'-VO!
I ALWAYS HAD IT IN ME.
AND YOU...
YOU BELIEVED IN ME!
YOU'VE CONQUERED
YOUR DEMONS.
WHAT HAPPENS NEXT
IS UP TO YOU.
HOW WAS CLOSING
LAST NIGHT?
NOT THE SAME
WITHOUT YOU.
MAYBE NEXT TIME
IT WILL BE MORE FUN.
KC! THIS MUST HAVE
BEEN SO EXPENSIVE!
IT WASN'T.
REALLY.
I HAD TO BUY JENNA A BABY
VIDEO MONITOR. (LAUGHS)
THAT WAS EXPENSIVE.
YOU'RE RIDICULOUS,
YOU KNOW THAT? (LAUGHS)
I'LL SAVE A DANCE
FOR YOU TONIGHT.
HEY.
HOW DID THE PITCH GO?
I REALLY, REALLY NEED
TO THANK YOU.
THANK ME?
YES! YOU INSPIRED ME.
YOU WERE MY MUSE!
THAT'S GREAT, ELI!
I'M REALLY GLAD
I COULD HELP.
SO WHAT'S THE PLAY
ABOUT?
(LAUGHS) RIGHT.
IT'S CALLED "LOVE ROULETTE".
A TALE OF HIGH SCHOOL
ROMANCE GONE WRONG.
THE HERO'S BETRAYED
AT THE SCHOOL DANCE
BY A MANIPULATIVE LOVER,
WHO'S BECOME OBSESSED
WITH A RELIGIOUS PSYCHO.
SOUND FAMILIAR?
IT'S A LIE.
YOU CAN'T.
I THOUGHT I WAS THE REASON
EVERYTHING FELL APART
BETWEEN US,
BUT NOW I KNOW THE TRUTH,
IT WAS YOU.
YOU SOUND CRAZY, ELI.
HAVE YOU BEEN TAKING
YOUR MEDICATION?
NO. I'M BETTER.
I DON'T LOVE YOU ANYMORE,
CLARE. I'M FREE!
YOU NEED HELP!
I HAVE ALL THE HELP
I NEED.
AT YOUR SERVICE,
ELI GOLDSWORTHY.
COME ON, IMO.
I'VE GOT A PLAY TO WRITE!