ADAM:
HEY, DID IMOGEN
RETURN YOUR CALL?
NOPE.
YEESH.
NOW YOU'RE PISSED.
SHE'S SUPPOSED TO BE
MY GIRLFRIEND!
SHE'S SHUNNING ME.
WELL, YOU DID FREAK OUT
AND SMASH HER CAMERA.
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT!
AFTER SHE TOOK MY FACE,
AND MADE ME INTO A BIPOLAR
ART PROJECT.
I GUESS WE'RE BREAKING UP.
ADAM:
WELL, IF YOU STILL LIKE HER,
JUST PLAY IT COOL;
ASSESS, BE BREEZY.
ELI:
I CAN DO BREEZY.
HEY.
SORRY I MISSED YOUR CALLS
LAST NIGHT.
MY PHONE WAS OFF.
I BROUGHT THE CAMERA.
THANKS.
I CAN EXPLAIN-
NO NEED.
WHAT DID YOU GET UP
TO LAST NIGHT?
STAYED HOME.
HOMEWORK AND SUCH.
WEIRD.
I STOPPED BY.
YOUR DAD SAID
YOU WERE OUT WITH A FRIEND.
YOU WENT TO MY HOUSE?
AROUND SIX.
MY DAD'S SUCH
A SPACE CASE.
I WAS OUT WALKING MY DOG.
YOU HAVE TO MEET VOLTA
SOME DAY!
ELI:
THAT EXPLAINS EVERYTHING.
UM, I'LL SEE YOU IN CLASS.
HER DOG WAS AT HOME
WITH HER DAD.
SOMETIMES GIRLS DO THINGS
THEY DON'T WANT THEIR BOYFRIENDS
TO KNOW ABOUT.
LIKE CHEAT ON THEM.
LIKE GET THEIR
MUSTACHES WAXED.
DON'T OVERREACT.
OKAY. I'LL JUST KEEP
ACTING BREEZY.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh... ♪
(Oh-oh-oh)
♪ I can make it through ♪
(I can make it!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
UH, SORRY.
I WAS JUST LOOKING
FOR SOMEONE.
IT'S ME.
(LAUGHS)
IT'S NOT FUNNY.
I WAS LATE FOR PRACTICE.
I'M THE NEW MASCOT
UNTIL MARISOL CAN FIND
A REPLACEMENT.
YOU'RE KIDDING.
IF THAT WASN'T
BAD ENOUGH,
MARISOL'S MAKING ME
ROAR FOR NICKELS
TO RAISE MONEY
FOR POMPOMS.
THIS IS SO HUMILIATING!
(LAUGHS)
OKAY, THIS IS WHERE YOU SAY,
"DON'T WORRY, TORI,
NO ONE WILL REMEMBER
IN A WEEK."
OH NO,
THEY'LL REMEMBER THIS ONE.
I MEAN...
IF YOU HATE IT SO MUCH,
THEN DON'T DO IT.
MAYBE I WOULDN'T FEEL
SO SILLY
IF I HAD MY BOYFRIEND
BY MY SIDE WHILE I ROARED?
I PROMISED I'D SKATEBOARD
WITH THE GUYS AT LUNCH.
CAN'T YOU UN-PROMISE?
TOR,
IF I DITCH THE GUYS
TO HANG OUT
WITH MY GIRLFRIEND,
THEY'LL MAKE FUN OF ME
FOREVER.
BRO CODE.
(BELL RINGS)
WHY DOES IT SMELL
LIKE CHEESE?
JAKE:
BY THE WAY, YOUR SPANISH NOTES
WERE A LIFESAVER.
THANKS.
IMOGEN:
I THINK YOU MEAN
MUCHAS GRACIAS.
(LAUGHING)
DIDN'T KNOW YOU AND JAKE
WERE FRIENDS.
HE'S FRIENDLY.
THEREFORE,
WE'RE FRIENDLY.
OKAY...
THAT'S ALL, ELI.
I SAID OKAY.
SORRY.
NO, I'M SORRY.
BOTH:
MAYBE WE SHOULD...
YOU FIRST.
GO SOMEWHERE
AND TALK?
ABOUT?
US.
WHY? US IS GREAT,
NEVER BETTER.
YOU REALLY THINK THAT?
DON'T YOU?
YEAH, I GUESS.
GOOD.
THEN THE ONLY THING "US"
NEEDS TO TALK ABOUT
IS WHAT WE'RE DOING TONIGHT.
I ALREADY HAVE PLANS.
WITH JAKE?
GIRLS NIGHT
AT CASA COYNE.
YOU'RE WELCOME
TO JOIN US.
HEY, JUST BECAUSE
WE'RE DATING
DOESN'T MEAN WE HAVE TO SPEND
EVERY SECOND TOGETHER.
OKAY.
ARMSTRONG:
OKAY. TODAY'S THE DAY
YOU'VE ALL BEEN WAITING FOR.
WE BEGIN LOGARITHMIC FUNCTIONS.
CONNOR.
THANK YOU
KC, DO YOU HAVE
AN ASSIGNMENT FOR ME?
NOT TODAY.
MINUS AN ENTIRE
LETTER GRADE
FOR EVERY DAY
IT'S LATE.
WHY DIDN'T YOU DO
YOUR ASSIGNMENT?
I WENT TO TY'S
CHRISTENING.
AND OUR BABY'S DOING GREAT
BY THE WAY.
HE LIVES IN THIS
AMAZING NEIGHBOURHOOD,
AND THE POWELL'S
ARE SO GOOD TO HIM.
KNOCK IT OFF, KC.
DON'T YOU CARE
THAT YOUR SON'S
ADJUSTING
TO HIS NEW LIFE?
OF COURSE I DO.
MAYBE IF YOU SPEND
SOME TIME-
I CAN'T!
HOW CAN YOU BE
SO SELFISH?
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO BARELY HELPED OUT
AFTER TY WAS BORN!
WELL, I'M MAKING UP
FOR IT NOW!
LOOK, TY NEEDS US,
JENNA.
YOU AND ME -
HIS PARENTS.
WE'RE NOT HIS PARENTS
ANYMORE!
MRS. COHEN:
CLASS!
JENNA.
(BELL RINGS)
TORI:
ROAAAAAR!
MARISOL:
COME ON, NINER,
LET'S HEAR ANOTHER ROAR.
TORI:
ROAAAAAR!
GUESS THAT'S WORTH A NICKEL.
MAYA:
WHOA. IS THIS SOME BIZARRE
INITIATION RITUAL?
I WAS LATE FOR PRACTICE
BECAUSE I WAS HELPING ZIG
WITH THAT VIDEO.
THIS IS MY PUNISHMENT.
THOUGHT CHEERLEADING WAS
REALLY IMPORTANT TO YOU.
IT IS,
BUT ZIG NEEDED HELP.
HE WOULD DO THE SAME
FOR ME.
THEN WHY ISN'T HE HERE
KEEPING YOU COMPANY?
HE REALLY,
REALLY WANTED TO,
BUT HE HAD
SKATEBOARDING PLANS.
TORI, I'M SORRY,
BUT IT SOUNDS LIKE
HIS SKATEBOARDING
TAKES PRECEDENCE
OVER YOUR CHEERLEADING.
YOU DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING.
MAYBE NOT, BUT...
I THOUGHT IT WAS COOL
HOW YOU STOOD UP TO MARISOL
TO MAKE THE TEAM.
WHY CAN'T YOU STAND UP
TO YOUR BOYFRIEND?
YOU'RE JUST JEALOUS
BECAUSE I HAVE A BOYFRIEND
AND YOU DON'T.
YEAH,
THAT MUST BE IT.
BUT AS LONG
AS YOU'RE HAPPY...
ADAM:
PAWN SHOPS SMELL WEIRD.
ELI:
AH, THE SCENT OF
IMPULSIVE BEHAVIOUR AND REGRET.
NOW I HAVE TO FIND A WAY
TO REPLACE IMOGEN'S CAMERA.
A PROBLEM FOR ANOTHER DAY.
TONIGHT, WE CELEBRATE
WITH A WII BOXING MARATHON
IN MY BASEMENT.
DREW'S ORDERING PIZZA.
ELI? HELLO?
JAKE'S A PRETTY
GOOD LOOKING DUDE, RIGHT?
SINCE WHEN ARE YOU
INTO DUDES?
I THINK THERE'S
SOMETHING GOING ON
BETWEEN IMOGEN AND HIM.
ISN'T JAKE WITH JENNA?
IS HE?
WOW, DUDE MOVES FAST.
HISTORY PROVES THAT WE HAVE
THE SAME TASTE IN GIRLS.
YOU KNOW,
THAT EXPLAINS EVERYTHING:
WHY SHE LIED TO ME
ABOUT WHERE SHE WAS;
WHY SHE COULDN'T
COME OUT TONIGHT.
WELL,
ANYTHING IS POSSIBLE.
I HAVE TO FIND OUT THE TRUTH.
OTHERWISE, I'LL GO CRAZY.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
IF IMOGEN'S AT FIONA'S TONIGHT,
THEN I HAVE NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
ADAM:
WELL, THE MOMENT YOU WALK
THROUGH THAT DOOR,
SHE'LL KNOW WHY
YOU'RE THERE.
THEN I WON'T WALK
THROUGH THE DOOR.
KC:
HEY, POWELL'S!
ED:
KC, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
CATHY:
DID YOU FORGET SOMETHING
LAST NIGHT?
NO, JUST DROPPING BY
TO SPEND SOME TIME WITH TY.
I MEAN, DOUG.
SORRY, THAT'LL TAKE SOME TIME
GETTING USED TO.
ED:
YEAH, I WISH YOU'D CALLED.
WE'RE OFF TO SEE
MY PARENTS.
OH,
I COULD COME WITH.
I'D LOVE TO MEET
THE REST OF THE FAMILY.
UH, I DON'T THINK
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
YEAH,
WE'LL GIVE YOU A CALL
AND WE'LL SET UP
ANOTHER TIME FOR VISIT.
YEAH,
I'M FREE THIS WEEKEND.
UH, WE'RE NOT,
BUT WE'LL BE IN TOUCH.
♪ There's a lot of nothing
in the words I know ♪
♪ Keep him talking
'cause he feels at home ♪
♪ Feels all right to be
growing old ♪
♪ But growing old
is just letting go ♪
♪ It's just the reason
I needed to leave this place ♪
♪ I haven't wanted
to run around ♪
♪ I had a different image
all my life ♪
♪ It's just that changes happen
all the time ♪
OKAY,
THIS IS FIONA'S BEDROOM.
I HEAR A GUY.
IMOGEN:
HE BROKE MY CAMERA,
WENT TO MY HOUSE,
LEFT ME A MILLION MESSAGES.
GAVE ME A NEW CAMERA,
THEN TOOK IT BACK.
I'M WORRIED
HE'S HAVING AN EPISODE,
BUT HE DOESN'T WANNA DISCUSS
ANYTHING BIPOLAR.
FIONA:
SO THAT'S WHY YOU'VE
BEEN HIDING OUT HERE?
IS THAT OKAY?
I FEEL COMFORTABLE TALKING
TO YOU ABOUT ANYTHING.
OF COURSE IT'S OKAY.
BUT I REALLY THINK YOU SHOULD
GIVE ELI ANOTHER CHANCE.
WE BOTH KNOW
HE'S AN AMAZING GUY.
(LOUD SQUEAK AND THUD)
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
SHHHHH.
SERIOUSLY,
BREAKING AND ENTERING?
DON'T YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING
A LITTLE OVERBOARD?
I NEED TO CATCH HER
IN THE ACT.
NOW ARE YOU COMING
OR NOT?
IMOGEN:
THAT'S YOUR WEAPON SELECTION?!
YOU HAVE A LAMP!
AGHHHH!
IMOGEN: ELI!
FIONA: ADAM?
SNEAKING INTO PEOPLE'S HOUSES,
WHO DOES THAT?!
WE WERE IN
THE NEIGHBOURHOOD
SO WE THOUGHT WE'D DROP IN
AND SAY HI.
ADAM:
HI.
SO WHERE'S THE FRENCH GUY?
FIONA:
WHAT? WE'RE WATCHING
A FRENCH MOVIE.
IMOGEN:
YOU WERE SPYING ON US?
OKAY, DON'T SAY THIS
IS A MANIC THING.
THEN WHAT DO YOU
WANT ME TO SAY?
BECAUSE EVERY TIME
I OPEN MY MOUTH IT'S WRONG.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW HOW TO ACT
AROUND YOU ANYMORE!
OKAY, BUT YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO LIED
ABOUT WHERE YOU WERE
LAST NIGHT!
I WAS HERE
DISCUSSING US WITH FIONA
BECAUSE YOU WON'T.
DO YOU BLAME ME?
EVERY TIME I EXPRESS
AN EMOTION,
YOU TRY TO TALK ME
OFF A LEDGE!
I'M WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
TELL HER I'M FINE.
TELL HER!
MAYBE WE SHOULD
JUST LET THE GIRLS
HAVE THEIR MOVIE NIGHT.
YEAH, GO TO HELL,
ALL OF YOU.
(PICTURES TEAR)
(DRAWERS RATTLE
AND BANG LOUDLY)
(PANTING)
BULLFROG:
IT'S 4:00 A.M.
WHAT THE HECK ARE YOU DOING?
GETTING RID OF EVERYTHING
THAT REMINDS ME OF IMOGEN.
YOUR FIRST EDITION SPAWN?
YEAH.
SHE TOUCHED IT ONCE.
ELI...
NO. YOU WERE RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, DATING IMOGEN
WAS A MISTAKE.
I THOUGHT SHE GOT ME,
BUT SHE'S JUST LIKE
EVERYONE ELSE.
I HATE TO ASK THIS,
SOLDIER,
BUT HAVE YOU BEEN
TAKING YOUR MEDS?
IT'S JUST THAT YOU SEEM
A LITTLE AGITATED.
I'M FINE.
THIS ISN'T FINE!
FIRST, YOU TAKE MY GUITAR
WITHOUT ASKING.
I GOT IT BACK.
IT'S ON FIONA'S FIRE ESCAPE.
AND THEN THIS...
BUT I'VE BEEN DOING
EVERYTHING
THE DOCTOR'S TOLD ME.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT,
KIDDO.
YOU HAVE AN ILLNESS.
I'M GONNA CALL
DR. FRANK.
WE NEED A LAWYER.
LISA:
A LAWYER?
THERE'S THIS CASE IN TEXAS
WHERE A BIOLOGICAL FATHER
SUED THE ADOPTIVE PARENTS
FOR VISITATION
AND WON.
I KNOW IT
WILL BE EXPENSIVE,
BUT MAYBE WE CAN WORK
SOMETHING OUT
WITH SOCIAL SERVICES.
KC, WE'RE NOT INVOLVING
LAWYERS.
WHEN THE ADOPTION
WENT THROUGH,
THE POWELL'S SAID
YOU COULD VISIT
A COUPLE TIMES A YEAR.
THAT'S NOT ENOUGH!
WELL,
IT'S GONNA HAVE TO BE...
FOR NOW.
AND I'LL ALWAYS BE
THE LOSER
WHO GOT A GIRL PREGNANT
AND COULDN'T HANDLE
THE RESPONSIBILITY?
YOU'RE NOT.
YOU'RE THE GUY WHO GAVE HIM
A CHANCE AT A BETTER LIFE.
THAT'S NOT THE WAY
JENNA SEES ME!
MAYBE NOT RIGHT NOW.
KC:
NO, SHE HATES ME!
AND IF I CAN'T BE
A PART OF TY'S LIFE,
HE'LL FEEL THE SAME WAY!
WHEN YOU WERE LITTLE,
YOU WANTED TO BE A DOCTOR.
I REMEMBER
BECAUSE I BOUGHT YOU
A STETHOSCOPE.
YEAH, LIKE A MILLION
YEARS AGO.
I DIDN'T GIVE YOU
THE BEST LIFE, KC,
I KNOW,
(SIGHS)
BUT YOU CAN BE SOMEONE.
SOMEONE TY CAN
LOOK UP TO.
YOU MEAN SOMEONE DOUG
CAN LOOK UP TO?
(LAUGHING)
YEAH.
P.A. ANNOUNCEMENT:
LET'S GET SOME FANS
IN THE STANDS.
DON'T MISS THE PANTHERS
FOOTBALL TEAM IN ACTION
TODAY AT BARDELL.
HEY, ZIG.
GUESS WHAT YOU'RE
DOING TODAY?
I DON'T KNOW.
COMING TO THE DEGRASSI
FOOTBALL GAME WITH ME!
YOU KNOW THAT'S NOT
REALLY MY THING.
BUT IT'S MY THING,
AND I REALLY
WANT YOU THERE.
HONESTLY, TOR,
I'D RATHER JUST GO
TO THE SKATE PARK.
WHY WON'T YOU DO THIS
FOR ME?
IT'S JUST A FOOTBALL GAME.
IT'S WAY MORE THAN THAT.
IT'S MY FIRST OFFICIAL
POWER SQUAD EVENT.
AS THE MASCOT.
BECAUSE YOUR
SKATEBOARDING VIDEO
MADE ME LATE
FOR PRACTICE.
I DIDN'T MAKE YOU STAY.
NO, I WANTED TO BECAUSE
IT WAS IMPORTANT TO YOU.
NAME ONE THING
YOU'VE EVER DONE FOR ME.
FINE,
I'LL GO TO YOUR GAME.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
DON'T BOTHER.
♪ You run, I walk ♪
♪ You go, I'll stop ♪
♪ I want you back ♪
ELI.
UH...
SO I WAS UP ALL NIGHT
TRASHING EVERYTHING
THAT REMINDED ME
OF MY GIRLFRIEND.
YOU AND IMOGEN
HAD A FIGHT?
MY DAD WAS RIGHT.
I'M NOT READY
FOR A RELATIONSHIP AND...
ONE MISUNDERSTANDING
JUST THREW ME OFF THE EDGE.
WHOA! NOW...
LET'S TALK ABOUT THIS.
YOU KNOW,
CONSIDERING WE'RE HERE,
HAVING THIS CONVERSATION,
YOU MAY NOT BE
"OVER THE EDGE."
NOW, ASIDE FROM LAST NIGHT,
HOW ARE YOU SLEEPING?
GREAT.
GOOD.
AND YOUR DIET...
AND YOUR EXERCISE,
ARE YOU STICKING
WITH THE REGIMEN?
YEAH.
I'M ALL OVER IT.
I DON'T REALLY THINK
THAT YOU HAVE ANYTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT
FOR THE TIME BEING.
OKAY. THEN HOW DO YOU
EXPLAIN MY BEHAVIOUR?
TEENAGE HORMONES.
(SCOFFS)
SO I'M NOT GOING CRAZY?
ELI, YOU KNOW
I DON'T LIKE THAT WORD.
OKAY, BUT THEN I SHOULD
PROBABLY STAY AWAY
FROM GIRLS
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
YOU KNOW,
AVOID TRIGGERS.
HEARTBREAK HAPPENS,
ELI.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO LEARN
TO DEAL WITH IT.
MRS. COHEN:
AND TOMORROW WE BEGIN OUR MODULE
ON ORGANIC EQUATIONS, EVERYONE.
KC:
HERE'S MY ASSIGNMENT,
MRS. COHEN.
A DAY LATE.
I'LL HAVE TO DOCK A GRADE.
I KNOW,
I MESSED UP.
I'VE BEEN DOING THAT
A LOT LATELY,
BUT I'LL MAKE IT UP
ON THE NEXT ONE.
I WANT TO APOLOGIZE.
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS.
IF IT WEREN'T FOR YOU,
WE'D STILL BE STRUGGLING
TO TAKE CARE OF A BABY...
AND NOW WE CAN DO ANYTHING.
IT'S JUST BEEN HARD FOR ME
TO MOVE ON.
IT SEEMS SO EASY FOR YOU.
IT'S NOT.
I MISS HIM TOO,
EVERY DAY.
WELL, MAYBE ONE DAY
WE CAN VISIT DOUG TOGETHER.
DOUG?
YEAH, THAT'S WHAT
THEY CALL TY NOW.
HMM...
I DON'T KNOW
WHEN I'LL BE READY.
MRS. COHEN:
KC, MAY I HAVE A WORD
WITH YOU?
SEE YOU AROUND?
UH, I'D LIKE TO DISCUSS
YOUR ANSWER
TO NUMBER THREE.
DID I GET IT WRONG?
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
IN THE CLASS
WHO GOT IT RIGHT.
I MIGHT HAVE A WAY
FOR YOU
TO MAKE UP
THOSE EXTRA MARKS,
IF YOU'RE INTERESTED.
SURE.
TORI:
SORRY, I'M LATE.
I COULDN'T FIND
THE MASCOT COSTUME.
I LOOKED EVERYWHERE-
MARISOL:
IT'S OKAY,
I FOUND A REPLACEMENT.
DOES THAT MEAN
I'M NOT ON THE TEAM?!
IT MEANS YOU NEED
TO GET DRESSED
BECAUSE THE BUS
LEAVES IN FIVE.
DRESSED?
LIKE IN MY POWER SQUAD
UNIFORM?
"LIKE IN YOUR POWER SQUAD
UNIFORM."
WHO'S THE MASCOT?
SOME NINER GUY.
WHOA... WHEW...
THOUGHT FOOTBALL GAMES
WEREN'T YOUR THING?
WELL...
MARISOL SAID AS LONG AS I WEAR
THIS SMELLY OUTFIT,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
SO YOU THINK YOU CAN DO
ONE NICE THING
AND I'LL JUST FORGIVE YOU?
WELL, I WAS KIND OF
HOPING SO.
WELL, IT'S NOT GOING TO WORK
LIKE THAT ANYMORE.
THINGS NEED TO CHANGE.
OKAY.
I'LL TRY HARDER.
SO UH...
DO I GET A KISS?
NOT WHILE YOU'RE WEARING
THAT STINKY OUTFIT.
(PRETEND OFFENDED GASP)
HEY.
THANKS FOR MEETING ME.
WHAT'S THIS?
MY ART PROJECT.
I TOOK IT DOWN
AND WITHDREW IT
FROM THE ART COMPETITION.
FOR ME.
CAN I TAKE IT?
I THOUGHT YOU HATED IT.
WELL, I'VE BEEN DOING
A LOT OF THINKING.
BREAKING INTO FIONA'S CONDO
WASN'T MY FINEST MOMENT.
I JUST DIDN'T WANT
TO LOSE ANOTHER GIRL
BECAUSE OF MY CONDITION.
I'M SORRY.
YOU SCARED ME.
YEAH, I SCARED MYSELF.
BUT THE GOOD THING IS
I WASN'T HAVING
A MANIC EPISODE.
JUST GOOD, OLD-FASHIONED
PARANOID JEALOUSY.
I SPENT A YEAR
FANTASIZING ABOUT YOU,
DREAMING ABOUT BEING
YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
BUT NOW THAT
WE'RE TOGETHER,
IT'S LIKE
I BARELY KNOW YOU.
OR YOU KNOW ME
TOO WELL...
I DON'T THINK YOU AND I
ARE GOOD FOR EACH OTHER.
WE WERE...
WHEN WE WERE FRIENDS.
OR DID I MESS THAT UP,
TOO?
CONNOR:
0.14 KILOGRAM BASEBALL
WITH A SPEED OF 40 METRES
PER SECOND IS CAUGHT.
IF ITS ENERGY'S ABSORBED
BY THE BALL,
WHAT'S THE TEMPERATURE CHANGE?
0.8 DEGREES CELSIUS?
I THINK WE'VE FOUND
THE FINAL MEMBER
OF OUR SCIENCE OLYMPICS TEAM!
(APPLAUSE)
WEREN'T YOU GUYS CITY CHAMPS
LAST YEAR?
YEP, AND WE WILL BE AGAIN.
SO DON'T MESS UP.
KC, ARE YOU SURE
YOU'LL HAVE TIME?
I MEAN, YOU'RE ALWAYS VISITING
THAT BABY OF YOURS.
DOUG DOESN'T NEED
HIS BIO-DAD RIGHT NOW.
BIO-DAD.
SOUNDS LIKE A SUPER HERO.
YEAH, MAYBE ONE DAY
HE'LL THINK THAT.
MRS. COHEN:
CONNOR?
CONNOR:
ARE YOU GUYS READY
FOR THE NEXT QUESTION?
OKAY, SO AN ATOMIC LEVEL SPECIES
IS FOUND TO CONTAIN 16 PROTONS,
16 NEUTRONS AND 18 ELECTRONS.
THE SPECIES IS
BEST DESCRIBED AS...?
♪ You kissed me on
the summer's edge ♪
♪ And oh your mother's words
would always sting the worst ♪
(KNOCKING)
WHAT ARE YOU SMILING ABOUT?
I'M JUST HAPPY
YOU'RE HAPPY.
DR. FRANK AND I TALKED,
AND APPARENTLY I'M NOT SUPPOSED
TO STOP YOU FROM DATING.
YEAH, WELL, THAT'S NOT REALLY
AN ISSUE ANYMORE.
SUPER SINGLE.
BULLFROG:
(SIGHS, SORRY) OH...
ARE YOU SURE?
'CAUSE THERE'S SOMEONE
HERE TO SEE YOU.
OH, HEY.
BAD TIME?
ELI:
NO. NO,
JUST KEEP YOUR DISTANCE.
IMOGEN:
SO I GOT A CALL
FROM THE ONTARIO YOUTH
ART COMPETITION.
AND APPARENTLY
I'M IN THE RUNNING
FOR THE EMERGING ARTIST AWARD.
OH GOOD,
THEY GOT IT.
YOU SENT IN MY COLLAGE.
IT'S A VERY NICE
PIECE OF ART.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO MAKE YOU
A POSTER CHILD.
WELL, IF IT SHOWS
THAT MENTAL ILLNESS
DOESN'T HAVE TO BE
A STIGMA,
WHY NOT?
YOU HUNGRY?
WANNA GRAB BURRITOS?
MMM...
THEY MAKE ME GASSY.
YEAH. ME TOO.
GOOD THING
WE'RE NOT DATING.
(LAUGHING)
ALL RIGHT,
IT'S ON ME,
AND I STILL HAVE
TO REPLACE YOUR CAMERA.
GO SHOWER, FRIEND.
I'M STARVED.
I'LL LEAVE YOU ALONE
TO GET NAKED.
NO, NO. STAY.
SINCE WE'RE NOT DATING,
IT SHOULDN'T MATTER.
FUNNY!
BOTH:
(LAUGHING)
♪ Ye-ah... ♪
♪ And the kids we were
back then ♪
♪ We could never be again ♪