(SWITCH CLUNKS)
THERE.
I'M GONNA LOOK FOR CLARE.
MARISOL:
WHAT IF THE POWER
GOES OUT AGAIN?
JAKE: IT WON'T.
MARISOL: HOW DO YOU KNOW?
CAN SOMEONE HANDLE HER?
I'M LEAVING.
DREW:
JAKE, CLARE IS JUST BEING
A DRAMA QUEEN.
SHE'S GONNA COME BACK, MAN.
BIANCA:
HELLO?
THE GIRL CAME ALL THE WAY
UP HERE FOR HER STEP-BROTHER,
THEN FOUND HIM KISSING BANDARI.
I WOULDN'T WANNA BE HERE EITHER.
SHE COULDN'T HAVE GONE
TOO FAR.
THE WOODS ARE DENSE
AROUND HERE.
IT COULD GET DANGEROUS
IF YOU DON'T KNOW
YOUR WAY AROUND.
'KAY, I'M COMING WITH YOU, MAN.
ALLI: ME TOO.
JAKE: NO, NOT A GOOD IDEA.
ALLI:
BUT SHE'S MY BEST FRIEND.
YOU'LL JUST GET
IN THE WAY.
BIANCA:
YOU'RE BETTER OFF HERE.
IN HORROR MOVIES,
BAD STUFF HAPPENS TO PEOPLE
WHO GO OUT TO THE WOODS,
AND CONSIDERING
YOU'RE THE SKANKY BITCH
IN THIS SCENARIO,
YOU DIE FIRST.
THIS ISN'T A STUPID MOVIE,
BIANCA!
CLARE COULD ACTUALLY
BE HURT.
OH!
AND WHOSE FAULT IS THAT?
SCOOCH OVER.
COMFORTABLE?
VERY.
READY?
YEAH, LET'S GO.
BE CAREFUL, OKAY?
DREW: OKAY.
JAKE: LET'S GO.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh-oh-oh ♪
(Ooh-oh-oh)
♪ I can make it through ♪
(I can make it!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(PANTING)
COME ON...
(PHONE BEEPS)
COME ON, COME ON...
(GASPS) YES!
(PHONE BEEPS)
NO. NO, NO, NO!
COME... COME ON!
(PHONE BEEPS)
LITTLE BAR, I NEED YOU!
COME... JUST...
(OBJECT CLUNKS NEARBY)
HELLO?
IS ANYBODY THERE?
(TWIGS SNAP)
(UNFAMILIAR BARK,
FRIGHTENED BREATHS)
(TENSE BREATHS)
LIGHTS DON'T JUST GO OUT
LIKE THAT, KATIE.
YES, THEY DO.
IT'S AN OLD CABIN.
MARISOL:
SOMETHING'S NOT RIGHT.
KATIE:
THE ONLY THING THAT'S
NOT RIGHT IS BIANCA.
WHY WOULD SHE COME UP
HERE?
WHY AREN'T THEY BACK YET?
BECAUSE SOMETHING BAD
IS HAPPENING.
EVERYONE'S FIGHTING.
THE LIGHTS WENT OUT.
THERE'S WEIRD NOISES.
BIANCA:
FUNNY,
EVERYTHING YOU JUST LISTED
ALWAYS LEADS TO A MURDER.
THAT'S IT,
I'M DRIVING HOME.
YOU CAN'T DRIVE ALONE
IN THE DARK,
AND WE CAN'T LEAVE BIANCA
UP HERE WITH DREW.
I'M FREAKING OUT.
BIANCA:
(TITTERS)
YOU THINK THIS IS FUNNY?
YOU DIDN'T HEAR
WHAT JAKE TOLD US.
THERE'S SOMEONE OUT THERE,
A MURDERER,
AND HE WALKS AT NIGHT
WITH A FIRE POKER!
MARISOL,
YOU NEED TO CALM DOWN!
SIT. I'LL MAKE YOU
SOME HERBAL TEA, OKAY?
OR I COULD TAKE THIS HERB?
WHERE DID YOU
GET THAT?
I FOUND IT IN THE COUCH.
KATIE:
YOU WANNA SMOKE SOMETHING
YOU FOUND IN A COUCH?!
LOOKS LEGIT.
TRY IT.
NO WAY!
IT'LL MAKE YOU
EVEN MORE PARANOID!
DON'T LISTEN TO BIANCA,
SHE'S MESSING WITH YOU.
I'M FREAKING OUT
BECAUSE OF
YOUR STUPID PRANK!
(SIGHS)
JUST A BIT.
PLEASE?
FINE.
IT'S YOUR FUNERAL.
UH, NO WAY.
NOT IN HERE.
IF I GO HOME
SMELLING LIKE POT,
I'M DEAD, SO...
JUST GO OUTSIDE.
KATIE:
OKAY, FINE.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
JAKE:
I CAN'T BELIEVE CLARE
FOLLOWED ME
ALL THE WAY HERE.
HOW DOES SHE EXPECT ME
TO MOVE ON?
DREW:
CLEARLY SHE DOESN'T
WANT YOU TO, BRO.
JAKE:
JUST EARLIER TODAY
SHE SAID WE WERE "SO OVER."
DREW:
YOU'VE MET GIRLS, RIGHT?
USUALLY WHEN THEY SAY
ONE THING
THEY MEAN
THE COMPLETE OPPOSITE.
IF I KNEW
SHE WAS COMING UP,
I NEVER WOULD'VE
KISSED ALLI.
THINK SHE'LL EVER
FORGIVE ME?
MAYBE -
IF YOU FIND HER,
AND SAVE HER FROM
THE DARK SCARY WOODS.
COME ON.
OH NO.
OKAY.
UM...
UH, WHAT IS THAT?
IT'S UH...
IT'S CLARE'S.
HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
SHE WAS WEARING IT
WHEN SHE CAME.
DREW:
UM, JAKE, IS THAT...?
IT'S BLOOD.
WHAT IF THE MURDERER
GOT HER?
THAT WAS JUST
A STUPID STORY!
COME ON.
NO!
CLARE!
OH MY GOD.
ALL RIGHT, JAKE,
WHAT NOW?
LET'S GO THIS WAY.
OKAY.
JAKE AND DREW:
CLARE! CLARE!
(LATCH CLICKS,
DOOR CREAKS OPEN)
WHAT IF SOMETHING HAPPENS
TO CLARE?
BIANCA:
YOU'LL PROBABLY NEVER
FORGIVE YOURSELF.
BUT HANG IN THERE,
IT GETS BETTER.
(SIGHS) I'M NEVER LEAVING
MY HOUSE AGAIN.
EVERY TIME I TRY TO HAVE
A LITTLE FUN,
IT ALWAYS TURNS
INTO A DISASTER.
EVEN FOR YOU,
KISSING JAKE WAS LOW.
EXCUSE ME?
THIS COMING FROM
BOILER-ROOM BIANCA?
RING A BELL?
YOU AND DREW,
MY BOYFRIEND AT THE TIME?
THAT'S DIFFERENT.
YOU WEREN'T
MY BEST FRIEND FOREVER.
I'VE NEVER ROASTED
A MARSHMALLOW BEFORE.
INTERESTED?
(BANGING AT THE DOOR)
ALLI:
UH...
DON'T ANSWER.
WHAT IF IT'S CLARE
AND JAKE?
(POUNDING AT THE DOOR)
THE DOOR'S UNLOCKED.
THEN WHO WOULD BE
KNOCKING?
(TERRIFIED SCREAMS)
(COUGHS)
WHAT WAS THAT?
PROBABLY BIANCA
TRYING TO SCARE US.
ARE YOU DONE?
CAN WE GO BACK IN NOW?
WHERE THE SCREAMING'S
COMING FROM,
AND A MURDERER
ON THE LOOSE?
ARE YOU NUTS?
MARE,
I NEED TO MAKE SURE
BIANCA ISN'T LOOKING
FOR DREW.
I SAW HER USING
HER FEMININE WILES ON HIM
IN DREW'S HOUSE.
FEMININE WILES...
I'VE GOT THOSE.
(LAUGHS)
WHAT IF SOMETHING HAPPENED
WHILE I WAS AWAY
AT OUR SOCCER TOURNAMENT?
YOU THINK DREW
AND BIANCA SEXED?
NOW WHO'S PARANOID?
YOU'RE A TERRIBLE FRIEND
WHEN YOU'RE HIGH.
I'M GONNA GIVE BIANCA
A PIECE OF MY MIND;
FIND OUT THE TRUTH.
IT'S LOCKED.
SOMEONE LOCKED US IN.
WHO WOULD DO THAT
TO US?
HMM...
TAKE ONE GUESS.
STARTS WITH A B...
AND RHYMES WITH...
ACTUALLY IT DOESN'T RHYME
WITH ANYTHING.
SUCKS FOR HER.
BOTH:
(LAUGH)
WE NEED TO FIND
A WAY OUT.
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS IN PAIN)
(OBJECT CLUNKS,
UNDERBRUSH RUSTLES)
(SHRUBBERY RUSTLES,
WOLF HOWLS IN THE DISTANCE)
(PANICKED BREATHS)
(LOW GROANING SOUND)
(SHRIEKS)
LET GO OF ME! NO! HELP!
MALE:
IT'S OKAY. CALM DOWN!
IT'S ME!
IT'S ELI!
(GASPING FOR BREATH)
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
I'M SORRY I SCARED YOU.
I WENT TO THE CABIN
AND ALLI AND BIANCA SAID
THAT YOU WERE MISSING.
THEY ALSO SCREAMED
WHEN THEY SAW ME.
WHY IS EVERYONE SO JUMPY?
IT'S BEEN A LONG DAY.
HOW DID YOU GET HERE?
I TOOK A BUS
TO THE NEAREST TOWN,
THEN I BIKED THE REST.
YOU BIKED?
YEAH. I'VE BEEN DOING IT
ALL SUMMER.
I PASSED BY JAKE AND THEM
AT THE DOT AND...
WELL, I THOUGHT IT
MIGHT BE A GOOD IDEA
TO HANG OUT
WITH SOME SENIORS
BEFORE SCHOOL STARTS.
SO HE INVITED EVERYONE
BUT ME.
YOUR HAND LOOKS BAD.
I FELL.
HERE.
LET ME LOOK AT IT.
KATIE: LET US OUT!
MARISOL: HELP!
OH, IT'S NO USE,
WE ARE GOING TO DIE
IN HERE.
WE NEED TO DIG
OURSELVES OUT.
UH, I THINK
THE SECONDHAND SMOKE
IS GETTING TO YOUR HEAD.
WHAT DO YOU EXPECT?
IT'S LIKE A HOT BOX
IN HERE!
IF WE DIG A HOLE
BY THE DOOR,
WE CAN CRAWL UNDER.
FINE.
BUT ONLY BECAUSE
I WANNA TONE MY ARMS
FOR THE POWER SQUAD.
(LAUGHS)
(TOOLS SCRAPE THE DIRT)
(CLUNK)
I THINK I HIT A ROCK.
(CONTENTS RATTLE)
WHAT IS IT?
BLING.
LOOK,
THEY'RE ENGRAVED.
DAVID PRATT...
AND JOYCE PRATT.
WHAT IF THEY'RE THE PEOPLE
FROM JAKE'S STORY?
WHAT IF THE JEALOUS KILLER'S
THE ONE WHO LOCKED US IN?
WHAT IF HE HURT
OUR FRIENDS?
WE'RE NEXT!
SHHHHHH!
MARISOL:
OH MY GOD.
THAT'S HIM!
(MUFFLED SCREAM)
HERE, PUT THIS ON.
THANKS.
SO, DID I INTERRUPT
AN INTENSE GAME
OF HIDE AND SEEK?
(SCOFFS) NO.
SO, MAY I ASK,
WHY DID YOU RUN
INTO A DARK FOREST
BY YOURSELF?
LET'S JUST SAY
A CERTAIN SOMEONE MOVED ON
BEFORE I HAD A CHANCE
TO TALK TO HIM.
STOP! YOU'RE OVERWHELMING ME
WITH DETAILS.
IS IT WEIRD TO BE GLAD
YOU WERE THE ONE TO FIND ME?
(HALF LAUGHS)
(APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS)
JAKE:
CLARE!
ELI!
YOU FOUND HER.
I DID.
ARE YOU OKAY?
LIKE IT MATTERS TO YOU.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I THINK...
I THINK HE'S GONE.
THAT'S WHAT HE WANTS US
TO THINK.
I DON'T CARE.
I CAN'T DIE IN HERE
AND LEAVE DREW TO BIANCA.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
UH...
ARE YOU GONNA KILL
BIANCA?
I'M GETTING US
OUT OF HERE.
HOW DO I TURN THIS ON?
THERE'S A CORD.
PULL IT!
WAIT!
SAFETY FIRST.
(CHAINSAW BUZZES LOUDLY)
(MUFFLED BUZZING OF CHAINSAW)
(SAW GRINDS THROUGH WOOD)
AGGGHHHHH!
RUN!
KATIE AND MARISOL:
(SHRIEKING)
MARISOL:
RUN! (SHRIEKING)
ALLI:
YOU GUYS OKAY?
KATIE:
OH MY GOD, SOMEBODY LOCKED US
IN THE TOOL SHED.
WE FOUND WEDDING RINGS.
AND THERE'S SOMEONE
OUTSIDE!
HE'S FOLLOWING US!
YOU GUYS ARE LOSING IT!
YOU WENT TEXAS CHAINSAW
ON THAT DOOR!
I KNEW IT!
YOU LOCKED US IN THERE.
UH, NO,
I WAS ROASTING MARSHMALLOWS.
YOU'RE TRYING
TO GET RID OF ME
SO YOU CAN HOOK UP
WITH DREW.
WAIT.
SO YOU ACTUALLY THINK
THAT I'M TRYING TO STEAL
DREW FROM YOU?
WHY ELSE WOULD YOU COME
ALL THE WAY UP HERE
AND LOCK ME IN
A TOOL SHED?
YOU'RE RIGHT;
WEED DOES MAKE YOU PARANOID.
I KNOW HOW YOU WORK.
YOU DID IT TO ALLI-
OH, PLEASE LEAVE ME
OUT OF THIS.
AND I WON'T LET YOU
DO IT TO ME.
I WATCH YOU, BIANCA.
YOU'RE ALWAYS READY
TO POUNCE.
YOU ARE SO INSECURE.
IF YOU CAN'T TRUST DREW
IN A ROOM WITH ANOTHER GIRL,
YOU'LL NEVER LAST.
GOOD LUCK WITH
YOUR RELATIONSHIP, HONEY.
REAL STABLE.
YOU FOUND HER.
ELI DID.
LET ME GET
THE FIRST AID KIT.
CLARE, ARE YOU OKAY?
SOMEONE'S FROSTY.
(CLARE WINCES)
I'M ACTUALLY GLAD
YOU CAME.
WHY DO I FIND THAT
HARD TO BELIEVE?
SEEMS TO ME THERE
MUST'VE BEEN A REASON.
THERE WAS.
AND THEN YOU KISSED ALLI.
ALLI...
ALLI KISSED ME.
REALLY?
YEAH, AND KISSING HER BACK
WAS THE STUPIDEST THING
I'VE EVER DONE.
WELL, THAT SHOULD DO IT.
THANKS.
(SIGHS)
LOOK, I TRIED...
I TRIED GETTING OVER YOU
ALL SUMMER
AND I COULDN'T.
AND WHEN I FOUND
YOUR HEAD BAND,
I... I THOUGHT THAT SOMETHING
REALLY BAD HAPPENED
AND I REGRETTED EVERY MINUTE
THAT I DIDN'T SPEND WITH YOU.
STOP.
I THOUGHT ABOUT
KISSING ELI
TO GET BACK AT YOU.
OH.
LOOK, CLARE,
I'M SORRY I RAN AWAY
ALL SUMMER -
FROM THE WEDDING...
HEY...
AND I'M DONE RUNNING.
JUST...
JUST GIMME ANOTHER CHANCE.
DREW:
SO? WHAT'D YOU GIRLS GET UP TO
WHILE WE WERE OUT?
YEAH, KATIE.
WHAT DID YOU GET UP TO?
KATIE:
JUST HUNG OUT.
THERE'S SOMETHING
IN THE WOODS.
DREW:
CAN SOMEONE PLEASE
SEDATE HER?
ELI:
EVERYONE'S IN HERE, RIGHT?
THAT MEANS NO ONE'S
IN THE WOODS.
BIANCA:
EITHER SHE'S TRIPPING OUT,
OR SHE JUST SAW SOMETHING
REALLY FREAKY.
DREW:
TRIPPING OUT?
ON WHAT?
WEED.
YOU TOO?
SECOND HAND!
DREW: HOLY CRAP!
ELI: OH MY GOD!
ELI:
LOCK THE DOOR!
YOU GUYS ARE KIDDING,
RIGHT?
MARISOL:
JAKE!
DREW:
JAKE, THERE'S SOMEONE
AT THE DOOR, MAN.
SO ANSWER IT.
EVERYONE: NO!
MARISOL: IT'S THE KILLER!
JAKE:
YOU GUYS ARE RIDICULOUS.
ARE WE?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
LOOK WHAT WE FOUND.
YOUR STORY'S REAL.
JAKE:
PRATT.
THAT'S THE NAME
OF THE PREVIOUS OWNER.
BIANCA:
OH MY GOD!
HE'S OUTSIDE.
HE WANTS TO KILL US!
OR KIDNAP A VIRGIN!
CLARE, KATIE,
SACRIFICE YOURSELVES!
JAKE:
EVERYONE, STAY CALM!
(KNOCKING AT THE DOOR)
DREW:
CALM? THEN WHY DO YOU NEED
AN AXE, MAN?!
(KNOCKING AT THE DOOR)
(LATCH CLICKS)
(DOOR SQUEAKS OPEN)
ALL:
(SCREAM)
DAD!
GLENN:
SOMEONE BEEN USING MY CHAINSAW?
BIANCA:
THAT WOULD BE KATIE.
THAT GIRL IS DANGEROUS.
HELEN:
CLARE! THANK GOODNESS
YOU'RE HERE.
WHAT'RE YOU GUYS
DOING HERE?
WELL, WE CALLED
TO CHECK IN ON CLARE.
SHE WASN'T ANSWERING,
SO WE GOT WORRIED.
HELEN:
WE COULDN'T ENJOY
OUR HONEYMOON,
SO WE CAME HOME
AND CLARE WASN'T THERE.
ALLI'S MOM LEFT
A VOICEMAIL
ABOUT HER BEING
AT OUR COUNTRY PLACE,
SO WE RUSHED UP HERE.
TURNS OUT YOU GUYS ARE
HAVING A LITTLE PARTY, HUH?
SORRY.
IT'S OKAY,
WE'RE JUST GLAD YOU'RE SAFE.
AND WHAT'S WITH THE AXE?
TOLD 'EM THE PRATT
MURDER LEGEND.
GUESS WE ALL JUST GOT
A LITTLE SCARED.
MARISOL:
BUT THE RINGS!
IT'S REAL.
I FOUND THESE WHEN WE BOUGHT
THE PLACE, ALL RIGHT?
I BURIED THEM
UNDER THE TOOL SHED.
JEALOUSLY MAKES PEOPLE DO
SOME PRETTY UGLY THINGS.
KATIE:
SO THE MURDERER ISN'T REAL?
WE WERE JUST SCARING
OURSELVES?
THE SCARIEST THING
ABOUT A CABIN FULL OF TEENS
IS THE TEENS.
ALL:
(CHUCKLE)
WHO AREN'T LEAVING,
BY THE WAY,
UNTIL MY SHED DOOR
GETS FIXED.
SO, COME ON,
LET'S GET AT 'ER.
MOVE.
HELEN:
YOUR HAND!
WHAT HAPPENED?
UH, IT'S OKAY.
JAKE HELPED STOP THE BLEEDING.
LET ME SEE.
YOU RIDING WITH ME?
DOES THIS MEAN
YOU FORGIVE ME?
NEVER RUN AWAY AGAIN,
OKAY?
WELL, SAME GOES FOR YOU.
BOTH:
(CHUCKLE)
I FEEL BAD FOR MESSING UP
OUR PARENTS' HONEYMOON.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
THEY'RE OFF ANTIQUING
ALL DAY.
IT'S MY MOM'S DREAM
COME TRUE.
YOU GUYS HAVE ROOM
FOR A THIRD?
YOU KISSED MY BOYFRIEND.
I AM SO SORRY, CLARE.
I HAD NO RIGHT.
BUT YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT I WENT THROUGH
AFTER I LEFT YOU
AT THE WEDDING.
WHAT HORRIBLE THING
COULD'VE HAPPENED
TO MAKE YOU DO
WHAT YOU DID?
ENLIGHTEN ME.
WHAT'S THE POINT?
YOU THINK MY PROBLEMS
ARE "PEDESTRIAN."
FIND SOMEONE ELSE
TO RIDE WITH,
WE'RE FULL.
HEY.
IT'S A LONG WAY
TO BIKE BACK HOME.
UH, WANNA RIDE WITH US?
AWESOME. THANKS.
HEY, MY CAR'S GONNA NEED
A JUMP.
UH, YEAH. FOR SURE,
WE CAN GIVE YOU ONE.
I'M PARKED HALF A MILE
DOWN THE ROAD,
SO I'LL WALK
AND MEET YOU THERE.
SOUNDS GOOD.
KATIE:
WHERE'RE YOUR MANNERS?
YOU'RE NOT GONNA LET HER
WALK ALONE, ARE YOU?
GOOD CALL.
DREW:
HEY, BIANCA, WAIT UP.
WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
BIANCA HAS TOO MUCH POWER.
I NEED TO LET HER KNOW
THAT I'M NOT JEALOUS.
ARE YOU?
A LITTLE,
BUT I TRUST DREW.
OW!
IS YOUR KNEE OKAY?
YEAH, I JUST TWISTED IT
LAST NIGHT.
LOOKS LIKE I'LL BE RIDING
WITH YOU GUYS,
IF THAT'S OKAY.
CLARE'S STILL MAD
AT YOU?
LEAVE IT TO ME TO LOSE DAVE
AND MY BEST FRIEND
IN LESS THAN 24 HOURS.
BACK TO SCHOOL'S
GONNA BE SO FUN.
MARISOL:
THE BUS IS LEAVING
THIS HELL HOLE!
LET'S GO!
(ENGINE ROARS TO LIFE)
♪ Faster, faster ♪
♪ Faster than you thought ♪
♪ And it's going
faster, faster ♪
♪ Faster, faster ♪
♪ What are you waiting for? ♪
♪ A chance to hear it ♪
HEY.
FEEL BETTER
AFTER THE SHOWER?
MUCH.
ARE YOU EATING
MY FACE?
WELL,
ONLY IF YOU LET ME.
GROSS.
BOTH:
(HALF LAUGH)
(FRONT DOOR OPENS)
HELEN:
WE'RE BACK!
HEY!
HOW WAS ANTIQUING?
GLENN:
IT WAS GOOD.
WE GOT AN URN.
UH, JAKE, I PUT FRESH SHEETS
ON YOUR BED.
SO IF YOU NEED ANYTHING,
THIS IS YOUR HOME TOO, NOW,
OKAY?
OKAY.
THANKS, HELEN.
HELEN:
SURE.
(YAWNS)
I AM TIRED.
I'M GONNA GO TO BED.
OKAY.
'NIGHT, JAKE.
CLARE: NIGHT!
GLENN: NIGHT.
♪ ...when we weren't afraid
of the dark ♪
NIGHT, JAKE.
♪ With your hand in mine
and in the hours apart ♪
♪ You were the beating
of my heart ♪
♪ We hold on tight ♪
♪ We had the summer
of our lives ♪
♪ The sun shines at night ♪
♪ We're in love
and it feels so right ♪