(RAIN POURS DOWN,
THUNDER RUMBLES)
CLARE:
AGGGHHHHH!
ALLI:
OH, COME ON,
THE DRESS ISN'T THAT BAD.
CLARE:
IT'S NOT THE DRESS,
IT'S WHAT IT'S FOR.
ALLI:
LIKE IT OR NOT,
YOUR MOM'S STILL GETTING MARRIED
TOMORROW.
I KNOW.
AND IF SHE WEREN'T MARRYING
MY EX-BOYFRIEND'S DAD,
I'D BE HAPPY FOR HER TOO.
WELL,
HAVE YOU TALKED TO JAKE?
NOT SINCE PROM.
HE'S, UH, BEEN WORKING
AT A CAMP
NEAR HIS CABIN.
SO JAKE AND HIS DAD
ARE MOVING IN
AFTER THE WEDDING,
HUH?
ARE YOU OKAY?
I STILL HAVE FEELINGS
FOR HIM,
BUT HE'S MOVED ON.
I HAVE TO DO THE SAME.
(DULL THUMPING SOUND,
LOUD THUNDERCLAP)
WHAT WAS THAT?
(DULL THUMPING)
UM, CLARE,
I THINK IT'S COMING
FROM THE CLOSET.
BOTH:
(NERVOUS BREATHS)
(THUDDING)
(TENSE BREATHS)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(GASPS THEN SIGHS, RELIEVED)
RELAX. IT'S PROBABLY
JUST THE STORM.
ALLI:
YEAH.
(DOOR CREAKS OPEN)
(GASPS)
THE LIGHTS!
ALLI AND CLARE:
(SHRIEK)
RELAX.
IT'S JUST ME.
JAKE, YOU SCARED US.
UH, CAN WE TALK?
THAT'S MY CUE TO GO.
I WILL-
NO. UH, STAY.
WE'RE GOOD.
I WAS, UM...
I WAS JUST DROPPING
SOME BOXES INTO MY...
MY NEW ROOM.
UH, GREAT.
THAT'S AWESOME.
OKAY, SO SEE YOU
AT THE WEDDING TOMORROW.
WAIT. UH...
I JUST WANTED TO SAY THAT
YOU GOING AWAY ALL SUMMER
WAS PROBABLY THE BEST THING
YOU COULD'VE DONE,
CONSIDERING WE'RE GONNA BE
BRO AND SIS NOW.
TOMORROW'S A NEW DAY
FOR US.
NO WEIRDNESS?
YEAH. NO WEIRDNESS.
OKAY. SEE YOU.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(SIGHS)
(LOUD THUNDERCLAP)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Ooh-oh-oh ♪
(Ooh-oh-oh)
♪ I can make it through ♪
(I can make it!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(DULL SLICING SOUND)
KATIE:
TRY AND CUT THOSE STRAIGHT.
KATIE, THIS WAS SUPPOSED
TO BE OUR WEEK OF FUN
BEFORE SCHOOL STARTS.
I JUST GOT BACK
FROM A SOCCER TOURNAMENT.
I'VE HAD NO TIME
TO PREPARE
FOR BACK-TO-SCHOOL.
BESIDES, THIS IS FUN?
I AM SLICING
"WELCOME BACK DEGRASSI"
POSTERS.
IT'S THE BEGINNING
OF MY PRESIDENCY;
EVERYTHING NEEDS
TO BE PERFECT.
HOW MUCH MORE PERFECT
CAN IT GET?
YOU'RE A SOCCER SUPERSTAR,
STUDENT COUNCIL PREZ,
AND YOU'RE DATING
THE HOTTEST GUY.
ADAM:
YOU DID NOT JUST SAY THAT
OUT LOUD.
KATIE:
OH, HE DID.
NOTE, DREW:
MY LIFE ISN'T MAGICALLY
PERFECT.
IT TAKES HARD WORK.
NOW SLICE.
BIANCA:
I'M GONNA NEED THAT TABLE.
UH, WE'RE WORKING HERE.
UH, NO, WE SHOULD CLEAR IT
FOR B.
YOU KNOW SHE'S BEEN
HELPING OUT
AT MY DAD'S OFFICE.
PART OF MY PLEA BARGAIN,
WHICH UNOFFICIALLY INCLUDES
WORKING IN THE BASEMENT
WITH THESE TWO BONEHEADS.
ADAM:
YOU RETURN
"LAST HOUSE ON THE LEFT"?
YEP, AND PICKED UP
"CABIN FEVER" -
DREW'S CHOICE -
AS WELL AS THE VINTAGE CLASSIC,
"THE BLAIR WITCH PROJECT."
UM...
WE'VE BEEN WATCHING
A LOT OF HORROR MOVIES.
YEAH, WHEN YOU'RE NOT HIDING
UNDER A BLANKET.
(LAUGHS)
YOU KNOW WHAT?
UM, YOU'RE RIGHT,
I DID PROMISE
THAT WE'D HAVE FUN.
SO WHY DON'T WE GO
TO LUNCH - ON ME.
DREW:
OKAY.
THERE.
YOU LOOK REALLY PRETTY.
EVEN THE DRESS IS NICE.
I WISH YOU COULD
STAY THOUGH!
BUT MY MOM SAID
ONLY BLOOD RELATIVES
BECAUSE OF THE LIVING ROOM
SPACE RESTRICTIONS.
DON'T WORRY.
I GET IT.
HELEN WANTS TO KEEP IT
LOW PROFILE.
YOU KNOW, PENELOPE CRUZ,
JAVIER BARDEM-STYLE.
DAVE HASN'T TEXTED ME BACK.
YOU KNOW,
THIS IS WEIRD.
WHEN I WAS AT SCIENCE CAMP,
WE TEXTED LIKE 24/7,
AND NOW I'M THAT I'M BACK
IT'S LIKE DEAD SILENT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
I SHOULD DO?
ABOUT WHAT?
ALLI:
THE PALESTINE ISRAEL CONFLICT,
CLARE.
DAVE!
LOOK ON THE BRIGHT SIDE,
AT LEAST YOUR MOM
ISN'T MARRYING HIS DAD.
BIGGER PROBLEMS RIGHT HERE.
YEAH.
I'M SORRY MY PROBLEMS
ARE SO INSIGNIFICANT, CLARE.
COMPARED TO MY LIFELONG
FAMILY-ALTERING NIGHTMARE?
YOU'RE COMPLAINING
ABOUT A LACK OF TEXTS.
I THINK YOU'LL LIVE.
(ALLI'S PHONE BEEPS)
LET ME GUESS.
DAVE?
YUP.
HE WANTS TO MEET AT THE DOT.
SEE? PEDESTRIAN DRAMA.
IT'S A GOOD THING,
TRUST ME.
HAVE A FUN WEDDING.
THANKS.
("JESU, JOY OF MAN'S DESIRING"
PLAYS)
(LOW HUM OF GUESTS' CHATTER)
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
GLENN:
SHE LOOKS BEAUTIFUL,
DOESN'T SHE?
YEAH,
SHE REALLY DOES.
MINISTER FRED:
WE ARE GATHERED TOGETHER TODAY
TO SHARE IN THE UNION
OF THESE TWO FINE PEOPLE.
IN THE BIBLE...
TOOK YOU A WHILE FOR YOU
TO RESPOND TO MY TEXTS!
HEH. I KNOW.
I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT.
IT'S FINE. IF I LEARNED
ANYTHING THIS SUMMER,
IT'S PATIENCE.
I MISSED YOU, GIRL.
DO WANNA SHARE
SOMETHING?
UH, NOW, HOLD UP.
FINE, I'LL ORDER
MY OWN CHICKEN WINGS.
NO. NO, NO. UH...
LOOK, I GOTTA BE UP FRONT
WITH YOU ABOUT SOMETHING.
I HAD A THING THIS SUMMER.
WELL, "A THING" COULD MEAN
A LOT OF THINGS, RIGHT?
WELL...
NO, I MEAN A THING
WITH ANOTHER GIRL.
IT'S OVER THOUGH.
WAIT.
DID YOU HAVE SEX
WITH HER?
DAVE:
LOOK, I MEAN,
YOU AND I WERE ON A BREAK.
LOOK, I FELT BAD
AFTER I DID IT.
I THOUGHT WE WERE GONNA
WAIT FOR EACH OTHER!
I, I KNOW,
WE WERE, OKAY?
IT'S JUST THIS
ONE MISTAKE.
AND LOOK,
I WAITED TO TELL YOU
FACE-TO-FACE.
THIS SUMMER WAS A TEST
FOR US
AND YOU FAILED!
LOOK. OKAY, ALLI, LOOK.
WHAT CAN I DO
TO FIX THIS?
YOU CAN LEAVE!
I'M SORRY, OKAY?
(SIGHS)
DREW:
HEY, DAVE.
WHAT'S GOING ON, MAN?
(DAVE MUMBLES,
DREW SCOFFS)
WHAT'S WRONG WITH HIM?
HEY, ALLI,
HOW WAS YOUR SUMMER?
MARISOL:
UM... YOU OKAY?
(SIGHS)
(POP)
ALL:
CHEERS!
(GLASSES CLINK)
SO, I GOT...
CHEDDAR, SWISS,
THE SMELLY KIND...
TAKE YOUR PICK.
I'M OKAY.
HEY, WE, UH...
WE HAVEN'T REALLY GOTTEN
THE CHANCE TO TALK
SINCE I'VE BEEN BACK.
YOU KNOW, I SHOULD GO HELP
REFRESH THE GUESTS' DRINKS.
WAIT!
MY DAD AND YOUR MOM TAKE OFF
ON THEIR B&B HONEYMOON LATER,
AND I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU WANTED TO HANG OUT,
RECONNECT?
YOU KNOW, I HAVEN'T HEARD
FROM YOU IN MONTHS,
SINCE YOU SENT ME
A TEXT SAYING,
"SEE YOU AT THE WEDDING,
SIS."
NOW YOU WANNA RECONNECT?
WHEN I WAS AT THE CABIN,
I WAS DOING
A LOT OF THINKING.
I THOUGHT ABOUT US
AND I REALIZED THAT...
I STILL LOVE YOU.
NO. YOU LEFT ME
HEARTBROKEN.
SO, ALL SUMMER,
I CONVINCED MYSELF
THAT WE WERE OVER.
I DEALT WITH THINGS.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD HAVE,
INSTEAD OF RUNNING OFF
TO A CABIN
TO ROMANTICIZE ABOUT SOMETHING
THAT IS SO OVER!
HELEN:
HEY! WHO WANTS CAKE?
♪ Lights lit up
and we got love ♪
♪ We moved everything we owned ♪
♪ And I walked you
back home alone ♪
♪ And it's so hard
to say okay ♪
♪ When our days
are looking grey ♪
♪ When we've found ourselves
in a place to stay ♪
♪ And you said we could
celebrate love ♪
JAKE MARTIN!
LOOKING GOOD!
DREW:
GRAB A SEAT.
ALLI:
IS THE WEDDING OVER?
NO, I JUST NEEDED SOME AIR.
SO, SENIOR YEAR.
YOU EXCITED?
JAKE:
YEAH, I GUESS.
SO, WHAT'D YOU GET UP TO
THIS SUMMER?
WORKED AT A CAMP,
HUNG OUT AT MY CABIN.
YOU HAVE A CABIN?
HOT.
ENH.
IT'S NOTHING FANCY.
ALLI:
MUST BE NICE, YOU KNOW,
TO HAVE A LITTLE ESCAPE.
HEY, UM, ANY CHANCE
THAT YOU GUYS
WANNA HAVE AN END OF SUMMER
CABIN PARTY TONIGHT?
UH, YEAH!
I'M SO IN.
ELI:
GREETINGS, DEGRASSIANS.
JAKE:
ELI.
BIKING IN THIS HEAT?
PERFECT DAY
FOR A LITTLE SHVITZ.
OR A PERFECT DAY FOR A PARTY
AT JAKE'S CABIN!
JAKE:
SO HOW SOON CAN YOU GUYS
BE READY?
PRETTY SOON.
OKAY.
(EVERYONE LAUGHS)
ALLI:
ALL RIGHT.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(TISSUE PAPER RUSTLES)
(CLARE'S PHONE RINGS)
HELLO?
HEY, CLARE,
PASS ME DREW?
WHO IS THIS?
BIANCA DESOUSA.
CLARE:
I THINK YOU HAVE
THE WRONG NUMBER.
NO. ADAM CAN'T FIND
THE XBOX CONTROLLER,
AND I TRIED CALLING DREW,
KATIE, AND EVERYONE,
BUT I DON'T THINK THEY'RE
GETTING RECEPTION UP THERE.
UP WHERE?
UP AT THE PARTY,
AT JAKE'S CABIN.
THERE'S A PARTY
BIANCA:
OOH... MY BAD.
ADAM THOUGHT
YOU'D BE UP THERE,
BUT I GUESS NOBODY
TOLD YOU.
OF COURSE NOBODY TOLD ME.
JAKE AND I GOT INTO A FIGHT.
I MADE A HUGE MISTAKE.
I NEED TO TALK TO HIM.
OKAY, TMI.
BUT IF I WERE YOU,
I'D GET UP THERE SOON.
CABINS EQUALS KISSING.
KISSING?
WHO'S THERE?
UM, DREW, KATIE...
MARISOL, TOO, I GUESS.
MARISOL?!
OKAY, YEAH,
I DO NEED TO GET UP THERE.
DOES HE KNOW WHERE
THE CONTROLLERS ARE?
SHE'S NOT WITH HIM.
BUT IT MIGHT BE FUN
IF WE CRASHED.
YOU UP FOR A SCARY ADVENTURE
IN THE WOODS?
CAN'T. PHYSIO.
CLARE, I CAN DRIVE.
I'LL PICK YOU UP SOON.
BE READY.
CLARE:
OH, NO. NO, BIANCA.
THAT'S O- (PHONE BEEPS)
(PHONE BEEPS OFF)
THAT'S OKAY.
(VEHICLES RUMBLE ALONG)
(CROW CAWS)
ALLI:
HOLD ON.
LET ME TEST IT...
(SNIFFS AND EXHALES)
THE AIR IS BETTER OUT HERE.
PINEY.
(LAUGHS)
JAKE:
I'M GLAD YOUR PARENTS
LET YOU COME.
HA! THEY THINK I'M AT
A POST-WEDDING CELEBRATION
AT CLARE'S NEW COTTAGE HOUSE
WITH PARENTAL SUPERVISION.
THANKS FOR NOT TELLING
CLARE.
ARE YOU SURE
WE SHOULDN'T CALL HER,
YOU KNOW,
LET HER KNOW WE'RE HERE?
WELL, IT DEFEATS
THE WHOLE PURPOSE,
WHICH IS TO GET OVER
SHE-WHO-MUST-NOT-BE NAMED.
MARISOL:
AHHH! THIS IS SO COOL!
(TITTERS)
JAKE:
BRING YOUR STUFF IN
THIS WAY, GUYS.
MAY I?
DREW:
JAKE MARTIN,
YOU ARE THE MAN!
JAKE:
ALL RIGHT...
MARISOL:
'KAY, ONE,
WHY DOES IT SMELL LIKE...
WET DOG?
AND TWO, PLEASE TELL ME
YOU HAVE BUG SPRAY.
JAKE:
CHECK THE TOP DRAWER
IN THE KITCHEN.
EW!
IF I GET WEST NILE...
ALLI:
WE HAVE A...
CANDLESTICK,
KNIFE,
LEAD PIPE, ROPE,
WRENCH,
REVOLVER... MAGAZINE.
NO BUG SPRAY.
UGH! KILL ME NOW.
DREW:
HEY, DON'T MIND IF I DO.
WHAT?
SHE ASKED FOR IT!
SO HAS THIS PLACE
BEEN IN THE FAMILY LONG?
WE GOT IT PRETTY CHEAP
IN '99.
NO KIDDING.
THE OLD OWNER CAUGHT HIS WIFE
IN HERE WITH ANOTHER MAN.
THE GUY KILLS HIM
WITH A FIRE POKER,
CHASES AFTER HIS WIFE
IN THE WOODS.
THE COPS CALLED IT
A DOUBLE MURDER SUICIDE.
YOU KNOW, PEOPLE SAY
HE CAN STILL BE SEEN
ROAMING THE WOODS AT NIGHT,
SEARCHING FOR HIS LOST LOVE.
DREW AND KATIE:
(LAUGH)
OKAY, NOW I'M CREEPED OUT.
ALLI, WANNA HELP ME GRAB
SOME KINDLING FOR THE FIRE?
UM... YEAH, SURE.
SCREAM IF YOU NEED ME.
TAKE YOUR CELL.
NO POINT;
RECEPTION'S SPOTTY.
WANNA GO EXPLORE?
I'M NOT GOING OUT THERE.
STAY IN WITH ME.
WE'LL WATCH TV.
(HALF LAUGHS)
WHAT TV?
THERE'S NO TV?
UGH! THIS IS HELL!
GREAT.
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE STAYING IN
TO ENTERTAIN MARISOL.
NO. LET'S GO DO
SOMETHING FUN.
OKAY.
UH... I DIDN'T DRIVE
ALL THE WAY HERE
SO YOU COULD DITCH ME
TO MAKE OUT!
HELLO?!
(SIGHS)
(RUSTLING SOUND)
(RUSTLING SOUND,
SPRINGS CREAK)
(BIRDS CHIRP AND CAW)
THE MAP'S UPSIDE DOWN.
I KNEW THAT.
EVIL DEAD,
THE STRANGERS,
FRIDAY THE 13TH -
ALL THE BEST HORROR MOVIES
TAKE PLACE IN THE WOODS.
IT'S SOMETHING ABOUT
THE SECLUSION.
IF YOU SCREAM,
NO ONE CAN HEAR YOU.
CAN YOU BE QUIET,
PLEASE,
SO I CAN FIGURE
THIS OUT?
IN A RUSH,
ARE WE?
I JUST WANNA GET
TO THE PARTY.
PLEASE, GIRL.
YOU LOVE
YOUR STEP-BROTHER.
ARE YOU WORRIED
HE'S HOOKING UP
WITH SOMEONE ELSE?
CAN YOU STOP PLAYING
WITH YOUR WHACK '80S HEADBAND
AND NAVIGATE,
PLEASE?
I'M TRYING, OKAY?
THERE ARE A SERIES OF DRIVEWAYS
ALONG THIS ROAD.
IT'S PROBABLY ONE
OF THE LAST THREE.
IF WE KEEP DRIVING,
WE'LL FIND IT.
(IGNITION CHUGS,
STRUGGLING TO START)
WHAT'S WRONG?
IT'S A 20-YEAR-OLD PIECE
OF CRAP IS WHAT'S WRONG.
IT'S GONNA BE DARK SOON.
BIANCA:
THEN WE SHOULD WALK FAST.
(SIGHS)
(MUSIC PLAYS
THROUGH HEADPHONES)
MARISOL:
♪ YEAH, BABY, DIP IT ♪
♪ YEAH, BABY, DIP IT!
WOO! ♪
♪ TOUCH THE FLOOR
WITH YOUR DERRIERE ♪
♪ DO-DO-DO ♪
♪ DO-DO-DO, YEAH ♪
(NEARBY THUD,
SOFT WHIMPERS)
HELLO?
KATIE!
FEMALE VOICE:
HELP ME!
HELP ME, PLEASE!
(WHIMPERING)
HELP ME.
(MARISOL SCREAMS)
(WHIMPERING)
HOODED FIGURE:
(MENACING ROARS)
MARISOL:
(TERRIFIED SCREAMING)
KATIE:
MARE! MARE, IT'S JUST DREW.
DREW:
GOTCHA! (LAUGHS)
MARISOL:
SCREW YOU!
SCREW BOTH OF YOU!
COME ON, WE'RE JUST
HAVING A LITTLE FUN.
YEAH, AT MY EXPENSE!
I HATE YOU.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
THE MURDERER!
IT WAS DREW'S IDEA.
NO, YOU SAID YOU WANTED
TO HAVE FUN.
IT WAS BOTH OUR IDEAS.
DON'T BELIEVE HIM.
GUYS, I'M ACTUALLY
REALLY SCARED.
YOU'RE KIDDING ME,
RIGHT?
OH, SUCK IT UP,
PRINCESS.
CAN YOU TELL
YOUR BOYFRIEND
TO STOP TALKING TO ME
LIKE THAT?
DREW, COME ON.
COME ON,
ARE YOU SER...
WOO-OO-OO!
(CRICKETS CHIRP,
OWL HOOTS)
(FLAMES CRACKLE)
ALLI:
(SIGHS)
THIS IS ALL THE KINDLING
I COULD FIND.
JAKE AND ALLI:
(LAUGH)
JAKE:
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF MY CABIN?
ALLI:
IT'S QUIET.
WHICH MEANS MORE
THINKING-ABOUT-DAVE TIME.
JAKE:
YOU KNOW, IT'S FUNNY.
I ALWAYS THINK
THAT COMING UP HERE
IS THE SOLUTION
TO MY PROBLEMS.
IT NEVER IS.
THIS IS NONE
OF MY BUSINESS,
BUT DID YOU HOOK UP
WITH ANYONE ELSE
THIS SUMMER,
WHEN YOU WERE AWAY
FROM CLARE?
I THOUGHT ABOUT IT.
AND EVEN THOUGH
WE WERE BROKEN UP,
IT STILL FELT LIKE
IT WOULD BE CHEATING.
SO, NO.
(HALF LAUGHS)
MARSHMALLOWS!
HERE.
'KAY.
THANK YOU.
ONE FOR YOU.
OKAY, THE TRICK IS TO HOLD IT
ABOVE THE EMBERS
FOR A SLOW BROWNING.
OH NO.
SEE, I'M MORE OF A
LIGHT-IT-ON-FIRE...
THEN-BLOW-IT-OUT
KINDA GIRL.
OH, NICE AND CHARRED.
(HOWLING NEARBY)
WHAT WAS THAT?
OH, PROBABLY JUST A WOLF.
A WOLF?
YOU CAN'T SHRUG
AND SAY, "WOLF."
SORRY.
SO YOU HAVE MURDERERS
WITH FIRE POKERS
AND WOLVES.
ANYTHING ELSE?
OH, NO,
THERE ARE A FEW COYOTES TOO.
YOU'LL BE OKAY,
JUST STICK WITH ME.
YOU KNOW,
CLARE'S REALLY LUCKY
TO HAVE...
SORRY,
I SAID HER NAME.
NOT HELPING.
IT'S OKAY.
EVEN WITH ALL THIS DISTANCE,
YOU CAN'T ESCAPE STUFF.
YEAH. IT'S FUNNY...
I'M FEELING PRETTY
FAR AWAY
RIGHT ABOUT NOW...
FROM EVERYTHING.
IT'S NICE.
YEAH, IT IS.
(FOLIAGE RUSTLES NEARBY)
(APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS)
CLARE:
JAKE?
ALLI.
BIANCA:
NOW THAT'S JUST WRONG.
KATIE:
G-6.
MARISOL:
HEH! MISS.
BIANCA:
PAJAMA PARTY OVER, KIDS?
MARISOL:
WHY'S SHE HERE?
GOOD QUESTION.
JAKE:
YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED
TO BE MAD.
YOU REJECTED ME,
REMEMBER?
THERE'S A REASON
I DIDN'T INVITE YOU.
(LIGHTS FIZZLE,
MARISOL SCREAMS)
ALLI: UH, JAKE?
MARISOL: WHAT'S HAPPENING?!
DREW:
YO, JAKE,
WHAT'S GOING ON, MAN?
JAKE:
EVERYONE, STAY CALM.
KATIE:
DREW?
(METALLIC CLINK,
FLAME WHOOSHES AND CRACKLES)
WHERE'S CLARE?
CLARE?
CLARE?! CLARE!
(PANTING)
(SOBBING)
(TWIGS SNAP NEARBY,
CLARE GASPS)
(NERVOUS BREATHS)
(BIRDS TWITTER,
RUSTLING SOUNDS)
(LOW GROANING SOUND)
(TENSE, SHAKY BREATHS)
(OWL CRIES)