♪♪♪
♪ We're only young
and naive still ♪
♪ We require certain skills ♪
MRS. EDWARDS:
DON'T BE LATE
FOR DINNER TONIGHT!
(DOOR SLAMS)
OKAY, DIAPERS...
BLANKETS, BOTTLE...
MAMA'S COMING!
JACKET...
(TYSON FUSSES)
MAMA'S COMING!
(GROANS)
UGH!
I'M COMING!
HI!
WE'RE GONNA MAKE IT,
RIGHT, TY?
(CRIES)
(SIGHS)
AS SOON AS I FIND
YOUR OTHER BOOTIE.
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ We lie beneath the stars
at night ♪
(ELI SIGHS)
♪ Our hands gripping
each other tight ♪
♪ You keep my secrets... ♪
IT'S A TRAGEDY
IT HAD TO END THE WAY IT DID,
BUT IT HAD TO END.
ALLI:
HE WAS SMOTHERING YOU, CLARE,
YOU HAD NO CHOICE.
CLARE:
I JUST, I HOPE HE'S OKAY,
YOU KNOW?
HAS HE TRIED TO CALL?
EMAIL? TEXT?
UH, N-NOT SINCE THE NIGHT
OF THE DANCE.
MAYBE THAT'S A GOOD SIGN.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THERE'S NO REASON
ELI AND I CAN'T BOTH
BE MATURE ABOUT THIS.
WE NEED TO MOVE ON
SO WE CAN WALK THESE HALLS
IN PEACE.
GOOD LUCK, SISTER.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
HEY.
HI.
SO...
HOW ARE YOU?
I'M GREAT.
THANKS.
OKAY... WANNA TALK?
NAH, I'M GOOD.
SEE YOU 'ROUND.
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Oooh... ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
GIRL:
HEY! OH, I MISSED YOU!
HOW WAS SPRING BREAK
IN FLORIDA?
THE BEST!
WESLEY:
DO YOU HAVE THIRD PERIOD
WITH MS. OH?
CONNOR:
YES.
ME TOO!
WHAT ABOUT SECOND PERIOD?
CONNOR:
MR. BETANKAMP.
WESLEY:
NICE! HIGH FIVE!
HEY, LADIES,
PLANS TONIGHT?
OTHER THAN FIRST DAY BACK
HOMEWORK?
LOOK, I'M TRYING TO GET
THE WHOLE GANG TOGETHER.
CAN I COUNT YOU GUYS IN?
SADIE:
THERE WILL BE NACHOS!
WE'LL BE THERE.
(GIRLS LAUGH)
HEY!
HOW'S YOUR BROTHER?
OTHER THAN GROUNDED
FOR THE REST OF HIS LIFE?
JUST TRYING TO LAY LOW
FOR A COUPLE OF DAYS.
WHAT'D THE POLICE SAY?
IS HE IN TROUBLE?
WE DON'T KNOW YET.
MOM FREAKED OUT,
GOT A LAWYER.
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
HE KILLED A GUY.
HEY,
IT WAS SELF DEFENSE.
DREW'S NEVER HURT ANYONE
IN HIS LIFE.
DAVE:
LOOK, MY DAD SAID
HE DID THE RIGHT THING.
HOLLY J:
PRIORITY IS PROM COMMITTEE.
WE NEED A THEME!
OH! DON'T FORGET
ABOUT GRAD PHOTOS.
AND GRAD GIFTS.
GUYS, THIS IS OUR LAST
SEMESTER TOGETHER.
ANYA, FIONA, AND HOLLY J:
AWWWWWW!
AWW, WELL I HATE TO BREAK UP
A GROUP HUG,
BUT THESE MORNING ANNOUNCEMENTS
WON'T READ THEMSELVES.
HOLLY J:
HIGH SCHOOL HOME STRETCH -
ARE YOU AND I OKAY?
SAV:
I AM IF YOU ARE.
SPRING BREAK WAS JUST
WHAT I NEEDED.
HOW WAS YOURS?
YOU KNOW,
DIALYSIS.
RIGHT, DRAG.
WELL, LET'S DO THIS,
WE GOOD?
GIRL:
YEP, LET'S GO.
OKAY...
WELCOME BACK, DEGRASSI.
NEXT WEEK WE KICK OFF
OUR SEMESTER LONG HEALTH
AND WELL-BEING INITIATIVE:
OUR HEALTH, OUR PASSION.
HOLLY J:
VISIT THE INFO TABLE
IN THE FOYER TO SIGN UP...
UH, JENNA!
JENNA:
ALLI!
YOU BROUGHT THE BABY...
TO SCHOOL?
I GUESS HE'LL BE GETTING
A HEAD START
IN GRADE TEN WITH MOM?
OH, I'M NOT ACTUALLY HERE
FOR CLASS.
OH, YOU'RE TAKING
SOME MOMMY TIME?
TILL NEXT YEAR.
IT'S JUST EVEN THOUGH
I'M TAKING A BREAK,
I DIDN'T WANT TO MISS
EVERYONE ELSE'S FIRST DAY!
SO, HOW IS HE?
ARE YOU GETTING ANY SLEEP?
TWO HOURS A NIGHT,
IF I'M LUCKY.
UGH! I CANNOT FUNCTION
WITHOUT MY BEAUTY SLEEP.
YOU'RE AMAZING.
OH, IT'S SO WORTH IT.
HE IS THE BEST THING
THAT'S EVER HAPPENED TO ME...
AND TO HIS DADDY!
WELL, I HAVE CLASS.
SEE YOU... SOMETIME?
YEAH! SURE!
OKAY.
ALLI:
WHOA! (LAUGHS)
HEY!
HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
TY AND I WANTED TO WISH YOU
A GOOD FIRST DAY BACK!
OH, THANKS.
YOU TOOK TWO BUSES
JUST FOR THAT?
AND TO SEE MY OTHER FRIENDS.
KINDA BORING AT HOME.
(BELL RINGS)
OH! I CAN'T BE LATE
FOR FIRST PERIOD.
HAVE A GOOD ONE,
BIG GUY.
YOU HAVE A GOOD DAY,
TOO!
THANKS.
(JENNA SIGHS HEAVILY)
LOOKS LIKE IT'S JUST...
YOU AND ME.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
GUY: HEY.
ADAM: HEY!
ADAM:
WELL, HERE WE ARE,
SCARY CIVICS CLASS.
YOU READY?
CLARE: YEAH.
I MEAN,
HOW BAD CAN IT...BE.
WHOA! THAT'S A BIG BINDER.
RIGHT.
(BINDER THUDS LOUDLY)
(SIGHS)
HELLO? YOU HERE?
CAN ELI REALLY JUST BE FINE?
HE TOLD ME HE WAS GREAT.
WELL, DID YOU HANG OUT WITH HIM
OVER SPRING BREAK MUCH?
HE HAD STUFF TO DO.
I MEAN, YOU HELPED HIM!
LOOK, THE BREAK-UP
IS THE BEST THING
THAT COULD'VE HAPPENED.
YOU GUYS GOING
TO "ABOVE THE DOT" TONIGHT?
UH... I GUESS, MAYBE.
GREAT.
(TRAFFIC RUMBLES)
(EXHAUSTED SIGH)
ALL RIGHT.
OH! AHHH!
NEED A HAND?
JENNA:
OH! KYLE, YOU'RE STILL HERE!
COULD YOU WATCH TY
FOR A BIT?
HE KEPT ME UP ALL NIGHT.
I CAN'T, LITTLE SIS.
I'M ON MY WAY TO WORK.
WHERE WERE YOU ANYWAY?
I WANTED TO SEE KC
BEFORE SCHOOL.
KYLE:
(SCOFFS) LUCKY GUY.
HE GOES TO SCHOOL,
SEES HIS FRIENDS,
DOESN'T GET WOKEN UP
BY HIS SCREAMING NEPHEW
FOUR TIMES A NIGHT.
HE'S DOING HIS PART.
HE'S BRINGING OVER
MORE DIAPERS LATER.
WOW!
HE SHOULD GET A MEDAL.
KYLE!
LOOK, I JUST THINK
THAT THE DUDE
WHO ACTUALLY HELPED
MAKE THAT BABY
SHOULD BE AROUND
A LITTLE MORE.
HE'S BUSY,
AND DEGRASSI
IS A THOUSAND MILES
FROM OUR PLACE.
KYLE:
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
I'M NOT GONNA GET ON YOUR CASE.
SEE YA LATER.
BYE, LITTLE T.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
ALLI:
MAYBE ADAM IS RIGHT.
MAYBE ELI IS OVER YOU.
MAYBE.
CLARE, YOU'RE GREAT,
BUT IT IS POSSIBLE.
THIS IS THE SAME ELI
WHO CRASHED HIS HEARSE
TO STOP US FROM BREAKING UP!
OKAY, MAYBE WE SHOULD
STAY IN TONIGHT.
YOU KNOW,
AVOID ALL ELI ZONES.
I'M FINE, ALLI.
IT'S JUST...
SOMETHING DOESN'T SEEM RIGHT.
HE'S NOT ACTING LIKE HIMSELF.
AS IN NOT OBSESSED WITH YOU?
CLARE, ISN'T THAT
WHAT YOU WANT?
MRS. EDWARDS:
HMM. YOU GOT ALL DRESSED UP
FOR DINNER.
DINNER?
THE MARTINS?
I TOLD YOU ABOUT THIS
WEEKS AGO.
BUT ALLI AND I ARE GOING OUT!
GLENN AND HIS SON
JUST MOVED BACK HERE.
HIS SON JAKE?
WHO THREW A DEAD FROG AT ME
LAST TIME I SAW HIM.
THAT WAS SIX YEARS AGO.
THEY GO TO OUR CHURCH,
I WANT THEM TO FEEL WELCOME.
REPORT BACK TO ME?
OF COURSE.
HAVE FUN.
(SCOFFS)
(CAR RUMBLES)
(DOORS SLAM)
WELL, HELLO!
HEY, WE EARLY?
MRS. EDWARDS:
OF COURSE NOT, GLENN.
COME ON IN!
THANK YOU.
HEY, CLARE.
WHO'S YOUR FRIEND?
(SIGHS)
(POT SIZZLES)
(DOOR SLAMS)
SORRY I'M LATE.
GOT HELD UP
ON THE BASKETBALL COURTS.
BUT I GOT THE POO PROTECTORS!
OH, YOU'RE A LIFESAVER!
HOW WAS DAY ONE?
IT WAS AWESOME!
THIS SEMESTER
I HAVE BOTH GYM AND ART,
SO HARDLY ANY HOMEWORK
FOR THE REST OF THE YEAR!
AND IT WAS TACO TUESDAY
ON MONDAY.
OH, I LOVE TACOS!
I KNOW!
I'M JUST HAPPY YOU'RE HERE.
I'VE BEEN WAITING ALL DAY
FOR SOME QUALITY TIME
WITH MY NUMBER ONE GUY.
JUSTIN BIEBER?
YEAH, BUT YOU'LL DO
TILL HE GETS HERE.
NICE.
HOW'S TYSON?
OH ASLEEP, FINALLY.
HEY.
(TYSON COOS)
GOOD.
WELL,
I'D LOVE TO HANG OUT
WITH MY VERY, VERY,
SEXY GIRLFRIEND,
BUT I TOLD DAVE
I'D MEET HIM AND THE GANG
AT "ABOVE THE DOT".
OH.
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
THAT YOU WERE HELPING
WITH TYSON TONIGHT.
WELL, UH,
HE'S SLEEPING.
WE DON'T BOTH NEED
TO BE HERE, RIGHT?
LEGALLY, NO,
BUT...
COOL!
I HAVE NO PLANS TOMORROW.
I'LL VISIT THEN.
PROMISE!
AND I'LL TELL THE GANG
YOU SAY HI.
(FRUSTRATED SIGH)
(DOOR SLAMS)
GLENN:
HELEN, THANKS FOR HAVING US.
JAKE:
MMM! CHICKEN'S GREAT!
MRS. EDWARDS:
WOULD YOU LIKE SOME MORE?
DARK MEAT OR WHITE?
UM, BOTH PLEASE.
MRS. EDWARDS:
CLARE, YOU SHOULD TELL
GLENN AND JAKE
ABOUT YOUR WRITING.
CLARE JUST GOT PUBLISHED
THIS YEAR.
WOW! THAT'S IMPRESSIVE!
WHAT DO YOU WRITE?
FICTION, MOSTLY.
WELL, YOU MUST BE
VERY TALENTED.
I GUESS.
MRS. EDWARDS:
I'M SORRY, CLARE'S NOT QUITE
HERSELF TONIGHT.
SHE'S JUST GETTING OVER
A DIFFICULT BREAKUP.
CLARE:
MOM!
MRS. EDWARDS:
THERE'S NOTHING
TO BE ASHAMED OF!
IT HAPPENS
TO THE BEST OF US.
CLARE:
I BROKE UP WITH ELI.
I'M FINE,
AND I'M HAPPY TO BE HERE!
SO...
WHAT CAUSED THE MOVE?
GLENN:
UH, WELL, THE, UH, CONTRACTING
BUSINESS UP NORTH IS DEAD.
SO I HAD TO DRAG JAKE HERE,
KICKING AND SCREAMING
TO THE CITY.
YOU DON'T LIKE IT?
IT'S NOT REALLY MY THING.
CLARE:
OH.
HOW ABOUT SCHOOL?
MRS. EDWARDS:
OH, THAT'S RIGHT, JAKE!
HOW WAS YOUR FIRST DAY
AT DEGRASSI?
WHAT?!
IT'S REALLY BIG;
I KEPT GETTING LOST.
CLARE, MAYBE YOU COULD
TAKE JAKE AROUND TOMORROW,
INTRODUCE HIM TO SOME
OF YOUR FRIENDS AT SCHOOL.
ACTUALLY,
I HAVE A BETTER IDEA!
ALL MY FRIENDS ARE
AT "ABOVE THE DOT" RIGHT NOW,
AND I'D REALLY LOVE FOR THEM
TO MEET JAKE.
CLARE, WE'RE IN
THE MIDDLE OF DINNER.
JAKE:
NO, IT'S COOL, I'LL GO.
YEAH, THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
YOU KIDS HAVE FUN.
GREAT! THANKS, GLENN!
CLARE: COME ON!
JAKE: OH!
(JAKE SIGHS)
(MUFFLED CHATTER)
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYS)
♪ Baby, we can roll the dice
and take a chance on love... ♪
(ALLI AND SADIE LAUGH)
ALLI:
TH-THAT'S NOT SO HARD.
HEY! YOU MADE IT!
AND WE NEVER GOT A CHANCE
TO PROPERLY MEET.
I'M ALLI.
JAKE.
CLARE:
HE JUST TRANSFERRED
TO DEGRASSI,
AND I WANTED TO INTRODUCE HIM
TO SOME PEOPLE.
OH, YEAH.
UM, I'M SURE JAKE
WOULD LOVE TO MEET ELI.
(LAUGHS)
JAKE, THIS IS KC, DAVE,
AND SADIE.
DAVE:
WHAT'S UP?
(POOL BALLS CLICK)
JAKE:
ARE THOSE HAWAIIAN NACHOS?
DAVE: GO NUTS.
JAKE: OH, THANKS!
COME WITH ME.
UH, I'M EATING!
HOW ARE YOU
STILL HUNGRY?
(SIGHS) ELI!
THIS IS JAKE.
HE'S NEW AT DEGRASSI,
BUT HE AND I HAVE LONG HISTORY.
AH.
WELCOME TO OUR HUMBLE HANGOUT.
I'VE HEARD A LOT ABOUT YOU.
ELI:
SOME GOOD THINGS,
I HOPE.
SEE YOU 'ROUND SCHOOL?
MM-HM.
FOR SURE.
JAKE:
SO, SHOULD WE MAKE OUT?
EXCUSE ME?!
BET IT'D MAKE YOUR EX
REALLY JEALOUS.
(PATRONS CHATTER AND LAUGH)
(KC SIGHS)
HEY,
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN
TO THE BABY?
JENNA:
NO, EVERYTHING IS NOT OKAY!
I'VE BEEN HOME ALONE
WITH THE BABY ALL DAY!
HE'S FIFTY PERCENT YOU,
AND I'M DOING 200 PERCENT
OF THE WORK!
I MISS MY FRIENDS!
I MISS ALLI, AND DAVE,
AND SADIE,
AND... NEW GUY!
IT'S NOT FAIR!
YOU GET TO SEE THEM
ALL DAY,
AND YOU LEFT ME HOME ALONE.
OKAY,
I'LL TAKE YOU HOME.
NO! I WANNA STAY.
BUT LOUD MUSIC'S
BAD FOR HIM.
S-SO YOU TAKE HIM!
(TYSON CRIES)
ME?
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
FIGURE IT OUT!
I'M GONNA HANG OUT
WITH MY FRIENDS.
ALLI: JENNA! HEY!
DAVE: HEY!
ALLI:
WHAT'S UP, JENNA?
SADIE:
YOU LOOK GOOD.
JENNA:
THANKS.
(ELI AND JAKE TALK QUIETLY)
♪♪♪
♪ The bully I can't fight ♪
♪ This dire need to fight ♪
♪ I'm on the side of the road ♪
♪ But it ain't cold ♪
♪ It ain't cold ♪
ALLI:
I HAVE THE DESSERT MENU.
OOH! OREO CHEESECAKE!
WANNA SPLIT?
JENNA.
JENNA...
JENNA, WAKE UP!
WHERE'S TYSON?
KC TOOK HIM HOME.
I HAVE TO GO SEE HIM.
NO, SWEETIE, HE'S FINE.
HE'S WITH KC.
SO STAY
AND HAVE A GOOD TIME!
ALL HE DOES IS EAT AND CRY,
AND POO.
BUT HE NEEDS ME, ALLI.
I'M ALL HE HAS!
WHAT ABOUT HIS DAD?
KC'S TRYING, BUT...
SOMETIMES I FEEL LIKE
I'M DOING THIS ALL ALONE.
KC LOVES YOU.
JUST BE HONEST,
AND I'M SURE HE'LL STEP UP.
THANKS.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(PATRONS CHATTER)
ELI?
CAN WE TALK?
MAYBE LATER.
WE CAN'T JUST AVOID
EACH OTHER FOREVER!
TWO MINUTES,
PLEASE!
OKAY.
HOW WAS YOUR FIRST DAY
AT SCHOOL?
DID YOU LIKE YOUR CLASSES,
OR-
NOT ABOUT THAT,
COME ON!
I REALLY DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU WANT ME TO SAY.
JUST TELL ME THE TRUTH!
I'M IN A GOOD PLACE.
CAN I GO?
(ELI SIGHS HEAVILY)
DID THREE MONTHS
MEAN NOTHING?
DID YOU FLIP A SWITCH
AND ERASE ME FROM YOUR MEMORY?!
IT TOOK YOU A YEAR!
A YEAR TO GET OVER YOUR EX!
DID YOU EVER LOVE ME AT ALL?
AND... SCENE.
LEAVE ME ALONE,
I'M NOT FINISHED YET!
YES YOU ARE, CLARE,
LET'S-LET'S GO.
CLARE: LET GO OF ME!
JAKE: CLARE, LET'S GO!
♪♪♪
♪ Got a secret ♪
♪ Can I keep it down ♪
(SIRENS WAIL,
HORNS HONK)
JENNA:
IS TYSON OKAY?
HE'S ASLEEP.
MY MOM WAS REALLY GOOD
WITH HIM.
DID YOU SPEND TIME
WITH HIM AT ALL?
YEAH, SOME.
BUT THERE'S ONLY SO MUCH
I CAN DO.
MY MOM SAYS I NEED
TO TAKE CARE OF YOU, TOO.
HOT MILK WITH HONEY.
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE?
IS THAT PILLOW OKAY?
UH...
IF YOU PREFER TEA
OR-OR WATER...
NO.
I-I'M SORRY I MESSED UP
TONIGHT.
IT'S NOT ABOUT TONIGHT.
I CAN'T RAISE HIM ALONE.
BUT YOU JUST SEEM
SO NORMAL.
YOU'RE LIVING YOUR LIFE
LIKE NOTHING HAPPENED!
I WANNA HELP,
I JUST DON'T REALLY KNOW HOW.
I NEVER REALLY LEARNED
HOW TO BE A DAD.
I COULD DROP OUT OF SCHOOL,
GET A JOB,
WE COULD USE
SOME EXTRA CASH.
THEN YOU'LL LEAVE ME
FOR WORK AND SCHOOL?
(SIGHS)
I NEED YOU.
MORE OF YOU!
REALLY?
I'M ACTUALLY KINDA GLAD
TO HEAR THAT.
IT'S NICE HERE...
WITH YOU.
(JENNA SIGHS HAPPILY)
(KC SIGHS)
CLARE:
BUT IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE!
DID I REALLY MEAN NOTHING
TO HIM?
YOU DON'T GET IT.
GET WHAT?
ENLIGHTEN ME!
SO WHAT IF HE DOESN'T HAVE
FEELINGS FOR YOU ANY MORE!
(GASPS)
THE ONE WHO NEEDS
CLOSURE HERE IS YOU!
OKAY.
IF YOU'RE SO SMART, HOW?
HOW DO I GET CLOSURE
IF HE WON'T EVEN TALK TO ME?
(LAUGHS)
I'M GLAD MY LIFE
IS SO ENTERTAINING FOR YOU.
I'M SORRY,
IT'S JUST...
WHY DOES EVERYTHING
HAVE TO BE SO DRAMATIC?
MOVE ON, CLARE.
OH, JUST LIKE THAT?
MOVE ON?
H-HERE,
LET ME TRY SOMETHING.
WHOA!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
JUST...SHUT UP FOR A SEC.
♪ My arms are heavy soldiers ♪
♪ Left out becoming rust ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, Yeah ♪
SEE?
NO BIG DEAL.
SO, SHOULD WE GO IN,
TELL OUR PARENTS
ALL ABOUT OUR NIGHT?
OR NOT.
(LAUGHS)
♪♪♪
♪ There's nowhere to run ♪
(JENNA YAWNS)
OH!
(SIGHS HAPPILY)
LISA:
SOMEONE'S HAPPY.
JENNA:
OH! MEGA HAPPY.
THAT WAS THE MOST SLEEP
I'VE HAD IN WEEKS.
WHY DON'T YOU GO TAKE
A LONG HOT SHOWER
AND WE'LL KEEP AN EYE ON TY.
THANK YOU!
YES, WE WILL!
WON'T WE?
(DOOR SHUTS)
MOM, I'VE BEEN THINKING
ABOUT WHAT I COULD DO
TO HELP WITH THE BABY.
WHAT KIND OF THINKING?
WELL, WITH ME AT SCHOOL
AND HER BROTHER AT WORK A LOT,
JENNA'S ON HER OWN WITH TYSON
ALL THE TIME.
I KNOW,
IT MUST BE TOUGH.
I KNOW OUR PLACE IS SMALL,
AND IT MIGHT BE IMPOSSIBLE,
BUT...
WHAT IF JENNA AND TY
MOVED IN HERE?
WHOA. UM...
THAT'S A BIG STEP.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT ELSE TO DO.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO SAY YES.
I CAN'T BE
A 24-HOUR BABYSITTER.
N-NO, NO, OF COURSE!
NO, AND THERE ARE GONNA BE
GROUND RULES,
AND I'M GONNA NEED HELP
WITH EXPENSES.
WAS THAT A YES?
(LAUGHS)
I WAS KINDA WAITING
FOR YOU TO ASK.
REALLY?
SO IT'S OKAY?
YEAH!
(LAUGHS)
LISA:
WHAT KIND OF GRANDMA
WOULD I BE, HUH?
UM, I WAS WONDERING
WHICH SHAMPOO...
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
WHAT IF YOU AND TY MOVED IN?
(SOBS)
(JENNA LAUGHS)
SO IS THAT A YES?
JENNA: YEAH!
LISA: YAY!
(ALL LAUGH)
(BELL RINGS)
ALLI:
SO HE KISSED YOU?
JUST LIKE THAT?
JUST LIKE THAT.
DID YOU TAKE A PHOTO
TO SHOW ELI?
FUNNY.
BEFORE LAST NIGHT,
I COULDN'T SEE MYSELF
KISSING ANYONE BUT ELI
EVER AGAIN.
BUT NOW?
I'M FREE.
SO, WAS THE KISS GOOD?
OH, YEAH.
CLARE EDWARDS,
YOU LITTLE HUSSY!
SO WHAT, ARE YOU TWO
LIKE AN ITEM NOW?
"AN ITEM"?
WHO ARE YOU, MY MOTHER?
NO, IT WAS...
IT WAS JUST FUN.
THAT'S ALL I WANT
RIGHT NOW.
HMM...
THAT'S WHAT THEY ALL SAY.
(CLARE SIGHS)
GIVE ME A SECOND?
ARE YOU GONNA RUB
ELI'S NOSE IN IT?
OH, YOU DO HAVE PHOTOS!
NO, ALLI!
I OWE HIM AN APOLOGY.
ALLI:
(EXASPERATED SIGH)
(LOCKER DOOR SLAMS)
CLARE:
I KNOW YOU PROBABLY
DON'T WANNA SEE ME RIGHT NOW,
SO I'LL KEEP IT SHORT.
I AM SO SORRY
ABOUT LAST NIGHT.
ONCE UPON A TIME...
WE HAD SOMETHING
REALLY GREAT,
AND MAYBE ONE DAY
WE CAN BE FRIENDS.
BUT I KNOW YOU DON'T HAVE
FEELINGS FOR ME ANYMORE,
SO I'LL LEAVE YOU ALONE.
I DON'T HAVE FEELINGS AT ALL.
WHAT?
I'M ON MEDS.
ANTI-ANXIETY PILLS
PRESCRIBED BY MY THERAPIST.
ARE YOU HAPPY NOW?
I'M SORRY,
I DIDN'T KNOW.
WELL, NOW YOU DO.
(SIGHS)
♪♪♪