(CAMERA FLASHES AND CLICKS)
LOOK AT THIS MESS!
YOU KNOW,
BREAKING IN AFTER HOURS
AND DAMAGING SCHOOL PROPERTY
IS A VERY SERIOUS OFFENCE.
ANY IDEA WHO WAS INVOLVED?
I DON'T KNOW, IT'S-
LOOKS LIKE A GRAD PRANK.
THE CLEANING STAFF FOUND
A STUDENT HERE LAST NIGHT,
SHE'S BEEN SUSPENDED
FOR THE DAY.
FIONA:
SIMPSON LOOKS MAD.
MARISOL:
GREAT. WE PISSED OFF
THE PRINCIPAL
THE FIRST WEEK OF SCHOOL.
DON'T PANIC.
MAYBE IMOGEN GOT OUT BEFORE
THE CLEANERS CAUGHT HER.
OR MAYBE SHE DIDN'T,
AND SHE'S ALREADY
RATTED US OUT.
SIMPSON:
WHEN I FIND OUT
WHO IS RESPONSIBLE
THERE WILL BE CONSEQUENCES.
MARISOL:
KATIE AND I COULD LOSE OUR
STUDENT COUNCIL POSITIONS.
MAYBE GET EXPELLED.
THEN I'LL TAKE THE BLAME.
TELL SIMPSON
IT WAS ALL MY FAULT.
MAYBE HE'LL GO EASY
ON EVERYONE.
DON'T YOU DARE!
SIMPSON DOESN'T KNOW
ANYONE ELSE WAS INVOLVED.
IMOGEN'S SUSPENDED
FOR THE DAY.
HE'S QUESTIONING HER
LATER SO...
WHAT IF SHE SAYS
SOMETHING?
MARISOL:
THEN WE'LL DENY IT.
TELL THE PRINCIPAL WE DIDN'T
INVITE IMOGEN TO A PARTY
AND SHE HAS A GRUDGE.
WHO'S HE GONNA BELIEVE -
THE CLASS CRACKPOT
OR THE THREE OF US?
OF COURSE,
IT WOULD BE EASIER
IF SOMEONE COULD KEEP
HER QUIET.
YOU WANT ME TO TALK
TO HER?
WE WARNED YOU
NOT TO INVITE HER.
I FELT BAD
SHE HAD NO FRIENDS.
NOW YOU KNOW WHY.
(SIGHS)
OKAY, UH...
I'LL SKIP MY FIRST CLASS.
GO TO HER HOUSE.
CONVINCE HER TO KEEP QUIET.
KATIE:
THE ONLY WAY
WE'LL SURVIVE THIS
IS IF THE THREE OF US
STICK TOGETHER.
♪♪♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
♪ And if I hold out ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Be the best ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
♪ I can make it through ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh... ♪
(Oh-oh-oh)
♪ I can make it through ♪
(I can make it!)
♪ Whatever it takes ♪
♪ I know I can make it through ♪
(KNOCKS)
BROUGHT YOU SOME
ORANGE JUICE,
AND A SLIGHTLY STALE
CROISSANT.
THE CAF WASN'T EXACTLY
BAKING FRESH THIS MORNING.
UM,
ABOUT LAST NIGHT...
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO APOLOGIZE.
FOR WHAT?
GETTING CAUGHT.
THE ONLY THING
THAT MATTERS
IS WHEN YOU GO TO SCHOOL
THIS AFTERNOON,
YOU CAN'T SAY THAT ANYONE
ELSE WAS INVOLVED.
SO YOU WANT ME
TO BE THE SCAPEGOAT?
IT'S ONLY FAIR. YOU'RE
THE ONE WHO GOT CAUGHT.
IMOGEN:
IT WASN'T MY FAULT!
I WAS LISTENING TO MY IPOD
IN THE THEATRE,
AND THE NEXT THING I KNOW,
THE DOOR WAS LOCKED.
WHO WOULD'VE DONE THAT?
MARISOL WAS WITH ME.
WHY IS IT SO HARD
FOR YOU
TO JUST TRY TO FIT IN
WITH EVERYONE?
YOU WERE DIFFERENT
LAST YEAR.
NOW ALL YOU CARE ABOUT IS BEING
ACCEPTED BY THE POPULARS.
TELL SIMPSON ANYONE
ELSE WAS INVOLVED
AND WE'LL DENY IT.
IT'S TWENTY OF US
AGAINST ONE OF YOU.
ENJOY YOUR CROISSANT.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE
TO WALK ME TO CLASS.
WELL, I'D HAVE CARRIED
YOUR CELLO TOO,
IF YOU'D LET ME.
NO SELF-RESPECTING
MUSICIAN
LETS SOMEONE ELSE TOUCH
THEIR INSTRUMENT.
THAT SOUNDED DIRTY,
DIDN'T IT?
A LITTLE.
I THINK WE HAVE
AN AUDIENCE.
MAYA:
EESH.
THOSE LOOKS COULD KILL.
YOU BETTER GET OUT
OF HERE.
YEAH, I'LL-
I'LL CATCH YOU LATER.
BYE.
(BELL RINGS)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
WITH ZIG?
WE'RE FRIENDS.
HE TOLD ME WHAT HAPPENED.
YOU WENT ON A FEW DATES,
THEN BROKE UP.
MAYBE ONCE YOU
GET OVER THAT,
THE THREE OF US
CAN HANG OUT TOGETHER.
HE'S ONLY USING YOU
TO MAKE ME JEALOUS.
YOU'RE NOT HIS TYPE.
THE TYPE THAT POSTS
A HUNDRED MESSAGES
ON HIS FACERANGE WALL?
IT WAS ONLY FIFTY!
TRISTAN!
THAT'S BETTER
THAN A HUNDRED!
MAYA:
MAYBE IT'S TIME TO ACCEPT
THAT YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO'S NOT HIS TYPE.
DON'T YOU DARE!
(SPIT SPLASHES)
AGH! AHHHH!
(FIGHTING GRUNTS)
MS. OH:
GIRLS! KNOCK IT OFF!
OFFICE! NOW!
(SIGHS)
JAKE:
HEY.
YOU LEFT EARLY
THIS MORNING.
DIDN'T GIVE ME A CHANCE TO
APOLOGIZE FOR BEING A JERK.
I NEEDED TIME TO THINK.
THE STUFF I SAID,
IT WAS-
IT WAS STUPID
AND IMMATURE.
NO MORE IMMATURE
THAT USING A QUIZ
TO DECIDE
IF I'M READY FOR SEX.
PART OF ME WANTS THIS.
PART OF ME IS SCARED.
I WAS JUST HOPING YOU'D
SAY THE RIGHT THING
TO MAKE ME FEEL READY.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THAT IS.
ME NEITHER.
WAIT -
DOES THAT MEAN?
OUR PARENTS
ARE OUT TONIGHT.
YEAH?
THERE'S NO REASON TO WAIT
UNTIL WE'RE MARRIED.
SO, UH,
WHEN'S THIS WEDDING?
HOW'D IT GO WITH IMOGEN?
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.
SHE'S GONNA KEEP QUIET.
(RELIEVED SIGH)
THANK YOU.
KATIE WAS MINUTES
AWAY FROM A HEART ATTACK.
SECONDS.
IF SIMPSON FOUND OUT MY KEY
THAT GOT US INTO THE SCHOOL,
I COULD LOSE MY PRESIDENCY.
I'M SORRY I LET HER
TAG ALONG.
KATIE:
DID YOU FIND OUT WHERE
SHE RAN OFF TO LAST NIGHT?
SHE GOT STUCK
IN THE THEATRE.
SHE THINKS SOMEONE
LOCKED HER IN.
KATIE:
OH NO, MARE.
IT WAS A PRANK.
I DID IT FOR FIONA.
FOR ME?
WELL, IMOGEN CALLED YOU
AN ALCOHOLIC!
(EXHALES)
I AM ONE.
RECOVERING.
AND WHEN OWEN DARED ME
TO DRINK,
IMOGEN WAS TRYING
TO PROTECT ME.
AGHH... I WAS SUCH A MONSTER
THIS MORNING.
I CAN'T LET IMOGEN
TAKE THE BLAME.
MARISOL:
WHY NOT?
IMOGEN WILL BE SUSPENDED
FOR A FEW DAYS...
A WEEK MAX.
KATIE:
I DIDN'T WANT TO SNEAK INTO
THE SCHOOL IN THE FIRST PLACE.
FIONA,
PLEASE DON'T DO THIS.
A WEEK SUSPENSION.
THAT'S PRACTICALLY
A VACATION, RIGHT?
(SIGHS)
OKAY, WHO WOULD
LIKE TO TELL ME
HOW THIS LITTLE DISAGREEMENT
STARTED?
TORI:
WELL SIR,
I WAS SITTING IN CLASS,
TUNING MY TROMBONE,
WHEN MAYA LUNGED
AT ME.
BECAUSE TORI SPIT AT ME.
THAT'S A LIE.
MAYA:
PRINCIPAL SIMPSON,
THIS ALL HAPPENED
CUZ TORI IS JEALOUS
I'VE BEEN HANGING OUT
WITH THE GUY SHE LIKES.
ALSO A LIE.
DO YOU KNOW
HOW DISAPPOINTING IT IS
TO SEE TWO SMART GIRLS
FIGHT OVER A GUY
THE FIRST WEEK OF SCHOOL?
OKAY. I'M GONNA LEAVE
FOR FIVE MINUTES.
WORK THINGS OUT?
ONE WEEKS' DETENTION.
IF YOU'RE STILL AT EACH OTHER'S
THROATS WHEN I GET BACK?
I'LL MAKE IT THREE.
GOT IT?
BOTH:
YES, SIR.
GOOD.
(CRYING)
IF THIS IS YOUR PLAN
TO MAKE ME TAKE THE BLAME-
ONE DAY,
ZIG AND I WERE HAPPY.
THE NEXT, HE WOULDN'T
ANSWER MY TEXTS.
I NEED TO KNOW
WHAT I DID WRONG.
I NEED, LIKE, CLOSURE.
I WISH I COULD HELP...
YOU CAN!
YOU COULD TALK
TO ZIG FOR ME.
OKAY. FINE.
BUT COULD YOU GET OFF
OF ME.
YOU'RE GETTING SNOT
ON MY SHIRT.
PERINO:
IN GRADE TWELVE HISTORY,
WE DON'T TAKE A HISTORIAN'S
WORD FOR IT.
WE DIG DEEPER.
WE SEARCH PRIMARY SOURCES
AND WE ANALYZE THEM -
AM I BORING YOU, MR. MARTIN?
UH, NO, SIR.
PERINO:
THEN WHY ARE YOU READING
SIZZLE TEEN, HMMM?
OH, LOOK, LET'S SEE WHAT
CHARLOTTE FROM VIRGINIA
HAS TO SAY.
DEAR SIZZLE TEEN,
I THOUGHT ME AND MY BOYFRIEND
WOULD BE TOGETHER FOREVER
SO I AGREED TO HAVE SEX.
AND THEN, LIKE, A MONTH LATER,
BAM! HE BROKE UP WITH ME.
AND NOW I'LL NEVER GET
MY FIRST TIME BACK.
WELL CLASS,
WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE?
A PRIMARY SOURCE.
PERINO:
EXACTLY.
BUT DO WE BUY HER STORY?
BIANCA:
HAPPENS ALL THE TIME.
A GUY LIES TO GET HER
INTO BED.
MAYBE HE DIDN'T LIE.
MAYBE THE SHE ASSUMED
THEY'D BE TOGETHER FOREVER.
BECAUSE THE GUY LET HER.
(CLASS LAUGHS)
PERINO:
ALL RIGHT. THANK YOU.
ENOUGH, MISS DESOUSA.
(BELL RINGS)
NOBODY EXPECTS A HIGH SCHOOL
RELATIONSHIP
TO END IN MARRIAGE.
CHARLOTTE DID.
AND IF HER GUY KNEW THAT,
HE SHOULDN'T HAVE JUMPED
IN THE SACK.
SIMPSON:
I CAN'T PHANTOM WHY YOU WOULD
DO SOMETHING SO IDIOTIC!
I'M NOT IMPRESSED, IMOGEN.
THIS IS NOT THE WAY TO BEGIN
A SCHOOL YEAR.
HOW'D IT GO?
LOOK, I WANT TO MAKE IT UP
TO YOU. A MOVIE?
A MOVIE?
OR DINNER.
THERE'S A GREAT
NEW ITALIAN PLACE
THAT MAKES THE BEST
TIRAMISU.
I'M SUSPENDED FOR A MONTH.
ON PROBATION INDEFINITELY.
FOR TIN-FOILING THE CAF?
IMOGEN:
FOR BREAKING IN AFTER HOURS,
VANDALIZING SCHOOL PROPERTY.
OH, AND DID YOU KNOW I BUSTED
A VENDING MACHINE?
THAT'S INSANE!
I THOUGHT SO TOO.
SO I TRIED TO TELL SIMPSON
THE TRUTH.
HE SAID IT WAS SUSPICIOUS
THAT I WAITED
UNTIL AFTER THE PUNISHMENT
WAS DOLED OUT.
LOOK, I'M SO,
SO SORRY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I WANTED
TO BE YOUR FRIEND.
YOU'RE JUST AS A BAD
AS KATIE AND MARISOL.
MAYBE THERE'S
SOMETHING I CAN DO.
LEAVE ME ALONE.
(SIGHS)
IMOGEN IS SUSPENDED
FOR A MONTH?
AND ON PROBATION INDEFINITELY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE SIMPSON
CAME DOWN THAT HARD.
HE USED TO BE SUCH
A SOFTIE.
WHICH IS WHY THERE'S
ONLY ONE THING WE CAN DO.
WE HAVE TO CONFESS.
UH, WHY WOULD WE DO THAT?
BECAUSE IT'LL FORCE HIM
TO BE MORE LENIENT.
HE CAN'T SUSPEND TWENTY SENIORS
FOR AN ENTIRE MONTH.
WE DON'T KNOW THAT.
WELL, IT'S WORTH A SHOT.
SO YOU'RE GONNA DO THIS
WITH OR WITHOUT US,
AREN'T YOU?
I DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
THEN NEITHER DO WE.
MARE,
YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS!
THIS IS IMPORTANT TO FIONA.
AND SHE'S IMPORTANT TO US.
THANK YOU!
THANK YOU! THANK YOU!
I KNEW YOU GUYS
WERE GOOD FRIENDS.
I'LL CALL AND SET UP A MEETING
WITH SIMPSON AFTER SCHOOL.
MARISOL:
WE'LL BE THERE!
HEY, CAN WE TALK?
OKAY, BUT FIRST -
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
YEAH. I'M NOT READY
TO GET MARRIED.
JAKE-
THIS MORNING YOU SOUNDED
READY TO SET A DATE.
YOU SAID "I DON'T NEED TO WAIT
'TIL WE'RE READY TO HAVE SEX."
WE AS IN YOU AND ME.
OBVIOUSLY, I CAN SEE MYSELF
MARRYING YOU IN THE FUTURE.
OTHERWISE,
WE WOULDN'T BE TOGETHER.
BUT I KNOW IT'S NOT
A SURE THING.
YOU DO?
SOMETIMES PEOPLE BREAK UP.
OUR PARENTS.
ME AND ELI.
SO IF WE BROKE UP
SOMETIME IN THE FUTURE,
YOU WON'T REGRET
THAT I WAS YOUR FIRST?
YOU LOVE ME,
DON'T YOU?
OF COURSE.
AND I LOVE YOU TOO.
SO AS LONG AS YOU'RE A 100%
COMMITTED RIGHT NOW.
I AM.
THERE'S NOTHING ELSE
I COULD ASK FOR.
ZIG:
SENT TO THE OFFICE ON THE FIRST
WEEK OF HIGH SCHOOL?
MY PARENTS
ARE GONNA KILL ME.
WELL, THIS IS MY FAULT,
YOU KNOW.
I GOT YOU ALL WRAPPED UP
IN MY JUNIOR HIGH DRAMA.
SO, WHY DID YOU BREAK UP
WITH TORI?
DID SHE DO SOMETHING
WRONG?
I GUESS, I DIDN'T WANT
TO START OFF HIGH SCHOOL
WITH A GIRLFRIEND.
I WANTED TO KEEP
MY OPTIONS OPEN.
IN CASE I MET SOMEONE COOL.
THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'S REALLY GOOD.
BUT I CAN'T TELL TORI THAT.
WHY WOULD YOU?
SHE ASKED ME TO FIND OUT WHAT
WENT WRONG IN YOUR RELATIONSHIP
SO SHE CAN GET "CLOSURE".
CLOSURE?
PROOF THAT THE RELATIONSHIP
IS REALLY OVER
EVEN THOUGH SHE STILL
LIKES YOU... A LOT.
WE DID DATE FOR NEARLY
A MONTH.
AND MOST OF IT
WAS PRETTY FUN.
MAYBE I SHOULD TALK
TO TORI INSTEAD.
REALLY?
YEAH. IT'S THE RIGHT
THING TO DO.
THANKS.
SIMPSON:
HM, KATIE,
I JUST HAD A NICE CHAT
WITH YOUR LITTLE SISTER.
TO WHAT DO I OWE
THE PLEASURE.
YOU TOLD US THAT IF WE KNEW
ANYTHING ABOUT THE CAFETERIA
WE SHOULD COME SEE YOU
IMMEDIATELY.
WE KNOW IT WAS PROBABLY
HARD FOR YOU TO BELIEVE
THAT IMOGEN DID IT
ALL ON HER OWN.
SHE DIDN'T.
SHE HAD HELP.
MARISOL:
WHEN FIONA TOLD US
SHE WAS THERE TOO,
WE CONVINCED HER TO CONFESS.
WE COULDN'T LET IMOGEN
TAKE ALL THE BLAME.
FIONA, IS THIS TRUE?
DID YOU SNEAK INTO THE
CAFETERIA WITH IMOGEN?
KATIE AND MARISOL
WERE THERE TOO.
HOW COULD YOU SAY THAT?
WE WERE AT MARISOL'S HOUSE.
AT LEAST TWENTY PEOPLE
CAN VERIFY THAT.
INCLUDING MARISOL'S MOM
AND DAD.
FIONA, DO YOU HAVE ANY PROOF
TO BACK UP YOUR ACCUSATIONS?
NO, BUT...
LADIES, COULD YOU GIVE US
A MOMENT ALONE PLEASE?
SURE. IF YOU NEED
ANYTHING ELSE...
I KNOW WHERE TO FIND YOU.
SIR, I KNOW THIS LOOKS BAD
BUT I CAN EXPLAIN.
FIONA, I THOUGHT THIS YEAR
WAS GONNA BE DIFFERENT.
I'VE CHANGED, MR. SIMPSON,
I PROMISE.
THAT'S NOT WHAT IT LOOKS
LIKE FROM HERE.
(SIGHS)
HEY,
SORRY I'M LATE.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
STANDING ME UP.
OH NO, WAS TALKING
TO TORI TERRIBLE?
NO, NO...
IT WAS GREAT.
SO EVERYTHING IS
WORKED OUT?
TORI GOT HER,
"LIKE, CLOSURE"?
ZIG:
SORT OF.
I GUESS, SOME OF THE STUFF
THAT YOU SAID,
IT KIND OF MADE ME REALIZE
THAT THERE'S NO GOOD REASON
TORI AND I BROKE UP.
I GUESS WHAT
I'M SAYING IS THAT-
YOU GUYS GOT
BACK TOGETHER?!
HOPE YOU'RE NOT MAD.
MAD?
WHY WOULD I BE MAD?
WELL, TORI KINDA THINKS
YOU'RE INTO ME.
SHE THINKS I'M INTO YOU?
THAT'S HILARIOUS!
TORI:
MAYA!
CAN YOU BELIEVE HOW WELL
EVERYTHING WORKED OUT?
NEARLY LIKE
YOU PLANNED IT.
OH, PLEASE!
AS IF I'M THAT SMART!
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
SO MUCH FUN THIS YEAR.
AND IT'S ALL THANKS
TO YOU.
♪ Out here every night ♪
♪ Those two are in love ♪
IT'S SCARY
HOW MUCH I LIKE YOU.
THIS IS IT.
A ONCE-IN-LIFETIME-MOMENT.
SOMETHING WE CAN NEVER
TAKE BACK.
AND I'M SO HAPPY
IT'S WITH YOU.
SOMEONE I LOVE.
WHO LOVES ME.
WHO I COULD BE
WITH FOREVER.
WHAT?
UM...
I'M SORRY,
BUT I CAN'T DO THIS.
♪ I'm ready ♪
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
♪ Take me up ♪
♪ I'm ready ♪
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
♪ Take me up ♪
♪ I'm ready ♪
READY TO GO?
I THOUGHT YOU HAD PLANS
WITH ZIG.
NOW HE HAS PLANS
WITH HIS GIRLFRIEND, TORI.
I DIDN'T REALIZE
HOW MUCH I LIKED HIM
UNTIL IT WAS TOO LATE.
AW, MAYA, I'M SORRY.
ARE YOU OKAY?
IS HIGH SCHOOL ALWAYS
THIS COMPLICATED?
AT LEAST.
REAL NICE.
I THOUGHT WE WERE FRIENDS.
MAYA, I'LL MEET YOU
AT MARISOL'S CAR, OKAY?
MAYA:
OKAY.
FIONA:
I'M SUSPENDED FOR A WEEK.
ON PROBATION INDEFINITELY.
AND I HAVE TO SPEND
MY ENTIRE WEEKEND HERE
CLEANING THE CAFETERIA.
I'M SORRY, FIONA,
I KNOW IT SUCKS,
BUT WE STILL NEED A CHAIR
FOR THE SOCIAL COMMITTEE.
YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
I STILL WANT TO BE FRIENDS.
WE WERE NEVER FRIENDS.
FRIENDS DON'T DO THIS
TO EACH OTHER.
FIONA, COME ON,
I'M SORRY...
YOU KNOW, I EXPECTED MORE
OF YOU, KATIE.
A PRESIDENT IS SUPPOSED
TO SERVE HER PEOPLE.
(SIGHS)
SO BIG PLANS FOR THIS
SUNNY SATURDAY?
NO. I WAS PLANNING
TO DO SOME HOMEWORK.
AND THEN SPEND
A COUPLE OF HOURS
WONDERING WHY MY BOYFRIEND
REJECTED ME.
I'M SORRY, OKAY?
NO, NOT OKAY.
YOU DON'T GET T RUN OFF
AND THEN APOLOGIZE.
NOT AGAIN.
DID I DO SOMETHING
WRONG?
NO.
THEN WHAT?
I DON'T THINK-
I DON'T THINK WE'LL
BE TOGETHER FOREVER.
I KNOW THERE'S A CHANCE
WE'LL BREAK UP-
THERE'S MORE THAN
A CHANCE.
WITH OUR PARENTS MARRIED,
WE'RE LINKED FOR LIFE.
HAVING SEX WOULD JUST
COMPLICATE THINGS.
A LOT.
CLARE?
I THINK
WE SHOULD BREAK UP.
IF IT'S GONNA HAPPEN,
WHY WAIT, RIGHT?
HELEN:
HEY GUYS.
GLENN AND I WERE GONNA GO
CHECK OUT THE FARMER'S MARKET.
GLENN:
YEAH, WE THOUGHT YOU MIGHT
WANNA JOIN US.
YOU KNOW, SPEND THE DAY
AS A FAMILY.
HELEN:
HEY, YOU COMING, CLARE?
(SIGHS)
(BELL RINGS)
FIONA:
BROUGHT YOU A COFFEE.
EXTRA STRONG.
LOOKS LIKE WE'LL NEED IT.
SO YOU WERE RIGHT.
THEY TURNED ON ME.
I ALWAYS DO THIS.
I ALWAYS MESS THINGS UP.
AND THIS YEAR,
I DON'T HAVE HOLLY J
TO FIX EVERYTHING FOR ME.
(SIGHS)
I DON'T HAVE ANYBODY.
I KNOW IT DOESN'T MAKE UP
FOR IT,
BUT I DID MANAGE TO GET YOUR
SUSPENSION REDUCED.
I'M REALLY SORRY,
IMOGEN.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO STAY MAD AT YOU
WHEN YOU'RE SUCH
A SAD SACK?
(CHUCKLE)
IF YOU WANT, WE CAN LUST
OVER JOCKS TOGETHER...
CAN WE?
AND PLAY STUPID GAMES
LIKE TRUTH OR DARE.
OOH... AND FIND GIRLS
LIKE US TO PICK ON...
I HAVE A BETTER IDEA.
LET'S GET KATIE
AND MARISOL BACK.
NOW YOU'RE TALKING.
DO YOU HAVE A PLAN?
NO, BUT WE HAVE ALL YEAR
TO FIGURE IT OUT.
(LAUGHS)
HEY, AFTER ALL THIS,
I HOPE WE CAN BE FRIENDS.
DEPENDS.
CAN I GIVE YOU
A MAKEOVER?
SURE?
GOOD!
OH WAIT... NOW?
IT'S A START.
(LAUGHING)
THERE YOU GO.
OKAY.
YOU ARE A WEIRDO.
YEP.
AND YOU'RE GONNA
LIKE IT.
(LAUGHING)
COME ON, SPIN.